Previously on Suits...
Maybe you don't know
how babies are made.
Because when people are trying,
they know they're trying!
And just because no one
ever wants to try with you
doesn't give you the right
to tell me how to run my associates!
I think Rachel should
handle the associates.
I am up here; Rachel's down here.
And you don't give dominion
over the associates
to someone down here.
Which one of my clients are you after?
Because we both know
you can't have Pfizer.
- Yes, I can.
- Then make me name partner.
Harvey's making his
friend name partner.
He's accused me of being jealous,
and I don't know what to do.
- Are you jealous?
- Of course I'm goddamn jealous!
If you keep letting your
emotions dictate your behavior,
you won't need to worry
about being replaced.
You'll drive Harvey away all by yourself.
Stop apologizing and
start intimidating.
That's a hell of a slogan, Harvey,
but what does it actually mean?
It means you go out,
you find a reporter,
and you control the narrative.
If I lose this case,
the only article that's gonna get written
is that I never should've been able
to practice law in the first place.
If you can't figure out a way to win,
maybe I shouldn't have brought
you back in the first place.
A reporter from the
"Times" is coming here.
We are doing an interview:
"The Redemption of a Fraudulent Lawyer."
I don't want my behavior
to drive a wedge between us,
which means I accept
Alex as name partner.
For what it's worth,
Alex is still coming,
but not as name partner.
- Really?
- You're right.
We can't water down the firm like that.
I have to say...
I've been wanting this for so long.
Never in my wildest dreams did
I think it would come true.
We're the only name
partners now, Louis.
And I meant it when I said it.
I want us to share things like this.
I can't tell you how
happy that makes me.
You're not gonna cry, are you?
Are you kidding?
The last time I cried in
here, I messed up the pH.
I had a yeast infection for weeks.
You're not gonna do the other thing you
told me you did in the mud, are you?
Harvey, I told you, that
was a one-time thing.
And believe me, you're no Missy Dietler.
Who's Missy Dietler?
- What is he doing here?
- What do you mean?
Harvey and I go mudding
together all the time.
So why don't you lug
yourself out of there
- so I can get my tub back?
- This is my tub.
And you always told me it was weird
for male friends to mud together.
But Harvey and I are
more than just friends.
We're best friends.
And then what did you do?
What do you think I did? I called you.
Louis, it was just a dream.
Just a dream? It was
a goddamn mud-mare.
Don't you get it?
Harvey let his buddy into my firm.
Now he's in my mud.
I mean, what's next? I
walk into my bathroom
and I find him shitting on my toothbrush?
Louis, we talked about this.
If you let this overwhelm you,
you're going to bring about the
thing you're most afraid of.
Did you hear me?
He was in my mud.
How the hell am I not supposed
to let that overwhelm me?
Well...
has it occurred to you
that instead of worrying this Alex person
is going to come between you and Harvey,
you could use this as an opportunity
to make a new friend?
That's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard.
Be that as it may,
as I see it,
you have a chance to have one more friend
or one less friend.
I suggest you go with one more.
- Donna.
- Rachel.
Can I get you two anything?
Coffee, tea, a copy of your
article in the "Sunday Times"?
Don't need it. Read it yesterday.
Have one at home.
And by one, he means ten.
Are you sure you don't want to
take just one more look at it?
I'm good. Thanks, Donna.
Okeydokey.
You have a nice day.
Something's going on
with her, I can tell.
What do you mean?
You telling me you didn't
notice that grin on her face?
Rachel, you've known
Donna longer than I have,
but I didn't see a grin.
I'm telling you, I think
you're imagining it.
Right. Totally imagined it.
- Harvey.
- Rachel.
You know, black can be slimming.
Something to think about next time.
I take it this is
your way of apologizing
for saying you never
should've hired me back.
And it gave me a chance
to say the slimming thing.
Sorry, Mike.
You had a point, Harvey.
This is the Radiant Technologies merger.
Yep. Back to one for me.
Great, except you
don't need me for this.
Deal's done. They sign tomorrow.
Which is why Klein Robinson
thought that I wouldn't mind
if they put a few last-minute
changes in the contract.
And a few last-minute changes means
they're trying to pull
some last-minute bullshit.
Now that sounds like the impressive young
lawyer I read about in the article.
Why don't you figure out
what they're trying to do?
And get it done by lunch.
Who says I need slimming?
FAKE LAWYER BECOMES REAL DICKHEAD
BIG BOY PANTS: THE MIKE ROSS STORY
www.Watch-tv-shows.org
-WATCH TV SHOWS WITH SUBTITLES-
Don't be hostile.
Louis, what are you doing?
- What?
- Leave him alone.
It's his first day.
No, Donna, it's not like that.
I come in peace.
You swear?
Yes, I brought him a living thing.
- Is it poisonous?
- No, Donna, it is not.
Okay. Well, I got my eyes on you.
And that plant.
Don't be hostile.
Alex Williams, Louis Litt.
I brought you a honeysuckle.
Excuse me?
It's a gesture, since we might've
gotten off on the wrong foot.
You mean because you tried
to poach my biggest client
and keep me from joining the firm?
Yes, perhaps that's
the foot we got off on.
But I was hoping we could
get onto other foot.
Here.
I appreciate the gesture, Louis.
By the way, your work on the
Andersen case was extraordinary.
You followed my Andersen work?
Yes. In fact, it reminded
me of my Pricehouse strategy.
Truth be told, I based it
on your Pricehouse strategy.
Get the fuck well then, you
took it to a whole other level.
Thank you, Louis.
I'm sorry about the poaching.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, would you like to grab lunch?
Eating at your desk is no way
to celebrate your first day.
You're right, it's not.
I'll meet you at the lobby at 1:00.
Sounds good. And thanks for the plant.
You're welcome.
I don't know if you care about
this, but cats love it.
Oh, I know. We've got
two tabbies at home
that are gonna go crazy
over that bad boy.
- Tabbies?
- Yup.
Holy shit, I'm gonna make a reservation
at the best restaurant in
the city, you... BFF, you.
Son of a bitch.
Mr. Reyes?
- Yes.
- Mike Ross.
They said you wanted to see me?
Yes, thank you for taking the time.
Of course.
Yeah.
I read your interview yesterday.
And my son was in prison too.
But... unlike you,
he didn't make it out.
This says your son
died of a heart attack.
Yes, a heart attack out of nowhere.
You think they're hiding something.
Well, they won't take my calls
or answer my letters.
What would you think?
I'd think that there
might be something wrong.
But that doesn't mean that there is.
Mr. Ross, my son was 28 years old.
And he was up for parole next month.
There's something they're not telling me.
All right, I'll look into it.
But I'm not gonna be able
to get to this for a few days.
A few days. Why can't you start now?
Because I have a deal
with my firm that allows me
to do cases like this, but
not only cases like this.
And right now, I'm in the
middle of something else.
Mr. Ross, the last lawyer I talked to
said there was some kind of a statute
that says I only have another
two weeks to file a lawsuit.
And I'm telling you, two weeks
should be more than enough time,
but I... I can't drop everything
just to take your case.
I understand.
But...
Chris was caught with
an ounce of marijuana.
He never should have been
there in the first place.
And if time runs out on this
and I couldn't get him justice...
Okay.
I'll see what I can do.
Stephanie, we need to
talk about this assignment.
Is there a problem with it?
Yes, the problem is you didn't do it.
Jason did.
Because Jason is better at
cataloging procedure than I am.
Right, but if you don't do
the things you're not good at,
you'll never get better.
The thing is, I don't really want to
get better at cataloging procedure.
I know that,
just like I didn't want to be a
paralegal specializing in research
for as long as I was.
But it turns out we had a case
last year that we only won
because I was outstanding at research.
Okay, I see your point.
- I won't do it again.
- Good.
Because I have another case
that requires some procedure
to be catalogued, and I put
it aside especially for you.
But Stephanie, I want your word
that you won't pawn it off on Jason.
You have my word.
Well, look who it is.
Don't tell me, you feel bad
about canceling the other night
and now you're dying to make it up to me.
It's as though you read my mind.
One of my many skills.
How does dinner tonight sound?
How does having it at my place sound?
You're a crafty one, aren't you?
What? I've got some steaks
I've been wanting to throw on the grill.
No, you want to have
dinner at your place
'cause it's the closest restaurant
in the city to your bedroom.
Did you read that in "Zagat's"?
No, I read your mind.
Then what time am I thinking?
How about 8:00?
Better make it 8:30. I
got to go buy some steaks.
Good, you're here.
Tell me you figured out what bullshit
they're trying to sneak into this deal.
They're not trying to
sneak anything into it.
They're trying to get out of it.
That doesn't make sense. They
came to us for this merger.
They must've gotten a better offer,
because they buried an escape clause
in the addendum.
- You know what we have to do.
- Yes, I do.
But you're gonna have
to do it without me.
Something's come up, it's on a deadline,
and I need to take care of it.
- What kind of thing?
- A pro bono thing.
Since when does one for
me mean two for you?
Harvey, a man died in prison
and it doesn't smell right.
Also, the only reason I
found out about it is
I took your advice and
did that interview.
So it's my fault that
you're dropping my case?
Yeah, I like to look at it that way.
Seriously, go get 'em.
Thanks, Harvey.
The last guy brought me a plant.
Let me guess, the last guy was Louis.
You got it.
Well, I guarantee my welcome
gift is a lot more fun than his.
Since when is a merger signing fun?
Since the guys on the other
side are trying to rip us off
and think we don't know.
Why didn't you tell me
that in the first place?
Come on. I'll fill you
in on the way over.
Wait, the meeting's now?
Yeah, is that a problem?
I told Louis we'd get lunch.
Business trumps lunch.
Louis'll understand.
Just call him and let him know.
Alex, hi, I was just
on my way to meet you.
About that, Louis. I
have to reschedule.
A work thing came up. I
hope you understand.
Yeah, of course.
- Business comes first.
- Thanks.
We'll do it another time.
In fact, I'm free all week.
Louis? You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I... it's allergy season.
I... I think it's probably best
that we don't have lunch today.
I... my... my chest
feels like a vice.
All good?
I think so.
What kind of plant did
he get you, anyway?
Honeysuckle.
I never knew that was an indoor plant.
Can be.
Matter of fact, our
cats are gonna love it.
- You have cats?
- Why you gotta be like that?
- Why you gotta have cats?
- I like my cats.
No, you don't.
Ms. Snyder? Mike Ross.
Is that name supposed
to mean something to me?
No, but I'm representing
the family of Chris Reyes.
Hoping that name does.
Of course.
Any time an inmate dies,
we take it very seriously.
But not seriously enough to
give an accounting of his death
despite repeated requests by his family.
I received no such requests.
It's a shame you didn't call first.
I could've prepared something.
I didn't want you to be prepared,
'cause I want to know
what actually happened.
Mr. Ross, when you do what I do,
you get used to people assuming
the worst about your company,
so I would appreciate a little respect.
Ms. Snyder, when you do what I do,
you get used to companies
proving you right,
so I would appreciate a little action.
Apparently Mr. Reyes was in a fight.
He was sent to solitary, where he
complained of difficulty breathing.
A doctor was called and
delivered treatment.
Unfortunately, he died a few hours later.
Well, if he was in a fight, there
has to be an incident report.
That may be, but you have
no right to access it.
We're a private corporation.
That's privileged.
Okay, then how about you give me
the names of the guards who saw it?
You know I can't give you that either.
And you know that if I
bring a suit against you,
I'm gonna get all of this anyway.
So why don't you save
yourself the publicity
and just give it to me now?
I don't care what that thing says.
It's not the whole story.
Mr. Reyes, I know this isn't
what you wanted to hear,
but I'm not seeing a case.
It says there that my son
died alone in solitary confinement.
Why didn't they take him to an infirmary?
Because he was seen by a doctor.
There was an explanation
for his symptoms.
I know you think I'm just a man
who can't accept his child's death.
But that's not true.
Mr. Reyes, a fight in prison
can elevate your heart rate.
Nobody knows that better than I do.
What they're saying
happened is plausible.
Then you didn't know my son.
I told you, he was up
for parole next month.
He wouldn't have gotten into a fight.
What exactly are you saying?
One of those inmates
must have come for him.
And that prison didn't give
enough of a shit about Chris
to protect him.
Mr. Reyes, I know that you came to me
because that article said
I wanted to help people
and I do, but...
I know. My son's already dead.
But if they could've stopped
this and they didn't,
it's going to happen again.
Chase, I'd like you to meet
our newest senior partner,
Alex Williams.
Two senior partners
just to sign a contract.
Seems excessive.
It would be, but we're
not here to sign anything.
What are you talking about?
He must think I'm pretty dumb.
People always underestimate
a pretty face.
Maybe he just thinks you're dumb.
'Cause of the droopy eyes.
Valid theory. Not unprecedented.
Nobody thinks you're dumb.
Then why the hell did
you sneak this clause
to the back of my goddamn contract?
We didn't sneak anything.
We were just looking at our options.
Bullshit.
You're trying to use us as a stalking
horse so you can merge with Gorban.
So what if I was?
What are you going to do to stop it?
I'll tell you what I did.
I called Alex.
And what I did was call my
law school roommate at the DOJ
about the anti-trust issues raised by you
merging with Gorban.
What do you want?
We want you to live up to the terms
- of the original agreement.
- With one exception.
You're gonna take a step down.
- I'm not stepping down.
- Yes, you are.
This new company doesn't
need two outside counsels.
Particularly one who
tries to pull shady shit
without his client knowing about it.
Looks like you're gonna
take one for the team, Chase.
The question is, would you like
to bow out or get kicked out?
How the hell can I calm down?
I was watching my mud-mare come true.
You don't know what you saw, Louis.
I'm sorry, I forgot I was blind.
I must've dialed your number
using my Braille-a-phone.
You know that's not what I meant.
No, you're right, it's
the only explanation
as to why I wouldn't
know what I just saw,
which was Harvey and Alex,
arm in arm, laughing at me!
Louis, listen to me.
We knew this was going to happen.
That I was gonna be
betrayed by my best friend?
No, that you were going
to try to be good...
- Did it.
- Try not to be you.
Accomplished.
Then perceive a potentially
nonexistent slight
and go straight to stage seven.
What the hell are you talking about?
Panic, sorrow, self-loathing,
hatred, justification,
self-loathing again, and rage.
I call it the seven stages of Louis.
You are so full of shit,
and you're a total fraud,
and I'm actually gonna...
ah... I see your point.
Stage 7b.
No one likes a gloater, Stan.
Be that as it may.
You need a strategy, Louis.
For now and the next time this happens.
The breathing exercises.
It's the only thing
that's ever worked for you.
What would I do without you, Doc?
No need to go down
that road, my friend.
Now, picture yourself near the ocean,
laying in the sand.
Isn't it lovely?
I got to say, that was pretty fun.
I agree.
I always wanted to pretend
I had a friend at the DOJ.
Not a bad first day.
Speaking of my first day,
what's up with that Louis Litt guy?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
First he tries to stop
me from coming over,
then he brings me a plant,
then when I called to cancel lunch,
I could've sworn he was
about to cry or something.
What?
Louis is...
he's complicated.
What do you mean, complicated?
Well, you know he didn't
want you here, right?
The thing is, it wasn't professional.
What else could it be?
He was worried that I was gonna be
better friends with you than him.
What the hell is wrong with this guy?
Does he have a crush on you?
No.
Yeah, he totally has a crush on me.
But not like that.
Maybe this'll work. You ever seen "MASH"?
Of course, but what does
that have to do with this?
Louis is Frank Burns.
Why didn't you say so in the first place?
Now I totally get it.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
He loves you, hates you,
and wants to be you,
all at the same time.
You do get it.
Yeah, I do. The question is,
are you sure he's gonna be okay with me,
or do I have to watch out?
Well, let me ask you this.
Did you tell him your cats are
gonna love his honeysuckle?
Yes.
Then I think you'll be fine.
Excuse me. You guys know Chris Reyes?
Doesn't ring a bell.
That's strange, 'cause
according to the incident report
the three of you were on
duty the night he died.
Even if I were, I wouldn't
have anything to say about it,
so you can get the fuck out of here.
Hey, come on. I just have a
few questions, that's all.
This is a prison. All questions
go through the main office.
Where do you think I got your names?
I don't give a shit where you got 'em.
You're gonna forget you ever heard 'em.
And if I see your face again,
there's gonna be a problem.
Okay, look, I'm not trying
to start any trouble here.
But a man is dead, and I need
to find out what happened.
For a guy who's not looking
to cause any trouble,
you sure don't listen too good.
Come on, Drew. Let's go.
That's what he wants.
I'm telling you, he's not worth it.
You're one of those assholes
who just love getting the shit
beat out of him, aren't you?
No, I've had the shit beat out of me,
and I can tell you, I
didn't love it at all.
Then you better get
the hell out of here
before it happens again.
I will, just as soon as
you answer my questions.
And why would I do that?
Because your name is
at the top of the list,
and I'm guessing you
know what that means.
Yeah, I'm the scapegoat.
But it also means anything they
get, they know it came from me.
Except you just told me to go to hell
in front of all your buddies,
and they saw you meant it.
That's why you came
to me at the prison.
Now you got cover.
And I suggest you use it.
Because I am gonna find
out what happened here,
and when I do, they are gonna
shield themselves from liability
and I am gonna end up
coming after you instead.
Or you can tell me what I need to know,
and I'll leave you out of it.
Look, I'm the one who pulled
him out of the fight
and threw him in the hole.
He started complaining saying he
was having problems breathing.
I told my supervisor, and my supervisor
said he was gonna call the doctor.
- That's all I know.
- Bullshit that's all you know.
Look, did Chris get killed
because he was onto something?
No.
Well, that kid, he didn't just up and
get in a fight without good reason.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Look, are the guards corrupt?
What the hell did you just say?
- Was somebody out to get him?
- No, he just died!
Look, there's no conspiracy.
Nobody's evil.
Just cheap.
What does that mean?
It means the only reason
they were able to wale on him
for as long as they did
is 'cause they didn't have
enough of us on duty that night,
'cause the prison doesn't
give a shit about anything
except its bottom line.
So what did you do?
So I told him he could have the money,
but if... if he tried
taking those albums,
we're gonna have trouble.
This was lovely.
But I have an early morning tomorrow.
I think I should get home.
Paula, what's going on?
It's nothing.
- Really.
- Nothing?
We had a great night.
All of a sudden you have to go?
You wouldn't understand.
Try me.
I had lunch with the woman
who was my mentor today.
And we were having a wonderful time
catching up with each other,
and then... out of the blue,
she asked me if I was seeing anyone.
I said no.
Well, we haven't exactly
been seeing each other
for very long. It's
understandable if you...
No, it wasn't that, Harvey.
- It's that I felt a little...
- What?
Ashamed.
This isn't a small thing,
what we're doing, Harvey.
- At least it's not to me.
- It's not to me either.
Well, I'm not sure I realized
exactly how not small it is
until today.
I don't understand.
We've been over this.
It's in writing.
There's no violation with
us seeing each other.
This isn't something that I am
trying to get away with, Harvey.
It's how I'm feeling inside.
- So what are you saying?
- I'm not saying anything.
I'm just saying I think I should
sleep at my place tonight.
Donna, I need to talk
to you about something.
About what?
About the fact that I'm pissed off.
What's going on?
I gave Stephanie Patel an assignment
and she handed it off.
Did you talk to her about it?
Yes, I did, and she gave me her word
that she would never do
it again, but she did.
I don't understand. This
has Stephanie's name on it.
I don't care whose name is on it.
There's no way that that wasn't written
by a first-year associate.
Rachel, please tell
me you're not thinking
about going to Louis with this.
Are you kidding me?
We took Louis off the associates
because of his incident with Stephanie.
If I tell him that she's being
insubordinate, he'll kill her.
Well, I can't believe I'm saying this,
but maybe you should take a
page out of Louis' book.
What do you mean?
When Louis first took
over the associates,
he used to plant a fake
associate and fire him
in front of the entire class on day one.
And I used to think he was crazy,
but Stephanie never would have
pulled something like this with Louis.
Okay, first of all,
that's just not how I operate.
And second of all, they've all been here.
They'd all be able to
tell that it was fake.
Then maybe you need to real fire her.
Because this is a second offense
and if you keep letting it go,
where does it end?
I'm not gonna do that.
Do you mind if I ask you why not?
Because I don't want my first
official act to be firing someone.
I understand that, Rachel.
But you better think of something.
Because the one thing
that Louis understood
was that you've got to come
out of the gate in command,
or they're gonna walk all over you.
Yes?
Mr. Reyes, it's Mike Ross.
I went to the prison, and I
talked to one of the guards.
What did he say?
He said all the prison cares
about is their bottom line.
So I'm filing a lawsuit tonight.
Thank you so much, Mr. Ross.
I thought that article was
maybe too good to be true.
I appreciate that,
Oscar, but don't thank me
until I get you the answers
you're looking for.
You finished the paperwork already?
I might have to give you a raise.
Save your money, Harvey.
I'm here about something else.
What's going on?
I just heard Mike Ross
is handling a pro bono.
Yeah, we have a deal. Why?
You need him for something?
Yeah, I need him to drop that case.
Why?
Because there's a conflict
with Masterson Construction.
Mike's pro bono is against some prison.
And guess who builds those prisons.
Wait a second.
Are you telling me to go back on my word
because your client's bullying you?
Harvey, I thought we
were in this together.
- So did I.
- Then get on board.
Because they're not just any client.
They're one of my biggest.
And if they leave because
you chose some prisoner
over one of the biggest
developers in the country,
people are gonna get the message
that we don't want to be in
the real estate business.
Did they say they were gonna
give people that message?
- Harvey...
- Did they or not?
- They did.
- Drop 'em.
- God damn it...
- I said drop 'em.
- No.
- Excuse me?
I may not be name partner yet,
but you don't get to tell
me who my clients are.
Yes, I do.
Harvey, listen to yourself.
It's one pro bono. He just took it.
He can drop it.
I gave him my word.
And you once gave your word to me
and went back on it and I let it go.
Because I understood it was business.
If this kid doesn't get that,
what the hell is he doing here?
Stephanie, I asked you
to come to my office.
That was over an hour ago.
I was working on the Sanderson brief.
I was about to come down.
Well, I need to talk to you now,
because you told me that you
wouldn't hand this off,
and you did.
No, I told you that I
wouldn't hand it off to Jason,
and I didn't.
I'm sorry, are you
trying to get out of this
on a technicality?
I'm your supervisor,
not opposing counsel.
Rachel, I tried to be nice about this,
but I'm a fourth-year associate,
and I'm not wasting my time
on something a first-year could handle.
Now, if you don't mind, I would
like to get back to work.
Actually, I do mind.
Excuse me, Stephanie,
I'm speaking to you.
It doesn't matter what year you are.
I'm head of the associates.
If I give you an assignment, you do it.
And when you give me one
that's worth my time, I will.
What's going on here?
Donna, I'm handling it.
What's going on is
that I am a grown woman,
and I don't need to be
told what to do by someone
with less experience as a lawyer than me.
Then you're really gonna
hate being told what to do
by someone with no
experience as a lawyer.
- Donna...
- Excuse me?
I said, you're here, and I'm here.
So unless you want to deal with me,
you'll listen when Rachel
tells you something.
I was recruited to come here.
And I was told that I would be valued
for my mind, my billings,
and my relationship with my clients.
And since I got here,
I have had to take shit from Louis.
And now you're asking me to
waste my time and my ability
on something like this.
- No...
- You're right, Stephanie.
You shouldn't have been
treated like that by Louis.
And Rachel and I took care of it.
Now as for your time and ability,
if you don't do whatever
assignment Rachel gives you,
I don't give a shit how good you are.
We are gonna show you the door.
Hey. Did you come by to tell me
that the work I did saved your ass?
It did, but that's not why I'm here.
Harvey, what's going on?
You have to drop your pro bono.
There's a conflict with
one of our clients.
What? Who?
I checked for conflicts
before I took the case.
- It's a new client.
- Well, if it's a new client,
then let's drop them.
We can't. They're a huge developer.
A developer? I'm suing a prison.
I know that, but they're saying...
I don't care what they're saying.
That's not a conflict.
That's a shakedown.
- Mike...
- No.
You're gonna give me the green light,
and then I find something,
and then you're gonna make me
dump them for no good reason?
It's not no good reason.
It's Alex's developer, and
I just brought him in.
I let him lose one of his biggest clients
his first week here, it's a disaster.
And I let a man die without
getting him justice.
- What the hell is that?
- Listen to me...
Listen to yourself. We had a deal.
Now this clown is asking
me to drop a client
that I made a promise to.
Except he's not asking
you to drop him, Mike. I am.
And if you don't, that
deal we made... it's over.
How could you do that?
Do what? I was helping you.
No, Donna, you were undermining me.
Undermining you?
You needed backup. That's
what I'm here for.
No, I needed to handle the situation,
which is what I was doing until
you decided to interfere
in something that you don't
know anything about.
No offense, Rachel, but I
did know something about it,
and from what I could tell, you
weren't handling it at all.
And you think what you
did was any better?
I think I told you that you
need to set the tone early on.
Okay, and the tone that you just set
is that if you're not there,
she can walk all over me.
Well, I don't know
what room you were in,
but she was doing that anyway.
And what does it say about
me if the other associates
see me letting her do that?
What it says is that you
trust my leadership style
instead of thinking that you
need to fight my fights for me.
Stephanie needed what I gave her.
And if you think that was
me fighting your fights,
you don't know what you're talking about.
Because if it were up to me,
I would've fired her on the spot.
Well then, why didn't you?
Because they're not my associates.
You're right. They're mine.
And I fought for you to get them.
And you just belittled me
and embarrassed me in
front of all of them.
And that is not something
that I thought my friend would do to me.
Well, you know what, I never
thought I would say this,
but maybe you weren't ready
for your new position.
Well, you know what, Donna?
Maybe neither were you.
Dr. Lipschitz, I.. I
know you're in a session.
I just wanted to say that you were right.
I was overreacting.
I do not have a problem with Alex.
And... if I ever get triggered again,
I have the deep breathing.
Anyway, thanks again.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Mike.
It's good to see you.
This'll just take a few minutes,
and then it's all yours.
No, it doesn't matter
how long it takes, Louis.
We can just charge the time
back to some client, right?
'Cause nobody around here
gives a shit about anything
other than making money anyway.
Mike, what is going on?
What's going on is that the
only reason I came back here
is that Harvey and I made a deal,
and it hasn't even been a week,
and he's already going back on it.
That's not gonna happen on my watch.
Okay? So just slow down.
Tell me what the hell
you're talking about.
Harvey, we need to talk.
Mike just told me you're
breaking a deal with him.
Well, he shouldn't have told you that,
because that's none of your business.
None of my business?
My name's on the wall as much as yours.
Look, if Mike doesn't drop that case,
we lose a major client.
- I can't have that.
- No, Harvey.
What we can't have is
you setting a precedent
that Alex's clients can run
roughshod all over us.
Keep your voices down.
Oh, I get it.
So this isn't about me
breaking my deal with Mike.
This is about you being jealous of Alex.
No, it isn't. I thought
it was a mistake
even before I found out
that it was Alex's client.
- Harvey, he has a point.
- Bullshit.
You told me you were afraid
that I was gonna become
better friends with him than
you, and that's what this is.
How dare you say that
to me in front of Donna?
I told you that in complete confidence.
This isn't about my
relationship with Alex.
This is about your relationship with Alex
and how you're afraid to stand up to him.
You want to run that by me again?
I just ran it by you.
What you are doing is a mistake.
I don't think so,
and Donna doesn't think
so, which means...
Actually, Harvey, I do.
And if it's all the same to
you, I can speak for myself.
- Are you kidding me?
- No, I'm not.
Because the last time you said
if I had something to say,
say it in the goddamn meeting.
Well, this is the goddamn meeting.
And I happen to think we
should keep our word to Mike
instead of letting some client bully us.
Well, I appreciate the input.
But I told you you'd get a vote
when I said there'd be a vote,
and this isn't a vote.
As for you, take a look in the mirror,
because the only reason that
you're pissed about this
is your new honeysuckle friend
canceled lunch on you for me.
Louis...
Aren't you a little old to be spending
your break in a comic book store?
Everybody has their hobbies, Mike.
Mine's comics.
Yours is helping big corporations
screw over the little guy.
Oliver, wait.
I just, I came here because
I owe you an apology,
and... this is my way of doing it.
What's that?
More money to make everything okay?
It's a case. It's one
that means a lot to me.
It's about a guy who died in prison.
If it means so much to you,
why don't you do it yourself?
I can't.
We have a conflict with
one of our clients.
Well, that's a nice speech,
Mike, but I'm not interested,
because there's something
in it for you, like always.
Oliver, please, look,
before you say no,
just listen to what I have to say.
I don't need to listen to you anymore.
God damn it, I almost died in there.
What?
My second night in Danbury,
I thought that someone was gonna kill me.
And then my last night,
I knew that same guy was
coming for me again.
But I got out.
This kid didn't.
The only thing that's in this for me
is making sure that this doesn't
happen to someone else.
This seems pretty cut-and-dry, Mike.
That's how they want it to look.
I already know they didn't have
enough guard staff on duty that night.
Which means they probably didn't
have enough medical staff either.
Or maybe none at all.
Look, I can't let them get away with this
without handing it off to the one lawyer
I know cares enough to see it through.
Okay, Mike.
I'm in.
- Donna, whatever it is...
- Rachel, I'm so sorry.
What I did was wrong and horrible
and showed you no respect,
and then you came and
tried to tell me that,
and I made it a thousand times worse.
Why would you do something
like that in the first place?
'Cause I'm new at this.
Then I saw Stephanie
treating you like shit,
and it felt like she
was doing that to me.
Because you're the one
that gave me the job.
Maybe.
And then you told me I cut your legs out,
and that made me feel even worse,
and I took it out on you.
- Donna...
- Rachel, you were right.
I'm not completely ready for this.
And I'm not always gonna
get things right,
and I got them really wrong today.
Maybe not all wrong.
What do you mean?
I thought about it too.
I am finally a member of the bar.
I don't want to supervise
anyone right now.
I just want to be the
best lawyer I can be.
I understand.
I'll take care of the associates for now.
Donna.
What made you realize all that?
Let's just say
I was reminded what it feels like
when someone speaks for you
and what they're saying
is the complete opposite
of what you wanted to say.
- Louis?
- Harvey.
The one who gave you your new position.
Exactly.
I'm so sorry, Donna.
I'm sorry too, Rachel.
Harvey, it's late. Whatever it is...
Did you pawn that thing
off to the clinic?
You asked me to drop
it, so I dropped it.
Bullshit.
You gave it to the clinic
you're affiliated with.
The clinic you told me I could
give cases to at my discretion.
Maybe you missed the memo.
If our firm is in any way
associated with that case,
we lose a huge client.
Harvey, I'm not working on it.
Then you're gonna put that in writing,
and you're gonna deliver
it to Alex's client.
Ironclad Chinese wall.
You have nothing to do with this case.
Are you saying you don't trust me?
You saying you didn't
know what you were doing
when you gave it to the clinic?
Okay, Harvey.
I'll put it in writing.
I want you word you're
gonna live by what you sign.
You have my word.
You wanted to see me?
Yes, I did, I was just wondering,
have you redone the assignment
that Rachel gave you?
Not yet.
I had a ton on my plate.
I was gonna get to it tomorrow.
You're fired.
Please, I-I really was going to do it.
I believe you.
But my rule is three
strikes and you're out.
Otherwise, where does it end?
In that case, why not do this publicly?
I don't need to do this
publicly, Stephanie.
When you're not here tomorrow,
people will know what happened.
But I do want you to
know, I wish you well.
Do you expect me to believe that?
I don't know.
But it's true.
Before you say anything,
I came here for a reason.
Because this is where we met,
but it isn't where I need to be anymore.
Harvey, I don't think...
I just have one question to ask you.
Are you worried about what
this woman's gonna think
or because you think what
we're doing is wrong?
Because if this is just about
what other people think,
it's crazy!
Well, it isn't crazy to me,
and I need you to understand that.
I do understand that,
but I also know we have a connection,
and to throw that away
because of some figment
of your imagination...
It is not a figment of my imagination.
And I'm not worried
about what she thinks.
I am worried about what I think.
And what is it that you think?
That what if this was
a terrible mistake
and it doesn't work out
and I look like a fool?
Okay.
I know I'm not the therapist here,
but isn't that the risk
of any relationship?
I'm scared, Harvey.
Me too.
What do you say we both
be scared together?
Can I help you?
Yeah.
My name is Mike Ross.
I would say nice to meet you,
but I'm pretty sure you
don't feel the same way.
Not particularly.
What's this?
My next 15 potential lawsuits.
I just want to make sure you
don't have any conflicts with any of these.
Maybe your client's grandmother
shops at the supermarket
across the street from number 12.
I'll take a look.
Good, 'cause just to be clear,
if I'd known there was a conflict,
I never would've taken the case.
I appreciate you dropping it.
I was bulldozed into dropping it,
just like I was bulldozed
into signing this.
Now, I can live with both those things,
but I never want to get caught
in this situation again.
What's so funny?
I just told my client
the same damn thing.
Bullshit.
You think this makes me look good?
Well then I guess we're
in the same boat after all.
It's nice to meet you, Mike.
Welcome to Pearson Specter Litt.
You said I needed a strategy
for when it happened.
Well, I used your strategy,
and I got over it,
but it didn't fix a goddamn thing!
Louis, calm down. I'm here for you.
No, you're not! You're
never there for me.
You're always against me.
I did what you said,
and this time, it's not my fault.
And I don't give a shit what you think.
I'm not the horrible person
you always say I am.
Louis, I don't think
you're a horrible person.
I think you're a wonderful person.
And if I haven't made that clear to you,
I am very sorry.
Well, you can be sorry
all you want, Harvey.
- Louis?
- But you are wrong about me.
I'm not a worthless piece of shit.
You failed me.
And you were wrong.
You were wrong!
www.Watch-tv-shows.org
-WATCH TV SHOWS WITH SUBTITLES-
www.tvsubtitles.net