I'm talking about
the both of us,
convincing Hardman that two
kickass junior partners
are worth as much as one new
senior partner.
You had the chance to triple
our business,
and all you had to do was
take a knee.
Tell me right now you weren't
the one
that Fletcher Engines
my game plan.
Hardman told me he wasn't
gonna make you partner anyway.
And once he offered it to me,
all I had to do was...
- Sell me out.
Mike's pro Bono
is against some prison.
And guess who builds
those prisons.
I gave him my word.
And you once gave your word
to me
and went back on it.
I had to lie to Harvey's face.
You either go and work
at the clinic
or you stay at Pearson Specter.
But you can't play them both
for fools
and put me in the middle.
I have a binding agreement
signed by his legal clinic,
stating that they would have
no outside help
from Pearson Specter Litt
on this case.
Yet they did.
You convinced me the only way
to heal
was to keep this from happening
to someone else,
and now I have nothing.
This isn't just about you
protecting
your client's interests.
It's about you protecting
yourself.
Why don't you tell me
what's really going on here?
That's it.
They've had me
by the balls ever since.
Jesus--how'd you let yourself
get compromised like that?
This is my situation, Harvey.
No.
This is a firm situation,
and we need to cut ties
with those bastards
right the hell now.
I don't believe this.
You're pulling rank
after I opened up to you?
That's bullshit.
No, Alex.
What's bullshit is
you letting yourself
be put in that position
for the last five years.
- Letting?
- Yeah, letting.
And now I gotta get us out,
because you did this to me.
Well, as long as we're
throwing blame around, Harvey,
I didn't do shit to you.
You did this to me.
All in.
Not this time, brother.
I got you.
Bullshit, you got me.
Uh-huh.
I know how you play.
You checked to open.
You got jack/ten at best.
This is a bluff.
I'm calling.
Do what you have to do.
Kings over sevens,
motherfu--er.
Trip sevens, little man.
Maybe you don't know
how I play after all.
Uh-uh.
You're on tilt.
You've been on tilt all night.
That was a stupid play
and you know it.
What's going on with you?
I was supposed to
make partner today,
but Louis Litt screwed me over,
so there.
That's why I'm pissed.
Shit.
I didn't know.
Well, now you do.
I don't understand, Harvey.
I thought you were Jessica
Pearson's guy over there.
I thought so too,
but she didn't have my back.
Well, what if I had your back?
What are you talking about?
I heard
Tommy Bratton talking.
They're looking to
bring someone in.
You say the word, I bet
I can get you in as partner.
What's in it for you?
Bratton's about to
make an offer
to some big-time earner
at Skadden.
I say you and me go in there
and tell him two junior partners
are a hell of a lot better
than one senior partner.
- Pass.
- Come on, Harvey.
At least think about it.
I don't need
to think about it.
I just went through
the same thing,
and the guy who proposed it
ended up stabbing me
in the back.
I wouldn't do that to you.
Yeah, well,
I appreciate your offer, but...
I'm not going to give you
the opportunity.
Now, you need me to stake you?
There's 300.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
I heard about
what happened in court.
I know you gave up the case,
Mike, I'm sorry.
Rachel, I gave the case up
because you reminded me
to be a man of my word,
but like I said,
I gave my word
to Oscar Reyes first.
What does that mean?
It means that
I don't want to lie to you,
and I don't want to lie
to Harvey, but...
I'm going to get this case
opened in criminal court,
and for the record,
that does not violate
the agreement that I signed.
So you're going to
tell Harvey, right?
If he asks me, I'll tell him,
but I'm not going to
volunteer it,
and I need to know
if you're good with that.
- Mike--
- Before you answer,
I want you
to think about the fact
that these guys are
extending sentences.
♪ ♪
What if it were me in there,
and it was my sentence
that got extended?
I just have one question.
What if Harvey asks me about it?
Then you tell him the truth.
♪ ♪
Then yeah,
I'm good with it.
♪ ♪
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 7x07 ♪
Full Disclosure
Original Air Date on August 23, 2017
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ ♪
What's this?
I never thanked you
for allowing me into the Bar,
and I figured you'd prefer a
criminal case to a fruit basket.
This is a civil case.
It was a civil case.
But it doesn't have to be.
That doesn't sound like
a gift to me.
It sounds like a favor for you.
Anita, you said you're about
doing what's right.
People are being kept
in prison for money.
That's not right.
If that's true.
I wish there was something I
could do about it, but I can't.
What do you mean,
you can't?
You know what I mean.
Nobody wants to see me
spending my time
getting bad guys
out of prison.
And what if I told you
it was a criminal conspiracy
between two Fortune 500
companies?
What are you talking about?
I couldn't pursue the case
because we represent
another client who was
pressuring me to drop it,
and there's no way
they did that
just to protect Reform Corp.,
which means they're in on it.
Do you have any proof?
No, but--
You bring me some proof of
a conspiracy and I'll pursue it.
That's the best I can do.
Anita, I don't have
the resources to--
Not my problem.
♪ ♪
And another thing...
Whatever you do bring me
has to be
on the Reform Corp. side
of the arrangement,
because if it isn't,
you're breaking privilege,
and I can't use any of it.
♪ ♪
Harvey.
There's something I want to tell
you, but I need to know
if you're over what happened
with Louis and the promotion.
I'm fine, Donna.
Good, because I need to leave
work early tomorrow night.
What for?
It's my six-month anniversary
with Mark.
What's that face?
- Nothing.
I guess I just didn't think
you were one of those people.
What people?
The people that celebrate
their niece's
third-grade graduation
like it was
the Moon landing.
And when was the last time
you saw anyone seriously
for six months?
I'm not the topic
of this conversation.
How could you be?
Because we're talking about
a mature and committed
relationship.
You're right, Donna, we are,
which is why I got you a gift
to celebrate your anniversary.
Harvey...
this is very generous,
but I can't accept it.
Why not?
Because Mark planned
a special night for us,
and how's he going to feel
when I pull out a gift card
to help pay for it?
- That wasn't the idea.
- I know,
but if you want to
really give me a gift,
promise you won't call or
interrupt me the entire night.
I promise.
Thanks, Harvey.
♪ ♪
God damn it, Jeffrey,
this is a place of business,
not a petting zoo,
so you either flush the goldfish
or you're fired.
You don't have the authority
to do that.
Section 207,
paragraph three of the by-laws:
Insubordination to a partner
results in termination.
This has nothing to do with
my fish and you know it.
It's got everything to do
with that fish,
and I don't want to hear
another word about it,
so unless you want to
say another word--
Louis,
can I talk to you for a second?
Hey, Jessica, I was just
in the middle of something--
Now.
Yes?
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
I'm exercising my authority
as junior partner
over that douche.
By trying to kill his fish?
No, by trying to keep order
in the bullpen.
Jessica,
Jeffrey's work habits are--
It's because I didn't
call him junior partner.
Shut up, this has nothing
to do with how I feel about
his stupid, disrespectful
asshole fish.
Louis...
have you considered
therapy?
Why would I do that?
That would be like Baryshnikov
taking dance lessons.
- Louis--
- Jessica,
shrinks are for pussies.
Now, can I go back to
yelling at Jeffrey?
Because these associates need
guidance and discipline.
Listen to me, Louis.
I stayed out of that whole
thing between you and Harvey
because that was Daniel's call.
And you want to go off on the
associates, that's one thing,
but you let this promotion go
to your head,
and you take it out on Harvey,
I'm going to step the hell
back in.
Jessica, you have my word
as junior partner:
if there's any problem
with Harvey,
it won't be because of me.
♪ ♪
I'm a little busy right now.
Well, whatever it is,
put it to the side.
Daniel wants you to work
with Louis
on the Reinsdorf case.
You got something to say,
Harvey, say it.
Okay, I'll say it.
You didn't have my back
when Hardman screwed me over,
and now
you're carrying his water
while he tries to humiliate me.
I don't care what he's doing.
I care about what I'm doing,
which is to see if you can
put that ego of yours aside
and play the long game.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Do you have any idea
how many times I had to smile
and take it when Charles Van
Dyke pawned his work off on me?
Or when Stanley Gordon would
call me into his office
just so he could ogle my ass
when I left?
That is not the same thing.
Not to mention when Schmidt
would talk about "the blacks"
like he was living in 1950.
I sucked it up for years,
Harvey.
Now it's your turn.
What if I won't?
Then you're not my guy,
because if you can't even
pretend to bend a knee
to your rivals,
it doesn't matter what you do to
get ahead of them in the future.
They're going to see you coming
a mile away.
♪ ♪
Mr. Kreuger,
I appreciate you meeting me.
This isn't Downton Abbey,
Harvey.
It's a construction firm.
Call me Pat,
or see yourself out.
Fair enough, Pat.
I'm sure you know that
a junior partner at our firm
broke his word.
I think you're owed an apology.
Usually the clients pay
the lawyers,
not the other way around.
This is a unique situation.
This looks a lot like
you're trying to pay me off.
I'm trying to make things
right, and allow you to move on.
You want to know how to get
someone's best effort, Harvey?
It's not paying them
the most money.
It's making sure that
their interests
are aligned with yours,
and Alex Williams wants this
case to go away as much as I do.
You don't need your interests
aligned anymore.
This case is over.
Maybe it is.
And maybe it isn't.
But I've heard that
from your firm once before.
And then I believe
it was your own associate
who opened the case again
in the first place.
So, you see, Harvey,
it's not just Alex's interests
that are aligned with mine.
It's yours.
And I plan to keep it that way.
♪ ♪
Let me guess: you're here to
go over my testimony.
I already told you
I'm not giving you anything
until my daughter gets paid.
It's not what I'm here for,
Frank.
I need to know if you know
anything about a conspiracy
outside of Reform Corp.
Conspiracy outside of R--
What are you talking about?
What the hell's going on here?
We got thrown off the case.
What did you just say to me?
- Frank--
- 'Cause you came in here
promising my daughter a future.
Now you're telling me
it's all a bunch of shit.
It's not a bunch of shit,
and I can get the case reopened,
but I need evidence
of a conspiracy
with Masterson Construction.
Then I can't help you,
'cause all I know is,
those are the guys
that put us all to work.
Work?
What are you talking about?
Those places
aren't like Danbury.
We work our asses off
to build their prison
so they can put more of us away.
But if you're looking for
a conspiracy, there's not.
They do it all out in the open,
call it "rehabilitation."
Well, it may not have been
hidden, but something is.
And I think you just pointed me
in the right direction.
♪ ♪
What the hell did you do?
What are you talking about?
You went to Masterson
behind my back.
I did what I told you
I was going to do.
I got you into this mess,
I'm going to get you out.
Then all
going to Masterson does
is put you
in their crosshairs.
I'm already
And now that
I know what happened,
I might as well have been
a part of it myself.
Then maybe
instead of poking the bear,
we should tell Mike Ross
the truth.
What are you talking about?
We both know that Mike is not
going to let this thing go
till he gets to
the bottom of it.
Maybe, if I just come clean--
Listen to me, Alex.
You go to him with your story,
you're going to give him
a map to what happened,
a can of gas, and a match
to light the whole damn thing
on fire.
I hope you're right, Harvey,
because I've got a daughter,
and if I didn't take a chance to
stop this thing when I had it...
I'm telling you, Alex,
you let it go.
♪ ♪
- Harvey.
- Louis.
Jessica said
Hardman wants us to work
on the Reinsdorf case
together.
She said the same thing to me.
Well, I'm here to help,
not get in a fight.
My feelings exactly.
Good, I thought we could start
by talking strategy.
I'm sorry,
but are you first chair?
No, you are,
but I just thought--
Doesn't matter
what you thought,
because our strategy is to go
after their general counsel.
And when would you like
to depose this guy?
Never, because I'm going to
put that asshole on the stand,
and I'm going to crack him like
a piece of matzo on Passover.
Louis, you put him on
the stand without deposing him,
you'll be asking questions
you don't know the answers to.
- So what?
- So,
that's the number one rule
of lawyering.
Well, thank you,
F. Lee Bailey.
And here I thought
the number one rule
was to know your goddamn place.
And I don't need to take advice
from a sixth-year associate.
And I don't need to take
a loss on my record
because you're too insecure
to listen to reason.
You know what, Harvey,
you don't need to take anything
because you're not in charge.
So it's up to you:
you gonna get on board
or are you gonna
go crying to mama?
♪ ♪
You're right, Louis.
You're the partner.
I'm just here to back you up.
♪ ♪
Donna, I want you to pull
whatever strings you have to
to get the Reinsdorf trial
moved up to tomorrow.
I'll get right on it.
And one more thing:
don't tell Louis.
What?
Harvey,
Jessica said
to bury the hatchet,
not stick it in Louis's back.
Donna, I went into his office
in good faith
and it took him
less than 30 seconds
to wave his title in my face.
What does that have to do
with putting the firm's interest
above your ego?
Because, when I brought up
a legitimate issue
with his strategy, he shot me
down for no other reason
than it came out of my mouth.
I'm telling you: we don't
do this, we're going to lose.
Look at me.
Are you sure
this is the right call?
Listen to me.
Jessica wants me
to play the long game,
and that's what I'm doing.
I sat in there, ate shit,
and he bought it.
So now, tomorrow,
I'm going to win this thing,
and Jessica's going to know
she can count on me.
All right.
I'll move the court date,
and I'll make sure
Louis doesn't find out.
♪ ♪
Harvey, good, you're here.
We didn't get a chance to
talk about what happened
with you, Alex, and Mike.
No, we didn't,
and as a matter of fact,
I'm wondering where Mike is.
Well, he was in earlier,
but then he left.
But I'm guessing
that's not really
the question you're asking.
You want to know if he's
somehow still pursing that case.
And what if I do?
I would say
from personal experience,
don't ask a question unless
you're really ready
to hear the answer.
♪ ♪
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Jessica, how did you know?
It doesn't matter how.
What matters is, I told you
to work it out with Louis,
and right now,
he's sitting in his office
with no idea
this case is starting.
Exactly, I'm playing
the long game, like you said.
No, Harvey.
You're not playing anything,
because this case is mine now.
- What?
- You heard me.
I gave you a direct order,
and you spat in my face.
Jessica, this is bullshit.
I went in there
and he spat in my face,
and I was willing to take it,
but what I'm not willing to take
is losing this thing
out of spite,
and if you take this case
right now,
you're going to lose,
because you have no idea
what's going on with it.
Maybe I will
and maybe I won't.
But sometimes you have to
bench your quarterback
to show 'em
who's running the team,
whether you take a loss or not.
All rise!
Time's up, Harvey.
Step aside.
Jessica, please don't do this
to me in public.
I'm not doing anything to you.
You did this to yourself.
Do we have a problem,
counselor?
No, Your Honor, we don't.
My colleague is needed
back at our firm.
I'm stepping in.
In that case,
be seated, everyone.
Court is now in session.
♪ ♪
Michael,
why are you closing the door?
You know I'm uncomfortable
with obstructed exits.
Because I need to
ask you something,
and I don't want
to be interrupted.
Michael, you're asking me to
hack a government institution.
I can't do that.
Look closely, Benjamin.
It's a private corporation,
and I'm telling you,
they're scumbags.
What's it for?
What do you mean?
I mean, if you're asking me
to do something like this,
I have to bill it to a case.
And what if I asked you
not to?
I would have to ask you why.
I'm going against
Harvey's wishes.
You asked me to do that
once before
for a mock trial.
And I need to know,
is this mock, or is it real?
It's real,
and Harvey can't know.
♪ ♪
Harvey, I didn't think you
ever got south of Canal Street.
Yeah, well,
today I'm making an exception.
Is that offer
still on the table?
Are you serious?
I'm here, aren't I?
Then hell yeah,
it's still on the table.
I'll talk to Tommy Bratton
right now.
Well, when you talk to him,
you tell him I'm only coming
over if he meets my demands.
And what demands
would those be?
I don't just want partner.
I want an office with a view.
I want to eat what I kill
and I want to get paid
more than any other
junior partner in the firm.
Those are some
pretty big asks.
I can't guarantee Bratton's
going to say yes.
You want to make partner on my
coattails, you make him say yes.
Your coattails?
I'm talking about
me helping you
as much as about you helping me.
Then do what you said
you were going to do,
because if you can't
make that happen,
they don't respect me,
and I'm not coming to a place
where I'm not respected.
Okay, Harvey,
but if you want respect,
you need to show
some damn respect.
I go in to stick my neck
out for you,
you don't come back
and say you'll consider it.
It's a done goddamn deal.
Okay, Alex, you have my word.
You get me everything
I'm asking for...
I'm done with Pearson Hardman.
♪ ♪
Jessica.
Hey, how are ya?
Louis, remember
when we talked about
not abusing your power
with Harvey?
Absolutely,
and that's why I treated him
with the utmost respect.
Well, if that's the case,
then exactly
why did he litigate Reinsdorf
behind your back?
Goddamn it.
What the hell did he do?
I'm not concerned with
what he did.
I'm concerned with what you did.
Jessica, I swear,
I was the perfect gentleman,
but then Harvey questioned
my leadership.
In other words,
he had a better idea than you?
Well, whether it was
or it wasn't,
he didn't respect
the office of junior partner.
Because there is no office
of junior partner, Louis,
and the real problem here
isn't Harvey.
It's that chip
on your shoulder.
What chip?
Louis, I need you to be
at this address
tomorrow morning at 9:00 a.m.
- Why?
- Because I believe
you will benefit
from therapy,
and this man is the best
in the business.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
back the truck up.
Jessica, therapy?
I'm the most stable,
secure man you ever met.
And you fight me on this,
you'll be the most
unemployed man I've ever met.
Do we understand each other?
Yeah.
9:00 a.m. it is.
And Louis,
when you walk
through that door,
you're going to be tempted to
turn right the hell around,
and I'm telling you,
if you want a future here,
you won't.
♪ ♪
Harvey,
what are you doing here?
I thought you were in court
all day.
Well, Jessica had other plans,
like booting me off this case.
What?
She walked in there
and threw me out
with my tail between my legs,
like I was a piece-of-shit
first-year associate.
Listen to me, you need to
calm down so we can figure out
what we're going to do.
I am calm,
and I already took care
of what we're going to do.
What are you talking about?
I got us an offer
at Bratton Gould.
If everything goes like I think,
we'll be there
by the end of the week.
What?
Harvey,
that doesn't make any sense.
Jessica's your biggest fan.
She's always been
in your corner.
Was she in my corner
when Hardman promoted Louis?
That's not fair.
That was his call.
Well, whose call was
cutting my balls off
in front of
the entire courtroom today?
I don't care what she did.
The woman paid for you
to go to law school
out of her own pocket.
The least you can do
is talk to her
before you do something
like this.
Donna, I tried talking to her.
But it doesn't matter.
It's too late.
I gave Alex my word.
It's a done deal.
♪ ♪
Well, it may be
a done deal for you,
but it isn't a done deal for me.
- Donna--
- I like it here, Harvey,
and you can't just
make this kind of decision
about my life without
running it by me first.
If this is your way of trying
to get me to stay...
I'm not trying to get you
to do anything,
but I'm not just gonna
follow you out the door
without thinking this through.
What do you want, Donna?
You want an apology?
Well, here it is: I'm sorry
I didn't consult with you.
I don't want an apology,
Harvey.
I wanted to talk this thing
through with you,
which, by the way, is what you
should have done with Jessica.
Well, you know what, Donna?
I didn't come to you for advice.
I came to tell you
to start packing.
But if you don't want
to come with me,
then don't come with me.
♪ ♪
Rachel, do you have a second?
Of course.
Mike went to prison for me.
I owe him, and I know it.
But he's not the only guy I owe,
and that guy's going to have
a serious problem
if I stick my head in the sand,
pretending Mike isn't
who I know he really is.
That's a shitty situation
to be in.
Yeah, it is, so I'm going
to ask you something,
but I need you
to be honest with me.
Is Mike still working on
the case against Reform Corp.?
He is.
And for the record, Harvey,
he told me that if you asked,
to tell you everything
you wanted to know.
What exactly is he doing?
He's trying to build
a criminal case
to give to Anita Gibbs,
which he has every right to do.
Because the agreement
he signed
only precluded a civil suit.
Exactly.
How far along is he?
I don't know,
but knowing Mike,
I'm sure
he's a hell of a lot closer
than he was this morning.
♪ ♪
What do you think?
Do you want to share
a bottle of rosé?
I think I remember
what happened the last time
we did that.
All the more reason
to get it, then.
I couldn't agree more.
Good, now that
that is decided...
Happy anniversary.
♪ ♪
Shakespeare's sonnets.
Everyone is talking
about this guy.
Apparently
he's all the rage right now.
This was my favorite class
in college.
How did you know?
I do my homework.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- What?
- Nothing.
It's just so nice
to be with a man
who's so thoughtful after
spending all day with a man
who doesn't even know
what the word means.
Talking about Harvey.
He's leaving the firm,
and he just assumed
that I would go with him.
He didn't even think
to ask me first.
We're celebrating tonight.
Let's not talk about Harvey.
I'm not talking about Harvey;
I'm talking about my life,
and a huge decision
that I have to make.
Wait a second--you're actually
thinking about going with him?
Even after the way
he treated you?
I don't know
what I'm going to do.
Well, what if I said that
I'd like you to stay
at Pearson Hardman?
- Why would you say that?
- You know why.
Because Harvey's like a silent
partner in our relationship.
I mean, we can't even get
through a dinner
without his name coming up.
Mark, I specifically told him
not to interrupt us tonight
so he wouldn't come up.
And yet he came up anyway.
- Mark--
- Look,
I don't pretend to be
as insightful as you are,
but if you can't even separate
yourself from him
when he's asking you to leave
a job that you love...
makes me wonder if it's really
the job you love after all.
What do you want me to say,
Mark?
I want you to say that you're
not going to follow the guy
wherever he goes
for the rest of your life.
I'm not going to say that.
Okay, well, I guess
I have my answer, then.
♪ ♪
Rachel, you are not
going to believe--
Mike,
before you say anything...
Harvey asked me if you were
still going after Reform Corp.,
and I told him that you were.
Doesn't matter,
'cause I got 'em.
What?
Gallo told me that Masterson
was using Reform Corp.'s inmates
to build new prisons.
Okay, but using inmates for
private companies is illegal.
It would be,
except five years ago,
Alex Williams got a waiver from
the state corrections board
allowing them to supplement
their workforce with inmates.
So where's the crime?
Wait a second.
Why are Masterson's budgets
on Reform Corp.'s email server?
More importantly,
why are the labor costs
1/5 of what they submitted
to the state?
Jesus.
Mike, they didn't just
use the inmates to supplement
the workforce;
the inmates were the workforce.
Which means Reform Corp.'s
not just extending sentences,
they're defrauding the state,
and they're splitting the
profits with Masterson, 50/50.
Mike,
where did you get all this?
- What does that matter?
- It matters because
if it came from Masterson,
then Harvey can stop Anita Gibbs
from using it.
Well, it didn't.
Benjamin got it from
Reform Corp.'s server,
which means we can redact
Masterson, give it to Gibbs,
and she can put the pieces
together herself.
There is nothing that
Harvey can do about it.
Mike,
he could fire you for this.
Rachel, I've been torn up
trying to reconcile
two parts of myself for
as long as I can remember:
pro Bono versus corporate law.
If he lets me go,
then he lets me go.
♪ ♪
Hello?
Hi, I'm Louis Litt,
here for
my 9:00 a.m. appointment.
Hello?
Hi, ya, Mr. Litt.
We've been expecting you.
I'm sorry, but did you just
speak in a German accent?
Please, taken ze seat.
Holy shit,
you're a goddamn Nazi.
What did you just say to me?
I said
I'm not going to sit here
and talk to you about
the weather,
let alone my goddamn feelings.
Thanks, but no thanks,
wiener schnitzel.
Please, Louis.
Just give me two minutes.
Two minutes.
First of all...
I take it you're Jewish?
Yeah, I'm not comfortable
answering that right now.
Well, it seems very clear,
based on the fact that
you just called me a Nazi.
What's your point?
Would it interest you to know
that I'm Jewish too?
Yeah, well, take out
your circumcised junk,
and maybe I'll believe you.
I'm not going to do that,
Louis.
But I will tell you
that my parents
were both children
during the war.
They survived by fleeing the
country and felt it their duty
to eventually return and raise
both my sister and myself
as proud Germans and Jews.
So, if you want to leave
because you don't like
the way I speak,
I understand, but if not,
why don't you tell me
what brings you here?
♪ ♪
I'm here because
no matter what I do,
nobody respects me.
♪ ♪
Jessica, we need to talk.
We do.
But if you're looking
for an apology--
I'm not here for an apology.
I'm here to tell you that
I'm expecting a job offer
from Bratton Gould.
You're expecting one...
or you went looking for one?
- Does it matter?
- It does to me.
Then you should know, I was
offered a job, I turned it down,
and it was going to
stay turned down
until you made it
crystal clear
that you don't respect me.
What I made clear is that
I call the shots,
and if you don't see how that
helps you in the long run--
Screw the long run!
They're going to make me
a partner now.
You won't even
go to bat for me.
You know what, Harvey?
I'm about done with
your little song and dance
about how
I don't have your back.
I picked you
out of the goddamn mail room,
and I've given you every
opportunity you ever had.
This was a mistake.
What was a mistake?
I came here
to give you a chance
to talk me out of leaving,
but when this offer comes in,
it's too late.
Just out of curiosity,
what would you have me do?
You know what the hell
I'd have you do.
Harvey,
you have more raw talent
than 99% of the partners
in this firm,
but I'm not going to give you
a promotion based on a threat.
You'll get one
when you're ready.
And if that's not good enough
for you...
then I wish you luck
at Bratton Gould.
Then consider this
my official notice.
♪ ♪
Louis, we spent
the last 40 minutes going over
every person
who has shown you disrespect
since the day you were born.
You kidding?
I'm just getting started.
Be that as it may,
if I ask you the one person
whose respect
you crave the most,
who would it be?
Don't dwell on it.
Just say the first name
that pops into your head.
Harvey Specter.
Good.
What's he like?
He's like a cross between
Marlon Brando and Superman.
What?
I'm just picturing.
This Harvey, is he a friend?
He's my best friend.
Would he describe you
as his best friend?
What the--what the fu--
is that supposed to mean?
- Louis--
- You son of a bitch.
Are you implying that
I'm not as good as him?
That I'm worthless?
Well you know what,
you Nazi supposed Jew,
I don't need to take that
from you.
I'm goddamn out of here!
Louis, this is wonderful.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Most people take years
to reveal their true selves.
But you, you are like a man
without skin.
I can see right through you.
This is fantastic.
How the hell
is this fantastic?
Because I can help you.
Your feelings of disrespect
are internal,
and you project them
onto the people in front of you,
and in your life,
those people throw
that disrespect back at you.
Well, I'm not going
to do that to you.
I'm going to be here for you.
That sounds like
a load of crap.
Listen to me.
If you keep treating the people
in your life like this,
you're going to push them away.
You know what, doc?
Jessica made me come here,
and I did.
And now that I have,
it's crystal clear
the last thing I need
in the world is therapy.
♪ ♪
Louis, calm down, you're
wearing a hole in the carpet.
Well, I'm sorry, Donna, Harvey
called an emergency meeting.
What do you expect?
I expect
a little self-control.
Good, you're here.
Gretchen said it couldn't
wait--what's going on?
I've got a move I want
to make, but before I do,
I want to put it to a vote.
- What kind of move?
- A big one.
Harvey, does this have
something to do with the fight
between you, Alex, and Mike?
Yes,
and I have reason to believe
that fight's not over.
Harvey, what's going on?
Alex has a gun to his head,
and if I don't do something
about it,
he's going to be in
some deep shit.
I have a way out of it,
but there's going to be
some consequences.
- For who?
- For Mike.
Harvey, is there any
other way out of this mess?
If there were,
I wouldn't be standing here.
Then tell us
what you want to do,
and let's get this over with.
♪ ♪
Don't tell me this is the "two
partners for the price of one"
idea you pitched me a year ago?
It is, but Harvey Specter
isn't like any lawyer
we've ever had.
Well, he's better not be,
if he has the balls to ask for
the moon and stars like this.
Look, the problem is,
I already have an offer out
to a hotshot at Skadden.
And if he hasn't already
said yes,
what the hell
is he waiting for?
I'll tell you what: he's afraid
he can't hack it here,
or he's using us
to get a better offer.
Either way, Harvey and I
are a better choice.
All right, Alex.
It looks like you two guys have
your shit together.
But here's the thing:
I pull this offer,
and your guy says no,
I'm left here with nothing
but my dick in my hand.
So you tell right now
you guarantee that he says yes.
You think I didn't know
you were going to demand that?
I already talked to him
about it.
He gave me his word.
Okay, looks like I have
two new partners.
But Alex...
this thing goes south, it's
your ass that's on the line.
♪ ♪
So you're having
a good coffee?
Is that what we're doing
with our 11:00s now?
Louis.
What the hell is your problem?
My problem is I found out
you moved my court dates,
so why don't you go
tell your work husband
if he thinks I'm going to
forget about this,
he's got another thing coming.
You know what, Louis?
Why don't you go
tell him yourself?
But you better hurry,
because as of Monday,
Harvey doesn't work here
anymore.
- What?
- You heard me.
Harvey's leaving,
my life is a mess,
and as far as I'm concerned,
that's on you.
Me?
What do you mean, me?
If you can't figure out
what I mean by that,
then you may be
a good junior partner,
but you got a long way to go
as a human being.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here?
What do you mean,
what am I doing here?
You wanted a conspiracy,
I got you one.
I don't want anything
from you, and for the record,
I was a fool to think I could
trust you in the first place.
Anita, I don't know what
the hell you're talking about.
Don't play dumb with me.
Pearson Specter doesn't just
represent Masterson;
you also represent Reform Corp.
Which means anything
I get from you is tainted
because you broke privilege.
Goddamn it, Harvey must have
just signed them.
So what you're saying is,
Harvey was never on board
with this in the first place?
Anita, you can still take
this case, all right?
You just say you received
the evidence--
Anonymously?
I don't think so, Mike.
And one more thing:
the next time you're looking
to involve me
in a war with Harvey Specter,
go to someone else.
♪ ♪
Jessica, I heard about Harvey.
Louis, he made his choice.
It's not the choice
that I wanted,
but we're just going to
have to deal with it.
Now, if you don't mind...
Well, actually, I do mind.
Jessica, this whole thing
was my fault.
I put him in a position where he
had to leave, and you know it.
Louis, that's big of you,
but--
But nothing.
Doctor Lipschitz said when
you don't respect yourself,
you go looking for signs of
disrespect in others,
and the way I got to
junior partner...
I don't respect myself for that.
What are you saying?
I'm saying if it was my pride
in refusing to admit
that he was right and I was
wrong that caused him to go,
I won't be able to
forgive myself.
So please, do not let him go.
Louis?
Yeah.
Did you mean what
you said the other day?
About the associates needing
guidance and discipline?
To tell you the truth,
I didn't at the time.
But yes, they do.
Then as the firm's
newest partner,
how would you like to officially
be in charge of the associates?
♪ ♪
I'd like that very much.
Treat them well.
I will.
♪ ♪
Did you come here to say
good-bye?
Because I think
we already did that.
No, Harvey.
I came here to let you know
that I did what
I should have done
in the first place.
And what exactly
does that mean?
It means I went to see
Daniel, and I told him
if the next person we promote
to junior partner isn't you,
I'm leaving.
You did that for me?
Sometimes playing the long
game means understanding
who you want to be teammates
with in the long run,
and the person I want to be
teammates with in the long run
is you.
I hope I'm not too late, Harvey,
but if I am,
I really do wish you luck
at Bratton Gould.
♪ ♪
Harvey,
Alex Williams just called.
Says it's a done deal.
♪ ♪
For the record,
I would have gone with you.
I should have asked you first.
♪ ♪
Hello?
Dr. Lipschitz,
it's Louis Litt.
Listen, you were right.
I do need someone who isn't
going to let me push them away.
I'm very happy to hear that,
Louis.
Do you think five days a week
is too much?
Why don't we just
start with an appointment
on Monday
and go from there?
Sounds good.
♪ ♪
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Nothing's wrong with me.
I ordered you
to drop this thing.
You didn't, so I figured out
a way to make you drop it.
You think signing
Reform Corp. is going to
make this go away,
you're out of your mind.
And if you think that's true,
you wouldn't be in my face
right now.
Harvey, they are lining
their pockets on the backs
of people who should have
gone free years ago,
and you're letting them
get away with it.
I'm their lawyer.
I'm not a prosecutor.
What the fu-- does
Alex Williams have on you, huh?
Nobody has anything on me.
Then why the hell
are you doing this?
'Cause there's no way
it's for the money.
You don't understand.
I'll tell you what
I do understand.
You owe him something,
and they have something on him,
and if I can figure that out,
how long do you think
it's gonna take before whatever
it is gets out anyway?
You listen to me.
If you ever valued the times
that we've had each other's
backs, you'll have mine now,
because I'm telling you,
I need it.
Then tell me what's going on.
I'm not going to do that,
because I can't trust you.
But I'll tell you this: You lift
a finger to do something
that even looks like
you're making
another move on this case,
I don't care if
you're calling Oscar Reyes
to wish him a happy birthday,
you're fired.
So why don't you take the night
and decide if
you trust me enough
to keep working here or not.
♪ ♪
Hey, hey.
You here to check out
your new office?
Because it's ready.
Alex,
I'm staying at Pearson Hardman.
What?
We had a deal.
I know that,
but then I realized
Jessica's family, and no title
is worth giving that up.
I don't care
what you realized.
I told Tommy Bratton
you'd sign on the dotted line.
He pulled an offer to that
hotshot from Skadden for me.
I know this puts you
in a bad spot.
Bad spot?
You stood in front of me,
gave me your goddamn word,
and I banked on that,
so I don't care what kind of
come-to-Jesus moment
you think you had,
that shit is legally binding.
If you want to try to
enforce that, go right ahead,
but what does it say
to the world
when a firm has to sue a lawyer
just to get him to come there?
What's it say when
I can't trust you anymore?
Alex, you don't need me
to make partner.
Maybe I don't,
but this is some bullshit.
I'm not saying it's not.
And I know right now,
my word means nothing,
but I promise you,
someday you're going to
need help with something,
and no matter what it is,
I'll be there for you.
I owe you one.
And you can let it go or not,
but I'm telling you, man to man,
this is something I have to do.
♪ ♪
Okay, Harvey, I'll let it go,
but you do owe me one,
and someday
I'm going to come calling.
♪ ♪
Harvey, I know
you want to help Alex,
but if it means losing Mike,
then I have to ask,
is it worth it?
Mike went to prison for you.
I know that, Donna.
Harvey, what did Alex do?
Why do you owe him?
Alex.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to come clean to you.
Does Harvey know you're here?
No--in fact, he told me
not to talk to you at all,
but you have a right
to know the truth, and...
I'm tired of having this whole
thing hanging over my head.
Come on in.
After Alex told Bratton that
I wasn't coming, he was nothing.
They gave him unwinnable cases
and worked him 90 hours a week
until one day,
Bratton came to him
and said there was a way back.
All he had to do was take on
Masterson Construction
as a client.
- Exactly.
- And he said yes.
Of course I said yes.
There were no red flags.
The waiver that put inmates to
work was just smart business.
On the surface,
everything was legit.
So how'd you figure out
it wasn't?
One day, I was at Brunswick,
and a guard gave me a letter.
It said an inmate had died
on the job site,
and that it was being
covered up.
Let me guess: you took it to
Pat Kreuger, Masterson's CEO,
and he said that
he'd look into it.
Two weeks later, that guard
was murdered by an inmate.
Holy shit.
And that's when he knew
Masterson and Reform Corp.
had been colluding
from the start.
So what did he do?
He went to
his managing partner,
and Tommy Bratton said it wasn't
collusion between two parties.
It was collusion between
three parties.
They tied all my bonuses
to all the key dates...
- The waiver...
- The start of construction...
- The guard's death...
- It looked like
I orchestrated
the whole damn thing.
So you covered up a murder?
I had no proof of anything.
I had a wife and daughter, and
it looked like I was in on it.
Harvey, that's horrible,
but this isn't on you.
Alex still could've made a call
anonymously.
And so could you when
you found out Mike was a fraud.
You didn't have to be a party
to a crime, but you were.
That crime wasn't a murder.
Did you hear me, Donna?
They had him.
I had a wife and daughter,
and they set me up.
What was I supposed to do?
Mike, I hate these people.
They deserve to go away
for what they did,
and every morning when I woke up
and every night
when I went to sleep,
I wanted to make that happen,
but I didn't, for one reason:
I didn't want my daughter
to grow up without a father,
and if you pursue this,
there's no way I don't get
caught up in it.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
When Bratton came after
our clients,
Alex signed a declaration saying
he took full responsibility.
Harvey, if you're asking Mike
to let this thing go...
I don't know if I can do that.
I'm not asking you
to let it go.
I'm telling you what will happen
if you don't.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net