Previously on "Suits"...
It's a no.
I thought you liked the idea.
That was before I realized
that it was nothing but
sassy remarks.
I thought you wanted our baby
to have a relationship
with its biological father.
If you're gonna get
this worked up, it makes me
think I don't really know you.
What if I could make it
more like you?
I might be able
to give it the ability
to learn from your heart.
You really think
we could do that?
We can try.
Rachel Zane deserves to be
in the Bar.
You're not only gonna
stop blocking her,
you're gonna run interference
for her if someone else does.
And in return,
you'll do what I want.
No, but I'll do what you want
for something else.
We need to come up
with a lawsuit
against Velocity Data Solutions.
No.
- What do you mean, "no"?
- Fabricating a lawsuit
to manipulate a stock
is illegal.
It's not illegal if we find
a legitimate suit.
Let's finish the job and get you
back to being a lawyer.
"Tenants are required
to be notified
of all construction
by certified letter."
Is this a certified letter
or not?
- Objection.
- Your Honor,
this is the fraudulent attorney.
Open your mouth
in my courtroom again
and you will be removed.
Mr. Grady, do you have
an objection or not?
- I don't.
- Then the court has no choice
but to dismiss this case
with prejudice.
The guy holding up your
interview was trying
to get us to do something
because he thought he could.
- Are you going to?
- Yes.
He is.
Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
I'm in.
Okay, Rachel's gone.
I don't want any bullshit.
You're telling me
that no matter what we do,
Rachel's getting into the Bar?
What I'm telling you is
if she doesn't get in,
that asshole isn't gonna be
the one that stopped her.
Okay. I'm in.
What do we have to do?
I told you what we need to do.
We need to make a dent
in Velocity Data's stock.
Harvey, that's no joke.
You realize how much we're gonna
have to sue them for
to make their earnings
take a hit?
You're damn right I do.
They're a huge company,
which means
it's got to be something huge.
I don't even know
if that matters.
No matter what we sue them for,
they're just gonna
want to settle.
I know that.
Which means we need to insist
on an admission of guilt.
I get it.
You want me to run this whole
thing through the clinic.
It's the only way to make it
look legitimate.
Harvey, I don't know if I can
convince Nathan to do that.
Well, you better,
because if anyone figures out
that we're doing this
for personal gain,
your chance of
getting into the bar is gone.
Wait, you were Captain
of the Glee Club?
The official title
is Lieutenant Colonel,
but that's cool
you didn't know that.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God. You still
had braces at 17.
Actually, I had them again
at 28.
Wow.
Between this,
your nasal passages,
the skin tag epidemic
and the foot surgeries,
you really had a lot
of medical procedures.
Tara, I know what you
must be thinking
and I swear,
I will not pass any of my
maladies onto our child.
Louis,
I wasn't thinking that,
but you do understand
that biologically
this isn't your child.
Of course I do.
Okay.
But I was thinking
we would have at least
one child of our own.
At least?
At least.
You were right, Louis.
Getting to know each other
is fun.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
Good, you're here.
I need your help.
Is this about the worker comp
case from Flushing?
No, this is about
Velocity Data Solutions.
- What about them?
- They're a dirty company.
They've been getting away
with shit for years.
I could never go after them
when I worked at Pearson Specter
because we were always on
the other side of these things,
but I can go after them now.
Mike, if this is going
to require me going to court--
It's not.
Look, Oliver, I know
what happened the other day.
But you don't have to be a trial
lawyer to be a great lawyer.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying that you have
skills that
other lawyers don't have
and I'm gonna put those skills
to use right now.
- What do you need?
- You see those boxes?
That's every case that Velocity
has settled in the last 20 years
where the names of
the plaintiffs have been sealed.
We need to figure out
who those people are,
what they got paid not to say,
and then we need
to get every damn one of them
to come forward.
Mike, what did
these guys do to you?
They didn't do anything
to me, Oliver.
I just don't like it when
people think they can get away
with anything just because
nobody is watching.
- That was fast.
- What was fast?
Well, I assume you're here
to tell me
you filed suit against Velocity.
What I'm here
to tell you, Craig,
is Mike Ross
is gonna handle Velocity.
Then we have a problem,
'cause I didn't cut a deal
with Mike Ross.
I cut a deal with you.
And there's a reason
you're an in-house counsel
and I'm not.
What are you talking about?
Once we drop
whatever bomb we're gonna drop,
they're gonna want to settle
without an admission of guilt
and everyone knows
settling is what I do.
So Mike Ross is gonna
take this to court?
He's not even
a goddamn lawyer.
Welcome to the conversation,
Craig.
That's what I'm here
to talk about.
You're gonna make
Mike's hearing official.
I can't do that,
it's too soon.
Bullshit.
You think I don't know
you only said yes about Mike
to get me to help you?
Of course that's why
I said yes.
And the hardest thing about
getting him into the Bar
is getting him a hearing when he
hasn't even gone to law school.
Which is why you're
gonna sponsor him
based on his years
of work at Pearson Specter.
You're talking about
reading the law.
You're damn right I am.
There's precedent
and you know it.
Listen to me,
I can influence the vote,
but I cannot sponsor someone
I'm going to be voting on.
Then find someone who will.
Because if you can't get him
a hearing in the next week,
this thing is off.
And one more thing, Craig.
You and I won't be
talking again
because in case you haven't
figured it out yet,
this is a hell of a lot
more serious
than cheating on your wife.
♪ Suits 6x14 ♪
Admission of Guilt
Original Air Date on February 15, 201
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Harvey, what are you
doing in here?
What do you mean?
It's an executive kitchen.
I'm an executive.
Yeah, but you're a bagel guy.
This place is like
croissant central.
Then maybe I just came in here
hoping to spend some
quality time with you.
Are you saying you want to
hear about my night with Tara?
Of course I do.
Right after we make friendship
bracelets
and braid each other's hair.
For your information,
it was a magical evening,
but actually,
I'm here to talk business.
- What business?
- Couture Apparel.
Jessica and I always gave
their CEO an annual analysis
of their legal needs
for the upcoming year--
And now that she's gone,
you want us to do it?
Exactly.
Sounds like
a dog and pony show.
It is more than that, Harvey.
It is a show of force.
For one day, Carly Donahue
needs to feel like
the most important client
in the portfolio.
And having one partner
go by himself
doesn't send that message.
Louis, relax.
I'm happy to do it.
You are?
Of course I am.
I told you, we're partners.
You know, Harvey, I always
dreamed it could be like this.
Partners, confidantes,
friends
I had the exact
same dream, Louis.
- Really?
- No, not really.
Does that mean you're never
gonna go mudding with me?
Yes, Louis,
that's what it means.
I'll give Donna the details
on that meeting.
Hey, I hope you got a hammer,
'cause I just brought you
some nails.
- You found something?
- Yeah, I did.
I already found six
cases we can use,
and that's just the tip
of the iceberg.
So let's grab our coats
and go kick Velocity's ass
up and down the street.
Easy, Tyson.
You have to tell me
what kind of suits these are.
They're mining suits,
which means health problems
or corporate negligence--
Either way, the damages
could be through the roof.
Oliver, this is great.
I know. And if you asked me
to make an argument
about it in court,
I'd probably shit the bed.
But, Mike, I'm telling you,
there's something here.
And I'm telling you,
maybe one day you'll overcome
your court stuff,
maybe you won't.
Either way, this proves that
you're a hell of a lawyer.
Yeah, thanks, Mike.
I gotta admit,
it feels pretty good to know
I can do what I just did.
Then why don't you start
drafting a suit.
'Cause after I get these
people on board,
that's exactly
what we're gonna have to do.
Donna,
you're never gonna believe
what Louis just asked me.
The Donna:
Give me three guesses.
He wants to be you.
He wants to look like you.
He wants to wear your skin
as a body suit.
Okay, did you just talk
without saying anything?
What's the big deal?
You do it all the time.
The Donna: Good one, Donna.
You're on fire today.
Okay, what the hell's
going on here?
Oh, you mean The Donna?
It's just a little product
that Benjamin and I
have been working on.
It doesn't have my emotional
intelligence yet
but I thought I'd have a little
fun with it in the meantime.
Do you have your emotional
intelligence yet?
When it can top that,
you might have something.
The Donna: Loser.
Okay, which one of you
said that?
both: She did.
Sorry, buddy.
Grill's shut down.
We don't open again till five.
That's okay.
I'm not here for a cheeseburger.
I'm here to talk about
Hazelton Mining Company.
- What about it?
- You filed a complaint
alleging life-threatening
health problems
resulting from work.
That complaint mysteriously
went away
and I want to help you get the
compensation that you deserve.
I don't need any help
from an ambulance chaser.
I'm not an ambulance chaser,
Mr. Stamos.
My name is Mike Ross,
I work at a clinic
and our commissions are capped
at $50,000.
So we are not in this
for the money.
Then what are you in it for?
Let's just say
Velocity is bad news,
Well, I'd like to help,
but even if I wanted to sue
those bastards, I can't.
I know.
You took a payout
and you signed
a non-disclosure agreement.
That's got nothing
to do with it.
They made us
all sign those things.
If any one of us breaks it,
it negates them all.
Then negate them all.
That's easy for you to say.
I'm dying of something
with a name so long,
I can't even tell you
what it is.
And you're talking about
your fee being capped
at more money
than they paid me.
Listen to me, if that's really
all they paid you,
and you really are dying,
we can shatter those NDAs
in about five seconds.
You don't understand.
I was their supervisor,
Mr. Ross.
I was responsible
for all those guys that got sick
and I'm the one that
got us the money
that went with those NDAs.
And let me guess:
ever since you signed them,
you haven't had
a good night's sleep.
Tell me I'm wrong,
I'll leave right now.
What do I have to do?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Rachel,
what are you doing here?
- Can I come in?
- Of course.
Can I get you something?
No, I'm good.
Thank you.
If this is about
checking out the place
for your wedding, it might be
better during the day.
No, I didn't come
to talk about that.
I came here to talk about this.
Rachel, this is terrific.
You passed the Character
and Fitness committee
without even having to go in.
I know.
Then why do you look
so concerned?
Because I know what
you and Mike are doing
to make this happen.
Rachel, this letter
has nothing to do
with what we're doing.
You deserve this and all this
guy is doing is the right thing.
Okay,
let's say that's true.
What about what you two
are doing to make
the same thing happen for Mike?
Listen--
No, Harvey,
I need you to listen.
He just spent the past
couple months in prison,
and it was supposed to be years.
And I can't let that
happen again.
It's not going
to happen again.
I know it isn't.
Which is why I'm here.
I need your word that if things
start to go south,
that you will pull the plug
on this whole thing.
- Rachel--
- Harvey, I want your word.
You got it.
Thing go south, it's done.
- Hey, Mike, you got a second?
- Yeah, what's up?
I was hoping you could
tell me.
Apparently Oliver was in
the conference room all day
working on some case
against Velocity Data.
Uh, yeah,
I gave him an assignment.
What do you mean
you "gave him an assignment"?
He had the workers comp case.
I took care of that.
Mike, your job isn't
to generate cases.
It's to consult on the cases
we've already taken.
I know that,
but it's also to help
our associates
become better lawyers.
Oliver got his ass kicked
in court the other day.
I'm just helping
to build him back up.
And there are plenty
of other cases
you could've used to do that.
Instead, you went
and you signed a class action,
which is something we do not do.
Well, why isn't it
something we do?
These men have life-threatening
health problems
They need someone
to give a shit about them.
It isn't something we do
because we don't have
the time or the man power
to take on
a giant like Velocity.
Nathan, I don't know
what you want me to say.
I went out there, I signed
these guys and they trusted me.
I can't back out now.
This the kinda shit you pulled
when you were
at Pearson Specter?
On occasion.
Then I want you to say
the next time you think
to pull something like this,
you have the common courtesy
to tell me before you do it.
♪ ♪
The Donna:
I suggest a warm bubble bath
and a pint of Chunky Monkey.
Because if you're not
good to yourself,
how can you expect anyone else
to be good to you?
And for your information,
the initial program
was vanilla bean
and an Enya CD,
but it learned from you.
Pretty awesome, right?
No, Benjamin,
it's not pretty awesome.
You can't just give it
platitudes.
What are you talking about?
The key to having empathy
is making people
feel supported
in their feelings,
not just trying to solve
their problems.
That is the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
No, it isn't.
And not only that,
you have to tailor
its response
to the feelings the person
is having.
How am I supposed to do that?
You have to have it listen.
Okay, I get it.
You're saying it has to
understand the feelings
of its user,
and express that understanding
in a sympathetic manner.
Exactly. Now, you think you
can do that?
Of course I can.
All I need to do
is continually expose it
to what it's not providing
and eventually
the feedback loop will show it
how to be more like you.
In other words, awesome.
Yes, that's the entire point
of this exercise.
And for the record,
no one awesome listens to Enya.
Well maybe not her later work.
You're the whole team?
Seems fair.
There's only one of you.
I'm not an attorney,
Mr. Ross.
I'm CEO.
Then you must be serious.
Why don't you give me
a number?
You want a number?
Zero.
'Cause I'm not gonna be
shaken down by the likes of you.
This isn't a shakedown,
Mr. Palmer.
Those men are dying
from conditions
that your company knew about.
Those men signed
non-disclosure agreements.
And if they break them,
we can come after them
for every penny they got.
And I've got a way
to bust every damn one
of those agreements.
No way, those things
are airtight.
Airtight doesn't apply
when signed under duress,
which is exactly what
dying of lung cancer
and not being able to afford
a doctor is.
Well good luck making
that argument a thousand times,
because I'm gonna fight
each and every one of them
to my dying breath.
You can't do that,
they're a class.
I can and I will.
And you move forward with this,
I'm gonna bury
that shit-hole legal clinic
of yours in so much paperwork,
you're going to choke to death.
So you just called me down
here to tell me no to my face?
I called you down here
to show you that if
you pursue this action,
those men are going to be
left with nothing
and so are you.
That's a hell of a strategy,
but I guess you didn't
get the memo
that my co-counsel on this
is Pearson Specter Litt.
Bullshit. Their name's not on
any one of these documents.
'Cause they wanted to keep
a low profile,
but go ahead, pick up the phone.
I'll call them myself.
Then I guess I'll see you
and your big law firm in court.
Because like I said,
I'm not gonna be shaken down
by the likes of you.
Harvey,
I just got a phone call
from the lawyers at Velocity,
They wanted me to confirm that
we're co-counsel
with Mike on this.
What'd you tell them?
What do you think I told them?
I told them yes.
Because if they're asking,
he obviously bluffed
and I'm not gonna hang him
out to dry.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna find out
what he did
and why he did it.
- What the hell did you do?
- Relax, Harvey,
I was just coming to tell you--
No, I specifically
said that I can't be seen
to be involved in this thing.
And you also said we only had
one shot at this.
I was the one in the room
with this guy.
He had me and he knew it.
So what?
So you always said that
if I'm in a knife fight
and I'm losing,
to pick up a gun.
And Pearson Specter Litt
is a goddamn gun.
Look, I know this isn't
exactly what we wanted,
but I can still be the one to
insist on an admission of guilt,
so what's really going on here?
I promised Rachel
that if this thing got too risky
I'd pull the plug, and it just
got a hell of a lot riskier.
Well, it also got real.
Those miners need us.
I'm not going to
abandon them, so...
what do you wanna do?
What do you think
I want to do?
I wanna kick this guy's ass.
Then here's the situation:
I got a 150 miners on board
and I can bust the NDAs.
But I can't make
the action a class
'cause they already
signed those rights away.
I get it.
He doesn't think
we can get all those
separate cases to court.
Well, he's got
another thing coming.
I got ten brand-new
associates upstairs
begging to work
on a case like this.
You're gonna oversee
every single one them
if it takes all night.
Then I have to meet you
at your office in an hour.
Something I need to
take care of first.
Louis, whatever it is,
it's gonna have to wait.
No, this'll just
take a second.
It's about
the Carly Donahue meeting.
I was thinking--
Louis, I'm sorry,
but I'm not gonna
be able to make it.
- What? Why the hell not?
- Mike needs my help on a case.
Harvey, you may not want
to accept this,
but Mike doesn't
work here anymore.
and firm business takes
priority over--
Listen, Louis,
this is firm business
and if what I think
is gonna happen happens,
Mike's gonna end up
back here when it's done.
- What?
- You remember that thing
that we took care of for Rachel
that you said might
be worth doing?
Well, it turns out
it was worth doing.
Only I'm doing it for Mike.
Holy shit. Seidel agreed
to go to bat for him?
Yes, and once it's done
and Mike's in the Bar,
he can come back here
and work again.
Harvey, that is great
and nobody wants that
more than I do,
but it's just one meeting.
Louis, I know that,
but in about three hours,
I'm gonna be under water
for the next three days.
Harvey--
Louis, I know I told you
I'd be there for you,
but I need you
to be there for me.
Okay, Harvey,
I'll do it.
Good, you're still here.
Box up the Velocity files
and meet me downstairs.
Where are we going?
Pearson Specter agreed
to partner up on the case.
- Shit, that's big.
- Want in?
Hell yeah.
Give me ten minutes.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
You wanna tell me
what this is?
That is an agreement
to co-counsel
and I was just gonna come
tell you about it.
How many times are you gonna
make a move without telling me?
Nathan, I'm sorry,
but I had to move fast.
The guy at Velocity was
putting the screws to me.
Is something shady
going on here, Mike?
- What?
- First you bring in
this huge case out of the blue.
Then all of sudden, you're
bringing in your old firm.
You're the one who said we
didn't have the resources
to handle this sort of thing,
so I just brought in
someone who would.
Yeah, and I bet they're
getting a sweet deal out of it.
It's not like that.
They're taking
half their usual fee.
That's all they're getting.
And what about you, Mike?
What are you getting?
What are you talking about?
You're gonna tell me
you're not using this
as a stepping stone
to get back to your old firm?
What? No, Nathan,
I don't want to go back there.
Bullshit.
I don't believe you.
Something is going on here
and I know it.
You know what, Nathan?
For your information,
Harvey Specter did offer me
a consulting job
just like you did,
except his had one more zero
at the end of it,
and I still turned him down.
I chose to be here,
but I don't want to be
second-guessed at every turn.
So either you're gonna trust
that my heart
is in the right place
or you're not.
Well, for your
information, Mike,
right now I really
don't have a choice.
- Hey, are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
How the hell am I supposed
to keep Carly Donahue's business
all by myself?
Because, Louis,
you're co-managing partner
and you're one hell of a lawyer.
Oh, you just don't
get it, do you?
This woman wants to know
that she's special to this firm.
If I walk in there by myself,
she's gonna
laugh me out of the room.
Then why didn't you
tell that to Harvey?
Because I know
how important Mike is to him
and I didn't want to
let him down.
- Then don't.
- That is not--
Louis, if this woman
needs to know
she's special to us,
there's more than one way
to do it and Harvey's
not the only one you can bring.
Donna, that's great.
But this meeting is tomorrow
and I don't even know
these new associates yet.
Yes, you do.
You know Katrina,
who's not just a new associate,
she's a Junior Partner
and you know Rachel,
who's as good as a fourth-year.
You go there with
a show of force like that,
trust me, this woman
is gonna be blown away.
Okay, Donna.
Show of force it is.
Holy shit,
Otis Redding's first album?
You sure Harvey won't mind
if I take it out?
Are you kidding me?
No, he says if that collection's
not for everyone,
then what's the point
of even having it here?
- Sounds like a great guy.
- The best.
Ghandi. Harvey.
- You serious?
- Hand to God.
Man's practically a saint.
- What's going on?
- Oliver, Harvey Specter.
Harvey Specter, Oliver.
Nice to meet you, Oliver.
Would you like me
to pour you a drink?
- Would you?
- No, I wouldn't.
Now put that down,
get out of my office
and if I ever catch you
touching one of my things again,
I'll shove it up your ass.
Is he serious?
Oh, not about the ass part,
but I'd put it back.
- You set me up.
- Mm-hmm.
Welcome to
Pearson Specter Litt.
[laughs] You enjoy that?
- Yeah, it felt okay.
- Good. Now why don't you go
make sure everyone knows exactly
what they're doing
It's 9:00 p.m.,
the clock's ticking
and we gotta
get this thing done.
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna figure out
what we're going to say
to that Velocity son of a bitch
when he walks in here tomorrow
begging for a settlement.
[dramatic music]
Do you have any idea
what this is about?
Gretchen said that Louis had
some special assignment for us.
All I know is I got
a rambling voicemail
- about Neapolitan ice cream.
- Neapolitan ice cream?
Yes.
Chocolate and vanilla
melded beautifully
with strawberry.
Just like we're about to do
for Carly Donahue.
Louis, did you just
call me chocolate?
Why would I do that?
You're my white swan,
Katrina's my black swan.
The math ain't that hard.
What's with the boxes, Louis?
This is everything
the firm has ever done
for Couture Apparel.
You're taking us
to your annual meeting?
I'm not just taking you.
We're running it together.
Okay, Louis--
I know what you're thinking.
How the hell
are a Junior Partner
and a third-year law student
supposed to
fill Jessica's size 13s?
Well the answer is:
you can't.
No one can.
Then why are we here?
Because we used to
dazzle Carly with rank.
This year, we're gonna
dazzle her with substance.
By knowing her business
better than anyone else.
I'll take care of
the business.
What you two are gonna do
is personally tailor
the presentation to her.
And as of now, we have
less than 24 hours to do that.
- We won't let you down, Louis.
- I know you won't.
You think Jessica
really wears size 13s?
That's exactly what
I was thinking.
Oliver, how's it going?
It's going okay.
I'm finished
drafting six complaints.
What is it?
It's nothing, it's just,
in the time I did six,
most of them did nine or ten.
I guess that means
you're in the home stretch, huh?
Guess I am.
Look, Oliver,
I know what you're thinking.
But I was telling Nathan
the truth.
I'm not looking to come back
here with these guys
instead of working with you.
I know you don't wanna
come back here, Mike.
I guess I just wanted to say
these associates are bad ass,
and I appreciate you choosing
to work with someone like me
over them.
You mind if I ask
how you're so sure
I don't want to come back here?
Because these associates
are amazing lawyers,
but not a single one of them
mentioned an actual human being
involved in this case
the whole night.
They're just trying to win.
And there's nothing
wrong with that,
but that's not you.
Yeah, Oliver, there is
something wrong with that.
And that's why you're
gonna be a better lawyer
than any one of these guys.
I'm gonna go tell Harvey
that we're in the home stretch.
[footsteps approaching]
- How's it going, genius?
- What?
I said, how's it going?
I'll tell you how it's going.
It's not going to work.
What?
But I thought that you said--
I don't care what you thought.
This isn't "Westworld."
I can't make her human.
Benjamin, I'm not asking you
to make her human.
I'm just asking you to give her
a little compassion.
Well I don't know how
to do that.
And it's supposed to learn
from itself, but it isn't.
Hey, what's going on?
The story I always told myself
was the only reason
I didn't work in Silicon Valley
was that I didn't want to,
but the truth is,
I don't have what it takes.
And then you come in here,
calling me a genius and--
Benjamin, it's okay.
You're only human.
If it doesn't work,
it doesn't work.
Really?
Really.
Besides, if I can't show
you compassion,
how can I ever expect The Donna
to show compassion?
Thanks Donna.
I'm sorry
if I got your hopes up.
Figure out what we're going
to say tomorrow?
You get those complaints
ready?
- I asked you first.
- Yeah, but I'm not the one
who had the least experienced
lawyer I've ever met
put this thing
over the goal line.
Come on, I thought I was
the least experienced lawyer
you've ever met.
No, you were
the least experienced dickhead
I ever met.
- Right.
- Because that kid may be green,
but he's the only one of you two
that actually went
to law school.
[laughs] Don't I know it.
Mike, what's on your mind?
Nothing. It's just--
this whole thing we're doing
is making me lie to a lot
of people, including Oliver
and I'm not thrilled about it.
What are you talking about?
Nathan thinks
there's an ulterior motive
to this case and he's right.
Oliver saw it and I had to lie
to them both to cover it up.
Maybe that's true,
but you need to
keep your eye on the ball.
You deserve to be a lawyer.
You're doing good
for those miners
and that's all that matters.
I don't know, Harvey.
What do you care so much about
what this kid thinks anyway?
Because he's the reason
I decided to change my mind
about doing this whole thing.
- What do you mean?
- He's a great kid.
And he's gonna be
a great lawyer.
But I had to watch him
tank a case without being
able to help him and a woman
ended up out on the street.
I thought if we do this, then
I'll never to have to sit back
and do nothing
when someone I care about
is losing ever again.
Then stop worrying about
what we're doing
because tomorrow
isn't about losing.
It's about winning.
This is ridiculous.
We've been up all night
and we've got nothing.
- Yes, we do.
- What is this?
This is the key to keeping
Carly Donahue's business.
How is a three-year-old
interview
with "Gourmand Magazine"
going to help us?
Because it shows
she's a foodie.
And like Louis said,
we need to show her
that we don't only understand
her company, we understand her.
I get it.
What if we structured
the presentation
like a nine course meal
and paired a discrete piece
of legal analysis
with each course?
Like a paired wine tasting.
Coupled with
a paired wine tasting.
Hold on,
are you a foodie, too?
What I am is a lover
of fine wine,
delightful cuisine
and the ballet.
In any order you pick.
[chuckles] Well, I don't think
we can have dancers
at the meeting.
No, we can't. Which means
unless you know how to cook,
we need to find ourselves
a world class chef
and we need to find it fast.
What about this:
Mike and I just met with
a world class, French-trained
chef to cater our wedding.
I mean, if he's available then--
Book him.
Well don't you wanna hear
more about his--
Rachel, if I can't trust
your taste in pairings,
I can't trust anyone's.
What are you talking about?
I never thanked you for this,
but you knew
your father and I
would be a great fit.
And if you hadn't set me up with
him after I was fired,
I don't know what
I would have done.
I'll book the chef.
I assume from the fact
that you called,
you got our Christmas present.
I didn't call you,
I called Harvey Specter.
Well, he called me.
And I wanted to come
have a little chat with you
before you got it into your head
that you could go behind my back
and cut a deal without
an admission of guilt.
- What?
- Look, I don't give a shit
how much you offered,
you're not gonna
buy your way out of this thing
without telling the world
what you did.
I don't think you understand
what the word settlement means.
I understand
what it means to you,
I just don't give a shit.
- One hundred million.
- With an admission of guilt.
Sure, where do I sign?
Listen to me.
$100 million is the biggest
payout this company's ever made.
No, it's not
because I'm not taking it.
What is wrong with you?
I'm willing to cut
your clients a check
that'll change their lives
and you're too stupid to see it.
Here's what I see:
Every day this case drags on,
your stock is gonna take a hit.
And every quarter
when the board meets,
that's gonna be
their first question
and your biggest
God damn headache.
So the real question
is are you ready
to take responsibility
for what you did or not?
I see you wore your power suit
for your return to the majors.
You gonna play in Yankee
Stadium,
you gotta wear the pinstripes.
How'd it go?
Good. He did exactly
what we thought he would.
Tried to lowball me,
called me an idiot
and then kicked me out.
How high did he go?
- A hundred million.
- [scoffs]
- What?
- Nothing, it's just
I would've gotten him up to two.
And how exactly would
you have done that
when you told me
not to counter?
I'm more intimidating.
I walk into a room, people cave.
It's a gift.
I think it's a gift
when you leave the room.
My gift to you
was saving your ass
when you screwed the pooch
by involving me in this case.
Seriously, Harvey,
I appreciate you
rolling with this thing.
Especially when
I had to improvise.
Don't worry about it.
The truth is,
I like getting the chance
to work with you again.
Besides, don't tell Rachel,
I like the added risk.
- Oh, I know.
- How do you know?
'Cause you told me.
"Life's like this,
but I like this."
What am I, Luke Perry?
- Sometimes.
- Look, I gotta go.
'Cause this asshole's gonna be
back in my office in an hour,
trying to cut a deal with me
behind your back.
Oh, my God.
This is amazing.
You really think so?
I know so.
It's the perfect legal analysis
combined with
the perfect presentation.
So, you don't think the fact
that Jessica isn't here--
Jessica Schmessica.
Carly's gonna be blown away.
I should promote
you both right now.
- Will you?
- No.
- Worth a try.
- Okay, we have some time.
So I'll meet you both
back here in an hour.
- Where are you going?
- Gonna go have a prunie.
Wanna clean out the pipes
for the nine course meal.
Mike Ross.
- Yes?
- I'm Craig Seidel.
What?
What are you doing here?
I wanna know
what the hell you're doing.
What you mean,
what am I doing?
I mean, you filed 150 suits,
not just one.
And James Palmer's
gonna fight each one of them.
Which means this thing
is gonna drag on forever.
And we're gonna
drop the hammer on him
as soon as he gets to Harvey's.
Now I don't wanna see you again
until I meet you for the first
time at that hearing.
Don't you walk away from me.
I hired Harvey to do a job,
he farmed it out to you
against my will and you're gonna
God damn listen to me.
No, you didn't hire Harvey.
You tried to mess with my
fiancée's life and you're lucky
we didn't
have you disbarred.
So instead of coming
to my place of work
and harassing me,
why don't you go back
to your hole
and we'll tell you it's done.
Okay,
but your window's closing.
This doesn't
get wrapped up soon,
your shot at being
a lawyer is over.
If you're gonna
bankroll a suit,
at least have the balls
to negotiate it yourself.
I take it
you didn't like the offer.
Admission of guilt
isn't an offer.
It's suicide.
It's Mike Ross' case,
it's his call.
Bullshit.
Mike Ross is some clinic worker.
You're Harvey Specter.
And from what I hear about you,
you don't give a shit
about guilt.
You're right, I don't.
So why don't you tell me
how much it's gonna take
to make this go away.
500 million.
Half a billion dollars?
Are you insane?
You poisoned your employees,
Mr. Palmer.
You're lucky
you're not in prison.
- 200 million.
- No.
- 300
Okay, make it 350
and call it a day.
500.
Not a penny less.
In that case,
make it zero
because you just confirmed what
I suspected since this morning.
You picked the exact number to
make my stock take a nosedive
and we both know
who benefits from that.
Craig Seidel.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Then I guess you also don't
know that Mike Ross
just got an appointment
with the ethics board
and it's a crime
to trade this for that.
Which means
your lawsuit is over.
Then I'll do something else.
You think I won't go after you
for stealing technology
from Seidel's company?
You have no proof
I did anything.
No, but he does
and I don't give
a shit about his marriage,
and I'm going to make him
come forward.
His marriage?
Is that what
he told you this is about?
Well, I've got news for you,
Mr. Specter,
the reason
he hasn't come forward
has nothing
to do with his marriage.
So, why don't you go find out
what's what.
And I got a feeling when you do,
you'll drop this
case by the morning.
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
[knocking]
- Hey.
You ran out
of the presentation so quickly,
I didn't get to ask
what you thought.
I had to get to class,
but I thought it went great.
What about Louis?
He was over the Moon.
I'm sure he's glad
to have you back.
I'm glad to be back.
- Well, I should, uh--
- What was it like
working with my dad?
You said it was a great pairing
and I was just wondering--
- What you were missing.
- Yes.
You were missing a brilliant,
tireless, sweet, funny,
charming man.
who may also be the best
litigator I've ever seen.
Maybe you didn't understand
my question.
I was asking what it was like
to work with Zane,
not Kaldor.
Rachel, I'm serious.
I learned a lot about
your father while I was there
and I'm telling you,
it was all good.
What about his temper?
Well, maybe it wasn't
all good.
Well, good night.
One more thing
I learned about him.
He doesn't just love you,
he respects you.
- How would you know that--
- When he offered you that job,
he was beaming.
He told everyone in the office
that his brilliant baby girl
was gonna work for us
and she was gonna
blow us all to smithereens.
- He said that?
- Rachel, I didn't tell you that
to make you feel bad.
He was okay
that you didn't take his offer.
It doesn't make me feel bad.
It makes me feel great.
- Is he in?
- No, he had to run out.
All right, do me a favor,
just tell him I need to
talk to him when he gets back.
You mind if I ask
what it's about?
I just got off the phone
with Carly Donahue.
Louis, what happened?
Rachel said that it went great.
I thought it did, too,
but then she called me
and said that the next time she
asks for a meeting
with me and Harvey,
she better get a goddamn meeting
with me and Harvey
instead of two nobodies.
- What did you tell her?
- I told her how dare she
talk about my superstars
like that.
She's lucky to have them.
Louis, that's great.
Good for you.
She fired us, Donna.
Oh, Louis, I'm so sorry.
Look, this isn't your fault.
- You couldn't have known.
- It's okay.
I just need to go home.
[sighs]
Shit.
The Donna:
It's okay, Donna.
It's not your fault, either.
Yes, it is.
I'm Donna,
I should have known.
The Donna:
Maybe, but you always say
part of being human
is messing up sometimes
and you may be Donna,
but you're still human.
Holy shit.
You are ready.
Oliver.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I want to know
if I was wrong about you.
- What are you talking about?
- I wanna know
if you're using this case
to get back to Pearson Specter.
Oliver,
we talked about this.
I thought you understood
that's not who I am.
I thought so, too,
but then I got to thinking.
You fooled so many people
for so long.
What if you're fooling me now?
Because you said Pearson Specter
would never take on
a case like this when
you were there before.
Yeah, because they never
wanted to be on the wrong side
of a corporate lawsuit.
Then why are they on
the wrong side of one now?
- Oliver--
- Please, don't lie to me, Mike.
Just tell me what's going on.
It's a long story,
but we brought the suit
so I that could
get into the Bar.
So you were lying to Nathan,
only not about what he thought.
- Listen to me--
- I'm not gonna listen
and you need to tell him
what's going on.
I can't do that
and I wasn't lying to him
when I said I'm not going back
to my old firm.
I wasn't lying to him
when I said
these people's lives
matter to me
and I wasn't lying to
either one of you when I said
I care about what kind of lawyer
you're gonna be.
Well, if you care what kind of
lawyer I'm going to be,
set the right example
because you owe it to Nathan
to tell him the truth.
- Hi.
- Hey.
What's this?
It's every yearbook
I've ever had.
It was so nice doing it
with yours the other night
I thought maybe tonight we could
do it with mine.
Louis, what's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
I, uh--had a bad day
and I wanted to talk
to you about it.
But you went to
all this trouble
and I don't want
to bring you down.
Louis, my yearbooks are always
gonna be here.
And hearing about something as
important to you as your work
isn't going to bring me down.
It's going to bring us closer.
Are you sure because I have
a lot of bad days at work.
Which is all the more reason
for you to have someone
to make you feel better at home.
Okay, but it's kind of
a long story.
Well then you sit right here,
I'll go make you a drink
and then you can tell me
all about it.
You know what
I'm in the mood for?
I can't tell which one yet,
but I'm pretty sure its either
a Peach Schnapps or a nice,
cold Prunie.
You really are getting
to know me, aren't you?
I sure am.
[knocking]
Jesus Christ.
What are you doing here?
You guys told me to stay
away from you.
Yeah, that was before
I had a chat
with your buddy James Palmer.
Look, I don't even know
James Palmer,
so whatever he said--
He didn't have to
say anything,
all he had to do was point.
So what? This is an off-shore
account in my name.
An off-shore account
with $300,000 in it,
deposited exactly a day
after Velocity supposedly
stole your technology.
I was told by my accountant
to shelter certain earnings.
Bullshit. You don't have
those kind of earnings.
And you didn't have to keep this
quiet because you're married.
You kept it quiet because
you're in on it.
I was in on it.
I saw a chance to jump ship
and get paid in the process.
But instead,
they pulled the job
and put just enough money
in that account to implicate me.
- You piece of shit.
- Please, my employees
are gonna lose their jobs
because of me.
We need to keep this suit going
and get that technology back.
Nuh-uh, buddy.
You don't give a shit
about your employees
and I don't give a shit
about you.
This deal is done.
You can't do this.
Yes, I can
and I didn't have
leverage before,
but I have it now.
So you're not just
getting Mike an interview,
you're gonna block anyone
who tries to vote no.
And if you don't,
your boss is gonna get
an anonymous tip
that you sold trade secrets.
And I'm gonna make sure to
send this along with it.
You're my attorney.
You work for me.
You can't do that.
I don't work for you.
Remember, Craig?
That's how I set it up.
See you at the Bar.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man