Previously, on "Suits"...
Listening to his
closing argument,
I almost want
to let him go myself,
except for one thing--
he's a liar.
He thinks he doesn't have
to play by the same rules.
But we know he does.
- What did you do?
- I pled guilty.
If you think I'm gonna
let you do this,
you're out
of your goddamn mind.
He cut a deal
to save this firm.
He cut a deal to keep us
from going to prison.
We give Evan people
who already want to go,
and I give Anita Gibbs murderers
in exchange for Mike.
And what if it doesn't work
and we lose everything?
Then we do. But if we don't
try to save him, who are we?
Make the deal.
I am not letting you
go to prison
for a crime
that I committed.
I'm not letting you go when
you're gonna be found innocent!
Why the hell would
you lie to me?
'Cause the truth
would've broken you.
You know what, Harvey?
You want to come to my wedding,
you let me know.
[glass shatters]
I'm not trying to take
your place anymore.
I'm trying to get you ready
because you're weak.
- Harvey, I am not weak.
- Yeah? Well, hit me.
Is this what you want?
That I hate you
and that you made me do this?
We lose everything
because of you!
I am not saying that
I don't want to get married.
You go finish law school.
And then in two years,
when I get out,
if you still want
to marry me...
They're all gone.
Watch your back
in there, Mike.
I will.
[cell door clangs closed]
[razor buzzing]
General wake-up
for all inmates is at 6:00 a.m.
You will be standing next
to your bed at that time.
If you are not, you will face
disciplinary action.
At least five inmate counts
will be held
during each 24-hour period
at random times.
You will stand still during
every one of those counts.
If you are not, you will face
disciplinary action.
You will be at meals on time
if you want to eat.
You will be at work on time,
no matter what.
You will keep your cell in
a clean and sanitary condition.
If you fail in any of these
areas, you will face...
Disciplinary action.
Good.
You're getting the picture.
Do you mind if I ask
what disciplinary action means?
Since you got the balls
to ask that,
I'm sure you're gonna
find out soon enough.
- What's this for?
- What do you think it's for?
Strip naked, put everything
you own inside that bag,
then follow me.
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
I came to let you know
that I dropped him off,
and, um, he looks as good
as he could look.
And I think
he's gonna be okay.
I appreciate that.
But you could have told me
that over the phone.
So what are you
really doing here?
I miss him.
I miss him too.
- Where the hell are you going?
- Where do you think I'm going?
I'm going home, Louis.
Look, don't you get it?
They're all gone--
every single one of them.
Yeah, well,
we knew that already.
No, no,
I don't think you understand.
I'm not just talking
about the partners.
I'm talking about everyone,
from the accountants
to the secretaries to the guy
who shines my shoes, Donna.
All of them, gone.
And what exactly do you
want me to do about it?
I want you to get Harvey
on the goddamn phone.
- Well, I'm not gonna do that.
- Why not?
Because tonight's not
the night to call Harvey.
Why, because of Mike?
I don't know if you've noticed,
but Mike is gone,
along with everybody else.
And if we don't figure
something out by tonight,
we are gonna be left
with nothing.
I didn't say we weren't gonna
figure something out, Louis.
I said we're not
calling Harvey.
Well, then what the hell
are we gonna do?
Right now
I'm gonna go to my office
and fix myself
a goddamn drink.
The first time I met him?
What do you think
I thought?
I...
I thought he was an idiot.
Imagine how I felt
when a bunch of weed spilled
out of his briefcase
ten seconds after he walked
into his interview.
I know. You were so horrified,
you got on the phone,
and you called the police.
No, wait.
You didn't do that.
You offered
the idiot a job.
That's because
after I heard his story,
I knew he wasn't
an idiot after all.
And I knew by the end
of that first morning
that he wasn't like anyone
I'd ever met,
and that if I wasn't careful,
I was gonna be in trouble.
- To trouble.
[cell phone vibrates]
[chuckles] Look at that.
Louis left me a voice mail.
I don't understand.
You seem happy about that.
That's because one
of my favorite pastimes
is to listen
to one of Louis's messages.
What if he's upset
about something?
He's always upset
about something.
That's why one
of my favorite pastimes
is to listen to one
of Louis's messages.
Damn it, Harvey,
pick up the goddamn phone,
because this entire firm
is a ghost town,
and I'm sorry
Mike's in prison,
but if we don't figure
something out,
what you and your
little sidekick did
is gonna be the end of us.
And don't give me some bullshit
about tonight isn't the time,
because--
I got to go.
Yeah, I know.
I'm coming with you.
Rachel, you heard
what Louis said.
This is gonna be a rough night.
You need to stay here.
Harvey, it's gonna be a rough
night no matter where I am.
And at least
if I'm with you,
there's a chance
that I could be of some use.
You better get your coat,
because we don't have much time.
Now what?
Now you get dressed,
and you wait.
Would you like
some more drinks?
Can I offer you an appetizer,
maybe some truffle fries,
or are we allowed
to talk business now?
All right, Louis,
what do you think we should do,
since it was
your recommendation
that landed us in this mess
in the first place?
I recommended that because
it was a last-ditch effort
to get Mike out of prison.
And you also said
we'd only lose 50%
of our partners
to Evan Smith.
How could I have known
that she had the capacity
to bring on more than that?
Don't you get it?
The rest didn't go
to Evan Smith.
They just walked the hell out
and went somewhere else.
Then we can sue
their asses.
With what lawyers,
what resources, and what money?
Because I don't know
if you noticed,
but this firm has been gutted
because of your recommendation.
No, Jessica, it was gutted
because of mine.
Damn it, Louis.
I told you not to call him.
Well, I did.
Because he's a partner,
and like he just said,
he was the one
who wanted to sever the
noncompetes in the first place.
You're right, Louis.
I did.
But I didn't come down here
to play Pin the Blame
on the Harvey.
I came down here to figure out
what the hell we're gonna do.
Then let's get to it.
May I help you?
Oh, I'm sorry to interrupt,
but there was no one
at reception,
and I have your order here.
You got to be kidding me.
You call me down here
for an emergency,
and then you take the time
to order Chinese food?
I didn't order anything,
asshole.
So you crouch your tiger,
hide your dragon,
or I'm gonna Wang Chung
your ass out of here.
Louis, calm down.
Clearly, there's some mistake.
No one at this firm
has ordered any food.
Well, I'm pretty sure
this is the right place,
because the name on your door
says Jessica Pearson,
and this order is
for a Jessica Pearson.
Yeah this is Jessica Pearson.
both: Louis!
What?
They know
I'm not really here
to bring you
an egg roll, asshole.
I'm here to serve you
with this.
- What is that?
- It's a class action.
We're being sued for every
case Mike Ross has ever touched.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 6x01 ♪
To Trouble
Original Air Date on July 13, 2016
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
That's why they all left.
They knew this was coming,
and they got out
so they could all
have it on record
that they were gone
before the suit came down.
Then we need to know
who the hell tipped them off.
It doesn't matter
who tipped them off.
What matters is,
if we lose this suit,
we can't handle the money.
How much are
they suing us for?
- $100 million.
- God damn it.
We need to get
those partners back.
I told you, we're never gonna
get them back.
And right now we don't even
know where they went.
I do.
How the hell did you
pull that off?
Because lawyers don't talk
to lawyers,
but secretaries
talk to secretaries.
That is a list
of who went where.
Okay, we need a paper trail
tonight--
notices of breach
of contract--
and we need to get on record
that those partners
aren't off the hook.
It's too late
to send out notices.
We already got served
with the lawsuit.
He didn't record the time.
Donna, there's $5,000
in the cigar box on my desk.
Get it now.
Wait. Where the hell
are you going?
I'm going downstairs
to tell that server
he can have every nickel of it
to say he didn't deliver that
thing for another two hours.
Assuming Harvey
doesn't shit the bed,
we've got two hours
to figure out
how we're gonna serve
every partner on this list.
Give me that list.
They can consider
themselves served,
because Louis Marlowe Litt
never backs down from a fight.
[line trilling, clicks]
Federal Correctional
Institution, Danbury.
Yes, I'm--I'm calling
to check on an--
Inmate?
Yeah. His name is
Michael Ross, and he--
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I can't give out information
regarding inmates.
Would you at least be able
to tell me
if he's been processed yet?
If he surrendered himself,
then he has been processed.
Okay, so does that mean
that he's in a cell now or--
Ma'am,
I'm a prison administrator,
not a hotel concierge.
I don't know the whereabouts
of any given inmate
at any given time.
Okay, would you be able
to tell me when I can see him?
Are you his spouse
or immediate family?
No.
Then you'll have to go
through the approval process.
But he doesn't have
any immediate family,
and I'm his fiancée.
And unless you have
a filed marriage certificate,
you'll have to wait
till next month.
Next month?
Um...
Look, am I--am I allowed
to ask your name?
My name is Ruth.
Ruth, Mike and I were...
supposed to be married today,
but we weren't.
And I can't stop thinking
about him,
and I'm not gonna be
able to sleep
unless I know
that he's gonna be okay.
He's in prison, ma'am.
I really couldn't say.
I am sorry.
[line clicks, dial tone]
[door buzzes, opens]
Nothing like prison blue
to make you realize
the clothes
don't make the man, huh?
- Warden Clark?
- Me?
[chuckles]
No.
Who told you you were going
to meet the warden?
Uh, no one.
I-I just thought--
That this was going
to be like a prison movie.
"Put your trust
in the Lord,
but your ass belongs to me"
type shit.
You know "Shawshank"?
Of course you know "Shawshank."
You work in a prison.
No, brother,
I know "Shawshank"
because it's the greatest
movie ever made.
Here...
What's this?
Your psychological
evaluation.
Why do I need
a psychological evaluation?
Because the federal
penitentiary system says you do.
Now, when I get back,
if there's a hole in the mirror
covered by
a Rita Hayworth poster,
I will not be happy.
Okay, Louis, calm down.
You've had a few misfires,
possibly had a stroke,
but you can do this.
You've entered
the requisite information.
You calibrated
the typeface perfectly.
All you have to do
is press "send,"
and those sons of bitches are
about to get Litt the hell up.
[computer beeping]
God damn mother--
What the hell are you doing?
I'm just doing
a little troubleshooting. Why?
That is a $400,000
piece of hardware,
and you have
no business even--
Wait a second.
What are you still doing here?
What any IT officer
worth his salt would do.
I'm maintaining our system,
so it appears we're still
a functioning law firm
to the outside world.
Can you electronically
serve legal notice
to every partner
in the next two hours?
As long as you've got their
official business addresses,
I can do it
in the next two minutes.
Well, it's a good thing
I have them right here.
Um, no offense, but I'm really
more of a lone ranger.
- Excuse me?
- I can get this done
in a more efficient manner
without you looking
over my shoulder.
Well, that's what I told
my mother
when I looked
at my first "Playboy."
But it didn't happen then,
and it's not gonna happen now.
[computer beeps]
Well, that doesn't matter
because...
we have a problem.
So you're saying,
in this office,
at any given moment,
there's $100,000 hidden away.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Where?
I'm not telling you.
Whatever the hell you two
are in the middle of,
it's gonna have to wait,
because secretaries
may talk to secretaries,
but liars talk to idiots.
Louis, what the hell
are you talking about?
I'm saying that that list
is a bucket of bullshit,
and the mighty Donna Paulsen--
she doesn't know
her ass from her elbow.
Watch yourself, Louis.
I don't need
to watch myself, Harvey.
See, I don't know
if you've noticed,
but we're being sued
for a $100 million.
The partners are gone,
and we can't stop them.
Maybe we don't have
to stop them.
What are you saying?
What I want to know right now
is what we're all worth.
What, are you kidding?
Why don't you just jam
a cattle prod up my ass?
It would be less invasive.
I'll jam my fist
in your face
if you don't start getting
with the program.
There you go, resorting
to violence, like you always do.
Because you don't want to admit
this whole thing
is your fault
in the first place.
My fault?
If I hadn't brought Mike in,
you'd still be here
sniveling around
like a goddamn
junior partner.
And if I hadn't given
Donna back to you,
you'd still be
having panic attacks
like a goddamn little girl.
- Louis!
- You smug son of a bitch.
That's enough!
I just watched the man
that I love go to prison
so none of you have to.
And it hasn't been
five minutes...
And you're already
ripping each other apart.
- Rachel--
- Let me finish.
I thought I wanted
to be alone tonight.
And then I realized
that I didn't,
because I wanted to be
with my family.
But if you can't keep it
together tonight...
of all nights, then as far
as I'm concerned...
you can all rot in hell.
Well, I'm gonna say
what she won't.
This is all on you.
Louis, this is the last place
I wanted to be tonight too,
but I came back here
to save my firm anyway.
But if you're gonna be
the same old Louis
and we're going to do
the same old dance,
then maybe you and this firm
can both go rot in hell.
Louis, I don't want
to hear it.
Well, that's good,
because I'm not here to say it.
Are you saying you didn't
come down here
to tell me Harvey
can go to hell?
I'm saying I came down here
to tell you,
if Harvey wants to go...
we should let him.
Oh, Louis.
Jessica, you once told me,
no matter what happens,
Pearson will always consider
Litt her partner,
which means whatever happens
with Harvey...
we can do this together.
What do you say--
you and me?
Pearson Litt.
Wow.
You say no.
- No, Louis--
- I should have known.
You never wanted me.
All you ever wanted
was your precious Harvey.
Louis, you have no idea
what I want.
And my hesitation has nothing
to do with you.
Then what exactly
does it have to do with?
Louis...
I have put everything I have
into keeping this firm afloat
for as long
as I can remember.
Well, now look around you.
The ship isn't sinking.
It sunk.
And I don't know
if I have it in me
to pull it back up
from the bottom of the ocean.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Finally.
- Excuse me?
They came and took
that thing away three hours ago.
I've been sitting here
twiddling my thumbs ever since.
You were not twiddling
your thumbs.
You were waiting for me to go
over the results of that thing.
And the results are
you are full of shit.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
I answered every one
of those questions honestly.
I didn't say you didn't.
Well, in that case,
I guess you didn't get the memo.
We're in a prison
filled with con men.
Everyone here
is full of shit.
And the difference between you
and them is they know they are.
What does that even mean?
It means that they know
they don't have the patience
to earn what they want,
and that's why they go out
and steal it from other people.
So that's why you left me
in here all that time,
just to prove
that I have no patience.
Evaluation number two--
narcissistic tendencies.
The world does not revolve
around you.
You know what?
I don't have to listen to this.
No, you don't, because
my day is done.
And I'm going to go home,
pour myself a cold beer
while you get settled in cell 42
on the south end of D block.
Yeah, I get it.
I'm no longer Mike Ross.
I'm just inmate
number 53296.
No, you're still
Mike Ross.
But my job is to help you become
a better version of him
when you leave
than when you came in.
And if you trust me,
that just might happen.
Trust you?
You came in here before
acting like you were on my side.
Whoa, let's get
one thing straight.
I didn't act anything.
You waltzed in here thinking
this was gonna be
like some prison movie.
Well, it's not,
so get that through your head.
It's not a movie, brother.
It's just prison.
[door buzzes, opens]
Don't you dare
push that button.
You're not leaving, Harvey,
not tonight.
- Yes, I am.
- Well, if you really mean that,
then you're not the man
I thought you were.
What did you
just say to me?
I said that
underneath that expensive suit
and that perfect record
is a coward ready to run
from one of the biggest
fights of his life.
I am not running
from anything, Donna,
and I don't need
this right now.
No, Harvey, right now
is exactly when you need this,
because tomorrow's
gonna be too late.
I know what I'm doing.
Then why don't you
enlighten me?
Because I, for one,
would love to know
exactly what you're doing.
I'm gonna go the hell home
and never look back.
And what about tomorrow?
I don't care
about tomorrow.
Well, maybe you should start
caring about tomorrow,
because if you don't,
you're gonna wake up
three weeks from now,
and you're gonna realize
that this was
the biggest mistake
of your life,
and all you did was give up
exactly what Mike went
to prison to save.
Mike did not go to prison
to save this goddamn firm.
No, Harvey,
he went to prison to save us.
And now you're
walking out on us.
And if you're gonna do that,
then tell me,
what did he save us for?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Let's get
one thing straight.
You waltzed in here thinking
this was gonna be
like a prison movie.
Well, it's not.
Ross.
It's not a movie, brother.
It's just prison.
Ross.
Did you hear me?
We gonna have trouble
your first night?
- No.
- Then get in there.
One more thing...
you're not authorized to leave
this cell the rest of the night.
♪ ♪
Jessica, I'm sorry.
I didn't--
You know, this used to
be my desk.
Different desk,
same spot.
Jackson was there,
Burns was there,
and Kleiman was by the door.
He hated being by the door.
I don't know
any of those names.
Because they got out
a long time ago,
because this life
isn't for everyone.
And it's harder on some
than it is on others.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying that...
for women,
the rules are different.
You can't be everyone's friend
and invite them to tea
because...
warm means you're weak.
I wasn't gonna be weak.
But now the flip side
to that is,
if you're strong,
they think you're cold.
And that's
why they're all gone...
because they see me as...
as unfeeling
and manipulative.
I'm tired of it.
Well, they're wrong.
You're just saying that
because you're seeing me
like this.
No, that has nothing
to do with it.
My dad told me
that the only reason he came
to the church today
was because you told him
if he didn't,
he would lose me forever.
And you didn't do that
because you were trying
to manipulate some situation.
You did it
because you care.
And because you did it,
I will be loyal
to you forever.
What can I do
for you, Harvey?
I came to tell you
that I'm sorry.
You should be.
I know.
So you gonna give me
a tongue lashing,
or you want to figure out how
we can get out of this jackpot?
I think that right now
you and me and Louis
should get in a room
and smoke a peace pipe.
Are you saying what I think
you're saying?
I sure as hell am.
And where exactly
are we gonna get that shit
this late at night?
'Cause the coffee cart guy
is long gone.
It just so happens I like
to brew my own coffee
from time to time.
I'm gonna go get
a drink.
That stuff's illegal,
you know.
- Put that down.
- Oh, hey, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to--
Touch my stuff?
Funny, I didn't see the picture
jump into your hands by itself.
Look, I was just--
Relax,
I'm just giving you shit.
That's my little nephew--
sweet kid,
dumb as a box of rocks.
Welcome to Danbury.
What's your name?
Mike. Mike Ross.
Frank Gallo.
Well, Mike, looks like
we're gonna be sharing
this little condo
for a while, huh?
Feel like telling me
what you're in for?
I get it. You don't know
if you can trust me.
Listen, truth is, you shouldn't
trust anybody in here.
Except I just asked
what you did,
and they obviously already
caught you, so what's the harm?
Well, if there's no harm,
then why don't you tell me
what you're in for?
That could take a while.
I don't know about you,
but I'm free
for the next two years.
Ah, careful.
See, now you've told me
how long you're in for.
Starts there, ends with you
telling me you were born
a poor black child.
- You know "The Jerk"?
- Yeah, you know "The Jerk"?
Yeah, I watched a lot
of movies growing up.
Ah, we watch a lot
of movies in here.
All right, you want
to know my story?
It starts long before
I did what I did,
because I wasn't born
a poor black child,
but I was born poor,
which made me susceptible
to wanting to be rich.
Of course I'm thinking
about myself.
What, you wouldn't?
Please, you'd throw
a giraffe off of Noah's Ark
just to save
your sorry ass.
The world's probably
without unicorns
because of one
of your ancestors, and I--
Will you just let me finish
a thought, for God's sake?
Louis?
What exactly are you doing?
Well, what does
it look like I'm doing?
I'm having a discussion
about the fate of the firm
with my
dead secretary's ashes.
Well, as long as
it's not something weird.
[both chuckle]
What exactly have you two been
doing the last half hour?
The same thing
you're about to do.
No way, I'm not doing
the Mary Jane.
- Yes, you are.
- I'm not huffing and puffing.
- Louis, it's the only way.
- No, I'm not doing the dirty.
It's okay.
I got this.
I mean, if Louis doesn't want
to smoke it, maybe Norma does.
- Oh, don't you dare.
- Relax, Louis.
It's not like
it's gonna kill her.
Harvey, that is
not funny, okay?
You're gonna get ashes
in her ashes.
Then why don't you
just smoke it yourself?
- Put that out.
- Nope.
I'm gonna light this joint
on the count of one...
- Harvey, I'm telling you.
- Two...
- Harvey!
- Three.
[exhales sharply]
[both laughing]
Did you
pull your back out?
Give me the goddamn thing.
[both continue laughing]
Jesus Christ.
That's the thing
about computers.
You can delete
whatever you want,
but it's never really gone.
So, if you had just
stopped one trade sooner,
they might never have
even caught you.
Yeah, I could've stopped five,
four, three trades sooner.
They might not have.
But how do you know?
I'll tell you
how you know.
You stop when you have
enough money
to put your kids
through college.
Yeah, but what college?
And what if they want
to go to med school?
And what if they need a car?
And then
somewhere along the way,
you stop thinking
about if they need a car,
and you start thinking,
"I need a car."
And that's when
you get caught,
because whether you want
to admit it to yourself or not,
you were never thinking
about them in first place.
And whether you
were or weren't,
once you start,
you don't stop.
That's one hell
of a story, Frank.
Yeah, well,
this is prison.
Everyone's got
a hell of a story.
Anyway, that's enough
for one night.
I'm gonna go to bed.
My story started
with my grandmother.
She was sick,
and she needed money...
and I found a way
to get it for her.
Holy shit.
This is
the best thing ever.
I love the both of you
so much.
- This is your doing.
- Harvey, we're making progress.
Holy shit. This is
the best egg roll ever.
Jesus Christ,
get me out of here.
This is so awesome.
I mean, I haven't been
this stress-free
since I took gold
in the Math-lympics
and Esther went to fat camp
in the same week.
Esther went to fat camp?
They called it
Violin All-Stars,
but we all know
what that's code for.
And if you so much as picture
her in a school-girl outfit.
Come on, Louis,
we're all feeling good.
You telling me
you never slipped up
and had an inappropriate
relationship?
Louis, I do not want
to know the answer to that.
I did. It was the most
shameful night of my life.
Harvey, don't--
What exactly was so shameful
about it?
Well, she was a paralegal,
and I took mud with her.
I don't understand.
Are you saying you sullied
her reputation?
No, I'm saying I sullied
the concept of mud.
What the hell
are you talking about?
What, do I need
a bullhorn?
I had a premature muddification.
What the hell does that mean?
I think we all know
what that means.
It means I couldn't
hold my mud.
I still don't know
what that means.
Did you take a shit in the mud?
No, that's disgusting.
Well, what part of this
conversation isn't disgusting?
I know I'm gonna regret
asking this.
Who exactly was it?
I cannot tell you
that information.
Okay, good, because
the truth is, I don't--
It was Missy Dietler.
Louis, I'm gonna ask you
a question.
I want you
to tell me the truth.
Does Missy Dietler know
you couldn't hold your mud?
Oh, heavens no.
The Turkish silt
was thick enough
to prevent her
from feeling it, so...
Was it thick enough to hide
you wanting to go sleep after?
My God, she knew.
I got news for you, Louis.
They always know.
Oh, you're so right.
You're so right.
She--
I need
15 minutes to myself.
[both laughing]
And that's it.
I cut a deal,
and now I'm here.
Wait a second.
If you're a fake lawyer,
they had to give you a chance
to turn on someone
to get out of it.
They did.
So why the hell
didn't you do it?
Because I wouldn't have been
able to live with myself.
Somebody out there
owes you a lot.
Yeah, well...
I owe him a lot too.
So, what, you're--
you're like a-a good guy
or something?
[scoffs]
Am I?
What do you mean?
I left the woman I love
at the altar today.
Why'd you do that?
Because I didn't want
to chain her to me
if there was even the chance
that she would regret it.
Then, yeah,
you're a good guy.
Thanks, Frank.
One thing about everyone
being gone...
we got the run
of the place.
I never knew what the ceiling
looked like in here.
It's like
"The Breakfast Club."
Do you ever not
quote a movie?
No, and you got a problem
with that, frankly, my dear,
I don't give a damn.
You're an idiot.
You think Louis is gonna
be okay with me now?
[footsteps approaching]
I think we're about
to find out.
Harvey,
what I was saying before...
You don't need
to say anything, Louis.
I'm not gonna tell anyone.
That's not what
I was gonna say.
It's not the only inappropriate
relationship I ever had.
I recorded you saying
that you knew about Mike,
and I almost gave it
to Anita Gibbs.
- Did you know about this?
- No.
But I suspected
when he tried to get me
to turn you in
to Gibbs with him.
And what exactly was
your response to that request?
She said we didn't need
to do that,
and if it came to it, you would
take the bullet for both of us.
- I would have.
- I'm sorry, Harvey.
I almost
ruined your life.
You don't need
to be sorry, Louis.
The truth is, I'm the one
that ruined all of our lives,
when I hired Mike.
And I never apologized
to either one of you for it,
but I will now.
I'm sorry.
So...
we good?
We're good.
All right, now that the two
of you have made peace,
let's figure out
how we're gonna win this war,
which starts with knowing how
much we have in our war chest.
What exactly
does that mean?
It means it's time
to answer the question
that she asked two hours ago.
How much money do we have?
This again?
Louis, after everything
we've been through tonight,
how hard could it be
for us to write down
how much we're worth
right now?
I need another 15 minutes
to myself.
- Again?
- Aw, Harvey, let him go.
He probably doesn't have
as much as we do,
and it's a vulnerable thing
for him.
"Vulnerable"?
He just told us he jerked off
in the mud an hour ago.
You don't think he's gonna do
that right now, do you?
Based on
what he told us,
he doesn't need
15 minutes for that.
[laughs]
You want to call her?
What?
Your fiancée,
you want to call her?
What are you
talking about?
I'm talking about
my first night in here.
I remember thinking
what I wouldn't give
to let Jennifer know
I was okay.
The thing is, I couldn't,
but you can.
I thought we weren't allowed
to have phones in here.
Yeah, well, I wasn't allowed
to make inside trades either.
But I did,
and now I'm in here.
What else are they
gonna do?
Uh, thanks, but...
I just...
I just can't right now.
Whenever you want,
phone's right here.
Let's try to get
some shut-eye, man.
You okay?
He's everywhere.
He's all around
here, Donna.
The first place
we met was down the hallway.
And the first time we kissed
was in the library.
And I met his grandmother
50 feet from here.
And right here,
he told me the truth.
- Rachel--
- He was standing
right where you are,
and I was upset with him
about something
that I don't even remember.
And then he told me that he had
lost everyone in his life,
and then he told me
he was a fraud.
And then we...
Mm.
- You're gonna get through this.
- I know.
I just wish I could see him.
What do you mean?
You can see him.
No, I can't.
I called the prison.
You called
the prison tonight?
Yes, because I wanted
to know if he was okay.
And they...
they wouldn't give me
any information.
So then I asked them
about visitation,
and they said
that I had to wait,
and I had to get
on a list, and--
How long?
At least a month.
I don't know what to say.
You always know
what to say.
Not this time.
Excuse me, ladies.
Sorry to interrupt, but I think
we might have a problem.
- What is it, Benjamin?
- We're being hacked.
Oh, that's a tidy little sum
you got there.
You're not doing
so bad yourself.
No, I am not.
Not bad for two people
that came from nothing.
I didn't come from nothing,
and you know it.
Bet it still feels pretty good
to write that number down.
Oh, it sure does.
[imitates explosion]
You're still a little high,
aren't you?
I sure am.
There. You wanted you
wanted to know my net worth.
You got it.
- Holy shit.
- Who are you?
- Are you a king?
- No, I'm just not an idiot.
What the hell have you been
doing with your money?
Louis, we're not
exactly poor.
That's what Bolivia says
to the U.S.,
but if NATO goes to war,
they're not kicking in dick.
Well, if you're so damn rich,
why didn't you pony up
for Donna's salary
when you had the chance?
Do you even know how to spell
"fiscal responsibility"?
I know how
to spell "cheap."
All right, that's enough.
At least now we know
we have enough to fund
ourselves for a while.
You guys have
two rich uncles?
'Cause I'm not carrying your
asses if this thing drags out.
Louis, this is a team effort,
and I swear to God,
if you don't come
through on this--
I hate to interrupt
your "Breakfast Club" moment,
but you need to sober up.
- Donna, what is it?
- According to Benjamin,
the partners
didn't just leave.
They're coming after
every client we have.
All right,
give me an update
and give it to me
in plain English.
I was able to shut
the hack down,
but not before they got all
three of your clients' files.
Shit, they're trying to put us
in the ground tonight.
Then we have to stop it
before it even gets started.
Well, the only problem
with that
is that we don't know
what bullshit story
they're out there
selling right now.
Then we need to figure it out.
We need to figure it out fast.
[telephone ringing]
It's the main line.
What should we do?
Donna.
Pearson Specter Litt,
may I help you?
One moment, please.
It's for you.
It's Jim Reynolds.
That's Decker Pharmaceutical.
Don't take it. He's leaving us.
Louis,
he's my oldest client.
I'm not ducking his call.
- Jessica.
- Put him on speaker.
Jim, how can I help you?
You can tell me
what's going on there.
I've been hearing
a lot of rumors,
and I need to hear
the truth from you.
All right, Jim,
you want to hear the truth?
We went out for the afternoon,
and when we got back,
every partner
in the place was gone.
But I'm telling you,
the name partners
are still here,
and we can still service you
and the board.
I know you can.
Then you're not calling to say
that you're leaving us?
I was calling to tell you
I've been sent notice.
They're bifurcating your firm,
and the other partners
have nothing to do
with Pearson Specter Litt
anymore.
Thanks, Jim. I appreciate it,
and I won't forget it.
Jessica, if you're not back
on your feet
by the end of the month,
I won't be able
to hold off the board.
If we're not back
by the end of the month,
I will call the board
and resign from service myself.
Isn't this good?
They're not trying to poach.
- It's just as bad.
- What do you mean?
It means they don't care
about clients right now.
They're bifurcating the firm
because they want
their buy-ins back.
And they hacked us to get
our clients' information
so that they could
deliver notice.
We need to move the money
that we have
in every account by tomorrow.
We don't need to move it.
We need to use it.
If you're thinking
what I think you're thinking,
you're a genius.
What are you talking about?
We can use their buy-ins
to settle
the class-action lawsuits.
And they won't be able
to sue us for the money back
because it'll already
be gone.
You really are a genius.
Thanks, Harvey.
Uh, might I point out
that I was the one
that brought the hacking
to your attention
in the first place, so...
You might as well tell me
what's on your mind.
I can hear you
staring at the wall
from all the way over here.
How do you handle it...
Being away from Jennifer
for so long?
Trust each other,
visit each other,
and don't ask questions
you don't want answers to.
That doesn't sound
like fun.
Yeah, well, it shouldn't be
that hard for you.
You're only here
for two years.
I'm here for five more.
- Jesus.
- You're telling me.
You know, maybe I'll just
send Rachel a text...
you know,
let her know that I'm okay.
Sure thing, kid.
Just give it back
when you're done.
Well, now that
we're starting fresh,
can we please finally get rid
of that hideous duck painting?
- No, Louis, we can't.
- Why not?
Because it's like you.
I can't stand it,
but it's part of the family.
Speaking of family,
where's Gretchen?
I can't believe
she would walk out on us too.
She didn't. We were supposed
to be at the wedding,
so I gave her the day off
to go to the orthodontist.
- Orthodontist?
- Yeah, the woman's in her 60s.
She still wears
a retainer.
All right,
we have a game plan.
Tomorrow morning,
we offer them
ten cents on the dollar
to settle these suits.
And from this point on,
we are all committing
to giving this firm
every ounce of blood, sweat,
and tears we have.
[cell phone chimes]
What is it?
I just got a text
from Mike.
What does it say?
It says
that he's settling in
and that he's getting along well
with his roommate...
[breathes deeply]
And that he thinks
he's gonna be okay.
Maybe he's gonna be okay,
but his roommate's
in for trouble.
To trouble.
Hey.
What?
She texted you back.
What did she say?
She says she got your text,
she misses you,
and she's glad you get along
with your roommate.
Thanks, Frank...
[sighs]
For everything.
[door buzzes, opens]
[whispering]
All right, let's go.
Come on, you got to get out
before next shift.
They can't know
I let you switch.
Wait. Switch what?
I'm in the right cell.
I'm in the one you gave me.
Yeah, but this isn't
the one they gave me.
What?
You're in the right cell.
I'm not.
What the hell are you
talking about?
Only thing I told you
tonight that's true
is that you shouldn't
trust people in here.
But you did.
Now I know all about you.
Why the hell would you
do that to me?
You said you could've turned
on a guy to get out of here,
but you didn't
because you owe him.
Well, I owe that
son of a bitch too.
Harvey.
Yeah, Harvey Specter...
put me away 13 years ago.
I've been dreaming about
getting him back ever since.
Then I read about you
in the paper,
and I realized
I could get back at him
without ever leaving
these walls.
- You son of a bitch.
- Take it easy, Mike.
You remember,
I know about you.
And I got your
little girlfriend's number
right here.
[sighs]
[door closes, buzzes]
[dramatic rock music]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man