- Good night.
- Bye.
But the least you could do
is be honest with Jenny.
That's what
this is all about?
- Yeah.
- You always liked her.
You kept flirting with me
long after
you started dating her.
Yeah, well,
that's gonna stop.
And while you're at it,
no more running to me
for favors
or asking me for help.
How 'bout you find yourself
some other paralegal?
Because, as far as I'm
concerned, we're done.
You haven't even
gone to any law school.
- I'm working there!
- Oh, yeah.
What, as a lawyer?
It's a long story, okay?
But you can't
tell anyone, ever.
This guy is not your friend.
He is an anchor.
He is my oldest friend.
You were there.
What would you do?
I'd tell him everything.
Watch Cameron go down.
Sleep like a baby
after I did it.
Harvey would never
use this,
and he'd kill me
if he knew I had it.
But can you use this...
to help him?
Clifford Danner.
He was 18.
I put him in jail
12 years ago.
He's innocent.
Cameron buried the evidence.
- You have enough to overturn?
- I don't know.
So what are you
going to do?
I'm gonna get him out.
[Upbeat pop music]
Mmm.
[Laughs] Go, go.
9224-4930-754229.
Nope, that's not right.
Right.
I gave it to you backwards.
I have to keep it interesting
for myself.
Ah, security code.
[Sighs]
You know I know it.
Why are you wasting our time?
'Cause I wanna
make you work for it.
Oh, really?
Well, maybe I don't feel
like working for it.
Okay. All right--
767! Stop.
No, no.
[Laughs]
[Distant siren,
shower running]
What are you doing?
Showering.
Oh, you don't trust me
being here without you.
No, I--
I trust you, I just...
You know,
I like everything just so.
Well...
just so doesn't mean clean.
It means just so.
Gotcha.
- Uh--
- have a good day.
- Bye.
Trevor.
- Jesus. Uh--
- Surprise.
- Can I come in?
- No.
You, uh--
well, I'm late.
So we should, you know,
grab a coffee on the way.
Well, let me just--
let me just take a piss first.
No, no.
Uh, Trevor, stop!
Stop.
You got a girl in there,
don't you.
[Chuckles]
Let's go.
- I'm just gonna take a pee.
- Trevor, stop. No, no--
- It's fine.
- That's not even funny.
Get your hand off the knob.
- We're going. I'll buy you breakfast.
- You're so serious.
- He loves you!
- Go.
I got a job.
Law firm mail room,
of all places.
Huh.
I was wondering, um...
think I could stay with you
for a couple days?
Uh...
I don't really know
if that's such a good idea.
You know, I could have
died that day,
if it hadn't been
for you and your boss.
And I don't want to live
that life anymore.
I really don't.
I don't have anybody else.
[Sighs]
Okay.
I was thinking, you know,
maybe I'll try
and call Jenny.
Yeah.
Uh, you should.
[Car horn blows]
What are you doing here,
prosecutor?
I believe you're innocent.
You just found out you only
got six months to live?
'Cause today ain't the day
you get your conscience clear.
That's not the reason I'm--
You know, I've been in here
a dozen years...
While Jason Black
and Matt Bailey
are out there
living it up.
You think I give a shit
what you believe?
- You wanna hit me?
- I wanna kill you.
But I lay a finger on you,
and they put me
in the hole for 48 hours,
extend my sentence.
I got four years left.
I ain't doing another minute
than that.
Good, 'cause I'm here for
your absolution.
I'm here
for your redemption.
This is the letter
I told you Jill wrote me.
I know.
The one you didn't
believe existed.
I believe it now.
You were involved with her.
- This is the proof.
- Involved with her?
I loved her.
And she loved me.
Then why did you keep
this relationship a secret?
Look at me, man.
They gave me a scholarship
to that school.
But nobody wanted me
dating anybody at that school.
I had a record.
If her father
ever found out,
I'd have been done.
They wouldn't have cared.
Like you didn't care.
Where'd this come from?
It was buried,
but it got found.
And this is why you
believe I'm innocent?
Yes.
And it's enough
to get me out?
No.
But that wasn't
the only thing they buried.
Jill's dress had
your DNA on it.
But there's another piece of
clothing that had blood on it.
A camisole,
and they buried that
because that DNA wasn't hers
and it wasn't yours.
Let me guess.
It was Jason Black's.
Unfortunately,
I don't have access to his DNA.
So you finally gonna go after
him and Matt Bailey?
I'm not
a prosecutor anymore.
Then what the hell
are you here for?
I want you to let me
represent you.
You think I'm gonna trust you
after what you did to me?
I don't see anyone else
lining up
to get your ass out of here.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna
see what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
What's that?
It's an article where
Clifford Danner took his plea.
- Do you want me to read it to you?
- No.
"Clifford Danner
had a history of violence.
"This poor girl
was brutally murdered
"at a high-end,
private school and, quote,
"'this doesn't
sound like the work
"of the squash team captain
to me.'"
I don't know, Harvey,
this article makes
a pretty compelling case
that he's guilty.
Well, he's not.
- It's quoting you.
- I was wrong.
Jessica,
I don't think you should
let Harvey take this case.
Louis, we're talking
about a man's life.
And if Harvey thinks
the kid didn't do it,
then so do I.
I understand that,
but what Harvey thinks
and what Harvey can prove
are two different things.
In my experience
with Harvey,
it's one and the same.
Listen to me--
he was set up.
Jill Hodgkins
went to him and said
that she was gonna turn in
these two other guys
for selling coke.
They killed her
and planted the coke
in Clifford's room.
I didn't buy his story
because his DNA was on her.
He claimed that it
was because they were
having this
secret relationship.
But he had no proof.
And now he does.
Okay, I hate
to disagree with you here,
but I took a little poll
of the partners--
Whoa. You did what?
Well, I was discreet,
I assure you.
And they feel, as I do,
that Harvey's actions
will hurt this firm.
This firm?
You mean my firm.
And when you're
running the firm
of Litt, nothing,
and nobody,
then you can make
whatever call you'd like.
Until then,
you can just
get back to work.
I'm telling you,
those guys did it.
And as far as his violent
history is concerned,
you of all people
are gonna tell me
that a person can't change
if they get a second chance?
What do you need me to do?
Hey.
I need your help.
I thought I made it clear
that I don't expect
to hear those words
from your mouth ever again.
- It's important.
- It's always important.
- It's for Harvey.
- It's always for Harvey.
He specifically
asked for you.
By name?
He said he wanted the best.
Well, if he didn't
specifically name me,
and you didn't specifically
tell him,
then I am going to
specifically decline.
[Sighs]
Rachel.
Are you kidding me?
Okay.
I know that you're
mad at me.
But we're talking about a guy
roughly our age
who spent over a decade
in prison
for a murder
that he didn't commit,
and we are trying
to get him out.
I think that's more important
than our little...
whatever.
Whatever?
You know what I mean.
Problems with two people.
Hill of beans.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Casablanca.
Oh, I've never
seen that movie.
- You--
- No, it's--it's old.
Old?
Oh, my God.
Okay, what's your basis
for getting him out?
- Prosecutorial misconduct?
- Buried evidence.
Okay, then you need
precedence to overturn.
- I already got those.
- Then what?
I need to find out
everything I can
about the former D.A.'s cases.
[Sighs]
Okay.
Gone With The Wind?
- No.
- Citizen Kane?
- Dirty Dancing?
Nobody puts Baby
in the corner.
- I can't believe you.
- I'm helping you.
- Let's go.
- Ah...
You thought to do this
on your own?
I decided
to think like you.
This is a high-profile
murder case
against the new district
attorney himself.
- You know that, right?
- I know.
And you think I'm gonna
let you come with me
for this, don't you?
I know you are.
You known, I don't want you
thinking like me and--
Now you know how
the rest of us feel.
- Aha, right there.
- I always would have said that.
- You wouldn't.
- Yes, I would.
Harvey Specter.
Terrance Wolf.
That's your case?
I thought it best
to cut a deal,
let him out for time served.
Hm, high profile murder
at a prep school.
No, I don't think I'll
be cutting any deals.
Miguel Ruiz,
Lawrence Baker,
Ray Jenkins,
Calvin Reynolds.
And who are
these gentlemen?
They're other cases
with improprieties
that we'll be forced to cite
if we have to file to reopen.
You, of all people,
don't want that.
Really? Why not?
Because it'll
make you look bad.
Didn't happen on my watch.
You're supposed to be
cleaning up the office.
I find sunshine is the best
disinfectant.
Your mother teach you that?
No, Harvey,
life taught me that.
This man's innocent.
Then he should have
gone to trial.
Evidence was buried.
Then dig it up.
And make your case.
Mike...give me a minute.
Terrance, you're
forcing me to do something
that I'd rather not do.
- And what is that?
- Take this case on.
I win.
It's what I do.
It'll send a message
around your entire office.
That you can't
handle your business.
Well, if I lose, I lose.
That's the way
the law works.
But, Harvey, don't think
I can't send a message
or two myself.
Rumor has
it you're the traitor
who sold out
his former boss.
It wasn't me.
Those rumors are wrong.
So mysterious evidence
from back in the day
on your old boss
just appeared?
You didn't know.
It wasn't you.
But it had to be somebody,
right, Harvey?
Have a nice day.
My office--now.
I have never thought about
firing you.
You took something
when we quit the D.A.'s office?
Come clean right now,
or I'll let you go
and not give it
a minute's thought.
[Sighs]
I knew it.
You were in trouble.
You had no right.
I don't care.
What'd you do with it?
She did
what she had to do.
She gave it to me.
And the two of you saw fit
to fight my battles for me?
We did what you would have
done for either one of us.
So get off your high horse.
Leave the woman alone.
We work because I've always
known that I can trust you.
Don't ever go behind
my back again.
You're welcome.
Wait, he called you?
Yeah.
He left a message.
What did he say?
[Sighs]
That...
he wanted to see me.
And what did you do?
Texted him and I told him
I wasn't interested.
Uh...we gotta tell him.
No, we don't.
Yeah, we do.
I'm already
living a lie at work.
I-I can't live one
at home too.
Do you think that if you
told Trevor about us
he's gonna keep
your secret to himself?
I know Trevor.
If I tell him,
he will take it up with me.
If he hears it
from someone else--
- Who's gonna tell him?
- I don't know!
Okay? I just--I know
that he's over there right now,
and it's drilling a hole
in my brain.
Then stay here.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Because he came to me
for help.
Okay.
Okay what?
Tell him.
But please wait until
he has his life back together.
What do you mean?
He came to you for help.
How much help do you think
hearing about us
is gonna be for him?
Okay.
Okay what?
Okay, I'll stay.
Could you just not
touch anything?
Because, uh...
I like my place just so.
What?
This place is a mess.
What are you...
[Both laugh]
The court finds
sufficient misconduct
to warrant a new trial.
Any pretrial motions
at this time?
Yes, Your Honor.
The state advises
that we will be seeking
the maximum sentence
of life in prison.
What?
Your Honor, my client
has four years left.
Mr. Specter,
the state has every right
to seek that penalty.
Would you like to confer
with your client
before I vacate
his conviction?
You could just withdraw
your motion right now.
I'll confer with my client,
Your Honor.
Get the message?
Four more years.
Or you get out now.
Or stay in
the rest of my life.
September 19, 2007.
What?
His halfway point.
Day I realized
I could make it.
You never said
this could happen.
He's sending a message.
It's got nothing
to do with you.
It's got everything
to do with me.
What do you wanna do?
What do you think?
If we win, I want in.
If we lose, I don't.
We'll win.
How do you know?
Because I know.
Same way you knew
I was guilty?
What do you think?
I think Harvey
wins his cases.
What would you do?
I'd trust him.
Harvey, can you
give us a minute?
[Door shuts]
Clifford...
I don't you,
and you don't know me.
But I'm gonna tell you a story
about what that man did for me.
And why I think
you should trust him.
Mr. Specter...
Gonna withdraw your motion?
Your Honor, my client
wishes to proceed to trial.
Gensync Chemical.
You dropped this today.
Louis's client?
Louis's Fortune 500 client.
You wanna guess why?
His ears?
They freak a lot of people out.
That was one client.
His teeth?
Fidgeting?
Could be anything.
All right, stop it.
Let me guess:
One of the board members
has a kid
who went to his school.
A daughter.
And Lou's correctly
pointed out
that they might not be
the only clients
that will punish us
for taking this case.
- Which costs us money.
- Mm-hmm.
Louis is in the majority
this time.
Which hurts your position
with the partners.
You telling me to crop this?
I'm telling you to win.
But that's not why
I called you in here.
Have a seat.
Donna.
Mm-hmm.
You need to get over it.
I'm trying.
It's not that easy.
Yes, it is.
Tell me.
Okay.
Think about what your life
would be like without her.
Now I know.
Know what?
How you always forgive me.
Oh, it's nowhere near
as easy to forgive you.
Thank about it.
Oh, I do.
Every goddamn day.
Hey.
We're starting trial today.
I know,
you've got five minutes.
Never start a trial
without doing our thing.
Yeah, well,
you don't have time.
There's plenty of time.
You don't have time.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Don't push it.
Okay, let's go.
You got three minutes.
Okay, here or in my office?
- Here's good.
- Okay, on three.
One, two--
Wait, let's go
in your office.
- I'll get the can opener.
- Yeah.
You left that
in the kitchen.
Thanks.
I hate it when I do that.
You don't have any numbers
in your speed dial.
I don't need 'em.
And yet you
forgot your phone.
It's not the same thing.
Okay.
Hey, Rachel...
Um...
thank you for before.
Sure.
I mean...
it was for Harvey.
Yes.
Hmm.
[Phone ringing]
Hey.
Today's your first trial.
What? I've been
to trial before.
Yeah, but not when
you've been with me.
Fair enough.
Okay, I wanna start
a ritual with you.
What do you wanna do?
We're on the...
phone.
Remember that gymnastics video
we saw?
Yeah, I can
get behind that.
- Feeling good?
- Never better.
- You?
- I'm ready to roll.
Don't think I didn't
see that can opener.
What do you think you're doing
by opening this case?
I'm making sure
an innocent man
doesn't suffer
for the crimes of others.
And what about Jill?
Don't you care
how she suffered?
You two would know more
about that than anyone, right?
Excuse me.
I bought the devastated friend
act
12 years ago.
But I know better now.
Mike, meet Jason Black
and Matt Bailey.
Just don't
shake their hands.
They've got Jill Hodgkins' blood
all over them.
Look, I don't know
what you think you know.
But when I'm done testifying,
the jury's gonna know
that Clifford killed Jill.
Just 'cause
you switched sides,
doesn't mean the rest
of the world did.
- We just lost the letter.
- The what?
I didn't realize he'd have
the nerve to lie on the stand.
It's not exactly a giant leap
from killing someone.
Perjury and murder,
they aren't the same thing.
Yeah, murder's worse.
It's easier.
Nobody's watching.
Let's go.
Mr. Black, what exactly
did Jill tell you
regarding the defendant?
She told me
she felt trapped.
I thought she was
talking about school,
but now I know
what she meant.
That letter was dated
a week before she was killed.
She must have
broken up with him,
and this is how
he paid her back.
Mr. Black, you said you didn't
see Jill Hodgkins
at all on the day
of the murder.
- Is that correct?
- Correct.
So there'd be no reason
for your blood
to be on any of her clothing
at all.
No, there'd be no reason.
Would you be willing
to have a  DNA test, Mr. Black?
Objection, Your Honor.
Prejudicial.
We'll pay for it,
if that's a problem.
Mr. Specter.
It's about the DNA,
and they can't spin that.
Detective Packel,
the dress wasn't the only
article of clothing
that you submitted,
was it?
No, there was a camisole.
Was it in your report?
Yeah, if you bothered
to read it.
I did read it, Detective.
And what was the DNA analysis
on that camisole?
- I never picked it up.
- Why is that?
Well, it wasn't ready
till two days later
and we already had enough
from the dress.
Enough?
A man's life is at stake.
Enough for what?
Enough for you
to put him away
without bringing it up
for 12 years.
Well, I did
pick up that test,
along with the camisole.
Your Honor, I'd like
to request a side bar.
On what grounds?
The camisole and any evidence
connected to it
are inadmissible.
This is bullshit.
Easy.
What?
Your Honor, in between
picking up the camisole
at the precinct
and dropping it off
at the lab,
you can see here
the document is flawed.
Therefore, the chain
of possession
with respect to the camisole
was broken.
You gotta be kidding me.
It's inadmissible.
First six.
What?
First six months
are the hardest.
In your mind.
I don't know if I can
do that again.
Mr. Specter, you are
accusing a police officer
of tampering with evidence.
Yes, I am.
When the results
of the DNA test came back,
they didn't line up,
and Detective Packel
changed the custody documents.
Even if Mr. Specter's
assertions were true,
it would automatically
taint the evidence anyway.
He's got a point.
That camisole
was what allowed us
to reopen this case
in the first place.
The camisole was proof
that evidence was buried.
That's why the case
was reopened.
An entirely separate issue
from whether that evidence
can be used in this trial.
Clifford...
I don't know what's
going on in there,
but no matter what they rule,
he's not gonna
lose this one.
You sure?
Yeah.
I am.
- Your Honor...
- What's enough.
I'm instructing the jury
to disregard
all testimony relating
to either the camisole
or the resulting DNA test.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm so sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Get out of my face.
What the hell are you doing,
reopening this?
You worried
about getting caught
intentionally
tainting evidence?
I didn't taint anything.
What I did was help you
put away a guilty man
for brutally killing
a young girl.
I'm not gonna let you drag my
reputation through the gutter.
Not without consequences.
Are you threatening me?
'Cause the truth is,
you wouldn't even be here
if you hadn't
done something wrong.
Me? Yeah.
That's all well and good
for you to drag up shit
from the past, huh?
You're protected by
you shiny suit, right?
What are you talking about?
Lawyers never
go after their own.
What is that Denzel movie?
"Tell it to me
like I'm a five-year-old."
Sometimes, the good guys
gotta do bad things
to make the bad guys pay.
It's time to start painting
outside the lines.
How?
If Mohammed won't
come to the mountain,
we need to bring the mountain
to Mohammed.
Really?
The mountain to Mohammed.
- It's a thing.
- Yeah, I know.
It just has no meaning to me
in this situation.
You said you could
think like me.
Figure it out.
Okay, yeah.
I got it.
- What is it?
- You tell me--I'll confirm.
- Nice try.
- Damn it!
[Rock music playing]
Why'd you text me, Matty?
We got nothin'
to talk about.
I didn't text you.
You texted me.
We gotta go.
Come on, does it really matter
who texted who?
Why not take advantage of the
fact you get to see each other?
- Catch up.
- Talk about old times.
Yeah, like that time
that you murdered that girl
and framed an innocent man.
We didn't do anything.
- You're wasting your time.
- Am I?
We know the truth.
It's just a matter of time
until one of you
turns on the other one.
Question is,
who's it gonna be?
We'll be there today.
You're the ones
running out of time.
[Whispering] Asshole.
Looks like
the rattlesnakes
are starting
to commit suicide.
Holy shit, that's
from Mississippi Burning.
This whole idea
is from Mississippi Burning.
You know that movie?
I was trying to stump you
with that one.
Front to back.
Give me a break.
Problem is, those two
don't seem like
they're gonna break.
They know
we don't have anything.
Only now we do.
So by the mountain
to Mohammed, you meant...
DNA, comin' to Mr. Wolf.
That's good.
[Knocks]
Hi, Donna.
- Hi, Louis.
- You're never...
- I know.
- Why?
I need a favor.
You mean Harvey
needs a favor.
Oh, that's
very astute of you.
A big one.
You know your cousin
in the DNA lab?
- We need something today.
- No.
- It's for--
- I know what it's for.
What do you want?
I don't want anything.
I will fill in for Norma.
Okay...
I'm not being vindictive--
I'm sorry, do I have
the right office?
Listen to me.
I want you, God damn it.
And I will throw that secretary
right out the window
if any of you
were gonna be my secretary,
but I have a reputation
that I value.
And I'm not gonna be putting
my reputation on the line
for something that I
do not believe in...
American Ballet Theater.
No.
Followed by a one-on-one
dinner with...
Baryshnikov.
Ah ha.
[Chuckles]
Oh, mommy.
I--I--
no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
No. No.
Mm-mmm.
- Nope, I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- Can't do it.
- Got it.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Do you understand why?
It's very clear to me.
No, no, because do you
understand why--
I hear you, Louis.
- Louis--
- I want to, but I can't.
Shh...
What?
- Let go.
- What?
Let go.
[Sighs]
[Clears throat]
Jessica would like
to see you in her office.
Oh, that phony bitch.
- Call your cousin.
- It is not that simple.
Yes, it is.
You've compromised
your principles before.
- Do it now.
- Like I told Donna,
this isn't for me.
- This is for Harvey.
- Wrong!
It's for me.
Okay, you know,
you want this so bad,
why don't you maybe compromise
your principles a little bit?
Excuse me?
Yeah.
You know my billables.
You talk about it all the time.
"Louis has got big billables."
You see my loyalty.
Yet you refuse
to acknowledge my value.
- Where's this going?
- Where is this going?
When you said
"Litt, nothing, and nobody,"
you know what that
said to me?
That said, "Louis, you're never
gonna make senior partner."
Well, Harvey's
running out of time.
This is my leverage.
I want to make
senior partner,
and I want to make
senior partner now.
Louis...
I do not respond to threats.
I make them.
So if you ever want to be
senior partner,
you call your cousin.
Now.
All right.
I don't need
to see the results.
I saw their faces.
They did it.
What happened
to the letter?
They...
[Scoffs]
They made it seem like
it didn't matter.
Like, uh, he was jealous,
and so he killed her.
[Sighs]
Wow, that...
What?
I'm just wondering...
what would have happened
if they hadn't kept their
relationship a secret?
I have to make
a phone call.
[Whispers] Okay.
Jenny, hey.
It's me.
I can't keep this a secret
from Trevor anymore.
I need to tell him.
Call me.
DNA results.
Jason Black and Matt Bailey,
they match the samples
of the DNA
taken from that camisole.
They did it.
Where'd you get that?
I found it.
Well, it doesn't
prove anything.
- It's their blood on it.
- So what?
They could have had
a gym class together,
played flag football,
or any one of 100 other reasons.
Jason Black said
he didn't see her that day.
It's two specks of blood
from what could easily be
any other day.
- What's wrong with you?
- Me?
You come in her with some
unauthorized DNA test and--
and right away,
you expect me to just release
a convicted felon into the stree--
- He didn't do it!
And how can you allow him
to sit in there
while these two other
murderers go free?
Let me explain something
to you.
My job's to prosecute.
Your job is to defend.
I didn't bury any evidence.
I didn't toss that DNA.
The judge did that
based on fact.
You're coming after me
for the sins of someone else.
This piece of paper here
means nothing.
So unless one
of those two boys
just up and volunteered
that they killed that girl,
your client's
gonna go back to prison
for the rest of his life.
Terrance, you have
a reputation as a fair man.
I don't give a damn
what other people think of me.
I care about
what I think of me.
Yeah.
Didn't work.
What's next?
What's next is we have
to put on a defense tomorrow.
- We got nothing.
- So what are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Ooh, Rachel.
What are you doing in here?
You have access
to the partners' kitchen.
Yeah, I like to keep
my finger on the pulse.
Plus, they don't
have Cheetos.
Actually, I don't care
about the pulse.
Hmm.
Okay, either
I am losing it,
or you are upset
about something.
So...
What are you upset about?
I don't wanna
talk about it.
Got it.
Mike Ross.
How do you know that?
I'm Donna.
I know.
Donna, what
am I gonna do?
There's only
one thing to do.
- Quit?
- [Imitates buzzer]
- Kill her?
- Well...
- [Grunts]
- You need a drink.
Yes.
Two?
- We should barf.
- [Giggles]
[Buzzer]
Take 'em off.
Huh?
He's not an animal.
I want to talk to him
like a man.
What happened?
Wolf won't
drop the charges.
What?
I tried everything.
Y-you tried?
Look, we can cut a deal.
We can ask for more time.
- He already said no way.
- We've got to...
Try?
Try like you did
with the DNA?
I had 4 years--
4 years of 16
that I only had in the first
place because of you.
- Clifford, we--
- Shut up.
Why don't you
take it out on me?
What did you say?
I said take it out on me.
- Harvey--
- I put you in there.
I let you rot.
I didn't give it
a minute's thought
for over a decade.
- Don't push me.
- Why not?
I deserve it.
It's my fault.
You said it yourself.
Harvey...
They'll put me back
in the hole, that's why not.
And increase your sentence?
It's gonna happen anyway.
- Guard.
- Come on.
You know, Jason Black--
I said don't push me.
- Guard, come in here!
- They killed Jill.
And they are out there
laughing their asses off--
- oof!
- Hey, knock it off.
- [Shouting indistinctly]
- Let's go.
Get off of him.
Let's go.
You said you'd get me
out of here!
You said you'd get me out!
What just happened?
I just bought us
48 hours.
Now what?
I'm gonna beat the shit
out of one of those guys
and get him to rat
on the other one.
- Which one?
- The weaker one.
Which one is that?
The one who didn't testify.
You're serious.
You can't do that.
Who's gonna stop me?
Harvey, it wouldn't
be admissible.
You'll never
get them that way.
- It'll get Clifford out.
- How?
Wolf won't be able to deny
that he's innocent anymore.
Harvey, you don't do this.
You can't beat people.
That's not what you do.
- It is today.
- Harvey, stop!
Listen, I got another idea.
- What?
- You'll like it.
It's from
Mississippi Burning.
Come on.
[Soulful ballad]
♪ ♪
So all of these things
are from clients?
Yeah, pretty much.
This pen?
Remember that big
Trump scandal
you heard about last year?
- No.
- Exactly.
[Giggles]
Ooh, don't touch that.
Signed by Patrick Ewing.
He'll know.
I'll never hear the end of it.
All right.
And this one?
- Bird.
- He's from Boston.
You know,
white man's hero.
Oh.
Yeah, it's Kobe.
He won't care.
You really know him.
Hmm.
I really do.
No.
Never?
Ever?
No.
- Never, ever?
- No.
Why not?
Because you can
never go back.
I gotta pee.
[Phone ringing]
Hey, man.
I got your message.
What'd you wanna talk about?
It can wait.
Remember when you said
you would have died that day
if it hadn't
been for Harvey?
Yeah.
Well...
He needs your help.
[Distant dog barking]
Wake up, Matt.
[Muffled grunts]
Who are you?
What do you want?
It's not who I am.
It's who I represent.
Jason Black.
He knows you talked
to the police.
No, I didn't, I swear.
That's not my department.
Now, Matt...
you're gonna
retract what you said.
You're gonna leave town.
And you're never gonna
talk to them again.
Or next time....
that's gonna be your head.
Bye, Matt!
[Door slams]
[Sniffles]
[Coughs]
[Liquid pouring]
[Bottle clinks on counter]
[Glass slams on counter]
[Sighs]
Somebody call the police?
[Gasps]
You.
You, what are you--
what are you doing here?
Hey, Matt...relax.
The Detective was across
the street the whole time.
We knew Jason
would send somebody.
What?
Who do you think
told Jason
you went to the police
in the first place?
I did...
Harvey showed me the results
of the DNA test.
Two splotches.
Jason Black's and yours.
[Exhales]
Okay, um...
Uh, I want to file
a report.
Oh.
Sure.
I'll take you downtown.
You can look
through the books.
Maybe you find something.
Maybe you don't.
But your real problem
isn't that guy.
It's Jason Black.
Somebody was gonna
turn him in once before.
And I think you know
the lengths he'll go to...
to shut somebody up.
No, I don't.
We were here this time.
We won't be here next time.
Next time?
What would have happened
if he would have
killed me this time?
Well, you'd be dead,
and we'd have caught the guy
and used him to put Jason away
for murder.
Shit, we should have
done that.
- Yeah.
- Harvey, behave.
What do you want?
What do you want from me?
What do you want
from me?!
Confess to the crime.
Turn in Jason Black.
No, I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
I'll tell you why.
You were 16.
A juvenile.
That's three years maximum.
Less, if you're the one
who comes forward.
We'll get you a deal.
No, you can't
make that promise.
You're not the D.A.
You'd rather negotiate
with Jason?
Because he'll kill you,
and you know it.
It was his idea.
I didn't wanna do it.
I didn't
wanna do it.
Okay. Get dressed
and come with me.
Go.
Hey, by the way,
where'd you get that bruise?
Sometimes the good guys
got to do bad things...
Both: To make
the bad guys pay.
That's right.
[Sighs]
What?
What? Should have
let me do the talking.
Wouldn't work.
You're not ready yet.
Not ready?
This whole thing was my idea.
You lost in housing court.
You think you could
handle a murderer?
Mississippi Burning.
You're welcome.
I let you say
the juvenile thing.
That was pretty bad-ass,
wasn't it?
Really?
Thought I nailed it.
Shower girl.
Hey, Mike, it's Rachel.
I know I shouldn't
be doing this,
and I--I know you're
seeing Jenny,
but I--I can't stop
thinking about the kiss.
And...I can't go back.
[Phone clunks on table]
Looks like one of 'em
up and confessed.
We'll get your client out.
I'll back your motion
to expunge his record.
I'll facilitate his release.
You don't seem very happy.
You think I don't know
you set those boys up
and coerced that whole thing?
Set 'em up?
How would I do that?
I don't know.
What difference does that make?
- I know you did it.
- You know?
The same way you knew
Clifford was guilty?
No, you don't get to tell me
it's one way in court
and another out here.
You can't prove it...
you don't know anything.
Well, you broke the law.
Tell yourself
whatever you want.
I'll tell myself
I got an innocent man out
and I put
two guilty ones in.
The I'll close my eyes
and I'll sleep like a baby.
One other thing.
You got a little something
right over here.
I like you.
By the way, how did you
make those guys
think that they were
texting each other?
I bought a prepaid phone.
Set it to "private."
I texted each one
it was the other.
- Who else would it be?
- You.
Yeah, but they're
not gonna think that.
That's cool.
You'd make a good criminal.
Yeah, better than you.
Uh, excuse me,
I was an amazing criminal.
You don't remember--
briefcase popping open,
drugs spilling everywhere.
Okay, that was
a mechanical failure,
and that could have
happened to anybody.
Weed was all over
the floor.
Oh, shit, I forgot
my phone again.
- Here, can I borrow yours?
- How do you have this memory?
- You keep forgetting your phone.
- It's not the same thing.
Trevor, it's Mike.
Uh, I need you
to call me back.
Remember that thing
that I said could wait.
It can't anymore.
Something I gotta tell you.
Ms. Pierson.
I'm Trevor Evans.
I'm a friend of Mike Ross.
Yes?
I wish I didn't
have to do this.
There's something
you need to know about him.
Something Harvey Specter
hasn't told you.
What is it?