Previously on "Suits"...
- It's an offer letter.
- We need you.
I just got out of prison.
I'm not trying to go back.
You're not going back.
Your title's
gonna be consultant.
You don't have to
do this for me.
Do me a favor.
Just think about it.
Your last LSAT score
was significantly higher
than your previous ones.
I studied incredibly hard
the last time.
Did you study hard,
or did your fiancé
study hard for you?
I'm pregnant.
This has to be
some kind of record--
- Louis.
- It's his.
You make impulsive decisions,
and you go back on them
all the time.
- This is different.
- How?
Because it's a baby.
You want to merge?
Jessica, you got
knocked down the mountain.
Without help, you're not gonna
be able to get back up.
I've had my name first
for too long.
I can't go back
to having it last.
Tara Messer,
will you marry me?
Yes, Louis, I'll marry you.
[chuckles]
You can't just
throw this all away
after we gave everything
to save it!
No one's saying you have to
give up the firm, Louis.
You just have to let me go.
You sure about this?
I'm not sure about anything,
and it scares the shit
out of me.
You gonna be okay?
She was my mentor.
But, yeah,
I'm gonna be okay.
[stirring blues music]
♪ ♪
Hey, if it's gonna be
much longer,
I could just get some
on the way.
Hold your horses, mister.
That was the best cup
of coffee I've ever had.
I told you
it was worth the wait.
♪ ♪
That was nice.
It was.
And as much as I'd like
to spend all day doing it,
we should get going.
Just do me a favor--
Harvey.
I don't think you understand.
I told you
once this happened again,
I don't work for you anymore.
Donna, you can't leave me.
I'm not leaving you, Harvey.
I just don't work for you.
- That's leaving me.
- No, Harvey.
That's not leaving you.
Jessica left you.
And you need to get it
through your head,
she's never coming back.
[gasps]
[panting]
What you thinking about?
[inhales]
[sighs softly]
Just thinking about names.
I always wanted
a boy named Cooper...
And a girl named Lucy.
Louis, I appreciate you
thinking about this, but--
I know.
I'm not the father.
It's just that if
I'm gonna help raise him,
I'd like to give him something.
It doesn't matter.
Because whatever his first name
ends up being,
you're gonna be the one
who gave him his last name.
Louis, I'm gonna be a Litt,
which means our children
are going to be Litts.
You really mean that?
Of course I do.
[warm music]
♪ ♪
Tara, I got to get going.
Wh--what's wrong?
Oh, nothing's wrong.
Jessica left last night,
which means Harvey and I
got to figure out
what we're gonna do.
Dad, what are you
doing here?
I know I'm a little early.
But I came to bring you...
a graduation present.
This is a job offer.
Not just any job offer.
An associate,
at Rand Kaldor Zane.
I already have a job
when I graduate.
Rachel,
we talked about this.
When you graduate,
you're gonna have to stand
before the bar
and pass the character
and fitness test.
And you think
working at your firm
looks better than
looking at mine.
Yes, I do.
Dad, I...
Rachel, I understood
when you wanted to work there
when Jessica was still there.
But now that she's gone,
that firm is gonna turn
upside down,
and I don't want you there
when it does.
Dad, you are my family,
and I would do anything for you.
But Pearson Specter Litt
is my work family,
and they've always
been there for me.
I'm not going to leave them
when they need me the most.
Just remember,
as long as
I'm running my firm,
the offer
will always be there.
Mike, what are you
doing here?
Can I come in?
Of course.
You want a cup of coffee?
Yeah, that'd be good.
Look, I want to talk to you
about your offer.
You thought about it.
- I did.
- Good.
Don't tell me you're here
to renegotiate the terms.
I'm not taking it.
- Mike--
- Just listen to me.
When I was on trial,
I said that
I was given a gift
and I threw it away.
Well, I wasn't just trying
to bullshit the jury.
I meant that.
And as easy as it would be
for me to just
come back and pick up
right where we left off,
I can't look myself
in the mirror
if all I'm doing is
going back to corporate law.
Why don't you just
come back for a month?
What are you talking about?
Well, it's easier to find
a job when you have one.
Come back, pad your résumé
while you look
for something else--
Come on, Harvey,
if I come back
for one month,
it'll be two months,
then six months;
the next thing I know,
I won't have helped
a single person in ten years.
Not true.
You'll have helped me.
That's not what I meant
and you know it.
I don't care what you meant.
Jessica left last night.
I know you know that.
I just need somebody I can trust
until we figure things out.
- Harvey, I'm not doing this--
- God damn it.
You stood in front of me once
begging me to hire you,
and I did.
And now I'm asking you
to do the same thing,
and you're telling me
to go screw myself.
That's not what I'm doing
and you know it.
Mike, I need this.
Look, I'm sorry, Harvey,
I--I can't.
[tense music]
I just can't.
♪ Suits 6x11 ♪
She's Gone
Original Air Date on January 25, 2017
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Harvey, where you been?
We need to talk.
Louis, if you're here
to tell me
our bank account is empty
and we're on our knees,
then I need to have this
conversation some other time.
Well, you're in luck
because I'm here to tell you
the opposite.
What?
Been here since 6:00,
going through the books.
You're never gonna believe this,
but between not having to pay
any of the partners,
signing a few new clients,
and subletting our space,
we're actually flush with cash.
- You kidding me?
- Take a look.
[chuckles]
Finally, some good news.
Now, if it's not
too much to ask, can we
go back to your office
and work on a game plan?
No, Louis,
it's not too much to ask.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
Hey, uh, we don't open
for another 15 minutes,
but if you got a delivery,
I can take it.
Oh, no, I appreciate that,
but I'm--I'm not here
to deliver anything.
I'm here for a job.
[chuckles]
Not a lot of lawyers
show up to work on a bike.
Well, I'm not like
a lot of lawyers.
Tell you the truth, I'm not
like any other lawyer.
I like you.
Was up to me,
you'd be starting today,
but what I can do
is let you go in on there,
so you'll be the first person
they see when they get in.
Thanks.
Hey, what's your name?
- Darryl.
- Mike.
Good luck in there, Mike.
♪ ♪
I think the first thing
we should do
is send a message
that we're back
by hiring a new class
of associates.
Yeah, I love the idea
of sending a message,
but I'm not ready to talk about
hiring associates right now.
- Why not?
- Because I'm not.
In that case, maybe you're
ready to talk about a merger.
Robert, what are you
doing here?
Jessica didn't tell you?
Before she left,
I offered her a lifeline,
and now I'm gonna offer
the same thing to you.
We appreciate your offer,
- but...
- But what?
But we don't need
your charity.
Yes, you do.
You were struggling
before she left.
And at noon today,
the whole world is going to know
that you suffered another blow.
The only thing
the world's gonna know
is, Jessica had such confidence
in our abilities
that she decided to move on
to another phase of her career.
I don't care
how you want to spin it.
Even if you manage
to keep your clients,
you've got a boulder headed
your way, and you know it.
What are you talking about?
Which one of you two
is gonna take
Jessica's seat at the table?
Because you can only avoid
that question for so long,
and my money says that
the second I leave this room,
you two are gonna
fight to the death.
And what's left of this firm
is gonna be ripped apart.
So... come see me
when that reality sets in.
You were right.
We should hire
a new class of associates.
What, are you kidding me?
You're gonna ignore that
gauntlet he just threw down?
He wasn't throwing down
a gauntlet, Louis.
He was trying to capitalize
on an opportunity.
Bullshit.
He challenged our leadership.
And if we don't
get it together right now,
he's gonna tell
the entire city
that we can't even agree
on who's in charge.
Louis, Jessica's flight
hasn't even touched down yet.
I'm not gonna get in
a pissing contest with you
over who should run the firm.
I knew it.
You don't think I should be
the one in charge.
What I think is,
you were here at 6:00 a.m.
looking at the books,
figuring out a game plan
that I wasn't ready
to implement, and now I am.
So instead of
picking a fight with me
that I'm not
in the mood to have,
why don't you do what
you said you were going to
and hire a new class
of associates?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Hey. Oliver.
Oh, uh, Mike.
Mike, sorry
to keep you waiting.
What can I do for you?
- I'd like to apply for a job.
- That's great.
We are definitely
short-handed right now.
Are you a lawyer?
Not exactly.
Okay?
I mean, no, I'm--I'm not.
That's all right.
We need help across the board.
Do you have
any legal experience?
A lot, actually.
It's a long story.
Well, I look forward
to hearing it...
After you fill this out.
Great.
Um, you want me
to take it home or--
It's only two pages.
Why don't you do it here,
get it back to me?
I'm just right back there.
There's about a dozen
miniature Deadpools on my desk.
Don't judge. It's a great movie,
and you know it.
I do know it.
Saw it three times.
You bullshitting me?
Of course I am.
I want to work here.
[laughs]
Get it back to me.
I'll take care of you.
- Thanks, Oliver.
- Anytime, Mike.
You want to talk about it?
Talk about what?
You saw Mike this morning,
didn't you?
How'd you know?
Because instead of
telling Louis
that you need to be
managing partner
because you know
he can't handle it,
you avoided the conflict
because you already
had one this morning.
He turned me down
because he wants
to do good in the world.
Good for him.
No, Donna, not good for him.
Jessica left.
I need him, and he's
hanging me out to dry.
He's not hanging anyone
out to dry.
And in case you forgot,
he went to prison.
So he's probably trying
to figure out a way to make up
for what put him there
in the first place.
That's my point, Donna.
He's a convicted criminal.
I don't care if he tries
Mother Teresa.
Any place he goes isn't gonna
give him the time of day,
which means he's not gonna
be able to do good for anyone.
Then maybe
instead of telling me
why he'll never be able
to accomplish his dream,
you should be figuring out
a way to help him do it.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What are you doing here,
Gretchen?
I heard you were looking
for a new class of associates,
so I went ahead and contacted
every top law school
in the country.
These are the résumés
of the best 100 candidates.
- Throw 'em away.
- What?
Louis, you're not telling me
you're still going
with that Harvard-only
bullshit, are you?
I'm saying, instead of picking
fresh fruit off the vine,
I'm gonna steal
some ripe bananas
right out the grocery store.
The question is,
whose grocery store
are you planning
on knocking over?
It's Robert Zane,
and before you try
to talk me out of it,
he just said that
I'm not fit to lead
right to my face.
[tense music]
Then give me a gun
and point me up a hill,
because if he's coming
after you, he's coming at me.
And I got your back.
You convinced Simms Chemical
they had no proprietary right
to your client's patent?
Not only that. I got them
to pay for half the research.
It's good to see you, Louis.
It's good to see you too,
Katrina.
Listen, if you came here to
make sure that I kept my word--
Oh, Katrina, that was
a long time ago.
I'm here because
I want you to come home.
Back to the firm?
Yes.
Back where you belong.
- Louis, I can't do that.
- Yes, you can.
And not only that, you can get
the ten best associates
from Robert Zane's stable
to come with you.
Louis...
assuming I agreed to do that,
what makes you think
I could even convince
the ten worst associates
to come with me?
- This does.
- What is this?
It's the class list
of Rand Kaldor Zane associates
in the last 20 years.
Back then, six of ten
made partner.
Ten years ago,
it was down to three.
Class of '09--
Don't tell me.
Zero.
Look it up.
None of you are ever
going to make partner
because there is
no room at the top.
And what's in this for me?
You make this happen
by the end of the week...
I'll make sure that you are
the youngest senior partner
we have ever had.
Michael.
What are you--
what are you doing here?
It's a long story,
but I, uh--
I ended up
getting out early.
I'm glad.
Uh, what's on your mind?
Been out job-hunting all day.
[chuckles] Nice.
What kind of work?
Uh, legal clinics.
I want to find a way
to give back.
Well, you didn't come here
just to tell me that.
I came to tell you that
every application
I filled out today
asked if I was
a convicted felon.
[sighs]
Michael, please tell me
that you're not thinking
about lying again.
No, I'm not.
I just don't know what to do.
You know, I know that
none of these places
are gonna hire me
after seeing I checked that box.
You don't know that, Michael.
It's the first day.
I know I saw 30 different
looks on 30 different faces,
and they all said
the same thing.
Well, what if I told you
I know a place
where they won't
give you that look?
You offering me
a teaching job?
Yeah. I am.
I mean, a legal clinic isn't
the only way to give back.
Father, I'm not sure
if you heard me.
I'm a convicted felon.
Michael, you--
you came from here.
[laughs] And if we can't
offer redemption
to one of our own, then...
what kind of church are we?
I don't know, Father, I...
Father Conroy's going on
vacation for two weeks.
Just take his classes.
See what it's like.
The worst thing is,
you'll realize
that this isn't right for you.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
Dean Herrick?
Is this a good time?
Of course.
Have a seat, Rachel.
What's on your mind?
[sighs nervously]
I wanted to know
what you think my chances are
of passing the character
and fitness portion
of the bar.
Why are you
coming to me with this?
Because you questioned
my integrity once before,
and I--I want to know,
did you mean it,
or were you just helping
Anita Gibbs?
You want the truth?
It's why I'm here.
Then my answer is, if I were
on the ethics committee,
I don't know whether
I'd pass you or not,
because the fact is,
you're engaged to a man
who pretended to be a lawyer.
And I find it hard to believe
that you didn't know about it
the whole time.
And since then,
he's paid his dues.
And what about you?
What about me?
Do you think the committee
would have me break up
with the man that I love
just because
he went to prison?
What does that say about
character and fitness?
You make a good point.
And if I were you,
I'd be prepared
with some others,
'cause I'd say one day soon,
you're gonna
have to make your case.
And do you think
I have a better chance
of making my case
if I work for my father
instead of at
Pearson Specter Litt?
Yes, I do.
Hey.
You look like that
famous professor Henry Gerard,
but there's no way that guy's
still teaching at his age.
I don't think
you could ever call
what that clown did
"teaching."
He had his moments.
Good to see you, Harvey.
I'd ask you
to join me for dinner,
but I'm pretty sure
that that's not
what you came here for.
Mike Ross got out of prison.
As far as I'm concerned,
there's no reason
he shouldn't be able
to practice law again.
I don't disagree,
but technically,
he didn't practice it
in the first place.
Well, that's exactly
why I'm here.
If Mike's gonna have a chance
to pass the character portion
of the bar, he's gonna need
someone like you
to testify on his behalf.
Someone like me?
Or me?
I didn't fly
all the way up here
for someone like you.
Harvey, I'd love to help,
but you know as well as I do,
I'm not the one
you should be coming to.
You're exactly
who I should be coming to.
It's the New York bar.
I'm a Massachusetts professor.
Henry, please.
Harvey, even if I did
what you're asking,
I'm not the one that's
going to make the difference.
Then who is?
You know who is.
You're just afraid
to go and see them.
Hey, what's going on?
What do you think?
Blue or this maroon one?
You got a job in one day?
I wouldn't be trying on ties
if I didn't.
Mike, that's amazing.
I knew people would see
the real you.
Wait, don't tell me--
the clinic in
Morningside Heights.
Actually, uh, the church...
in Queens.
What?
Father Walker offered me
a teaching position
at Saint Andrews, and I...
said yes.
So you're gonna be a teacher?
Why?
You think it's a bad idea.
No, no.
I just, I--
I thought that you wanted
to stay connected to the law.
I do, but none of those places
are ever gonna call me back.
You don't know that
because it's only been one day.
Rachel, it's time for me
to accept the truth.
I am a convicted felon.
I am never gonna be able
to practice law again.
At least this way,
I'll be able to do some good.
Then I'm glad,
because you are going to make
a great teacher.
[warm music]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, everyone.
Morning.
As most of you are aware,
Father Conroy is on
a well-deserved vacation.
I should know;
I don't think he's had one
since I had him here
15 years ago.
[laughs] I get it.
I wouldn't be impressed
by me either.
Um, I don't know
if you guys like movies,
but, uh, every movie
I've ever seen starts with
the sub writing his name
on the board,
and the kids can throw
something at him.
So let me get that part
out of the way right now.
I have a short name,
so I'll take my time.
Mr. Ross.
But you guys
can call me Mike.
[quiet laughter]
Okay, what'd you guys
come up with?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Who did this?
Team effort.
Think this is funny?
I sure do.
How about you, Chris?
Cracks me up that our teacher
was in prison last week.
[class murmuring]
[scoffs]
All right, well, now that
we've all had our fun,
why don't we open up
our textbooks?
Chapter seven,
Battle of Appomattox.
We did that yesterday.
No, you didn't.
Father Walker
gave me your syllabus.
This is what we're
covering today. Come on.
Yeah, well,
we all forgot our books.
Well, then I guess
we have no choice
but for you to read
from mine.
♪ ♪
I just have one question
before I read.
♪ ♪
You ever drop the soap
in the shower?
[laughter]
♪ ♪
Donna, do you mind calling
Dr. Lipschitz for me?
Gretchen's at
her grandson's play.
I know where Gretchen is,
Louis.
I've been answering
her phone all morning.
Now, would you like to tell me
why a "Katroina Bonnet"
just called to say
Operation Fly The Coop
was a resounding success?
- Sounds like the wrong number.
- Oh.
It sounds like you just
got Katrina Bennett's help
poaching half Robert Zane's
associates.
How could you possibly
guess that?
Gretchen's grandson
could have guessed that.
Louis, Robert Zane is a bear,
and you just poked him.
I didn't poke him;
he poked me
when he came
all the way down here
to question my ability
to be managing partner.
No, he came
all the way down here
because he's trying
to help us.
And if you're trying
to prove something to him,
it's not gonna work.
Oh, it is gonna work.
And for your information,
I'm just getting started.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means that
Gretchen's still out,
and I need you to set up
a meeting with Jeremy Cohen.
Louis, that's Zane's
biggest client.
I know he goddamn is.
He's about to be
my biggest client.
I don't believe this.
You're trying to tell the world
that you should be
managing partner,
and the first thing you do
is burn every bridge in sight?
I don't care if I burn
every bridge ever built.
I am not letting
Robert Zane come in here
and push me around
the day after Jessica leaves.
So get Jeremy Cohen
on the goddamn phone, Donna,
or I'm not gonna forget
you didn't.
Then don't forget it,
Louis.
Because when this comes back
to bite you in the ass,
I want you to remember
that I tried to stop you
and you didn't listen.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here,
Harvey?
I'm here for a fresh start.
I assume by "fresh start,"
you mean you want me
to do something
to help Mike Ross now that
he's out in the world.
Anita, you heard
his speech to that jury.
He was given a gift
and he threw it away.
And the reason it was so
effective is 'cause he meant it.
Get to the point, Harvey.
If Mike puts himself
in front
of the character
and fitness committee,
will you stand up there
with him?
I don't believe this.
He's not been in there
three months,
and you want me to help him
con more people?
He's not trying to con people;
he's trying to help people.
Then let him go work
in a soup kitchen.
Look, you proved your point.
The whole world knows
he's a fraud,
and he may not have served
his entire sentence,
but he deserves a chance
to lead a life
now that he's out.
So why don't you go back
to the same person
that got him out
in the first place?
What?
Don't act like you don't know
what I'm talking about.
Sean Cahill has as much sway
over that committee as I do,
and he owes Mike; I don't.
So why aren't you
going to him?
Because a word from
the woman who put him away
is worth a thousand from
the guy who got him out.
Nice try, but you two did
something to get that kid out,
and you don't want
to shine a light on that
by appearing together
in public.
- That's not true.
- No?
Well, let's get Cahill
on the phone right now
and see if his lies
match your lies.
I didn't think so.
You're the same man you were
when Mike went in.
And the fact that
he made a crooked deal
to get himself out
lets me know that he is too.
Anita.
Sell it somewhere else,
Harvey.
Because I'm done.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Now I know
why school ends at 3:00.
[laughs] Why's that?
'Cause if it went till 6:00,
no teacher would ever
come back again.
I take it you had
a rough first day.
You never told me
you were gonna put me
in a class full of
juvenile delinquents.
[sighs heavily]
Would you have
taken my offer if I had?
I don't know.
Michael, you said
you wanted to help people.
These kids need your help.
I wanted to help people
as a lawyer,
not as a teacher.
What's the difference?
Difference is,
clients actually want my help.
Michael, these kids need it.
They just don't know it.
I don't know, Father.
This is...
Michael,
if I just needed someone
to grade papers
and take attendance,
I could've got a trained monkey
to do that.
I wanted you
because I thought you,
of all people,
could get through to them.
Yeah, how am I supposed to
do that in two weeks?
If it takes
more than two weeks,
so be it.
Father Conroy's
not on vacation, is he?
No, Michael, he's not.
He's got cancer.
He's probably never
coming back.
And when exactly
were you planning
on letting them in on that?
'Cause you're not
doing them any favors
by keeping it from them.
You're right.
I'm not.
I was gonna tell them this week,
but then you showed up.
I know you don't think things
happen for a reason, Michael,
but I do.
I thought maybe the reason
you came to see me when you did
is because teaching's
your real calling.
I'll understand if you don't
want to come back tomorrow.
Just let me know.
I'll take the class myself.
[indistinct chatter]
All right,
everyone take your seats.
Could you put the ball away?
Cell phones too.
[indistinct chatter]
I'm not gonna say it again.
Sit the hell down!
[book slams]
I was gonna come in here
and talk about
what happened yesterday.
I figured if you guys
had the balls
to put that picture on my desk,
then you're probably
old enough to hear
about what prison was like,
what I did to get there,
how I thought about being killed
every single day.
I don't want to talk about me.
I'm--I'm nobody to you.
Father Conroy's dying.
What?
That's right.
He's got cancer.
He's probably not gonna
make it.
That's the reason that I'm here
and he's not.
So we can get to work...
or we can spend the morning
sharing our memories of a man
who spent the last 40 years
giving his life to kids
like you and me.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Third grade.
Camping trip to Lake Kanawauke.
[sniffs]
Fishing with a stick.
He's still
fishing with a stick?
Still coming up empty.
[soft laughter]
He taught me
how to swim on that trip.
Yeah, me too.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
I don't mean
to interrupt you,
but I'm pretty sure
you didn't mean to leave this
in the McKenzie file.
Oh, my God.
[sighs]
Gretchen, I'm sorry
to put you in this position,
but I have to ask you to
please don't tell anyone.
You don't have to
ask me anything.
What you do is your business.
You don't understand.
It's not what you think.
Doesn't matter what I think.
You got to take care
of yourself.
If my father offered me a job
in a firm with my name on it,
well, I'd be leaving things
in files by mistake too.
Gretchen?
If this was just about that,
then I--I wouldn't
be thinking twice.
I would just tell him no.
Then if you don't mind
my asking,
what is it about?
My father thinks
I have a better chance
of getting past the bar
if I'm not still working
at the firm that hired Mike.
But you're loyal
to the people here,
and you don't want
to leave them.
Yes, but if it means
that I can't...
be a lawyer at all, I...
I can't help you with that
part of the equation.
But if Tweedledee
and Tweedledum
don't get it together,
you may not have to make
that decision at all.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Katroina Bonnet,
as I live and breathe.
Pouis Pitt.
I do declare.
No, um, you see,
Katrina, you need to work
on your code name for me,
'cause it's way too obvious.
You're right, Louis.
"Katroina Bonnet" is the
gold standard in spycraft.
Precisely.
Now get your game face on
because I just set up
our first meeting for tomorrow.
I was born
with my game face on.
Who are we going after?
J.C. Analytics.
What?
That's Zane's biggest client.
Yeah, that's exactly why
we're going after him.
Listen to me.
Whatever time
you set up that meeting,
I guarantee you, Jeremy Cohen
called Robert two minutes later,
which means we need to figure
out a way to make amends.
No, I don't need
to make amends.
I need to make a statement,
and that statement is,
"Do not mess with
the new managing partner
of Pearson Specter Litt."
Louis, that is
the wrong statement to make.
And if you insist on making it,
I won't come work for you.
God damn it, Katrina,
I thought you were a killer.
I am, but I'm not gonna
take a shot at the man
who's doing both of us
a favor.
What?
Louis, we have noncompetes.
And I was working on a way
to get around them
when Zane caught wind
of what we were doing,
and he not only waived them;
he wished us luck.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
He really was trying to help us,
and I couldn't see it.
Does that mean you're not
gonna go after his client?
It means a whole lot more
than that, Katrina.
It means I'm not ready
to be managing partner.
You wanted to see me,
Father?
Yeah, uh, sit down, Michael.
Look, if this is about
what happened in class today,
I know it wasn't
my news to share,
but if I'm gonna
get through to them,
I have to be honest with them.
It's not about that.
It's...
One of the students
told his parents
that you were in prison.
Parents called the archdiocese
to see if it was true,
and then--
Don't say it.
[sighs]
I'm sorry, Michael.
I tried to explain
the situation to them,
but they--
they wouldn't budge.
You have nothing
to feel bad about, Father.
♪ ♪
You took a chance.
Someone else will too.
♪ ♪
See you around, Father.
Take care of yourself,
Michael.
♪ ♪
I know it's only been
a couple of days, but, uh,
will you say good-bye
to the kids for me?
Of course I will.
♪ ♪
Robert.
Twice in one week?
What brings you by?
Do you really think
you could try to poach
my oldest client
without me finding out?
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
Jeremy Cohen!
I don't know anything
about Jeremy Cohen,
and I'm not trying
to poach anyone.
Then you're even less prepared
to be a leader than I thought,
because your partner's out there
coming after my firm,
and you don't even know it!
Maybe Louis
wouldn't be doing that
if you hadn't come here
with some bullshit merger
designed to rip us apart.
Are you really that stupid?
Are you really telling me
that isn't what you wanted?
If I wanted to rip you apart,
you'd be in million pieces
right now,
because Jessica is gone,
and you're not in my league.
I offered the merger because
my daughter has some kind of
misguided loyalty to you,
and I didn't want
to extinguish that spark
in her.
If I'm not in your league,
why is she loyal to us
instead of you?
- Watch yourself, Harvey.
- Robert...
I'm not looking to get
in a fight with you.
But as my partner
told you before,
we don't need your charity.
Then I'll stop
giving it to you.
But you better
put that dog on a leash
and shut that shit down,
or I'll shut you down.
The next time you want
something from me, Mr. Ross,
at least have the balls
to ask me yourself.
What are you talking about?
You gonna tell me
you had nothing to do
with Harvey asking me
to help you get a law license?
That's exactly
what I'm telling you.
I didn't even know about it
till you just showed up here
and told me.
Then why did I get five calls
from five different
legal clinics
all asking about your case?
Because the day
after I got out,
I followed through
on my promise to that jury
to try to do some good.
If that's all
you came here to say,
why don't you leave me alone?
I've had a rough day.
I'm gonna leave you alone
but not before I tell you
what I tried to tell
your old boss.
You want to do good,
be my guest,
but do it
in another profession,
because if I ever
even catch wind
of you trying to get work
at any of these places,
you can bet your ass I will do
everything I can to stop it.
Did you know
what Louis was up to?
I did.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I said Louis wasn't
ready to be managing partner,
but maybe you aren't either,
because you're not around enough
to know what's going on
around here.
I don't believe this.
You're the one
who said, "Do something
about Mike."
Yes, I did, but I didn't
say that you should
spend your entire existence
doing it.
Donna--
Harvey, you can't do
whatever you want.
Jessica's not here to
pick up the slack anymore.
You think I don't know that?
Well, if you do,
then it's time you do
what she would've done already.
[soft dramatic music]
You need to tell Louis
he can't be managing partner.
He doesn't want to hear it.
I know that.
But the real reason
we're having this conversation
is that you're afraid
to say it.
It's up to you, Harvey.
Either step up
and take the reins
or start looking
for another job,
because if you don't tell Louis
he's not ready to run this firm,
we're gonna be out of business
one way or the other.
♪ ♪
What the hell did you do?
Mike, not now.
I'm not in the mood.
Well, I wasn't in the mood
when I got home
to find Anita Gibbs
waiting for me.
- Mike, I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
She came to my house
to tell me that
if I even so much as try
to get a job at a legal clinic,
she's gonna make it
her life's mission to stop me.
- She can't do that.
- Did you hear me?
I wasn't even on her radar.
I had one thing
I wanted to do,
and you ruined it for me
just because
you can't accept the fact
that I don't want
to come back here.
I wasn't trying
to get you back.
I was trying to help--
I don't believe you!
- Mike--
- Are you telling me
you don't want me
to come back here?
Of course I do, and you
can come back at any time,
but that doesn't mean that--
I don't care what it means.
And just to make it
absolutely clear,
in case there is any doubt,
if by some miracle
the hand of God touches me
and I'm somehow able
to practice law again,
this is the last place
that I am ever coming back to.
- Mike--
- Stop messing with my life!
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Harvey.
I'm glad you're here.
I was just gonna come
talk to you.
What for?
To tell me how you tried
to ruin everything
that Jessica's ever worked for
by making an enemy
of the one man who's been
trying to help us?
That's what I wanted
to talk to you about.
You couldn't even
shine Jessica's shoes
and now you're trying
to tear her legacy down.
I was trying to live up
to her legacy.
Yeah, I don't give a shit
what you think
you've been doing.
- Harvey, please.
- You know what?
Just let me say
what I was gonna--
I don't care what you
were going to say to me,
Louis, because
all you care about
is proving to me that you
should be managing partner
when everyone in the world
knows that you shouldn't--
me, Robert Zane, even Donna.
Harvey, please!
Jessica didn't even want
your name up on the wall,
so if you think I'm gonna
let you be managing partner
while she's still breathing,
you're out
of your goddamn mind!
Harvey!
That's enough.
I have the start paperwork
for those associates
in case you want to
look it over.
I'll just leave it here.
I was gonna tell him,
you know.
I was gonna tell him
that he's the one
that should be
managing partner.
Louis, you may
have your flaws,
but he had no right
to talk to you like that.
Yes, he did.
I did everything he said I did,
and the reason I did it
is because
all I ever care about
is for people to see me
as more than I am.
- Louis...
- The funny thing is,
all I ended up with
was the shortest,
most humiliating run
as managing partner
in the history of the world.
If you ask me,
you may have had a short run,
but you made your mark.
What are you talking about?
Well, unless I'm mistaken,
we have ten associates
starting tomorrow
who chose to come here
over one of the best law firms
in the city.
They did that
because of you.
It was because of me,
wasn't it?
Yeah.
And you did that
all on your own.
Nobody asked you to do it.
Where I come from,
they call that stepping up.
You're right. It is.
Thank you for being
the secretary
to the shortest-tenured
managing partner in history.
Well, now that
you mention it,
before you hand over
your reins,
there's something you can do
to cement the future
of this firm.
What's that?
Show a little love
to someone
who's been loyal to us
for as long as I've known her.
Rachel, you have a minute?
Honestly, Louis,
I am swamped.
So if it can wait
until tomorrow--
Oh, I wish it could,
but it can't.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
Except for one thing.
I have been derelict
in my duties
as head of the associates.
I don't understand.
Rachel, you've given your
heart and soul to this firm
for almost ten years,
and now that you're about
to become a lawyer...
I'd like to formally
extend you an offer
to work here
as soon as you graduate.
This says
second-year associate.
I know it does.
I...
I don't know what to say.
I think you do.
You're right.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Yes, Louis.
I accept your offer.
♪ ♪
All right, you drive
a hard bargain.
Third-year associate it is.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
Thank you, Louis.
No, thank you, Rachel.
♪ ♪
She's not coming back,
you know.
- I know she's not.
- Do you?
Because you just
lashed out at Louis
when your intention was to
let him down gently,
and I find it hard to believe
it had nothing to do
with this office being empty.
She didn't even come back
to say good-bye.
She just packed up her things.
- Harvey...
- They're all leaving, Donna.
First Jessica, now Mike.
They're family.
And family's not supposed to...
Harvey, I've always stayed
away from a certain subject
with you, but I can't anymore.
You always talk like
we're your only family.
We're not.
You have another one,
and you need to reconcile
with them.
- Donna, I am not gonna--
- Enough is enough.
You need to go make things right
with your mother.
Because as long as you keep her
at arm's length,
you're gonna keep looking to us
to fill that void.
And I'm not sure
that any of us can.
Please?
Go see her.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man