Previously on "Suits"...
I've been after Sutter
for three years now.
This guy's one
slippery son of a bitch.
Wait a second, William Sutter?
He came to me a week ago
to take him on.
You cross one line
that puts me in jeopardy,
I'm gonna pull the plug
on this whole thing.
I need a large,
expensive home in the Hamptons.
Why are you buying
a vacation home?
Because I told Tara Messer
that I have
a property out there,
and I hired her
to remodel it for me.
Damn it, Harvey,
I'm not colluding on this,
and you're in here
trying to get me
to bring an indictment
against your own client.
Because when you bring that
indictment, I'm gonna beat it,
and if you don't bring it,
and continue investigating
my client, I'm gonna sue you.
I think it's pretty
goddamn funny
that you don't trust me,
when you're the one
that won't even tell me
what you're in here for.
Okay.
I'll do it.
- Excuse me?
- Your pro bono.
Bring me the file
tomorrow morning.
It was a good fix, Sean.
- It was a good move, Harvey.
- Want to get a drink?
- Why don't we just
have one here?
Why?
As of right now,
you have no action
pending against my client.
But as of tomorrow, I do,
'cause those indictments
are coming down in the morning.
- Kevin, what did you do?
- I got in a fight with my wife.
I got drunk. I got into my car,
and I almost killed someone.
I'm missing 1,000 chances
to hug my kids in the morning
and kiss my wife good night,
all because I couldn't
control myself.
What were you fighting
with your wife about?
I can't.
I just can't.
[door buzzes]
Harvey.
What are you doing here?
Mike, sit down.
I need to tell you something.
What's going on?
I'm working on getting
you out of here.
Yeah, I know you are.
I'm not talking about
what we're doing for Cahill.
I'm talking about
something else.
Harvey, we're in a room
full of people.
You can't be talking
about Cahill.
If Kevin finds out--
It doesn't matter
if Kevin finds out now.
He's done.
What do you mean, "He's done?"
I mean Rachel's dead...
and Kevin killed her.
[tense music]
What?
It's true.
You son of a bitch.
You're lying to me.
Goddamn it.
He told you he did it.
- Bullshit.
- He got drunk.
He got in a car.
He murdered the woman you love.
- Stop saying that.
- And now you're going
to be stuck in here with him
for the rest of your life.
Stop it.
Kevin would never do that to me.
- Mike, wake up.
- No.
- Mike.
- Wake up. Wake up.
- No!
- Mike, wake up.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Mike, wake up.
[heavy breathing]
Hey, you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
- You sure?
'Cause that was some dream
you were having.
I'm fine.
Just going back to sleep.
[elevator dings]
Harvey, good,
there you are.
- What's going on?
- Sutter just called.
Let me guess,
the indictments came down?
He wants you in his office
an hour ago.
I'll tell him
you're on your way.
No.
Tell him you couldn't reach me.
You want him to start
sweating, but why?
Because when people
start sweating,
they start talking
to their lawyer.
I'll tell Ray to be on hold.
No, tell him to pull around.
But you just said you weren't
going to Sutter's.
I'm not.
I'm going somewhere else.
♪ ♪
Oh, look who it is,
the man of the hour.
Did you get my indictments?
I sure as hell did.
Now that the party's started,
why don't you tell me
what Kevin Miller knows?
- What are you talking about?
- You went after the guy
to try to get him
to flip on Sutter,
so what'd you think
he was gonna give you?
- I'm not gonna tell you that.
- Why not?
- Because I told you
when I started this thing,
I'm not gonna collude.
We're not colluding.
It's called discovery.
So why don't you tell me what
the hell Kevin Miller knows?
He developed
the trading programs
that Sutter claims to use
to get his superior returns.
Then that program's got
to be full of shit,
because if it isn't--
Then Sutter's not
inside trading,
which he sure as shit is.
So you're looking to have
Kevin testify
that software is bullshit,
and Sutter knows it.
- Bingo.
- Then let me ask you this,
what exactly did you
put Kevin away for?
And why do you need
to know that?
Because it might help us
figure out
what his weak spot is.
We got him on
vehicular assault
while driving
under the influence.
Are you kidding me?
Why didn't you think
to tell us that?
Why would I?
Mike's parents were killed
by a drunk driver.
And how the hell
was I supposed to know that?
I don't know.
It would have been nice
to know what this asshole did,
before we sent Mike
back into a cell with him.
♪ ♪
Hey, what happened
to you this morning?
What do you mean?
- You skipped breakfast.
- I wasn't hungry.
- That all it was?
- What are you talking about?
- Come on, Mike, you had
a nightmare last night.
You've been avoiding me
all morning,
and you're acting weird
right now--what's going on?
Nothing's going on.
Then why the hell were you
in a cold sweat,
muttering something about
someone not finding out,
and then calling out
my name?
♪ ♪
All right, Kevin, you want
to know what's going on?
I had a dream that you
killed Rachel in a car accident.
That's probably why
I don't particularly feel
like hanging out
with you this morning.
Because of what you told me
about your parents, Mike,
I'm really sorry.
Are you?
What--what's that
supposed to mean?
I mean, last night you told me
you almost killed someone.
Are you sorry about that?
You got to be kidding me.
You have a dream,
and now you're questioning
if I feel bad
about what I did that night?
You still haven't answered
whether or not you do.
You know what?
You need to be pissed off
at me to deal with your shit,
you go right ahead.
But I feel horrible about
what happened that night,
and for your information,
the guy that I hit
is fully recovered right now,
and I'm still in here
paying for this shit.
♪ Suits 6x06 ♪
Spain
Original Air Date on August 17, 2016
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Break out the champagne,
Louis.
That house in the Hamptons
is gonna be yours
in 60 to 90 days.
- They accepted my offer?
- That they did.
Well, then I have something
much better than champagne...
Wood.
I don't really see how
that's better than champagne.
Of course you don't.
Because you don't know
that I'm having a replica
of my house made for Tara,
so she can see her
designs come to life.
Louis, that's actually
really sweet.
I know.
Now, all I need to do
is pick the perfect wood.
- I don't follow.
- Donna, the kind of wood you
get says everything
you need to know
about what kind of man you are.
How hard or soft it is.
How much it bends
when you're working it.
How firm it is compared--
- I got the picture, Louis.
- No, I don't think you do.
Making Tara love my wood
is the first step
toward making her love me.
- Okay, Louis, calm down.
- No.
I don't really want
to calm down,
because all I can think
about my wood.
So tell me, exactly how many
different kinds of wood
have you sampled in your day?
All of them.
Mahogany, chestnut, walnut,
all the nuts.
Ebony?
Don't even get me
started on ebony.
When I see ebony, all I want to
do is put my hands all over it.
- Oh, God.
- I want to live in it.
I want to smack it
and hit it, rub it down.
I just want to eat it.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Um...
I just think that
a man needs to follow his heart
and choose the wood
that just feels right.
- Feels right.
- Yeah.
That's it.
Donna...
I need you to help me
feel my wood.
Oh, dear God.
[playful music]
God damn it, Julie,
call his office again,
and this time tell him to find--
If you're talking about
my office, there's no need.
I'm right here.
What the hell
took you so long?
- I was unavailable.
- Well, I just got indicted,
so from now on
you make yourself available.
I get it.
This all just got real
for you,
so why don't you tell me right
now, how real is the rest of it?
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying, Cahill claims
that you can't make
the returns you do.
You say you can, and I want
to know how you do it.
We use a proprietary
trading algorithm.
- Developed by who?
- My son-in-law.
Good, then we can
give it to Cahill,
'cause he just subpoenaed it.
- No, we can't.
- Why the hell not?
Because the trades
on which I make
the most money have nothing
to do with that program.
Are you kidding me?
You're admitting
to inside trading?
I'm not admitting to anything,
except that sometimes
I trade with my gut.
Well, I got news
for you, William.
To a jury, that's gonna sound
like you're full of shit.
Okay, smart guy,
pick up that journal.
Give me a stock.
NASDAQ, New York Stock Exchange,
I don't give a shit.
Just pick one.
- All right, Computech.
- Computech.
1.59 billion shares
outstanding.
Yesterday's close, 32, flat.
Today's opening, 33 1/4.
P/E's at 17.
Earnings expected
to grow at 2% a year.
What it doesn't say in there,
is that the earnings
aren't gonna grow,
because the CEO
doesn't give a shit,
which makes it a value trap
dressed up like a princess,
and I wouldn't touch it
with a ten-foot pole.
That's a pretty
neat trick, William,
but it isn't gonna stop
this subpoena.
It's not a trick.
It's what I do.
What you're gonna do,
is stop that son of a bitch
from getting his hands
on my program.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Rachel, whatever it is,
it's going to have to wait.
Okay, but you told me
to bring you everything
I have on the Bailey
case this morning.
Great.
Leave it on my desk
and I'll get to it
sometime this week.
Oh, I'm sorry,
Jessica,
I was really hoping
that we could go over it today.
I was hoping to be out
the door by now.
Look, I know that I said
this wouldn't take up
too much of your time, but--
Rachel, I said I would
do this, and I will,
but you just have to be patient.
I understand.
It's just, Leonard Bailey's
been patient for 12 years.
And I have sympathy
for the man,
but today's not the day.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
Don't bother with another menu.
I'll just have a Cobb salad.
What do you think
you're doing?
What does it look
like I'm doing?
I'm having lunch with a client
to discuss his
investment business.
You don't represent
my investment business.
Which is exactly why
we need to have lunch.
No, we don't need
to have anything,
'cause the deal was Harvey gets
me cleared of criminal charges,
then you get the rest
of my business.
I don't care what
the deal was, William.
I care what the deal is.
Because now that that
indictment's come down,
Harvey is going to be
spending all of his time on you.
That's not my problem.
I'm making it your problem.
We get all of your business,
or we handle none of it.
Bullshit.
You quit, you lose billables
you can't afford to lose.
We quit, and it looks like
we realized
your case was a loser
and wanted distance from it,
which you can't afford.
You really want to start a
business relationship this way?
I don't give a shit
how it starts, William.
I give a shit how it looks.
Oh, that's why you did
this here.
You want it to look like you
already represent my firm.
Well, look at that.
Looks like I'm worth
hiring after all.
So are we actually
going to talk business,
or am I just gonna bill you
for the pleasure of my company?
[dramatic music]
Mike,
what can I do for you?
You can tell me if you do
straight-up therapy or not.
- What's on your mind?
- You didn't answer my question.
I didn't think I needed to,
since we've been doing
straight-up therapy
since you got here.
So, you want to tell me
what you're here for?
My parents were killed
by a drunk driver when I was 11,
and yesterday I found out that
Kevin almost killed
someone drunk driving.
So I need you to help me
act normal around him,
so that I can get what I need,
so I can get out of here.
Oh, well,
that's gonna be a problem.
Because the goal of therapy
is not to act normal,
it's to be normal.
Yeah, well, I'll be normal
when I'm home
with the woman I love
instead of dreaming
that the guy I'm sharing a cell
with killed her.
- What?
- I had a dream last night
that I didn't have to inform
on Kevin anymore,
because he killed Rachel
in an accident.
And I must have been
talking about it in my sleep,
because he asked me
about it today,
so I told him the accident part,
and then we got in a fight.
- Fight about what?
- I asked him
if he even felt bad
about the guy he hit.
So you turned it
back on him?
What is that even
supposed to mean?
It means that I think
you picked a fight with Kevin
because you didn't want to think
about why you had that dream.
I know why I had the dream.
It's because he almost
killed someone
the same way
my parents were killed.
No, you had the dream,
because you don't want to deal
with what you're doing
to your friend.
- Oh, this again.
- Yes, this again.
Mike, why do you think part of
the dream was finding out
that you didn't have to inform
on him anymore?
God damn it,
I did not come here
to second guess my decision.
Do you know what?
I don't care.
Because I wouldn't be
doing my job,
if I didn't inform you
that actions have consequences,
and you seem to think that
the only consequence
of what you're doing
is getting out of here early,
but it's not.
I think you don't know shit
about what I've been through.
It's a mistake coming
to you for help.
And this is the fifth bedroom,
and I'm completely open
to you knocking down walls
or removing windows,
by the way.
No, I love the windows.
They let in so much light.
I agree.
We should add a wall of glass.
What do
I think the place
is beautiful,
and I appreciate you bringing
these photos over,
but when can we
go see it in person?
- In person?
- Yes, of course.
I need to see the space before
I can start drafting anything.
I was just thinking we could
work closer together
for the next 60 to 90 days
before you started that.
- That wouldn't be productive.
- But I couldn't possibly
make it out there in less than
seven to ten business days.
That's too bad.
I was gonna be out there
the day after tomorrow.
I was thinking
we could see the space,
and then maybe go have lunch.
Lunch?
Together?
Well, I wasn't thinking of
eating in separate restaurants.
Ha!
Of course you weren't.
Day after tomorrow's perfect.
- But I thought you couldn't--
- I can, and I will,
and I will meet you
at my ancestral home,
that I've owned for quite
some time, day after tomorrow.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Your Honor,
I'm simply requesting
Mr. Sutter hand over--
Something he has not right to.
I have every right
to make sure
that your client
is operating within the law.
And what exactly is your basis
to say that he isn't?
Your Honor, when you break
the home run record,
and someone says,
"Your bat is corked,"
you turn it over
to show it's not.
Except when that bat is the
reason you hit all those homers,
because the second he gets it,
everyone in the world's
gonna know what's in it.
And my client might as well
go out of business right now.
That is
a ridiculous supposition
without a shred of proof
to back it up.
How's this for proof?
Your Honor, six years ago,
Mr. Cahill
went on a fishing expedition
just like this one.
That has nothing to do
with this.
Oh, doesn't it?
He subpoenaed a proprietary
trading program
from Kessler Capital.
It proved no wrongdoing,
and ten months later
they were out of business.
That has nothing to do
with my subpoena.
And I have an affidavit here
from Mr. Kessler
saying it was directly
because of your subpoena.
Mr. Cahill,
is what he's saying true?
Did you go after Kessler
in the same manner,
and did he go
under ten months later?
- Yes, but--
- No buts,
do you have
any other evidence
to present to the court?
Not at this time, Your Honor.
Then your request is denied.
[bangs gavel]
♪ ♪
Oh, there you are.
What the hell
are you doing
in the executive kitchen?
What does it look like
I'm doing? I'm being executive.
But you're not an executive.
Until I made the
executive decision that I was.
Now, is there something
I can help you with?
Yeah. I want you
to forget that latte
and get me unfettered access
to my new home,
after thoroughly cleansing it
of any trace
of its former occupants.
And why, exactly,
do you need me to do that?
Because Tara wants
to see the house,
and then have lunch
with me the day after tomorrow.
Louis, your offer
was just accepted,
and there's never been
a one-day escrow
in the history of escrows.
You don't think I know that?
I just spent the last hour
arguing with five
different escrow officers.
I get it.
You want me to get people
to do things
they'd never be willing to do,
in a timeframe
that makes it impossible
for them to do it in.
- Exactly.
- Then make me a double latte
and get the hell out
of my way,
because I'm about
to executive decision
your sorry ass
into that house.
What are you drinking?
A 60-year-old bottle of the
finest single malt in the world.
Then get me a glass.
Not until I know
what happened in court today.
Well, let me put it this way.
The only thing
that Sean Cahill's
gonna be drinking tonight
is a shit-out-of-luck
daiquiri.
- How'd you get it done?
- I established
a pattern of him going fishing
without enough bait.
Then have a drink
before you get back in there
and knock the bastard out before
he can throw another punch.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying,
I want you to get
this entire action dismissed.
William,
that's a terrible idea.
Not to me,
because he's got nothing.
I don't care.
What you're suggesting
is a mistake.
You still haven't
told me why.
Because you only get
one shot at dismissal,
and now's not the time
to take it.
Well, I say it is.
I'm not suggesting it.
I'm flat out telling you
to do it.
I didn't get where I am
by letting my clients bully me.
And I didn't get
where I am
by allowing my employees
to dictate terms,
which I already did once today.
I'm not gonna do it again.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means Jessica Pearson
convinced me
to give your firm
the rest of my business
this afternoon.
So if you don't move to have the
charges against me dismissed,
I'll have her do it for you.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Harvey, I was just
on my way out.
Well, you can be
on your way back in,
because I just came
from Sutter's.
I take it he told you about
our little conversation today.
If, by conversation,
you mean going behind my back
and getting his
investment business,
then yeah, he told me.
I didn't go behind your back.
I saw an opportunity,
and I took it.
Well, now he's seeing an
opportunity, and he's taking it.
- What are you talking about?
- He's leveraging what you did
to get me to move
for an immediate dismissal.
And, don't tell me,
you think it's gonna work?
I sure as hell do.
And the second it does,
Mike's chance
at getting out goes with it,
thanks to you.
Hang on there, tiger.
You're not in this position
because of something I did.
You're in it
because of Sutter,
and he'd be demanding
you have this case dismissed
whether we have his
other business or not.
- Oh, that's not the point.
- No, Harvey, the point is,
I have been out there
busting my ass
trying to find us
new business for days,
and do you know
what they keep asking?
Why don't we have
Sutter's investment business.
Goddamn right.
We needed it.
I got it, and now
they're not asking anymore.
Well, what's gonna happen
when we lose this case,
and his business goes away?
What happens is, we're already
built back up by then,
so instead of blaming me
for the position Sutter
has put you in,
I suggest you go ahead
and find yourself
a way out of it.
♪ ♪
Rachel,
what can I do for you?
I was hoping you could
do something for Leonard Bailey.
I drafted a motion
to reopen his case,
but I need a current member
of the Bar to file it.
And what happened
to the person
you said
was gonna take this on?
She can't get to it
till later this week,
but I want to get on this
as soon as possible.
Rachel, I'm sorry,
but I told you before,
I don't have the resources
to work on this case now.
Professor, this man has a wife
who gave up on him
and children
that he doesn't see.
His entire life
is passing him by,
and the only way for him
to start getting it back
is to just have someone
who cares enough about him
that they give him
a half hour of their time.
Let me see your motion.
[exhales sharply]
This is well drafted.
Thank you.
But I'm afraid it won't work.
What are you talking--no--
look, there's no reason that
he should have been convicted.
Look at the evidence.
That's not the point, Rachel.
I've worked on dozens
of these cases,
and like it or not,
the standard to reopen
is higher than what it says
in the books.
You need something undeniable.
Then what am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to use your
gumption to find that something,
and get Leonard Bailey the
justice he's been waiting for.
Harvey, it's late.
Whatever you're doing here
is gonna have to wait
until morning.
- It can't.
- Why's that?
Because Sutter wants me to
move for an immediate dismissal.
What?
You leveraged me
into bringing this indictment,
and now you want to toss it?
I don't want to toss it,
but if I don't,
he's gonna find
someone else who will.
What are you
doing here, Harvey?
Nothing, I'm just finishing
my dinner.
The thing is,
I don't like to litter,
so why don't you
do me a favor?
If I forget this when I go,
why don't you take it upstairs
and throw it away?
What's in the bag, Harvey?
A wrapper, couple napkins,
and a few extra fries.
What the hell is
in the bag, Harvey?
What you needed to keep
this case going,
and I stopped you
from getting.
Damn it, you said
you were gonna defend him
to the best of your ability.
And I meant it.
But I also knew,
if push came to shove,
I'd do what
I had to to get Mike out,
and I made my peace with it.
- Yeah, well, I haven't.
- Yes, you have.
- What are you talking about?
- You've been giving me
this song and dance
about not colluding,
and it didn't matter
what I said back to you,
as long as it was something
to let you believe we wouldn't.
Because that song wasn't for me,
it was for you.
- Oh, for me? Bullshit.
- I don't think so, Sean,
because you don't break a guy
out of prison
just to advance your career.
Look, this means something
to you.
I don't need to know
what it is,
but it means something
to me too,
so let's just admit
that we're in this together
and get this thing done.
Take that garbage
and throw it away.
♪ ♪
Now can I have champagne?
You got the realtor to
give you the key to the house.
Not only that, I got him
to agree to take the Kellmans
to brunch tomorrow
from 10:00 to 2:00
to celebrate their big sale.
Well, that is great,
Donna,
but I don't just need
to get into the house.
I need Tara to believe that
it's my house, which means--
No lock box on the door,
no for sale sign in the yard,
and no personal
belongings in the house,
which is why we are
gonna be there at 10:01
to stage the shit
out of that place.
Oh, and these
are coming with us.
You reframed pictures
of Bruno?
In the style of the house.
And not just Bruno...
Mikado.
That's perfect, Donna.
I just thought showing Tara
your wood
wasn't the only way to show her
what kind of man you are.
Thank you, Donna.
You're welcome, Louis.
Since when do we get a room
instead of having to use
those damn phones?
Since I officially
became part of your legal team.
- My legal team?
- That's right.
The firm that I work for
is taking your case.
After all this time.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
But we still need
to get the case reopened,
and to do that we need
to find something new.
So where do we get that?
I was going through
the state's case file,
and I read your police report.
You said there was a woman
with you that night
who can testify that you didn't
kill that couple.
That's right, Maria,
but that's not new.
Well, it's new as far
as the court's concerned,
because it was never
admitted at trial.
- Well, let's admit it.
- It's not that easy.
I need to understand
why it was never admitted.
Because the damn woman up
and disappeared before my trial.
My lawyer didn't do a thing.
You had an alibi witness,
and your public defender
let her get away.
That's what I've been saying.
Maria could have told the jury
that I didn't do it,
instead no one told them.
Two weeks later,
I'm in here,
and I've been here
ever since.
Is there anything else
I need to know?
Then I need to find
Maria Gomez.
Look, man, please,
I really don't want to talk.
Good, 'cause
I want you to listen.
When I was a kid,
I thought we had it good.
And we did. Had a nice house,
nice neighborhood.
Except for one thing.
Turns out my father...
was a criminal.
One day he got caught.
He went to prison.
My whole life fell apart.
How old were you?
15.
I'll tell you something.
I hated that man for doing
what he did to me,
so I did what messed up
15-year-olds do.
- Started acting out.
- Acting out?
Brother, I was on my way
to a place worse than this.
Finally, my mom made me
see someone,
and he helped me realize
that if I didn't change,
I was gonna ruin my life.
So I straightened out
and turned my life around.
And that's why you do
what you do.
Yeah.
- Why are you telling me this?
- Because the way
that man got through to me
was to open up about himself,
and I realized that if
I really want to help you,
I got to do the same.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
All right, I dragged this out
as long as I can,
but I'm pretty much done
drafting this motion.
So I'll need you to proof it--
Harvey, before I do that,
I think you should take
a look at these.
- What is it?
- Cahill issued subpoenas
to deposition William Sutter
and Kevin Miller.
- That sneaky son of a bitch.
- Why are you smiling?
Because last night
I went to Cahill
and tried to give him
Sutter's trading program.
- You did what?
- It was the only way
I could see to stop the case
from getting dismissed,
but he wouldn't take it.
And this buys you time.
It does, if the judge
waits to rule on our motion
until after Cahill conducts
these depositions.
Harvey, even if that works,
what if Cahill doesn't get
enough from the depositions
to keep the case alive?
Then Mike's chance of getting
out of prison is gone,
which means Cahill's
not the only one
that needs to use this
to try and get something.
I have to admit, Ms. Zane,
when you said
you were looking into the Bailey
case, my interest was piqued.
That was a long time ago.
Well, you've obviously
come a long way
since your public defender days.
You don't exactly see the best
of humanity at that job,
which makes it one
you can only do for so long.
But you didn't come here
to be my therapist.
No, I came to talk
about Maria Gomez.
What about her?
I'm curious as to how you
can have an alibi witness
on a murder case,
and your client ends up
on death row.
Because I didn't have
an alibi witness.
I had a no-show
who vanished into thin air,
and I didn't have the resources
to find her.
And you didn't think
to ask the police at trial
why they didn't follow up
on Leonard's alibi?
I did think of it,
and they would have said
what they always say,
"Every murderer claims
to have an alibi,"
and if I couldn't produce her,
why should they?
Well, you could have
at least asked for postponement,
to have time to find her.
And I would have,
except for one thing.
I wasn't sure a drug addict
with a prior conviction
would have done
Leonard Bailey much good.
That's about her character,
not the facts of the case.
Her character is
a fact of the case,
and when I pressed her
as to what the two of them
were doing at the time
of those murders,
she admitted they were
both on meth,
and it wasn't the first time.
Which, by the way,
might have something to do with
why she never
showed up at trial.
So you can try to reopen
this case if you want, Ms. Zane,
but I am telling you,
you're wasting your time.
♪ ♪
What's going on?
What's going on is,
the clock's ticking.
Sutter wants me
to get the case dismissed.
- What? If that happens, I'll--
- I know.
Now, listen to me.
I bought us a little time,
but I need you to do something.
Okay.
What is it?
Sutter doesn't know this yet,
but he and I are gonna
be here tomorrow
to have a practice deposition
with Kevin.
So I need you to do the best
Sean Cahill
you have to get them talking.
You want me in the room?
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Didn't you hear me?
We're running out of time.
I heard you, but I don't think
it's a good idea
for me to be in the same room
as Kevin right now.
- The drunk driving.
- You knew?
- I just found out.
- Well, then you also know
it's probably not the best time
for me to chum up to him.
I'm not asking you
to chum up to him.
I'm asking you
to piss him off.
- What are you talking about?
- Kevin knows something,
and he's not talking.
So we could sit around here
for the next two years
waiting for him to tell you,
or we can light a fire
under his ass
by reminding him
that Sutter's out there,
while he's in here.
Now, are you with me or not?
I'm with you.
I take it you're here
to give me the good news.
- I'm afraid not.
- I thought I made myself clear.
If you don't make a motion
to dismiss this--
I did file a motion
to dismiss,
but it doesn't matter,
because Cahill filed subpoenas
to depose you
and your son-in-law first,
and until those
depositions happen,
the court won't file
on the motion.
Goddamn it.
How the hell did he know
to do that
when we're about to have
the case thrown out?
I don't know, but that's not
what I came here to talk about,
because we need to get you
and Kevin Miller
in a room to prepare you
for your deposition.
- You want us to go to prison?
- I don't see any other choice,
so you should call whoever it is
you were gonna meet this morning
and tell them
you can't make it,
because you and I
are going to Danbury.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Were you really serious
about wanting to help me?
Why do I get the feeling
that's not a simple question?
Because I want to know if
you're willing to give me access
to certain records.
I'm sorry, Mike, I cannot give
information on other inmates.
Oh, that's okay, because those
aren't the records
I'm looking for.
Did you find Maria?
You know, I haven't even
started looking for her yet,
because you lied to me.
What?
I didn't lie to you
about shit.
Well, you certainly didn't
tell me that you and Maria
were high the night
of those murders.
- Who told you that?
- Georgina Casey.
You went to see my old lawyer?
Yes, I did.
And now you sitting over there
looking at me like,
"You know, maybe he could have
killed those people after all."
Leonard, when I went into that
meeting, I was on your side.
And you came out of it
off it.
No, when I came out of it,
I had questions.
Okay, ask them.
I got nothing to hide.
Really? Because you hid
something from me the last time.
That was different.
- No, it's relevant.
- No, it isn't.
You were high the night
of the murders,
and you lied to me about it.
Because I'm ashamed of
how I used to be.
I was a high school dropout
on my way nowhere,
so, yeah, I looked for an escape
when I could afford one.
I'm not saying
I didn't make some mistakes
or maybe even commit
a few crimes,
but killing those kids
was not one of them.
♪ ♪
And that's the truth,
but I guess it doesn't matter,
because if you don't
find Maria,
someday they're gonna walk me
down that hall
and put me to death.
Then I guess I better
get back to finding her.
But, Leonard,
I'm telling you,
if you're not straight
with me,
this isn't gonna work.
Then I won't ever leave
anything out again.
This is ridiculous.
This kid's no Sean Cahill.
This kid made Sean Cahill
look like a fool
without even having
a law degree.
Just so you know, when
you attack opposing counsel,
it kind of makes
you look afraid.
[scoffs]
I'm not afraid of you.
Okay, then why don't you
tell me this,
what's the best thing
about having so much money?
- What?
- You heard me.
You got the penthouse
in Manhattan.
You got the villa in the south
of France. You get two yachts--
- So what?
So I wouldn't want
to give all of that up.
Would you, Mr. Miller?
- Me?
- Yeah, you.
I mean, you had use
of all of these places too,
until you threw it
all away driving drunk, that is.
- What?
- Objection.
Irrelevant.
I think it's very relevant.
For all I know,
Kevin could be somehow involved.
- That's insane.
- That's insane?
You're the developer
of the trading software.
And I'm not the one
who's on trial here.
Then let's talk about
the one who is.
How do you feel about the fact
that your father-in-law
never came to visit
you in prison?
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
He hasn't come to see you once.
How does that make you feel?
- It doesn't matter to me.
- [chuckles]
He could be lying on a beach
in the French Riviera,
while you can barely see
your wife and kids,
and that doesn't matter to you?
Mr. Miller's family
has nothing to do
with this investigation.
Mr. Miller's family
is the subject
of this investigation,
and his father in law
clearly doesn't give a shit--
I'm grateful for everything
Kevin's done for me,
and he knows it.
Yeah, right.
I'm sorry, what was that?
Are you disputing the fact
that he's grateful to you?
I'm not answering
that question.
This isn't
getting us anywhere.
He's getting
you ready for Cahill.
I wouldn't have
to get ready for Cahill
if you did your goddamn job
and got this case dismissed.
That's right,
get someone else
to cover up your mess
like you always do.
You got something you want
to say to me?
I got something I want
to do to you.
You better remember
who you're talking to.
I know exactly
who I'm talking to,
the guy who doesn't
give a shit
about anyone else
other than himself.
- That's enough.
- That is enough.
This is your trial.
It's not mine,
and I'm done with this,
and I'm done with you!
♪ ♪
Guard.
[bangs on door]
♪ ♪
[bangs on table]
Son of a bitch.
I knew that kid
would be a problem.
Relax. That's the whole reason
I wanted Mike in here.
If Kevin gets
any funny ideas,
Mike's gonna calm him down
and let us know.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
You guys really get under
each other's skin, don't you?
You have no idea
how many times
I thought about punching
that bastard in his smug face.
I'm guessing he's thought
about punching you too.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means his daughter
married a criminal.
He's got to live with that.
You know what?
I've had just about enough
of you
giving me shit
for what I did.
Well, maybe I'll stop
giving you shit
when your story starts
adding up.
Excuse me?
You said you got three years
for drunk driving,
but you got no priors,
and this guy
made a full recovery.
99 times out of 100, that means
you're getting probation.
Then I guess
I had shitty representation.
Bullshit.
Money like yours doesn't
buy shitty representation.
Then I don't know
what to tell you.
How about you start with
telling me the goddamn truth?
You want to know the truth?
I'll tell you,
because I'm sick
of holding it in, man.
I got three years, because when
they offered me a deal
to turn on him,
I said no.
You had to turn them down.
He didn't do it.
No, I had to turn them down,
because he's not
the only one involved.
What?
You asked me why
I was drinking that night.
It was because I found out the
thing that I worked so hard on
to get that prick's approval
was nothing but a lie.
- Your trading program.
- Yeah, my program.
Turns out he wasn't
using it at all.
He was just
insider trading the whole time.
Okay, so you got home,
you told Jill,
and she didn't believe you.
No, Mike.
She not only believed me,
she...
she already knew.
[exhales sharply]
She was in on it.
Yeah.
So I went out,
and I got drunk.
And the next thing
I knew,
I had to choose between
going to prison for three years,
or the mother of my children
going away for a whole lot more.
- Kevin, you got--
- No.
♪ ♪
Okay, I have removed
every possible trace
of the Kellmans' existence
and replaced it with yours.
Now all I have to do is fill the
refrigerator with prune juice,
and then I've got
to set up the--
- Okay, get out.
- What?
What do you mean get out?
I haven't set up the--
She's pulling up.
She's here,
and I don't want her
to see us together
and get the wrong idea.
- And exactly what idea is that?
- Okay, don't you understand?
No woman could compete
with you,
if she thought there was
even a chance
of you and I being together.
- Really?
- No, she blows you away.
Now, get the hell out,
and use the service entrance.
Tara, you're here.
Oh, my God.
Louis,
this place is wonderful.
How long have you had it?
Had it for generations.
Great-grandma Litt,
she used to make wool
right over there by the fire.
The natural light
is phenomenal.
Phenomenal.
And there's a wildness
to the landscape,
an uninhibited energy.
Wild.
Uninhibited.
It's perfect for us, Louis.
I'm glad you like it.
I don't just like it.
I love it.
Just like I love you.
[tense music]
Oh, Tara, I love you--
- What?
- It.
Your idea...what you were
talking about earlier.
- Which idea?
- What happened?
Louis, are you okay?
[door opens]
What the hell
is going on here?
Nothing's going on here.
What the hell are you doing
in my house?
- Your house?
- Louis, who are these people?
These people are
the registered owners
of this property.
You mean the one you said
had been
in your family
for generations?
That's a lie.
We built this house ourselves,
and until five minutes ago,
we were gonna sell it to him.
Tara, I can explain.
I don't need you to explain.
I've heard enough.
Tara, wait.
Please.
Tara, please wait.
You know, I've heard
about people like you.
You're trying to get free
design work out of me,
so you can decide whether or not
you want to buy this house.
That has nothing
to do with it.
Really?
Because, first,
you tried to get me
to work on this
without even seeing the space.
Then you lured me out here
under false pretenses.
So why don't you tell me what,
exactly, is going on here?
I lied to you about owning
a house in the Hamptons
so I could spend time
with you.
What?
Why--why would you do that?
Because you are perfect,
and beautiful,
and intelligent,
and talented,
and so far out of my league.
It was the only thing that I can
come up with to find the time
I needed to make you
fall for me.
You were willing to buy
and remodel
- an entire house to do that?
- I was.
That's the most romantic thing
I've ever heard.
Really?
Yeah. Yes, really.
[chuckles]
Tara, would you like
to have dinner with me?
I'd love to, Louis.
- [chuckles]
- Yeah.
[soft music]
What are you working on?
An engagement letter.
You got a new client.
I got us two new clients.
So that's what you had
to do the other day.
Well, something like that.
The one I got the other day
led to the one I got today.
That's great.
Yeah, what's on your mind?
I know you said that you'd
give me
an hour of your time
later this week,
but I need that hour tonight.
Rachel, it's been a long day.
Can we talk about this
in the morning?
No, Jessica, we can't.
Leonard Bailey's
execution date's been set,
and I don't know how to tell
a man that he's going to die.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
You know,
I always knew that Jill and I
were from two
different worlds.
And she was a Sutter,
and I was just--
and didn't have much else?
Figured it was only
a matter of time
before she came to her senses,
but she never did.
Well, let me guess,
William never accepted it.
No.
So when he asked me
to develop that algorithm,
I thought,
"This is my chance."
And when I gave it to him,
he acted so proud.
Started calling me
his genius son-in-law.
But I was really just
the world's biggest sucker,
because I let that son
of a bitch get one over on me,
and I'll regret it
for the rest of my life.
What if you could get
one over on him?
What are you talking about?
You said yourself,
they offered you a deal.
I bet they'd still take it.
No way. If I give them him,
they go after her.
Not if you get them
to give Jill immunity first.
- No.
- Kevin, you have to--
It's too big a risk,
and you're
my father-in-law's lawyer.
You can't even be
saying this to me.
I am nobody's lawyer.
I am your friend,
and I am saying--
Well, my answer's no,
and I want your word, right now,
that you won't tell anyone
what I told you.
- Kevin, please, you're not--
- Mike, I'm serious.
No one can ever know anything
about what I told you.
♪ ♪
You have my word.
Did I ever tell you
my mother was a teacher?
First grade.
Everybody always said she was
the best teacher
their kid ever had.
She loved it.
She also always dreamed of
seeing Spain when she retired.
That was supposed
to be six years ago,
but then the state
teacher's pension fund
decided to invest its money
with William Sutter.
She died last year,
still working.
And every year,
I tried to pay for her trip,
but she just wouldn't let me.
Sean, why are you
telling me this?
Because a judge decided
to rule on your motion
to dismiss after all.
Which means
we're out of time,
and you didn't just come here
to tell me about your mother.
No.
I came here to ask
for that trading program.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man