- You're good with me working
on the takeover with logan.
- As long as we don't let that
affect this.
- We won't.
- I do always get what I want,
And what I want to do with
this company is strip it down,
Flip it over, and then...
- That's enough.
We're done.
- You're right.
- When I told you that
our relationship was now
Purely professional,
I was serious.
- What's not purely professional
about lunch?
Unless you mean the sex
that'll be following lunch.
- Phillip, your son,
you lost him,
And that's what this company
is to you now, your family.
I lost both my parents
when I was 11 years old,
So I know a little something
about needing family.
- Since when does the s.E.C.
Go around
Intimidating law firms
by going after their clients?
- They don't,
but they will when eric woodall
Starts there next week.
- [yawns]
[sighs]
- Another all-nighter?
- Yeah.
- Work or school?
- Work.
- What were you working on?
- You know what I was
working on.
I am so sorry, but I'm so tired.
I have to go get some sleep
before I go back to the office.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I haven't seen you in two days.
Give me five minutes.
- Okay,
but I can't be responsible
For anything that I say.
- Well, okay, in that case,
Is logan going
after another board member?
- Nice try.
- Mm, is he running out of cash?
- I can't tell you that.
- Did you love him?
- How long have you been waiting
to ask me that?
- You know, just when you were
at your weakest
And most vulnerable.
- I did love him,
but I don't love him now.
I love you.
- Who ended it?
- Does that matter?
- It does to me.
- I ended it.
Now, do you have
any other burning questions,
Or can I go to sleep, please?
- Um, let me see.
What's the most expensive thing
you ever shoplifted?
Were you a mean girl?
Are you interested in taking
a pole dancing class?
You know what?
We'll get into that later.
Sweet dreams.
- God, enough about you.
I want to talk about me.
- We were just talking
about you.
- Not enough.
All right, fine.
Let's talk about harvey.
- Mm.
- So guess what he's been up to.
- He found the master tapes
for his father's solo album.
He's working on buying them.
He's been trying to find them
ever since he lost his father.
- Oh, I see why
you're telling me this.
Because you're afraid of what
this fight is gonna do to us.
- I'm afraid because of what
it's already doing to you.
I'm talking ali-frazier.
- Come on, donna.
- Listen to me.
They started out like brothers.
Then they went toe-to-toe
three times,
And joe frazier went to
his grave hating muhammad ali.
- I didn't know
you were a boxing fan.
- I'm a harvey fan.
- So am I, and that's why
I'm giving him my best.
Thanks for the coffee.
- You're welcome.
[knocking]
- You're in late.
- I was up late.
- Working on my stuff?
- Working on a lot of stuff.
What can I help you with?
- I wanted to talk to you.
- About?
- Well, when I told you before
that I'm not the same guy
That I used to be,
what I meant was,
I got caught up in emotion
back then.
I'm not caught up
in emotion anymore.
- And?
- And that means
that I'm gonna have to do
Some calculated things,
And I needed to know
that you're okay with that.
- Why wouldn't I be?
- You know why.
- Logan,
you don't have to come and have
These little check-in talks
with me.
I am a big girl, and I know how
these things work.
So just do what you have to do,
and stop worrying about me.
- Great.
Harvey,
what the hell's going on?
- At the moment,
I'm 18 minutes away
From owning steve mcqueen's
shelby cobra.
- You know what
I'm talking about.
Last time I saw you,
you told me you were gonna
I just found out waiter gillie
funded his pension.
- Did you think
they wouldn't fight back?
- I expected them to fight.
Right now,
we're getting our ass kicked.
- Well, what scorecard
are you looking at,
Because we just got them
to give up half their war chest
- I don't give a sh...
what the scorecard says.
I want a knockout.
- Well, it doesn't work
that way.
- It can if you hit them
below the belt.
When my father went up
against carl icahn,
He said that you waited
till he wasn't looking,
You walked up behind him,
and you shot him in the back.
- Walter gillie
isn't carl icahn.
- I'm not talking
about waiter gillie.
I'm talking about mike ross.
- I don't care
who you're talking about.
That icahn deal
was completely different.
- The only difference I see
is that this deal
Is against your surrogate son.
So are you willing to do this
or not?
- You want below the belt?
I'll give you below the belt.
- ♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
- Louis, we talked about this.
- It's just so weird to see him
in my old office, you know?
It's like when you drive
by the house you grew up in,
And there's another family
in there,
And all you want to do is
break in and make yourself soup.
You know that feeling?
- Well, it depends on the soup.
- [scoffs] mushroom barley.
- Then no.
Hey, did you get him
that apology gift
- Except instead of scotch,
I got us two front-row tickets
To the ballet.
- Oh.
Well,
it's the thought that counts.
- Louis, can I help you
with something?
You and me,
we got off on the wrong foot.
Words were said,
hurtful caricatures were drawn,
And I did some bad things too.
- Water under the bridge, louis.
See, um, I once was told
that actions have consequences,
And I want to turn things around
by inviting you...
To the american ballet company's
production of giselle.
- The ballet?
- Yeah, you and me tonight.
Louis, I would love to go
to the ballet with you.
I really would, but I have
knicks tickets tonight, man,
- All right, I'm gonna let it go
that you're choosing basketball
Over giselle, but I really need
to make this up to you, jeff.
I can't be in the red.
I am always,
always in the black,
- Well, now that you mention it,
I could really use some advice.
- About a case?
- About jessica.
I just pulled adam grieves
as opposing counsel.
And long story short,
he hates me,
And I could really use jessica's
help to run some interference,
But I'm the new guy,
it's only my second case,
And I don't know what to do.
- Well, I'll tell you
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna get you
front-row tickets
To jessica pearson's help.
- Okay, harvey, you didn't
bring me here to make me
Choke down
these brussels sprouts.
- No, I didn't,
but you are going to have
To choke down something else.
- Let me guess.
This is about waiter gillie.
- No, it's not about waiter.
It's about the line of credit
That you're about to stop
giving him.
- And why on earth
would I do that?
- Because if you don't,
I have a feeling
That every
pearson specter client
That you currently
do business with,
Suddenly gonna move
their accounts to chase.
- You really want to cripple
his company that badly?
- His company's already dead.
- That doesn't give you
the right to threaten me.
- If I were threatening you,
I'd come right out and say it.
If you don't do this,
tomorrow morning,
You lose $2 billion
worth of deposits.
- You son of a bitch.
- That he is.
- What are you doing here, mike?
- What do you mean?
I just came
for the brussels sprouts.
You know how I know
how good they are?
- Because this is where harvey
brings bankers
To strong-arm them
into doing some bullsh...
- Don't listen to him.
- No, he should listen to me.
I'm waiter gillie' partner,
and if he cuts off our funding
At any point in the next two
months following this lunch,
Then the next time
you're talking about
These brussels sprouts will be
in front of a grand jury.
Oh, vernon,
don't take it personally.
He did the same thing
to the guy from leeds
At the exact same table
seven months ago.
- Louis, I got your memo,
And if you want to get
an antique diving bell
For your new office,
it's on your dime.
- Okay, that's bullsh...,
but whatever.
I'm here about jeff malone.
You two are gonna have to work
your sh... out on the playground.
- But you see, that's just it.
We already did.
- Something's not right.
- I'm here because you need
to run interference.
- I thought you just said
you worked it out.
- No, not with me,
with adam grieves at the s.E.C.
He has it in for malone.
- Louis, I'm glad you two
are going to be
Walking to school together
from now on,
But I hired jeff malone
to handle the s.E.C.,
Not to get me to handle them
for him.
- You know, you're always
telling me not to make enemies,
And for the first time
since harvey,
I have just made a new friend,
So I'm asking you...
Please do it for my friend.
- If you won't do it for him,
please do it for me.
- I just had a very interesting
chat with louis litt.
- Louis is
a very interesting guy.
Did you know he's never eaten
an olive?
- I did not, but I do know
you fed him some bullsh...
- That doesn't sound like me.
- Really?
'Cause he thinks we need
to work together
Because there's bad blood
between you and adam grieves.
- I don't like to talk about it.
- Of course not,
because you and adam grieves
Play basketball every Wednesday.
- What happens on the court,
jessica, stays on the court.
- And I thought I was clear
about boundaries.
- Well, listen,
if that's really how you feel,
Why don't you just tell louis
that you want to bow out
Because you don't trust yourself
around me?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
See you tomorrow.
- What happened to going
below the belt?
The referee stepped in and threw
a grand jury at my face.
- Well, I wasn't asking you
to go below the belt
I was asking you to go
below the belt with ross.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm saying you hire
a private investigator
To find every skeleton
in his closet.
He wakes up in the morning, and
it's all over the front page.
- Logan, that's not going
below the belt.
That's just nuts.
- You're full of sh...
You don't want to do this,
because you don't have
The stomach to do it
to your boy.
- No, I don't want to do it,
because we're on a path
To win this thing,
and I let you bait me into doing
What I already did
because I thought you were
Just a little impatient.
But now I'm starting to realize
what it really is.
- What is that?
- Who's full of sh... now?
- This has nothing to do
with rachel.
- You got there
pretty damn fast.
- Hey, I asked you to put
mike ross down with one punch.
You said you would,
and you didn't.
So either do what I'm asking,
or I'll do it myself.
- You can't do it, harvey.
- Yes, I can.
Logan's gonna do it anyway.
At least this way it'll be me.
- What's the difference
if you hire somebody
To look into mike or logan does?
You know damn well they're gonna
uncover his secret.
- I don't know that,
and you don't either.
- Yeah, I do.
- No one's ever found it before.
- Because you were hiding it
from people
Who weren't looking for it,
not from people who are.
- What do you want from me,
donna?
- I want you to get mike
to give up.
- Well, I'm not gonna do that,
Because I know
he's not gonna give up.
- How do you know that?
- Because I know.
- This is mike
we're talking about.
- If it were anyone
other than mike,
I'd have an article
in the journal tomorrow.
- That's not what
you told logan.
- Because I goddamn lied
to logan, and it didn't work.
Now I'm gonna do
what I have to do.
- Well, the least you can do
is warn him.
- He's on the other side.
I'm not gonna warn him.
That's not how it works.
- Well, maybe you should think
of something
That won't ruin
his goddamn life.
You ready to get down
to business?
I was thinking that maybe we
could do all this over lunch.
- It's 10:30.
- There's a lot to discuss,
jessica.
- No, there isn't.
We need to bury them
in paperwork.
We just need to come up
with a legitimate reason
Why brooks made that trade.
- There is no legitimate reason.
- I didn't say there needs
to be one, jessica.
- You are taking to defense
like a fish to water.
Just for my genetically superior
bone structure, did you?
- Mm, no, that's what
I brought him in for.
- Hey, sorry I'm late.
I was just getting up to speed.
- You brought louis in.
Three heads are better than two,
unless you have an objection?
- No.
Are you kidding me?
I would never turn down
a threesome, right, buddy?
- I hear you.
- Good, because jessica and I
were just having
A little difference of opinion
about what to do next.
- Yes, and I'm sure louis,
the man that I hired,
The man who owes
his very career to me,
Will see things my way.
- Well, I don't want to step
on anyone's toes.
- No, louis, you're not stepping
on anyone's toes here,
And to be fair, I think
you're an amazing attorney
Who doesn't owe anyone anything.
Ooh, do you work out?
- Oh, I-I try to stay fit.
- Try?
Mission accomplished.
- [chuckles]
- Can we get to the point?
Lou?
Louis?
Jeff and I have two different
approaches to this case.
- Exactly, go for the knockout
punch or bore them to death.
- Oh, well,
when you frame it that way...
- I can't believe you're using
that old debate team trick.
- Farm boy strong.
That's what you are.
Jessica, what debate team trick?
- Calling my approach
"bore them to death"
And yours "a knockout punch."
Are you...
have you done this before?
Look, jessica, you can make
assumptions about how
This farm boy's gonna come down
on this all you want to,
But I think we all pretty much
know he's playing on my team.
- Jeff, you're right.
You are right, and in fact,
I think that,
because you and louis
See eye to eye on this case,
that you should work together,
And I should bow out.
- You actually think
that bothers me?
Because now I've this farm boy
all to myself, jess.
Just you and me, cowboy.
It's like ernie and bert.
- Jeff malone is in love
with me.
- I was just in a meeting
with him,
And he started off
by patting my shoulder.
- He's a jock, louis.
- No, he was then rubbing
my shoulders.
Then he touched my arm.
- Wow.
What was that meeting about?
Donna, his arguments are loaded
with double meaning.
Who invokes the penal code
in an s.E.C. Case?
- He said "penal"?
The third time,
we were just talking about
The glass-steagall act,
which is purely civil, and it...
God damn it, woman,
do I have to draw you a map?
- I mean, come to think of it,
Athletes coming out
is all the rage now.
- And guess what his favorite
sport is: Basket... Ball.
- Oh, my god.
- No,
I want to shut the back door.
- Okay, louis,
Now that we've firmly
established his gayness,
Why would he think you're gay?
I mean, you're...
[exhales] straight as an arrow.
- I may have said
that I eat cock for breakfast,
Lunch, and dinner.
- It was a different kind
of cock, donna.
- Okay, louis, what exactly
do you want from me?
- I want you to tell me
what I should do about it.
- I'm gonna tell you exactly
what you're gonna do about it:
Nothing.
- What do you mean, "nothing"?
- I mean don't give him
anything back.
He'll get the message.
It'll pass.
- [chuckles]
Donna, I don't think
you understand the power
Of my sexuality.
- Oh, you know, it's just a
little something for your file.
- I have a file?
- That information
is classified.
- Wait, why?
- It's in your file.
- Oh, sh...
[alternative music]
♪ ♪
- Harvey specter.
If you'd be more comfortable,
I have a couple rocks
- Most people would go with some
tall weeds I could hide behind.
- Most people don't take
these fights personally.
I do.
- That's exactly why I'm here.
- Meaning?
- I came here to tell you
something man-to-man,
Because I know what this company
means to you.
- If you knew what this company
meant to me,
You wouldn't be trying
to steal it.
- Walter,
I know how your son died.
- Get the hell out of my office.
- Not before I tell you that
mike ross was a drug dealer.
- Bullsh... he was,
and I'm calling security,
And if you're not gone
by the time they get here,
Their job's going to be
getting me off you.
- Fine, I'll go, but ask him.
Ask him if he ever dealt drugs.
Ask him if he ever refused
to take a drug test.
Ask him if he was ever high
at work.
- And ask him
if on the very day he came to me
Looking for a job he had a
briefcase filled with marijuana.
- This is how you do this,
come here "man-to-man"
And use my son's death
to take my company from me?
Well, you are nothing
but a piece of sh...
- You're right.
I am a piece of sh...
But that doesn't make what
I'm telling you any less true.
- Walter,
what are you doing here?
- I'm having second thoughts.
- About the takeover.
- About you.
- I'm sorry.
I don't understan...
- Have you ever been involved
in a drug deal?
- [scoffs]
Walter, look, I'm trying to save
your company here.
- And I'm here to find out
what kind of man
I'm in business with,
so I'm going to ask you again.
Have you ever been involved
in a drug deal?
- What did harvey tell you?
- Looks like he told me
the truth.
- The truth is that harvey
can't beat us,
So he's trying to divide us, and
he's using your son to do it.
- Just like you used his memory
to make you my partner.
- To save your life's work.
- Another lie from another liar.
You two deserve each other.
We're done.
- Mike, are you okay?
- I don't care who you find.
I want you to hire someone to
get every piece of dirt there is
On logan sanders.
- Uh...
- Just do it.
- To take care
of something else.
I got him that weird zucchini
cake he likes from the bronx.
- What cake?
- Somebody returned
stutman's chair.
- And the "no questions asked"
memo in the kitchen worked.
- What did it stop?
- Mm, it's not important.
- None of these things
are important.
- Oh, and one more thing.
Louis thinks malone
is in love with him.
Your secret's safe.
And you're welcome.
- Hey, louis,
do you have a minute?
- Well, it's about all I have,
'cause I'm super, super busy.
- Yeah, well, listen,
I just wanted to check in
And see if you're ready
to pull an all-nighter.
I just got
all the brokerage tapes in,
And I figure we could just
grind it out.
- Tonight,
unless you want to go right now
And just pound it out
all at once.
- Okay, that's it.
I mean,
you have got this all wrong.
Jeff,
I like you... As a friend.
- Right, louis.
I like you too.
I think I've made that
perfectly clear.
- Too clear, man, too clear.
I mean, enough
with the come-ons, already.
- What?
- Yeah, I mean, I get it.
You know, we're a perfect match,
you know,
If you go that way,
ebony and ivory.
But I play
a different instrument, so...
- Oh, louis, no...
- Look, I...
look, it's just that...
I just don't...
I don't want there to be,
You know, just awkwardness,
especially since jessica
Just bowed out,
and it's just me and you now.
- Right.
[sighs]
Well, now that you've seen
right through me, louis,
I...I am disappointed.
- Are you gonna be okay?
- To be honest, I'm feeling
a little raw right now.
- Oh, sh...
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
- Maybe it's best
if you just told jessica
That she needs to step back in.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Can do, yeah.
- Get up.
- You here to fight me?
- Oh, should I wait for you
to turn your back?
- I'm sorry, were you
expecting me to give you a call?
- No, I was expecting you to be
a human being.
- From where I'm sitting,
I was a goddamn saint.
- Oh, yeah?
How's that?
- If I didn't do what I did,
logan was gonna hire
A private investigator to
smear you up and down the block.
- So what?
- You know what.
I shot you in the knees, so he
wouldn't shoot you in the face.
You're welcome.
- You know what, harvey?
I'm gonna take pass
on the thank-you
And instead skip right
to the part where I call you
A piece of sh...
I'm getting a little tired
of hearing that.
And what does that make you
for threatening to bring
Criminal charges
in that restaurant?
- You deserved criminal charges
For what you were doing
in that restaurant.
- You didn't have a problem
when we did it
- Seven months ago, you weren't
lying to somebody about me.
- I didn't lie,
and seven months ago,
You were goddamn here.
- So that's what this is about.
You can't stand
that I got out of here
And that I'm succeeding
without you.
- Without me?
I made you.
Without me, you're nothing.
- Right there.
That's who you are,
and that's why I left.
- Bullsh...
Don't lay that on me.
You left because you needed
to feed that huge ego.
- Ego?
Ego?
If I stayed here, you know what
would have been hanging
Over my head for the rest
of my life.
- Which is why I told you
to move somewhere
Nobody ever knew you.
But you stayed here,
so that thing is still
Over your goddamn head,
and I stopped it.
- I don't care what you think
you stopped.
You're gonna go
to waiter gillie,
And you're gonna make
this thing right.
- It is right.
It's over.
You lost.
- Nothing's over.
And you're the one who lost
something today.
- What are you talking about?
- You went personal.
I went personal.
Your father's master tapes...
I've got 'em.
- Those tapes have nothing to do
with this deal.
- They do now.
- Harvey...
I did this.
- What?
- The tapes.
Mike found out about them
from me.
I've been meeting him for coffee
just because I wanted
To make sure that everything
was okay between the two of you,
And I never, ever thought that
he would do something like this.
I'm so, so sorry.
- It's not your fault, donna.
- What are you gonna do?
- Nothing.
The tapes have nothing to do
with this deal.
The second I believe they do,
I'm done.
- Ugh, perfect timing.
Do you want me
to get rid of him?
- I'll handle it.
- What part of
"drag mike ross through the mud"
Did you not understand?
- The part where you come off
looking like a rich,
Vindictive douche bag.
- Based on your years
of experience in takeovers?
Here's something they didn't
teach you in snowboarding school
Or wherever the hell you went
Before you decided to be
a grown-up.
Never destroy anyone in public
When you can accomplish
the same result in private.
- Meaning?
- I severed mike's ties
with waiter gillie.
It's over.
- You know, you told me
that mike ross wasn't a threat,
And then he handcuffed us
with a t.R.O.
You said that you'd
take him down with one blow,
So here's something that I did
learn in snowboarding school.
When someone talks sh...,
I demand proof.
- Proof of what?
Logan, we won.
You don't need...
- Need to what?
Come off like a rich,
vindictive douche bag?
I want proof
that he's giving up his bid,
And if I don't get it
by the morning,
I'm gonna call
my private investigators,
And I'm gonna finish
what I started.
- Where are you going?
To get mike to sign an agreement
to give up his bid.
- You can't.
- Why not?
- Because you were right.
He's never gonna listen to you.
- Donna, I know you're feeling
bad about the tapes, but...
- That has nothing to do
with it.
- Then what are you saying?
- I feel guilty that I told him,
but what he did,
That's on you.
And the reason he's not gonna
listen to you
Is because you acted like
an asshole.
- Excuse me?
For why you did what you did,
and you threw gas on the fire.
- I gave him an explanation.
- Yeah,
you told him he was nothing.
About a half an hour ago, you
told me this was all your fault.
- A half an hour ago,
I was thinking about what I did.
I wasn't thinking
about what you said to him.
- It doesn't matter
what I said to him.
I saved him.
- Harvey, you said before
if it had been anybody
Other than mike, you would have
done what logan wanted
Well, if anybody other than mike
had walked in here
The way he did,
You would have shown him
the tiniest bit of compassion.
- He bought those tapes
before he ever walked in here.
- Those tapes were not the first
thing that he told you about,
But he made damn sure
they were the last.
- So you just flagged me down
to call me an asshole?
- No, I flagged you down
to tell you
That he's not gonna listen
to you,
But he might listen
to somebody else.
- Just heard from louis.
He has the stomach flu,
So I'm gonna have to step in
tonight.
- Oh, that's too bad.
- This wouldn't have anything
to do with him thinking
You're in love with him,
would it?
- No idea.
- Feel like sushi?
- Jeff, you can play
all the games that you want,
But an all-night review
of the evidence
Is a waste of my time.
So why don't you get
a couple of associates?
And I will see you
in the morning.
- Listen, if you don't want
to be here, that's fine.
But I am gonna do this
by myself,
Because I don't have associates
do my work.
- And why is that?
- Do you really want
to know why?
Dalton foster was a con man
who somehow convinced
Terminally ill people to sign
over their insurance policies.
Anyway,
he was my first big case,
So I decided
that I would get some help
Going through the evidence,
just like this.
The help screwed up.
Dalton foster walked.
Six months later,
he pulled the exact same scam.
Only this time, the problem was,
One of his dying clients
had a miraculous recovery.
So one day, dalton came up
from behind her...
And he beat her to death
with an aluminum bat.
So am I glad you're here,
jessica?
Yes.
Did I take advantage of louis?
Absolutely.
I may play games
to get us together,
But I never play games
with a case.
Never.
- You have a minute?
- This must be serious.
- Because you usually
just tell me what to do.
- Remember when you said
if I want you to deliver
A message to mike,
I should come to you directly?
- You want me to get him
to give up.
- If mike doesn't give up
tonight,
Logan is gonna hire someone
to dig up
Everything they can on him.
- That's why you went to gillie.
You had no choice.
- That's not the way
mike saw it.
- You know, you could have come
to me before you did that.
- I'm coming to you now.
- The same way
we bill everything.
Say it took twice as long
as it did.
- [groans]
Okay, I take it back.
My strategy?
My strategy isn't
"knockout punch."
We should've called it
"needle in a haystack."
- Getting frustrated?
- This guy?
This guy does not shut up.
I now know about his bronchitis,
His problems
with his dry cleaner,
But absolutely no explanation
whatsoever
- Oh, you mean besides
being tipped that he invested
In a giant ponzi scheme.
Wait.
- It's a call with an analyst
predicting a downturn
In small-cap stocks
in the next quarter.
Listen.
- The ponzi fund was made up
of small-cap stocks.
- That's a legit reason for him
to have cashed out.
- Exactly what we need to get
the charges dropped.
- And exactly the kind of call
a junior attorney
Might have missed.
- So do you see why we needed
to do this together?
- Yes, I see.
- [chuckles]
What is it?
- [sighs]
I have responsibilities that you
Just don't want to understand.
- No, I don't.
- I am the only woman partner
At this level in the city.
If word got out
that I hired a partner
That I was
in a relationship with...
- What, you'd be disbarred?
- You think this is a joke.
- I think you're making excuses
for keeping me out of your life,
Jessica,
and I'm calling you on it.
- Oh, what the hell is that
supposed to mean?
- It means that I'm making you
a promise, all right,
That no one... no one will ever
find out about us,
So if that's what
you're really afraid of,
If that's what's truly
holding you back,
Then it is off the table.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, so I know we said
We're not supposed to talk
about the deal...
- Why did you lie to me?
- What are you talking about?
- When I asked you
about you and logan,
You said that you ended it.
According to this,
you swore it was him.
- This is my deposition
from his divorce.
You read this?
Why... why would...
- He looked into me.
I looked into him.
- This is looking into me.
- You still haven't answered
the question.
- Mike, I told you the truth.
Logan was trying to patch
things up with his wife,
And he asked me to back
his story, so I did.
- You lied for him.
You loved him that much.
- I told you that I loved him.
- Yeah,
but you didn't tell me that.
And I've been sitting here
all night
Wondering why you wouldn't...
Why wouldn't you tell me that?
- I'm gonna tell you now.
We had an affair.
We fell in love,
and he wanted to marry me,
And I said no,
And then three months later,
he had a change of heart,
And he wanted to get back
with his wife
During his divorce proceedings,
so he asked me to help him,
And I did.
But when he wanted to marry me,
I said no,
Because he wasn't the man
I want to spend my life with.
You are.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- Surprise.
What? What?
- You have to go.
- Logan,
is there somebody at the door?
- Just...
- I am, um...
I'm from pearson hardman,
And I... I had a few files
to bring your husband.
- Where are they?
- They're... they're right here.
Um...
- Get out.
- Allison, what the hell?
- It is 7:30 in the morning.
You think I'm an idiot?
- What are you talking about?
- I know that that's her.
- God, I told you I'm not...
- Stop lying to me.
At least be a man
and admit that that's her.
- I don't even know that girl,
okay?
And you think that if I was
having an affair
That I would have it with a
paralegal from my father's firm?
Rachel.
- I want you to stop
the personal attacks on mike.
- I know.
It sounds terrible, but...
- And it's how the game
is played.
I don't care.
I want you to stop.
- Look, can we talk
about this inside, please?
I understand that you...
- No, look,
you say you're a changed man,
But what you're doing now, it's
not a change for the better.
It's for the worse.
- You told me
this wasn't gonna be a problem.
- And you stood right here
and told me
That you didn't love your wife.
And then three months later,
You asked me to lie for you,
so you could get her back.
- You don't have to stop this
because you're some changed man.
You have to stop this, logan,
because you owe me.
- Okay.
- Louis.
Listen, I was up late,
I haven't had my coffee,
So can we talk about whatever
this is in, like, an hour?
- I'll be quick.
I ran into your enemy
this morning.
You remember adam grieves?
He asked me to tell you
that you guys
Are still on for ball
on Wednesday.
- Everything you told me,
it was bullsh...
You're not trying to get
into my pants.
You're trying to get
into jessica's.
You thought you could move
your way up the ladder,
And you used my friendship
to cozy up to her.
- Louis, that's just not true.
- [shouting]
well, then, what is it?
Why did you lie to me
to get me off this case?
Tell me what I'm missing here,
jeff.
That's what I thought.
- Louis, please...
- For once I let my guard down
and believed that someone
Genuinely liked me
without a hidden agenda.
I will not make that mistake
again.
- I'm here to see mike ross.
- What the hell are you
doing here?
- I came to see you.
- I have a meeting.
- I came to apologize.
- For what?
- For trying to win dirty.
I can't undo what I've already
done, but I can stop doing it.
I don't want to win that way.
- That sounds like something
your publicist
Would tell forbes.
Why don't you tell me
why you're really here?
- You want the truth?
I don't want to hurt rachel.
- Walter.
- I have nothing to say to you.
- Walter, please.
- You have 30 seconds.
- Okay, look, I get it.
I tried to tell you
there's more to the story.
You didn't want to hear it then,
And you don't want
to hear it now.
But you need to hear this.
Whether you like me or not,
I am the only one
in your corner,
And you know it.
- I started this company
with no one to trust but myself.
That's how I go out,
So be it.
We're done.
- Well, I'm sorry to hear that,
Because I'm gonna be
in your corner anyway.
I just bought another 2%
of your stock,
Which means
I'm saving your company
With or without you.
- Time's up.
I don't want to see you again.
- Jeff, it's late.
- It's not about us.
- Woodall.
- It started.
- How many?
- Seven clients,
seven subpoenas,
All coming tomorrow.
- [exhales]
It's time for you
to start earning your money.
[soft rock music]
♪ ♪
- You get me a present?
- It's from mike.
- It's my dad's tapes.
- He said they're yours.
- You got him to back down.
- No, but I got logan
to back off.
- How'd you manage that?
- It's between me and my client.
- You know, you could have come
to me first.
- I'm coming to you now.
♪ ♪