Previously on "Suits"...
Jessica Pearson in court.
I haven't seen that
in a while.
We took over
an Innocence Project case.
He killed my girl!
But I believe that
Leonard Bailey is innocent,
and I'm going to make sure
that he gets the fair trial
that he never had.
By tracking down
some junkie witness?
Maria Gomez never had
a chance to be heard.
Leonard Bailey's
alibi witness is dead.
That doesn't mean
her testimony is.
You want me to testify
to what she told me?
My protégé took the liberty of
drawing up a sworn affidavit.
You can either sign it
or you can lie under oath
that this isn't true.
Are you saying that
this case needs to be re-opened
based on Leonard Bailey having
inadequate representation?
It sure as hell
is our plan now.
You set me up.
I'm gonna make sure
the world knows it.
You can tell the world
anything you want, William.
But you got no proof.
Either way, I suggest
you sign this deal.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
I'm coming home.
- We did it.
- We did.
[rousing rock music]
♪ ♪
Whoa, how many people
are joining us?
Wasn't which Scotch
you'd want,
so I went ahead
and ordered them all.
What if I'm in the mood
for a beer?
You just got out of prison.
You're not in the mood
for a beer.
Yeah, you're right.
Welcome home.
Oh, damn that tastes good.
That's not even the best thing
I have for ya.
- It's an offer letter.
- Take a look at the number.
This is the same money
I made as a junior partner.
Because you are
a junior partner.
The best there is.
And we need you.
I just got out of prison.
I'm not trying to go back.
You're not going back,
because even though
you'll be acting
as a lawyer,
your title's gonna be
"consultant."
Look, Harvey, I appreciate
the gesture, but...
everyone left that firm
because of me.
I'm not gonna do that
to you again.
- Mike--
- No, listen to me.
You've done enough, you don't
have to do this for me.
I'm not doing this for you.
I'm doing it for me.
I miss working with you.
I miss working
with you, too.
Then do me a favor:
just think about it.
If the answer's still no
in a few days,
I won't bring it up again.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
Because you're never here,
that's why!
We've been over this,
Virginia.
I do my part.
That's the problem, Alan.
You think your part is just
getting a paycheck.
A paycheck?
This family lives like
no other family we know.
Jessica, honey--
What's going on?
We're just
having an argument.
It'll be okay.
You don't need to sugarcoat
things for her, Alan.
And you'd know this
if you were ever here
instead of out doing
whatever it is you're doing.
What I'm out doing is saving
lives, and you know it.
Well, maybe if you worked
as hard on our relationship
as you do for your patients,
what's happening
wouldn't be happening.
What's happening?
Your father and I are taking
a little break for a while.
♪ ♪
How long?
I don't know, baby.
I don't know.
♪ ♪
Harvey?
I'd love to chit chat,
but I've got trial in an hour,
so unless it's urgent...
I just wanted to thank you.
For Mike.
You don't have to
thank me for that.
I wanted him out
as much as you did.
I know, but you didn't
have to back me
when it came to Sutter,
and you did.
You would've done
the same for me.
And now that he is out,
let's get back to the business
of keeping this firm alive.
If I were you, I would start
by locking up Jim Reynolds.
- Excuse me?
- What're you talking about?
I'm talking about the fact
that your first client
is shopping for another attorney
behind your back.
Don't tell me,
you're about to pounce.
I'm not trying to poach
your client, Harvey.
But if you can't keep him,
I will.
I appreciate you
coming down here, Robert,
but it's not exactly your style
to give the competition
a heads-up.
When I was kid,
the Yankees and the Red Sox
were the best
damn rivalry ever.
What's your point?
My point is, after Bucky Dent
hit that beautiful
home run in '78,
the Sox fell off a cliff.
It wasn't any fun anymore.
You're saying you don't want
to dominate the division?
I'm saying
you fell off a cliff.
And if you want a chance
to get back in the game...
We better keep Jim Reynolds.
And you better
get on it right now.
Because I may not be
looking to pounce,
but every firm in this city is.
Damn it.
The last thing we need is
Jim Reynolds leaving right now.
What happened to calling,
like he did last time,
instead of going
behind our backs?
I'll tell you what happened.
He's getting pressure
from his board
like he said he would.
And you said we'd
get back on our feet
by the end of the month
and we did.
And that's exactly what
you're gonna tell them.
What do you mean me?
Did you not hear what I just
told you five minutes ago?
I've got trial in an hour.
I don't care.
You've been his lead attorney
since they got here.
If you don't go over yourself,
we're gonna lose him.
- Then take Louis with you.
- Jessica--
Harvey, all you have to do
is open up our books
and show them we're standing
on solid ground.
Or you can make this the
priority and get a continuance.
It's a death row appeal,
Harvey.
How's it gonna look if I start
a trial saying that my business
is more important
than a man's life?
You don't say that.
You come up with
some other reason.
Whatever reason
I come up with,
that prosecutor's gonna make it
look like I don't care.
And I'm not taking that risk.
- Jessica--
- No, enough.
You want to thank me
for having your back with Mike,
then take care of this.
[tense music]
♪ Suits 6x10 ♪
P.S.L.
Original Air Date on September 14, 2016
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Donna, where the hell
is Gretchen?
- I have no idea.
- Well, you need to find her.
Harvey, what's going on?
What do you need her for?
I don't need her,
I need Louis,
and I don't know where he is.
Well, why didn't you
start with that?
He had an emergency meeting with
a client and he ran out of here.
- When?
- Half an hour ago.
I saw him at the elevators
before he left.
You tell him
the second he gets back
I need to talk to him.
Harvey, what's going on?
Jim Reynolds is
threatening to leave.
What?
Harvey, I was there the night
he put Jessica on notice.
If he's leaving, then you don't
have time to wait for Louis.
I know, but if I can't make it
work with Reynolds,
I'm gonna need Louis
the second I get back.
I'm on it.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
What the hell is this?
You know what that is.
It's a subpoena.
I signed your affidavit.
You have what you need.
Did you really think
you wouldn't have to testify
that Bailey had an alibi?
What I didn't think was that
you were going to
paint me as incompetent.
We did what you
should've done 12 years ago.
Represent your client.
And you weren't even
forming sentences
when I handled this case.
Well, I'm forming sentences
now, so instead of being angry,
you should be thanking us for
not bringing an action
against you
on Leonard's behalf.
- Bring it on.
- Georgina, you made a mistake.
We're giving you
the chance to fix it
whether you like it or not.
I don't give a shit
what you think you're doing.
I'm not here to fix it.
I'm here because of this.
Then I'll see you
on the stand.
♪ ♪
Harvey,
what're you doing here?
I'm here to stop you
from breaking your word.
Then I suggest you turn around
and walk out of here
as fast as you can.
Look, just hear me out.
The night you spoke to Jessica,
we'd lost 75% of
our revenue stream.
But since then--
Listen to me.
My taking meetings has nothing
to do with your revenue stream.
Then what the hell's
this about?
It's about the rumors
that you tanked
William Sutter's case.
- I didn't tank shit.
- I told him that.
I don't believe any of it.
Well, it doesn't matter
what you believe, Jim.
Because the board
believes it.
And let me guess,
you're the board.
Donald Mannis.
I'd shake your hand,
but I wouldn't want your
shady ethics
rubbing off on me.
The only thing that's
rubbing off on you, Donald,
is a load of bullshit
from William Sutter.
Your former associate was
in prison with his son-in-law,
and the day Sutter goes down,
your guy gets out.
You may call that bullshit,
but his story adds up to me.
And this company
can't have an attorney
who's willing to turn on
his own client.
♪ ♪
You see what
I'm dealing with?
I only took those meetings
because I'm being pressured
to take those meetings.
I get it.
That asshole wants your job.
He doesn't just want it.
If I don't let you go,
he's gonna get it.
And the one thing that might've
changed that was Jessica
coming in here and showing him
how important we are to her.
You are important to her,
Jim.
But Jessica's
in trial right now.
Then you should've sent
Louis Litt,
because the last thing
that asshole needed to see
when he walked in here was you.
♪ ♪
Your Honor, permission to
treat the witness as hostile.
On what grounds?
The witness hasn't even
said anything yet.
On the grounds that
five minutes ago,
she told me she'd sooner deny
Leonard Bailey
a new trial than to risk
looking incompetent.
Is this true?
Yes.
Then permission granted.
Ms. Casey,
when you were Leonard Bailey's
public defender,
did he tell you that
at the time of the murders,
he was in the apartment of
a woman named Maria Gomez?
Yes.
Which means he not only
had an alibi,
he had a witness that could
testify to it.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Then why in God's name
didn't that witness
ever take the stand?
Because she left town
without telling anyone
right before the trial started.
- Did you try to locate her?
- Yes, I did.
- How hard did you look?
- I did my best.
The truth is, you didn't
look for her at all, did you?
That's not true.
I did everything
I could to try to find her.
But you didn't.
And if you had,
there would have been
an alibi witness
that would've told the jury that
he couldn't have possibly
have committed those murders.
That witness was a drug addict
with a prior conviction,
and she would have been
eviscerated on the stand.
Then why did you
try to find her at all?
♪ ♪
Let me suggest an answer.
You did try to find her,
because you knew if you did,
Leonard Bailey would be
found innocent.
But you dropped the ball.
Leonard Bailey
went to death row.
And you'd rather
let him stay there
than to admit the truth.
♪ ♪
Ms. Casey, in your estimation,
was Leonard Bailey innocent?
Objection, Your Honor,
calls for a conclusion.
Your Honor, they opened
the door to this
when they put her on the stand,
and no one is more qualified to
answer than his own attorney.
I'll allow it.
Ms. Casey?
I thought Leonard Bailey
was guilty.
And I still do.
♪ ♪
Louis, the next time you have
an emergency meeting,
you better clear it with me.
I'll keep that in mind
for the future, Harvey.
But the reason I had
an emergency meeting was you.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Jensen Analytics heard a rumor
you tanked Sutter's case
and they're threatening
to walk.
Shit.
What'd you tell them?
What do you think
I told them?
I told them William Sutter's
a lying son of a bitch
who'll do or say anything
to get what he wants.
What did they say?
They said if Jessica's
oldest client's leaving,
why should they stay?
Goddamn it.
Harvey, if they think that,
then it's just a matter of time
until all our clients
think that.
Which means we need to get
Jim Reynolds to stay.
What're we gonna
tell Jessica?
We're gonna tell her if
she doesn't do something
about Reynolds soon,
she's not gonna have a firm
to come back to.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Rachel, listen to me,
it went as well as it could've.
You don't have to
look so worried.
How can I not look worried?
Mike, that woman said that
she thought he was guilty
and the prosecutor
got it on record.
And Jessica got it on record
that she was incompetent
before he did that.
The jury heard it.
Yeah, but you saw the jury
as well as I did.
They're not convinced.
Put Leonard on the stand.
Mike, we haven't
prepped him yet.
He's not ready.
Rachel, just listen to me.
When I was on trial,
I didn't just give the jury
a reason to let me go.
You gave them a reason
to want to let you go.
Exactly, and it turns out,
they were going to.
And I was guilty.
What do you think they're gonna
do for a man
who's actually innocent?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
What are you doing here?
I needed to see you.
Me too.
Had a rough day.
Got some bad news.
You're a sight
for sore eyes.
Louis...
What's wrong?
I had a doctor's appointment
this morning.
Well, whatever it is,
we can deal with it together.
Modern medicine is a wonder.
There's almost nothing
that they can't--
I'm pregnant.
Oh, my God.
I mean, I knew the Litt sperm
were powerful,
but this has to be
some kind of record.
Louis.
Don't tell me.
It's his.
Louis, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean for this
to happen.
I'm usually so careful.
I don't care.
Louis, I don't think
you know what you're saying.
No, I know exactly
what I'm saying.
I love you.
And if being with you means
raising another man's child,
then I'll raise
another man's child.
You say that now,
but it hasn't sunk in yet.
That's not true.
I'm gonna say
the same thing tomorrow
and the day after that
and the day after that.
Then say it to me then.
But it has been a long day
for both of us.
And I think we should
both just get some sleep.
Tara, please
come home with me.
Good night, Louis.
♪ ♪
Jessica, we have a problem.
Not what I want to hear
on my way out, Harvey.
Then you're not gonna want to
hear that you need to be at
Jim Reynolds' next
board meeting.
That doesn't sound like
you put out the fire.
What I couldn't put out
were the rumors
that we threw Sutter's case
to get Mike out.
Are you kidding me?
That's what this is about?
Jessica, it's not Jim.
He's loyal
and always has been.
Don't tell me.
It's Donald Mannis
using this shit
as a power play.
Exactly.
And I walked right into it,
because I showed up
without you.
Son of a bitch.
Jessica,
the only thing we can do
is hold onto Reynolds
and hope the others
fall in line.
All right, set up a meeting
for Tuesday morning.
The trial should
be over by then.
But Harvey, it won't make
a bit of difference
if Sutter's out there telling
the world we're the kind of
lawyers that throw cases.
You do what you have to--
you shut that man the hell up.
♪ ♪
Who's he?
Leonard,
this is my fiancé, Mike.
He used to work at the firm
and he has an idea.
Let Leonard tell his story.
That's risky.
We're giving them
the chance to paint him
as a drug user
and a criminal.
They're already doing that.
And they're not gonna stop.
Leonard, this is as much
your call as it is ours.
What do you want to do?
I wanted to say my piece
last time,
but that lady didn't let me,
so please,
put me on that stand and give me
a chance to say it now.
Okay.
Is the defense ready to call
their next witness?
The defense calls
Leonard Bailey, Your Honor.
We'd also like to request
that Ms. Zane
be permitted to
question the witness.
Objection,
Ms. Zane is a law student,
not an admitted member
of the bar.
She's also been
a practicing paralegal
for the last eight years.
I don't care if she was the
President of the United States.
She's not a lawyer and they're
laying grounds for a mistrial.
Your Honor, it's obvious
Mr. Bailey's first attorney
didn't care about him at all.
But Ms. Zane fought to have
this case taken on,
and she's the reason
we're even here today.
Which is why Mr. Bailey is
simply asking
that she be with him now.
So unless the prosecution
is so unsure of its case
that he can't handle
a law student,
we ask that she be allowed
to question the witness.
Prosecution withdraws
its objection.
Then your request is granted.
♪ ♪
[knocks]
Harvey.
I thought I might
get a visit from you.
And I thought I told you
to keep your mouth shut.
Well, I stopped taking advice
from you when you sold me out.
Now get the hell off my property
before I call the police.
There's only one problem
with that, William.
This isn't
your property anymore.
What the hell
are you talking about?
At 8:00 a.m.
tomorrow morning,
it's being seized
by the government.
Bullshit.
This is a Homestead state.
Turns out,
I did a little checking,
and you closed on this house
before you sold the last one,
which means they can take it
and they're going to.
What do you want?
You're gonna repair
my reputation.
And you're gonna start by
calling every member
of Jim Reynolds' board
and telling them that
you spread those rumors about me
because you're a lying
son of a bitch.
And what makes you think
they'll believe me?
Because you're a hell of
a salesman, William,
when you're motivated,
and I'm pretty sure that when
you get out of prison,
you're gonna be motivated
not to live on the street.
♪ ♪
I was getting high
with my friend Maria.
I won't deny that.
But all I did to those kids
was try and help them.
Help them how?
Me and Maria got hungry so we
went to get something to eat.
That's when we saw them.
Lying there on the sidewalk...
with blood all over 'em.
Maria, she, uh...
she freaked out,
But I wasn't thinking,
so I just ran up.
I mean, they were kids,
you know?
They--they were in trouble.
So then what happened?
Well, I yelled
for Maria to get help.
But the boy...
he was already gone.
And the girl, she just kept
asking for help, over and over.
I stayed with her.
And then the police came.
And the next thing you know,
I was being charged
with murder.
Leonard...
you were married before
you went to prison, weren't you?
My wife, she left me
two years after I went away.
She said she couldn't
handle it anymore.
And what about
your children?
Do you still see them?
I haven't seen my son
in over ten years.
And I hadn't seen Maya
until you found her
and told her I was innocent
and you were going to prove it.
That's her right there.
♪ ♪
Leonard, is there something
that you would
like to say to her?
I lost 12 years
for a crime I didn't commit.
♪ ♪
But I won't regret any of it
if it ends up being the thing
that got me clean
and reunited with you.
♪ ♪
Because if I died
with you believing
your father did this...
She doesn't think that.
She knows that you didn't
hurt those kids.
♪ ♪
I have no further questions,
Your Honor.
♪ ♪
Your Honor,
we reserve the right
to cross examine
the defendant.
But for now, since he's claiming
he knows what it feels like
to be an aggrieved father,
I'd like to call Victor Forrest
to the stand.
♪ ♪
Thank you for agreeing
to do this, Mr. Forrest.
I know how difficult
it must be for you.
Would you mind telling us a
little bit about your daughter?
What can I say?
Kim was our everything--
she was sweet, kind.
Incredible sense of humor.
She played soccer,
didn't she?
Used to watch her run up
and down the field.
Never got tired,
she just kept running,
big smile on her face.
She had such
a beautiful smile.
It's obvious you loved her
very much.
I didn't just love her.
I tried to protect her.
I warned her about boys.
Drugs.
And I said, "If you're ever
in trouble, you call me."
And the thing that gets me is,
she did call that night.
Not to say she was in trouble.
To say she was coming home.
But she never did
make it home.
No, and I don't care what some
junkie witness was gonna say.
They found that animal standing
over my little girl's body.
Her blood all over him.
He took away my everything
in one night.
And he did it for money
to buy more drugs.
And how do you feel about
the speech he gave to the jury?
He talked about getting
a second chance with his family.
What about my family?
Our lives were
ruined that night.
My little girl never even
got a first chance.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
♪ ♪
Mr. Forrest...
did you actually see
Leonard Bailey
kill your daughter?
Of course I didn't,
but that doesn't mean--
No further questions,
Your Honor.
♪ ♪
Donna, can I talk to you
for a second?
Well, since you asked so
nicely, I'll even give you two.
I have some bad news
I have to give Louis,
and since he and I are finally
in a good place...
You want to know how to
break it to him
without blowing things up again.
Yeah.
How bad is it?
It's not good.
Then do what
you just did with me.
Approach him with respect,
pull the Band-Aid off,
and if you have that
same look on your face
as you do right now,
he'll send you on your way
with a handshake.
Thanks, Donna.
Stu?
It was nice having you here.
♪ ♪
What?
You should've seen yourself
thunder away at Kendrick today.
You were amazing.
And if I were Dawson or Downey
and I had to choose between you
and your father
to represent me on this,
I'd choose you any day of
the week and twice on Sunday.
What're you talking about?
I'm talking about
"A Few Good Men."
Mike, I don't have time
for movie quotes right now.
I'm not trying to quote
a movie, Rachel,
I'm trying to tell you that
it doesn't matter
what that girl's father said.
You're still in this,
and you were
great up there.
Wait a minute,
her father.
What about him?
He called Maria
a junkie witness.
How would he even know
that she was a drug user?
What do you mean?
The same way I would know.
Leonard and his public defender
said so on the stand.
No, but he used those exact
words when he came at me
trying to get me
to drop this whole thing.
- He came at you?
- It's fine, I handled it.
But he did try to
intimidate me.
And a man who would
intimidate you might do
the same thing
to Maria Gomez.
Yeah, but I don't think
he intimidated her.
I think he did the opposite.
What're you saying?
I'm saying I think we need to
pay that man a visit.
[dramatic music]
Louis, do you
have a minute?
Tell you the truth, Stu,
I kind of have
a full plate right now,
so unless it's a matter
of life and death,
I'd rather it wait.
This can't wait.
We have to move out.
What do you mean,
"move out"?
We're relocating.
I wanted to tell you in person
so there's no hard feelings.
Oh, bullshit,
you can't do this.
Louis, I don't
have a choice.
Sutter went bankrupt
two days ago,
and they owed us
under their contract.
They're offering us their space
to cover their obligations
and I have to say yes
by tomorrow.
You wouldn't even have
those obligations, Stu,
if it weren't for us.
I know that,
but I can't tell my bosses
I'm passing on a fortune
in free rent
'cause you guys
did me a solid.
Well, then you tell them
you have a lease
and I'm gonna
sue your goddamn ass.
Louis, there's a clause
in the lease that gives me
a 30-day out
and you know it.
Stu, please.
You cannot do this
to us now.
Not tonight.
I'm sorry, Louis.
I hate to hang you out to dry
and if I could help you
in another way, I would.
But we can't
rent this space.
♪ ♪
[glass shatters]
I have nothing to say to you.
Please, Mr. Forrest,
you confronted me
when I didn't
want to talk to you,
and I gave you the respect
to hear what you had to say.
You can at least hear
what we have to say.
You got 60 seconds,
then I'm calling the police.
Go ahead,
but when they get here,
we'll tell them all about how
you sent Maria Gomez away
so that she couldn't testify.
- That's insane.
- Is it?
Because a woman who was never
in the court record
as a drug user went to a rehab
facility she could never afford
and you know enough about her
to call her a druggie
to my face a month ago.
That's not proof of anything.
And that's not the answer
of an innocent man.
Look, Mr. Forrest,
I can't begin to understand
what you've been through,
but right now, the wrong man
is sitting on death row
because of what you did.
- I didn't do shit.
- Please.
Can't you imagine what this has
been like for Leonard Bailey,
what his life has looked like
for the past past 12 years?
The only thing I want to
imagine is what my life's
gonna be like after that man
takes his final breath.
Your time is up.
♪ ♪
Louis, is everything okay?
What do you mean?
I mean, I saw
what happened with Stu.
I know he's leaving,
but it's gonna be okay.
Harvey's gonna fix things
with Jim Reynolds,
we're gonna get
more clients--
Tara's pregnant.
It's not mine.
What did you tell her?
I told her I'm going to stay
with her and support her
every way I can,
because I'm in love with her.
And what did she say?
She said we need to
sleep on it
because it hasn't sunk in
for me.
Then what were you
so upset about?
What if she's saying that
because she can't
decided what she's gonna do?
- Louis--
- How do I know
she didn't wake up
this morning
and decide to
run back to him?
That's not what's going on.
This is a huge decision
and she wants to make sure
that you're in it
for the long haul.
Donna, I would never
go back on my word.
That's not true
and you know it.
You make impulsive decisions
and you go back on them
all the time.
- This is different.
- How?
Because it's a baby.
I would never do that
to a baby.
I hear you,
but all I'm saying is,
don't do something rash.
Because this isn't something
you can change your mind about.
♪ ♪
You got to be kidding.
You went to see the victim's
father without telling me?
Jessica, we didn't have time
and we had to know.
And like you taught Harvey
and Harvey taught me,
it's better to ask forgiveness
than permission.
You're not asking
for either one.
You're asking me to accuse the
man of obstruction of justice
in open court.
Jessica, we looked
the man in the eye,
and I'm telling you,
he did it.
I don't give a shit
if he did it or not.
There's no way on the planet
we can prove it.
We don't have to prove it if
you can break him on the stand.
Are you out of
your goddamn mind?
- It's the only way--
- It's not the only way.
And I'm not doing it.
What're you so afraid of?
Don't you dare
say that to me.
That man's life is in my hands
because your fiancée
told him not to
take the deal.
And if we attack the father
and it backfires,
we lose the jury for good
and his life is over.
♪ ♪
Jessica, this guy wants to
tell everyone the truth
because he's proud of it.
You just need to lead him right
where he's dying to go.
And what if
I can't do that?
Mike has something
that might help.
What're you talking about?
I'm asking if you've seen
the movie "A Few Good Men."
♪ ♪
- Donna, what're you doing here?
- Waiting for you.
Because I've been calling you
and texting you
and you obviously haven't
checked your phone.
I haven't checked my phone
because I've been going to every
client we have reassuring them
that Sutter's gonna recant
his bullshit and Jim Reynolds
isn't going anywhere.
Yeah, well, if you don't
do something soon,
you're gonna have to
recant that.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Jim Reynolds called.
They moved his board meeting
to tomorrow.
♪ ♪
- We need to talk.
- I don't believe this.
I'm about to give the most
important cross examination
in my life
and you're showing up now?
Jessica, we left you
a dozen messages.
Jim Reynolds' board
moved up the meeting.
Then tell them to push it back
because I can't go right now.
Goddamn it,
don't you get it?
They moved it up so they
can get it over with.
They're gonna fire Reynolds
and they're fire us.
And he made it clear that
you need to be there.
Jessica, Louis is right.
If we show up without you,
we may as well
not show up at all.
Is the defense
ready to proceed?
Your Honor, I'd like to ask
for a half-day continuance.
On what grounds?
It has to do with
my law firm's survival.
Then let her associate take
the reins for half a day.
She's not ready for this.
Well, she was ready
for the other thing.
That was different
and the prosecution knows it.
What I know is whatever's
happening with your firm
is not my concern.
So either let your associate
handle this
or handle it yourself.
But this case
is moving forward.
♪ ♪
Do whatever you can.
I'm not abandoning Leonard to
some corporate power struggle.
This isn't a goddamn
power struggle.
We're gonna go
out of business.
I can't think about that
right now, Louis.
That man's life
is on the line,
and I'm not hanging him
out to dry.
Ms. Pearson,
are you ready to proceed?
We are, Your Honor.
Defense would like to recall
Victor Forrest to the stand.
♪ ♪
Jessica, what a surprise.
You never come to my office.
When did you get home
from school?
This morning.
Oh, if I'd known
you were coming--
I didn't want you
to know, Dad.
I have some news.
What is it?
Is everything okay?
I got into Harvard Law
next year.
And I'm going.
What?
I'm going to be a lawyer.
What happened to our plan of
you becoming surgeon?
That was never our plan, Dad.
It was always yours.
Don't you speak to me
like that.
I'm not speaking to you
like anything.
I'm telling you the truth.
You want the truth?
Doctors save lives
and lawyers are nothing but
power-hungry bottom-feeders.
They don't have to be
and I'm not going to be.
- And I raised you better.
- No, Dad.
You raised me to do
what inspires me.
And what inspires me
is to be a lawyer.
You go to that school,
you're gonna get infected with
their lawyer mind-set
and when you come out,
you're not gonna
give a shit about
your fellow man.
If you think that,
then you should've
spent more time with me.
Because you don't
know me at all.
♪ ♪
Ms. Pearson?
Ms. Pearson, are you ready?
Mr. Forrest...
so many lives
were ruined that night.
Your daughter's,
her boyfriend's, yours.
Is there a question?
Someone had to pay for that,
didn't they?
Yeah, they sure as hell did.
Is that why you paid
for Maria Gomez
to go to rehab
to keep her from testifying
at Mr. Bailey's trial?
What?
Objection, Your Honor, she's
putting the victim on trial.
My client is the victim here.
Ms. Pearson, you better back
this up fast.
Then ask the witness
to answer my question.
I never even heard of that
woman until yesterday.
Your Honor, the defense would
like to admit into evidence
the admissions form for
an Allison Dobsen
into the Pathways Rehabilitation
Center from 12 years ago.
Wha--who is that?
She was Maria Gomez's
roommate.
And I'm gonna put her
on the stand.
No, that's can't be.
No--you can't do that.
And she's going to say
that Maria told her
that she felt terrible about
abandoning her friend.
- Objection, hearsay.
- No, she won't.
Overruled.
And she's going to testify
that you paid
for Maria to be there.
I had nothing
to do with anything.
That's not what
she's going to say.
- I don't care, she's lying.
- Why would she lie?
She just wants to put
the record straight.
- The record is straight.
- Not according to her roommate.
- She's lying!
- Objection, badgering.
How could you know?
Because Maria Gomez didn't
have a roommate!
♪ ♪
What did you just say?
Yes, I paid for her.
Because she's a junkie who'd say
anything to get him
out of what he did,
so I got her out of the way
'cause he did it.
- Mr. Forrest--
- He did it!
♪ ♪
Your Honor...
the defense asks that
Mr. Bailey be exonerated
and his sentence be commuted
immediately.
Mr. Marsden?
We have no objections,
Your Honor.
Then the jury
may be excused.
And Mr. Bailey...
you're free.
[gavel bangs]
[uplifting music]
I can't believe it.
We did it.
♪ ♪
I can't thank you enough.
You don't have to thank me,
Leonard.
You just have to walk out
that door.
♪ ♪
That was one hell
of a cross.
Well, I'd like to say
it was no big deal,
but I'd be lying if
I didn't say
it was the most satisfying
moment of my entire career.
What's this?
Got a call from
Jim Reynolds.
He said that if you didn't
show today,
they were gonna
sign with me.
And we both know
you didn't show.
You want to merge?
I said all that stuff about
rivals because I didn't want to
say this in front of Harvey.
But I know you tanked
the Sutter case for Mike
and I can see what
you've been doing for Rachel.
So this isn't just
professional.
For me, it's personal.
- Robert--
- Jessica,
you got to knock down
the mountain.
Without help, you're not gonna
be able get back up.
Please, take my hand.
I appreciate your offer
more than you know, Robert.
But I've had my name first
for too long.
I can't go back
to having it last.
Jessica, if you don't do this,
you're not gonna have it
anywhere.
Then so be it.
Besides, we both know lawyers
are nothing but
power-hungry
bottom-feeders, anyway.
♪ ♪
You two don't look like
Jessica Pearson.
Then again, it doesn't really
matter,
because in 15 minutes, your firm
is no longer going to be
in the employ of this company.
Maybe not.
But while we are,
I think you're gonna need
one more chair.
What're you
talking about?
We're talking about your
brand new largest shareholder.
What shareholder?
Hey, guy.
Stu Buzzini.
This one at the head of
the table looks good to me.
[clears throat]
Look, I don't care who you are
or how many shares you bought.
You're not a member
of this board.
No, but as of next quarter,
I will be.
So either you keep
these two as your lawyers
and Jim Reynolds
as your CEO,
or at our next meeting,
you'll be out on your ass.
You can't do this to me.
That's where you're wrong,
Donald.
We can and we did.
Because he just
bought up your company
and you messed with the wrong
goddamn Marine.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Yeah, what are you
talkin' about?
- He's quoting "A Few Good Men."
- Finally, somebody gets me.
- I got your back, bro.
- Don't bro me, dude.
- You got it, Chief.
- Hey, can I get in on this?
Both: No.
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
[keys clatter]
♪ ♪
Hey.
I got you a present.
[giggles]
You didn't have to
do that.
I know.
I know we're not supposed to
take pictures in there,
but I couldn't help myself.
This is unbelievable.
No.
What you did for that man
is unbelievable.
[poignant acoustic music]
♪ ♪
Harvey offered me a job.
Back to the firm...
as a consultant.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know.
♪ ♪
What is that, a cup of tea?
Just a moment of
quiet reflection.
Well, to hell with that.
This is a moment
for celebration.
That's right.
'Cause a man's life wasn't
the only thing saved today.
Don't tell me.
You managed to lock down
Jim Reynolds after all.
We did.
The firm is safe, Jessica.
Thank you.
But it's not my firm
anymore.
It's yours.
What do you mean, "ours"?
I mean,
I've decided to step down.
- What?
- Jessica--
Listen,
somewhere along the way,
I forgot why I became a lawyer
in the first place.
And it wasn't just to fight
for money and power.
It was to fight
for something more.
Bullshit, you're not fighting
for something more,
you're running away.
- Louis--
- No.
We bust our ass to
save this goddamn place,
she decides to up and leave?
We committed to this.
Louis, she isn't
doing this to you.
She's doing it for herself.
I don't give a shit
why she's doing it.
It's selfish and self-serving
and it's not gonna happen.
Do you think I want to
goddamn want do this, Louis?
I have to do this.
You can't just throw this all
away after we gave
everything to save it.
That's enough.
Louis, after the partners left,
we swore we were
gonna dedicate every ounce
of blood, sweat,
and tears we had
to this place.
But we didn't.
Harvey and I focused on
getting Mike out,
Jessica and Rachel focused on
Leonard Bailey,
and you focused on
finding love in your life.
[stirring music]
- That's not true.
- Yes it is.
♪ ♪
I'm not ready to
give up the firm.
No one's saying you have to
give up the firm, Louis.
You just have to
let me go.
♪ ♪
You sure about this?
Tell you the truth,
for first time in my life,
I'm not sure about anything,
and it scares the shit
out of me.
But I'm sure
I have to do this.
♪ ♪
To Pearson Specter Litt.
All: To Pearson Specter Litt.
♪ ♪
[knocks]
You busy?
Of course not.
I know you told me
to sleep on it.
I didn't know if that meant
take a day, two days.
I've never really been in
this position before.
- Louis, I'm sorry--
- Here's the thing.
I tried to sleep on it,
and all I could do was picture
a life without you
and your beautiful
unborn baby
and it just made me
crazy to think
I wouldn't be part a of it.
But Tara, you need to know that
I am not gonna say yes
today and change my mind
tomorrow.
And I don't know how to
give you that reassurance
without asking you
something first.
[poignant music]
Oh, my God, Louis.
♪ ♪
Tara Messer.
Will you marry me?
♪ ♪
Yes, Louis.
I'll marry you.
♪ ♪
Oh.
Jessica.
What're you doing here?
I wanted to talk to you
before you left for Chicago.
I'm glad, but I wouldn't have
left without saying good-bye.
I didn't just come here
to say good-bye.
I came to see what you think
about me coming with you.
What about the firm?
I'm leaving the firm.
Jessica, if you're walking
away from everything for me--
No, I'm not doing this
just for you.
I'm doing this for me.
♪ ♪
I don't want to be
a corporate lawyer anymore.
So, if you don't want me to come
to Chicago with you,
I won't.
But I'm walking away
no matter what.
♪ ♪
Then walk away with me.
You gonna be okay?
She was my mentor.
♪ ♪
But yeah,
I'm gonna be okay.
♪ ♪
You want to be alone?
No.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man