When you work here, you
don't think about home
- and families and babies.
- That's not fair.
He couldn't have known he was
gonna have a baby a year...
Let me tell you something, Stephanie.
Maybe you don't know how babies are made,
because when people are trying,
they know they're trying!
And just because no one
ever wants to try with you
doesn't give you the right
to tell me how to run my associates!
I got an offer for more money
than I'll see my whole life,
and you want me to turn
it down based on a feeling
that whatever happened to
Chris happened to other people?
- You're dating your therapist.
- I don't need a lecture from you, Louis.
Does Donna have any idea
about the two of you?
No, she doesn't,
and for right now, I'd
like to keep it that way.
Harvey, is there something
that you're not telling me?
'Cause it seems like you've
been different lately.
We win this, you're gonna be Andy Dufresne
sitting on a beach in Mexico
with a bank account full of cash.
I already make a nice living in here.
I was thinking maybe some of that
money might go to your daughter.
I wasn't lying about
working a case with Oliver.
I just didn't tell you which one.
- The prison one?
- Yeah.
- This is a fireable offense.
- Harvey isn't gonna fire me.
Yeah, but maybe he should.
What is your word worth?
The way things are going, it's
not gonna be worth very much.
[dramatic music]
Hey.
How long have you been up?
A while.
I've been thinking about what
you said to me last night.
Mike, I didn't mean to be so harsh.
No, you were right.
My word does mean everything to me...
which is why I'm gonna keep helping Oliver.
What?
When I gave my word to Harvey, I meant it.
But before that, I gave
my word to Oscar Reyes.
And I'm sorry, but I-I can't back out now.
Okay. [sighs]
So you're just gonna live your
life keeping secrets again?
- This isn't like that.
- How is it not like that?
You're keeping this from Harvey.
And Harvey kept things from Jessica.
Look at how that turned out.
I tell Harvey now, and it's
the same as if he catches me.
The case gets tossed, and all of the people
we're trying to help keep getting abused.
It's the same as before.
No, Rachel, this is not the
same as when I was a fraud.
And I'll tell you something else...
I used to have trouble sleeping at night,
but I sleep like a baby now
because I am helping these people.
I'm sorry, but that's
the word that I'm keeping.
Good morning.
Hey. Did you sleep well?
If you consider eight hours
of bliss sleeping well,
then, yes, I slept very well.
But now I have to go.
- Wait.
- Harvey, I have patients.
I know, but I wanted to get
your opinion on something.
What have you done this time?
I haven't told Donna we're
seeing each other yet.
Why not?
Come on, you know my history with her.
We're working together.
I just promoted her.
That's more an excuse
than a reason, isn't it?
I don't want to create a
problem when there isn't one.
And who says there has to be one?
There doesn't have to be one, but...
Harvey, first of all, you
may be underestimating her.
- I mean, Donna's a big girl.
- Paula...
And second of all, if I'm wrong
and you're not underestimating her,
then you're only gonna cause both of you
a lot more trouble down
the road when she finds out.
'Cause, Harvey, she is gonna find out.
So you're telling me to tell her?
You already know what you need to do.
You just asked me because sometimes
we need to hear it from someone else.
♪ ♪
They didn't tell me you brought a sidekick.
Frank, this is Oliver Grady. He's
the one that's trying the case.
Good for him.
I still don't know what
you're doing back here.
I already told you everything I know.
Not everything. It's time you
gave us the name of your source.
Uh-uh.
The deal is that money goes
into my daughter's account,
then you get the name.
- What the hell is this?
- It's a down payment.
Down payment? I don't think so.
- I want the whole thing.
- And if you think
we're giving you half a million without
a name, then you're out of your mind.
Then we are at what they call an impasse,
because I'm not giving you
that name without that money.
And there isn't gonna be any money
if the judge dismisses this case.
What the hell is he talking about?
He's talking about the fact that the other
side filed a motion to dismiss this thing.
Goes to court tomorrow.
If you don't give me the name of
your source, it's gonna get tossed.
Bullshit it's gonna get tossed.
I already admitted to
you I took part in it.
It's not enough.
Why is that not enough? You got my word.
We got no corroboration of your word.
What's to say you didn't make up
this whole thing when I came in here?
Then go to the goddamn prosecutor
I went to seven years ago.
She's got it all on record.
- I thought she didn't pursue this case.
- Then you didn't hear me right.
She pursued it. She just
didn't want to see it through.
Ask her if I'm telling the truth.
In the meantime, keep your pocket change,
'cause you're not getting shit from me.
♪ ♪
♪ See the money, wanna
stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece
of pie for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna
know how it feel ♪
see what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean
pie, I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so
busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Hey, buddy.
Louis, I was just making a cup of coffee.
I'm not taking any time off, I swear.
Whoa, Brian, it's okay to take
a break every now and then.
- It is?
- Yeah, absolutely.
In fact, coffee preparation
is very important.
Yeah. Actually, making coffee
is one of my favorite hobb...
That's great. Listen to me,
I need to ask you something.
The other day when I
said those things to you
about taking time off,
I mean, I don't even know
- if you remember it.
- Like it was yesterday.
Well, in that case I was just wondering...
how bad was I?
You weren't that bad.
Good.
Now, would you be willing
to swear to that in court?
- What? Why?
- No reason.
Truth is, my recollection
is exactly the same as yours.
You asked for a couple days
off, and I gave it to you.
See, I even wrote it in my diary.
"Gave Brian two days
off. Felt good about it."
It looks like you just wrote that today.
- What makes you say that?
- It has today's date on top.
I just wrote that down to
remember today's conversation.
Can I go back to work now?
Yep, just make sure you
have the affidavit on my desk
as soon as possible.
Thanks for seeing us on such
short notice, Ms. Randolph.
I have to say, when I
heard the name Frank Gallo,
my interest was piqued. What's this about?
We're representing a class of prisoners
suing Reform Corporation
for abusive practices.
We're here to confirm that
Frank Gallo came to see you
seven years ago and admitted to
being involved in a conspiracy.
Yeah, he came to me
offering to be an informant
in exchange for protection from
what was going on in Lambert.
And did you believe what he told you?
Of course I believed him. He was beaten up,
and he'd been in the infirmary
for two goddamn weeks.
Well, if you believed him, why the
hell didn't you pursue the case?
I did pursue it. I ran it up the flagpole,
and it came back down
like a concrete block.
No one gives a shit about prisoners
or the way they're treated.
So, instead, he offered to
inform on his fellow inmates,
and then he used that to
get himself transferred.
Exactly. Now, if you don't mind.
Well, Danielle, in fact, I do mind.
You see, I do give a shit
about how prisoners are treated,
which means you are gonna tell the court
exactly what you just told us.
Did you not hear what I just said?
It came back down on me
like a concrete block.
This is my career. I...
I am not gonna go on
record and jeopardize it.
Well, then this is
gonna go one of two ways.
You give us your records,
and we submit them quietly...
Or we subpoena your records under
the Freedom of Information Act
and put you on the stand.
And seeing as you're afraid
of ruining your career,
I suggest you go with option A.
[dramatic music]
You're a couple of little shits.
Good, you're here.
Listen, there's something I've
been wanting to talk to you about.
- Harvey, it's gonna have to wait.
- Donna, it's important.
Frank Gallo left a message
for you a few minutes ago.
- What did he say?
- He said you and Mike
better not be trying to screw him
over again, or you're gonna regret it.
Harvey, what's he talking about?
I don't know, but I'm sure
as hell gonna find out.
♪ ♪
What the hell are you
doing with Frank Gallo?
Harvey...
Don't pretend like you don't know.
He just left me a message asking me to
make sure that you don't fuck him over.
I told you, I'm working on a
Brooklyn Housing Authority case.
Gallo is from Brooklyn. He knows people.
And don't tell me he's making
you pay for his information.
Yes, he is, and I'm gonna pay him.
Mike, odds are he doesn't know jack shit
and he's just using you to get money.
No, I looked into it, all right?
What he told me checks out. He's
on the right side of this thing.
You're telling me he's all
of a sudden Mother Teresa?
This guy tried to kill you!
I know that. Look, I'm
not saying he's a saint.
I'm saying that I know what I'm doing.
Don't you get it?
A guy like Gallo finds
people to get revenge on.
He thinks about it and thinks about it,
and the only way to survive that
is to stay out of his mind
and let him find someone else.
Maybe you're right, but
I already promised him
something for his information,
and if I back out of that now,
I'm gonna end up on the top of his list.
Does Rachel know about this?
♪ ♪
- No.
- Then you better hope
Gallo doesn't leave her a message
the same way he left me one.
♪ ♪
Staring out the window, Louis?
That's a sign that something's going on.
Nothing's going on, Rachel.
Then why exactly did you make Brian
Altman relive that horrible day?
- Which horrible day?
- The one where you
treated him like shit because
you were losing your mind.
That day.
You want to know what's going on?
I'm being sued. That's what's going on.
- By Brian?
- No, by Stephanie.
For sexual harassment? Louis, this is bad.
- I know what it is, Rachel.
- Well, then we need to talk
about how you're gonna handle it.
No, we need to talk about
how you're gonna handle it.
Louis, that's not a good idea.
It's the only good idea.
You need to go over there right
now and put an end to this.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
Because I had a run-in with
Stephanie after you did,
and then I had another run-in
with her after Donna fired her.
She's not gonna listen to me.
It is sexual harassment, Rachel.
I cannot have it on my record.
Someone needs to convince
her to let this go,
and it needs to be a lawyer I can trust,
but it also needs to be someone
who's close to her level,
or she's gonna feel attacked.
Then I think I have the perfect choice.
Katrina.
I take it Louis got my lawsuit.
He did, and I'm here to ask
why you're bringing it now.
Because the things
you're alleging he said...
Alleging he said?
Wow. I guess it's lawyer
first, friend second.
That's not fair. I'm only
here because we're friends.
And because you wanted
to convince me to forget
that Pearson Specter Litt ruined my career.
Stephanie, I know you got fired,
but this lawsuit could destroy Louis.
Let me get this straight.
The woman who convinced
me to leave a good job
for one where I was treated terribly,
sexually harassed, and then fired is
now asking me for a personal favor?
Yes, I am.
♪ ♪
Well, I'm not in the mood to grant one.
So you can tell Louis
I will see him in court.
Stephanie, the woman I knew
at Rand Kaldor Zane wouldn't do this.
Please... [sighs]
tell me what's going on so I can help.
♪ ♪
I heard people here talking,
and they said that I got fired
because I couldn't hack it.
Well, that's not true,
and I won't have them thinking it is.
Then close that door and sit down,
because I'm betting that
we can work out a deal
right now that shows anyone
who's ever underestimated
you just how strong you are.
Alex, have you seen Donna by any chance?
- What?
- Donna. Have you seen her?
- I need to tell her something.
- I don't know, Harvey.
I don't have time to track your
former secretary's every damn move.
What the hell's wrong with you?
I'll tell you what's wrong with me.
Masterson Construction's
pissed about this prison case.
Still? You handed it off like they asked.
No, they wanted the thing
gone, not handed off,
and now it's turned into a class action,
and it's going to trial tomorrow.
Listen to me, it's not your
job to make this thing go away.
Harvey, I'm their attorney.
They had a problem,
they wanted it fixed, and I didn't fix it.
Bullshit, you got
Pearson Specter to drop it
like a hot potato. That's
all you could've done.
No, what I could have done
was kill the whole damn thing.
And since I didn't, they found
some inmate at another prison
to break the case wide open,
which is why I just had
to eat a ton of shit.
- What did you just say?
- I said they found a witness
at another prison, and now I'm
gonna lose my goddamn client.
Where you going?
Like I said, I need to find Donna.
♪ ♪
I want to know right now,
do you know where Mike is?
- No, I don't.
- You don't know where,
or you don't know what
case he's working on?
I don't know either one,
but if you calm down,
then maybe I can help you find him.
No, Rachel, I don't want help finding him.
In fact, I don't want you telling him
I was looking for him at all.
♪ ♪
- Oscar Reyes?
- Yes.
My name is Harvey Specter.
It's come to my attention
that you're filing a class-action lawsuit.
We are. How can I help you?
Our pro bono work means a lot to us.
We take it very seriously,
and I have a very difficult
question to ask you.
- What is it?
- I need to know
if you're happy with the way
your case is being handled,
because if Mike Ross isn't
doing everything he can
- to help you...
- Stop right there.
Mr. Ross has dedicated himself
to finding justice for my son.
And not only that, when I
was offered a settlement,
he convinced me to turn it down
and find out the real truth,
so you tell whoever's in charge
that I don't want anyone else
working on this case
other than Mike and Oliver.
Thank you.
[dramatic music]
You gave me your word you'd stay
the hell out of that prison case.
- Harvey, I...
- You're gonna stand there
and tell me you're not working on it?
Because Oscar Reyes told me you deserve
a medal for what you're doing for him.
Harvey, I meant to let
the clinic handle it, okay?
It just turned out that this thing
- was bigger than we thought.
- I don't give a shit
if it turned into the trial of the century.
- We had an agreement.
- No, you had an agreement with Alex,
and then I agreed to sign a document,
but as it turns out, stopping corruption
is more important to me than
some client's bottom line.
Then grow the hell up,
because that ends now.
Harvey, I have to see this through.
See this through? Are you out of your mind?
You think I don't know this is
what Gallo was helping you with?
I told you, Gallo is
not gonna be a problem.
And I told you guys like
Gallo are always a problem.
Yeah, and what about
what I told you happens
if I go back on my word with him now?
Or what you said about what
happens if he calls Rachel.
Were you lying when you said you'd pay him
- if he came through for you?
- No, I wasn't.
Then pay him right now.
You can take it out of my
pocket, but you're done.
- Harvey, it's not...
- No, listen to me because
I don't want there to
be any misunderstanding.
You spend one more minute on this case,
other than telling Oliver it's his,
- I'm shutting you down.
- What the hell does that mean?
It means I'm going to the hearing tomorrow
and telling them that
you broke your agreement.
And I don't care who the judge is,
they'll toss the clinic off the case,
and your friend Oscar won't get a dime.
♪ ♪
[blender whirring]
Louis, stop blending! I have news.
Katrina, thank God you're back.
Here, have a prunie.
Exactly how many prunies did you make?
I don't know. I'm stress blending.
If I don't hear some good news soon,
there's gonna be an
international prune shortage.
So please tell me that you talked Stephanie
out of this bullshit.
Louis, I couldn't talk her out of it,
but I did manage to talk her into this.
Okay, well, I can live with this amount.
But this says that I admit
to sexually harassing her.
- You did sexually harass her.
- Oh, that's a load of crap.
I never hit on Stephanie Patel.
And that's not the definition
of harassment, and you know it.
Well, I don't care. I can't accept it.
- Why not?
- Because I've been sued
for sexual harassment before, and
I can't have it look like a pattern.
I didn't know.
It was before your time,
and it was a bullshit suit
concocted by Daniel Hardman.
I can't have a reputation for this.
I understand that, Louis,
but Stephanie is worried
people think she can't hack it as a lawyer,
and making you admit to what you did
is the only way she sees to
make them think otherwise.
I'm sorry. I can't sign it.
Louis, I know this isn't what you
wanted, but in my professional opinion,
this is the best you're going to do.
At least take a day to think about it.
And, Louis, this goes without saying,
but however tempted you
are, don't go see Stephanie.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Don't "hey" me.
[sighs]
I take it you heard about what
happened between me and Harvey.
I take you didn't hear about what
Rachel, what did he tell you?
He didn't tell me anything.
He asked me where you were
and what you were working on,
and I had to lie to his face.
- Rachel, I...
- Did you hear me?
I had to lie to Harvey's face.
Yes, I heard you, and I'm sorry.
I don't want to hear "I'm sorry."
I want to hear that you're
dropping this goddamn thing.
- Rachel, I...
- No excuses.
You said it's your word to
Oscar Reyes that mattered to you.
Well, you know what, Mike? You need
to get your priorities straight,
because my word became nothing today,
and I don't ever want to be
put in that position again.
So it's up to you. You either go and work
at the clinic or you
stay at Pearson Specter,
but what you can't do anymore
is play them both for fools
and put me in the middle.
I'm gonna go now, and when I come back,
you can let me know what you've decided.
♪ ♪
[door opens, slams]
- [elevator bell dings]
- Oh, hey, you.
Paula, what are you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood,
and I was thinking maybe
we could get dinner.
[sighs] Listen, I'm sorry,
but I am just not in the mood tonight.
I'm sorry.
Does this have something
to do with how it went
when you told Donna about us?
What? No.
I didn't even get a chance to tell her.
Well, what does that mean,
you didn't get the chance?
It means I went to tell
her, but something came up.
What exactly came up?
What does it matter what came up?
Well, I'm just wondering
what was so important
that you couldn't find the
time to tell her the entire day.
Well, if you really need to know, a
murderer turns out to be working with Mike
on a case he swore to me
he wouldn't be working on.
I spent the entire day trying to fix it.
And I thought it was more important
than telling Donna about my love life.
I'm sorry I asked.
Look, I didn't mean to overreact.
I've just had a hell of a day,
and I'll tell her tomorrow, I promise.
[scoffs] Harvey, you don't
need to promise me anything.
In fact, I'd like to
stay out of it entirely,
if you don't mind.
- Paula...
- No, it's fine.
Because, you know, I'm not
the one that brought it up.
And, frankly, I don't like you behaving
as though I'm the one making you do this.
What's going on here?
What's going on here is you're rather keen
on keeping our relationship
a secret from Donna...
when you clearly had no
trouble telling Louis.
Are you worried that I
have feelings for her?
Of course you have feelings for her.
You started having panic
attacks after she left you.
We wouldn't even know each other
if it weren't for those feelings.
- Then what are you saying?
- I don't know.
Maybe you don't want to tell
her because you like being
the object of her attention and affection,
and you're worried this will change that.
Her attention and affection?
Would you like me to say it, Harvey?
She loves you.
At least part of her does,
and maybe part of you likes
it and doesn't want it to stop.
And we wouldn't even be discussing this
if you had the courage
to tell Donna the truth
- and let her move on.
- You know, for someone
who didn't want to be
involved in this anymore,
you sure have a hell of a lot to say.
Then I'll say one more thing.
If what I'm saying is wrong,
then you won't have any trouble
telling Donna in the morning.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Mike, where the hell have you been?
The motion to dismiss is tomorrow.
- I need to go over everything...
- Oliver, I can't help you anymore.
What?
I said I can't work the case anymore.
Why the hell not?
'Cause Harvey found out.
Shit, are you...
He's not gonna hand us in,
but he did make it clear
that if I spent another second on this case
that he'll pull the plug
on the whole damn thing.
I don't believe this. I mean, you come here
and you drop this bomb on me
the night before we go to court.
Oliver, it's not a bomb. You knew all along
you were gonna have to do this on your own.
I knew you wouldn't be up there next to me,
but I was counting on
you helping me to prepare.
- Oliver...
- Son of a bitch, Mike!
You know what happens to me!
It happened last time, and
now it's gonna happen tomorrow
because you're goddamn
hanging me out to dry!
You know what, Oliver?
I have had it up to here
with you blaming me for
every choice that you make.
You knew there would come a
time when you'd be up there
by yourself when you
agreed to take this case.
Now, last time we were in this situation,
I coddled you all night, and you
still dropped the goddamn ball.
So, this time, we're gonna
prepare by me telling you
to stop acting like a little boy,
start acting like a man,
and get the goddamn job done!
Because if you don't,
Oscar and those prisoners,
they're gonna be left with nothing.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
Stephanie.
What are you doing here?
I've been thinking about your offer,
and I was hoping we could talk.
Well, we can't because
we're on opposite sides
- of a lawsuit.
- I know that,
and I'm willing to sign whatever you want.
I'm willing to pay whatever you want.
I just can't admit that I...
Did exactly what you did.
Too bad.
Because if you won't admit it,
I'll make a jury admit it for you.
Stephanie, I'm trying
to be reasonable here.
Well, maybe you should have thought of that
before putting yourself in a position
to let a lowly associate
wipe the floor with you.
Wipe the... My reputation
is that of a pillar
of the legal community,
so you're not wiping the floor with shit.
Your reputation is that
you're a son of a bitch,
and I'm gonna prove it to the world.
No, Stephanie, the only thing
you're gonna prove is that
you're the pathetic loser
that everyone thinks you are,
because you just picked a fight with
someone who is way out of your league!
What delusional reality are you living in?
The one where I make it
crystal clear at trial
that you were fired for cause and
concocted this lawsuit out of spite.
I didn't concoct a room full
of witnesses who saw and heard
the real Louis Litt. So the way I see
it, you're gonna owe me so much money,
I'm never gonna need another job again.
♪ ♪
Harvey, what are you doing here?
Can't a managing partner have a drink with
his favorite COO every once in a while?
He can, but I got a ton of work to do,
and I'd like to get home before midnight.
There's something I need to tell you.
Harvey, what's going on?
I've been seeing Paula Agard.
And not as my therapist anymore.
We've been seeing each other.
- What?
- What do you mean what?
I'm just amused that
you think I didn't know.
- Donna.
- The day you made managing partner,
you drove yourself to
work, not in the red car,
but in the black Ferrari Daytona.
And on top of that, you told me and Louis
that you had things to
take care of that night,
but I know your schedule,
and I know what happened
was you drove yourself
straight home from the office,
you changed into whatever outfit
you thought would impress her the most,
and then you went right over to her house,
and you swept her off her feet.
But you just asked me the
other night if something
was going on because I've
been acting different.
'Cause I was trying to get you to
open up, but you missed the signal,
so I figured I'd just keep
on waiting, and here you are,
more or less right on time.
- More or less?
- Well, I was giving you
until tomorrow, so you're
actually ahead of schedule.
Well, that was Paula's doing.
I'm happy for you, Harvey, and
I want to hear all about it,
but like I said, I've
got a ton of work to do,
and I want to get home
before midnight, so...
Go on, finish. We'll talk later.
I'm glad you finally told me.
Thanks, Donna. Me too.
♪ ♪
Donna, are you okay?
You look like you just saw a ghost.
I don't know. I... [sighs]
I just got some news I should
have seen coming, and I didn't.
Do you want to talk about it?
No, I don't. I'll... I'll be fine.
Well, I just got some news
that we should have seen coming
but didn't, and it's not good.
What is it?
We've just been subpoenaed
to testify against Louis.
♪ ♪
What's that?
Moo shu pork and fried rice.
The way I treated you before,
I wasn't sure if you'd eaten yet.
- Harvey...
- And I was thinking
that maybe we could eat while
I tell you that I'm sorry
and that I told Donna.
- You told her?
- Yes. You were right.
I needed to tell her,
and it was unfair to her,
and it was unfair to you.
- I never said that.
- No, but you meant it.
Harvey, if you're not
careful, you're gonna become
a full-fledged outstanding boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Boyfriend.
Then I'll try not to be careful.
[chuckles]
Come in.
By the way, how did she take it?
She was fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Turned out she already knew.
Well, I'm glad you told her.
And I hope you got some egg rolls in there.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Katrina, hey.
Louis, what the hell did you do?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Then why were Donna and Rachel
slapped with subpoenas last night?
- Katrina, listen to me...
- God damn it, Louis!
How long did you wait to go over there
after I explicitly told you not to?
Well, you know what? It doesn't matter,
because now your job is to blow
that woman out of the water.
Well, that's gonna be pretty hard,
since she has a room full of witnesses
and she also has Donna on record
saying what you did was wrong
and that's why you lost
dominion over the associates.
Whoa, Donna did what?
She didn't know you were
going to get sued, Louis.
And when Stephanie gets her
up on the stand, we're dead.
Well, then she's just gonna
have to lie on the stand.
Louis, that is insane, and you know it.
Well, God damn it, we
have to figure some way
to get out of this, because I
have lost everything this year
- and I can't lose this.
- How about you tell her you're sorry?
What the hell did you just say?
I said tell her that you're sorry.
What are you even doing here?
Are you spying on us for her?
No, um, I came to tell you I'd
been served with a subpoena.
Well, Brian, I don't need your help,
because you can't apologize
without admitting guilt,
which is the whole thing
that I don't want to do.
Louis, I don't know if you've noticed,
but that's pretty much
going to happen anyway.
If I may...
it is admitting guilt,
and it is taking a chance,
but if I were thinking of suing you for
the horrible things you said to me...
that's what I'd want to hear.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here?
I thought you weren't supposed to
have anything to do with this anymore.
I'm not, but there's
nothing in that agreement
that says I can't come
watch my friend Oliver
kick some ass in court.
Well, strap the hell in.
'Cause this motherfucker is going down.
♪ ♪
May I come in?
What do you want this time?
Tell me I'm so worthless I
don't even deserve an office?
I want to tell you I'm sorry,
and if anyone's worthless, it's me.
Louis, if you think pretending
to give me an apology
is gonna make me drop this suit,
you have another thing coming.
I don't think that.
I just think that I owe you an explanation.
You see...
the night before
I said those horrible things to you,
my fiancée left me.
She was pregnant.
And even though the child wasn't mine...
I was finally gonna be a dad.
And when all that went away,
my entire life turned upside down.
I mean, I was reeling.
So, when Brian had asked me for time off
to go have a baby
and you defended him...
You took everything you
were feeling out on me.
Yeah, and I am ashamed of that.
Stephanie...
I will sign anything you want.
I will say anything you need to make sure
that the world knows that
you are not a pushover,
even if that includes admitting guilt.
And if for some reason they
still can't accept you here,
you have your job back
with us, standing offer.
♪ ♪
I appreciate you opening up to me, Louis.
But this wasn't really about
people thinking I'm a pushover.
It was about how you made me feel
when you said those things to me.
Why would they make you feel anything?
I mean, they were so clearly untrue.
- Were they?
- Come on.
What are you talking about? Stephanie...
I'm 34 years old. I work 90 hours a week.
I don't have anyone.
I don't have time to meet anyone,
and I'm worried that I never will,
that I... that I'll never have a family.
So, when you said no one would
want to have children with me...
I am so sorry, Stephanie.
♪ ♪
Thank you, Louis.
I feel like I want to come
over there and give you a hug,
but it's probably inappropriate
since you're suing me
for sexual harassment.
♪ ♪
I'm not suing you anymore, Louis.
Your Honor, this suit hinges on
the testimony of a convicted felon,
not to mention the entire
class is made up of felons
looking for a chance to
stick it to the prisons
that did their duty by incarcerating them.
Your Honor, this case doesn't
hinge on the word of Frank Gallo.
It hinges on the word of a U.S. Attorney
who had reason to suspect
abuses were taking place
at these supposedly upstanding prisons.
Your Honor, that file is inadmissible.
We weren't presented
with it during discovery.
Mr. Grady, if this is
some sort of end-around...
Your Honor, if you'll look at the file,
you can see it was
delivered to me yesterday.
So, unless opposing counsel
feels the U.S. Attorney
was fabricating that date,
that file is admissible.
Ms. Sterling, unless
you have another reason
as to why this case shouldn't move forward,
I'm inclined to allow it.
I have a compelling reason, Your Honor.
- And who are you?
- My name is Alex Williams.
Your Honor, this man has
no standing in this case.
I beg to differ, because
I have a binding agreement
signed by his legal clinic
stating they would have
no outside help from Pearson Specter Litt
- on this case, yet they did.
- You have no proof of that.
Then how about I put you
on the stand, swear you in,
- and ask you myself?
- There is no basis
for you doing that, there is
no precedent for you doing that,
and I'm not gonna get bullied
into getting up on the stand.
And for the record, Your
Honor, the court cannot make
any inferences based on me
choosing not to go up there.
Then how about I put
Mike Ross on the stand?
I notice he's sitting right over there.
I don't have a subpoena for him,
but I'm sure we can whip one up.
And when he gets up there,
we'll see if he tells the truth or not.
- Your Honor...
- That's enough.
Your Honor, I violated the agreement.
Then I have no other choice
but to dismiss this case.
[gavel bangs]
♪ ♪
- [knock at door]
- Hey. You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Why?
First, the way you were
when I walked in last night
and then how you were after
I told you about the subpoena.
Well, I was just worried
about Louis, Rachel.
He's being sued, and I
feel partially responsible
because I'm the one who admitted in
front of the associates that he was wrong.
And I've known you long enough to know
when you're not being straight with me.
[sighs]
Harvey told me he's involved
with somebody last night.
- Is it serious?
- Yes.
And that's the news you
should have seen coming.
- Yes.
- Donna, you're only human,
and I know you have this
amazing ability to read people,
but some things are gonna slip
by even you once in a while.
This one didn't slip by, Rachel.
I didn't see it coming 'cause
I didn't want to see it coming.
♪ ♪
I've always said that I want
Harvey to be happy, and I do.
But it bothers you.
And I hate that it does.
♪ ♪
And then when he told me,
I pretended I already knew,
and I hate that even more.
I don't know what to say.
I don't even know what I'd want you to say.
What do you say Michelle
Ross and Harriett Specter
go out for a drink this week?
Thanks, Rachel. I'd like that.
You told him, didn't you?
What are you talking about? Told who what?
Don't bullshit me. You told Alex
- I was working the prison case.
- I didn't tell Alex shit.
What I did was I told you to drop it.
And I did. I didn't spend
one more second working on it,
just like you ordered me to.
Then what the hell is your problem?
My problem is he just showed up to
the courtroom and blew up the case.
He embarrassed us, he embarrassed me,
and he did it in front of everyone.
The courtroom? I thought you
said you weren't involved.
I was sitting in the back watching.
There's no law against that,
and that is not the point.
No, the point is you went from A
to Z and assumed that I told him.
How the hell else would he know?
It's none of your damn business how I knew.
No, no, this is between me and Harvey.
Wrong, this is between me and you
because you broke your
agreement with my client.
I don't care what I did. You
didn't have to do that publicly.
I didn't make that decision. You did.
Bullshit, you could have
come to me privately.
- We could've had a conversation.
- I did it when this thing started,
- and I'm not doing it again.
- You son of a bitch.
- He's right.
- What?
Alex is right, you gave him no choice.
God damn it, Harvey, that
prison is doing shady shit.
His client doesn't care because
all they care about is money.
And you knew that when you handed it off
- and said you'd live by it.
- This is about you
- coming into a courtroom and...
- Okay, that's it! It's done.
I don't want to hear another
word about Reform Corp
or Masterson Construction ever again.
You made your bed. Now
you're gonna sleep in it.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Donna, you have a minute?
Louis, if you're here to
berate me for what I said
to Stephanie, then, no, I don't.
Uh, that is not why I'm here.
I came to tell you that I'm sorry
that I didn't listen to you weeks ago.
You're gonna have to be
a little more specific.
You kept telling me that
I wasn't dealing with Tara.
Well, I finally started,
and I think because of that,
it allowed me to get past my anger
and make peace with Stephanie.
I'm glad to hear it,
Louis. I'm proud of you.
Like I said, I wish I had
listened to you sooner.
But every bit of you hammering away
at my wall of denial is
what finally brought it down.
So I'm here to tell you thank you...
Because now I feel like I can finally
move forward with my life.
[scoffs]
You're welcome, Louis.
And I think that this means
that you're officially ready.
- Uh, for what?
- To take back the associates.
Okay, Donna, no, I appreciate that.
- But they're yours now.
- They were never mine, Louis.
I was always just taking
care of them for you.
I don't know how I can repay you.
You just did.
♪ ♪
Louis, if you're here
for the Stevenson brief,
I can have it to you in the morning.
Go home, Brian.
Am I fired?
Nope, there's just more
to life than working here.
Am I being punked?
No, not at all.
It's just that you have a new
supervisor starting tomorrow,
and he would like you to
get a good night's sleep.
And he told you to tell me that?
Oh, Jesus, Brian, please,
will you work with me?
I'm the new supervisor.
And listen, I am sorry for saying
all those horrible things
to you about undedicated.
I can't even imagine how
you balance being a new dad
with this workload.
Then I'll see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
Before you go, I got
you a little something.
[chuckles]
Louis, this is the best onesie a
man has ever gotten another man.
You just tell the little
guy to wear it well.
And feel free to bring
him in whenever you want.
But, you know, call first.
This is a place of
business, for God's sake.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
What's that?
Something I should have given
back to you a long time ago...
the key to your apartment.
I don't understand.
I didn't know about you and Paula, Harvey,
and I kept it from you, and I don't want to
keep it from you because I'm happy for you.
- Donna...
- I said I wanted more,
and I got what I wanted.
But when you told me about the two of you,
- for a second there, I...
- I get it.
- You do?
- I remember how it felt
when I found out about
you and Stephen Huntley.
And I told you before, it bothered me.
But it doesn't mean...
Exactly.
[smooth pop music]
♪ ♪
I really am happy for you, Harvey.
Thanks, Donna.
♪ ♪
Oscar.
Is it true, what happened in court today?
- Yes, but it's only a setback.
- Setback?
They said they threw out the whole case.
No. They didn't throw it out.
They just threw us off of it.
What the hell's the difference?
The difference is it's a good case,
and somebody else can still take it.
- We just have to...
- Stop bullshitting me!
Now, you told me to turn
down that settlement.
I trusted you, and now it's over.
No, it's not over, and I know I told you
to turn down that
settlement, but you told me
you weren't doing this for the money and...
Yes, I know. I told you I
was doing it for justice.
But I also told you I have a
son and two other daughters,
and you convinced me the only way to heal
was to keep this from
happening to someone else,
and now I have nothing.
No money, no justice, no healing.
♪ ♪
Oscar, I'm gonna make it right.
I'll believe that when I see it!
♪ ♪
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Harvey, if this is about earlier today,
I want to thank you for backing me.
It is about earlier today, Alex,
but I'm not here for you to thank me.
What are you talking about?
I got to thinking about what Mike said,
and he was right.
You could've done what you
did quietly, but you didn't.
- Harvey...
- Which means
this isn't just about you
protecting your client's interests.
It's about you protecting yourself.
So why don't you tell me
what's really going on here?
www.tvsubtitles.net