Harvey:
I lost Ava her company.
I assume my deal
with Edward is dead.
As long as you win
her murder trial,
you'll be
the next managing partner.
I'm sleeping with Stephen.
I can see that.
So you're not upset?
No.
I got an interview.
Look, I'm sorry, I just didn't
know how to tell you, Mike.
I don't know,
how about,
"hey, Mike, I might go
to law school 3,000 miles away"?
This isn't about me getting
personal with Gianopolous.
This is about me getting
personal with Donna.
Chain of custody is something
I know a little bit about,
thanks to you.
Save yourself
the embarrassment
and cancel this trial.
We're in the ring,
I'm still standing,
and this isn't done.
It's going up
on the wall tomorrow.
And this is your way
of getting me on your side?
I don't want you
on my side.
I want us to be
on the same side.
- You look happy.
- Do I?
Why?
Um, I don't know, Donna,
it's hard to explain.
All right,
I'll tell you.
Mikado finally slept
in my bed last night,
and when I woke up
this morning,
it felt like the whole world
was hugging me.
I lost 9 ounces.
My teeth whiteners
are working.
I found five new hairs
on the top of my head.
And to top it all off,
I just found out
that Esther broke her foot
in three places.
Your sister?
Yeah, crutches
for seven months.
Serves her right.
Dad's favorite.
Mm.
I need a day.
Dom Perignon's on ice
and Bloomberg's
closing Broadway
for the ticker-tape parade.
You saw the sign?
Yeah, dream come true
for any lawyer.
I don't have dreams.
I have goals.
Now it's on
to the next one.
When did you find out?
Last night.
Why didn't you tell me?
I shouldn't have to.
Meaning?
Meaning your focus hasn't
been where it usually is.
Okay, meaning that my focus
has been on Stephen.
If that's what you mean,
then just say it.
Just admit that it bothers you
about me and him.
I'm not admitting anything
because there's nothing
to admit.
And Stephen or not,
you know as well as I do
I've never had
to tell you a thing.
You've always just known.
- You've had too much coffee.
- What are you talking about?
After two cups,
your signature slants.
After three,
it scrawls.
And after four,
it's chicken scratch.
They're not gonna
accept these.
You're crazy.
How many cups
have you had today?
Five.
How'd you do that?
It's what I do.
I read, I analyze, I fix.
Bullshit.
You're wearing
a blue shirt,
which means you won big
in poker last night.
You missed a spot shaving,
which means you had
less than five hours of sleep.
And your left wrist,
which you claim you sprained
playing basketball,
still hasn't healed
because your loud tie is hanging
ever so slightly
to the left.
Loud, by the way, because
you won big in poker last night.
For your information,
I didn't lose sleep
just because of poker.
Yeah, you did.
Melanie's not
in the picture anymore.
- You knew about Melanie?
- And Charlotte.
And Nadia.
Okay, I don't want you
working for me anymore.
Harvey, stop playing
footsie with your secretary.
Mackenzie brothers
are here.
We need to get
these assholes to cave.
I had an idea.
Nite owl murders.
We're not using an idea
you got from L.A. Confidential.
How is that different
from you shooting a dead guy
just because Sean Connery
did it in The Untouchables?
[Imitating Sean Connery]
What are you prepared to do?
Is that supposed
to be Sean Connery?
Don't even think that you
can do Connery better than me.
[Imitating Sean Connery]
Junior.
He's a lying member
of a no-good race.
Ease up, James Bond.
So you gonna come out
and say it?
Say what?
All those observations.
You're into me.
I'm not into you.
I'm Donna.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means I could do
the same thing with Bertha
that I did with you.
All that means is that
you're into Bertha too.
Ooh, what if I am?
We can have
a threesome.
Trust me, if you were ever
lucky enough to have me,
you wouldn't want to share.
Dude, you gonna share
that shit with me or what?
Negatory.
Mmhmm.
All right, you can have some,
but take it easy.
It's gotta last
until tomorrow.
I thought you had
3 ounces.
I sold it.
Daddy's gotta eat.
Wait a minute,
you're dealing now?
Friends and family,
asshole.
What are you, AT&T?
What are you, the FCC?
You don't even know
what that is.
- Yes, I do.
- Really?
Tell me what they do.
I'll give you $500.
You're a dick.
A dick who just got
a hundred on his Calc midterm.
You got the results back
already?
No, but trust me,
hundred.
You know who else
thinks you're a dick?
That math test.
Well, that's fine,
because I just made it my bitch.
Up top, mother flecker!
Whoa, you're gonna
leave me hanging?
Like you're gonna
You got into Harvard,
dickhead.
They accepted
my transfer?
Yeah, they did.
Holy goddamn shit.
Wait a minute,
you read my mail?
What's the point
of going through it
if I'm not gonna read it?
I hate you.
[Both cheer]
Yeah, mother flecker!
Holy shit, dude.
We gotta celebrate.
Yeah.
Those douche bags over
at A.E. Pi are having a party.
It's on.
It's still on.
There's a reason Cameron
hasn't raised the white flag
with Ava yet.
What is it?
I was filing our motion
to dismiss
when I noticed his office
faxed the court
from the Waldorf Astoria.
He's been booking rooms
all over Manhattan.
And turns out
two days ago,
he also called in
the U.S. Marshals.
Protective custody.
- 20 men strong.
- Shit.
This case isn't over.
He's got
another goddamn witness.
♪ See the money wanna stay,
for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie,
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know,
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see,
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so very
busy busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
3x06
The Other Time
♪ The Greenback Boogie ♪
by Ima Robot
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
for www.addic7ed.com
Rachel, come on,
let's just sit down,
for ten minutes, please.
This is ridiculous.
I can't.
I don't wanna miss my flight.
You're not gonna
miss your flight.
It doesn't leave
for another three hours.
And you're supposed
to be there two hours before,
and the airport's
an hour away.
And you know what, instead
of giving me a hard time
about my travel habits,
it'd be nice if you'd just
come with me to the airport.
Rachel, you know the case
I'm working on,
you know the deadline,
and you know the stakes.
What I know is you don't
want me to visit Stanford
because you don't want me
to go to Stanford.
I never said that.
I just said I wish you had
told me that you had applied.
Well, I did,
and now you're being shitty
because you don't
want me to go,
and you won't even
just admit it.
Look, do you really want this
to be easy for me?
All I wanted is for you
to tell me
to have a good trip
and to mean it.
Have a good trip.
Okay, you're telling me
that if I can guess
your exact birthday,
you will kiss me right here.
If you can guess
my birthday,
I'll kiss you...
[Whispers inaudibly]
Wow.
That is very detailed.
All right,
I'm ready to get started.
Uh, I need 360--
I'm sorry, I gotta borrow
my friend here.
I need to borrow my friend
just for a second.
No, no, Trevor, 'cause we're
right in the middle of a thing.
I'm doing the birthday thing.
What are you doing?
I just found out
behind that door over there
is a poker game filled
with drunk A.E. Pi brothers.
No way!
Yeah, that's a great idea.
I should totally not pursue
this hot girl.
Dude, whatever,
you're always telling me
you're Mr. rounders.
Let's go take
their money.
Come on,
we're here to drink booze
and hit on chicks,
not sit in the dark
and play with a bunch of dudes.
Come on, now where was--
what?
Totally not cool, man.
- Of her or of you?
- Whatever.
Whoa, hey, excuse me.
Our house, our rules,
asshole.
Oh!
Douche bag.
Man, forget him.
Nah, I can't.
First week freshman year,
I was playing basketball.
He showed up with three
of his buddies.
I go up for a lay-up,
he comes in,
lays me out.
Stands over me and says,
"What are you gonna
do about it?"
I let it go.
I'm not letting it go
this time.
Let's roll.
You wanted to see me?
Mackenzie brothers.
I got 'em 25 years apiece.
You?
You wouldn't have gotten shit
without me.
Nite owl murders, baby.
Oh, don't do that.
What kind of person doesn't
high-five another person?
A person
who's not ten years old.
Oh, so you mean
like a dick.
No, I mean, like the guy
that can fire you on the spot.
Nite owl murders, baby.
All right, okay, okay.
All kidding aside,
great job.
Thank you.
That's not
why I called you down here.
Look, Harvey,
you're killing it,
and you've been killing it,
and I think it's time
that you got rewarded for it.
Head litigator.
Look, I know you got a deal
with Jessica to come back,
but I'm telling you,
in ten years, you could be me.
You think about it.
In the meantime,
celebrate the win.
Just stay away
from my scotch.
Well, I guess
I win again.
You guys are really
behind the times.
You ought to be playing
hold'em.
Don't give a shit
about moneymaker
and his bullshit game.
We're old school.
We play stud.
You lose at stud.
Not to you, asshole.
No, no, no, no,
you lose to me.
Come on, hurry up, old school.
Deal the cards.
Compliments
of Cameron Dennis.
Harvey, this isn't
just winning a case.
This is head litigator.
Scotch isn't good enough.
We need, like, a ritual
or something.
What did you have in mind?
I don't know.
I have an idea.
I'm listening.
It's not something
a gentleman should say out loud.
Oh, well,
then I'm willing to pretend
that you're a gentleman.
Okay, you are definitely
not a gentleman.
What would we even
do it with?
Whipped cream.
Enough about
this conversation.
I want to revisit
our earlier one.
This is our earlier one.
Come on, you know
you've thought about it.
Yeah, I think
about a lot of things.
And you would.
But I won't.
You're afraid
you'd fall for me.
Oh, please, if anybody's
falling for anybody,
it would be you for me.
Sounds like a challenge.
One you are never
gonna get to take.
Why not?
'Cause I don't get involved
with men that I work with.
Okay, then you're fired.
'Bout time.
What did I ever
do to you?
Nothing.
I get your chair.
Bertha, what are you
doing here so late?
Don't get all up
in my business
just because I interrupted you
hitting on red.
How do you know
I'm hitting on her?
Two glasses of scotch
and you.
I found a Mackenzie file
in the MacAllister box.
You're welcome.
And you better get
Dennis his scotch back.
He won't like that.
Shit.
What's wrong?
We left out
a piece of discovery.
Will it screw us?
It just did.
Well, I raise.
500.
Call and raise
another 500.
I don't have
another 500, so...
Wait a second.
He might.
[Mutters]
I have another thousand
on me.
How do you have
another thousand?
From the weed.
I told you,
I got rid of it.
Now do you have this guy
or not?
I got kings full of 2s.
He's got no aces showing,
and Jesus Christ Superstar
folded one on first street.
The only way he beats me
is with trip 3s or trip 4s
under there,
and Limp Bizkit
folded two 3s,
and Dickcheese over here
had a 4.
So he's got a...
- A straight.
- Straight.
Or he's bluffing,
but either way,
I got him.
Hey, do you always get
your girlfriend's advice
on everything?
Oh, this guy.
Well, let's raise
another 500.
Hmm.
Don't ask for more
unless you wanna lose it.
[Sighs]
Call.
Full house.
Four 4s, asshole.
Whoa, wait.
Wait, that's not possible.
He had--
he's cheating.
And what are you
gonna do about it?
You're not gonna get away
with this.
Well, I guess
your only option
would be
to call the police.
Of course,
I haven't been drinking,
'cause, you know,
I'm underage, like you boys.
You set us up.
Yeah.
See, I remember you.
First week,
you come into class,
Mr. "Oh, I got
the whole textbook memorized."
Made the rest of us
look like chumps.
No, you did that
all by yourself.
Yeah, well,
I don't need a super brain
to remember some guy who thinks
his shit don't stink.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, dude.
- Hey, back up.
Now get the hell outta here
before we put you
out of here.
Congratulations Harvey.
I had no idea
Jessica was planning this.
What do you want, Stephen?
I hear Cameron
got a witness.
He did.
What do you want?
I'm just checking to see
if there's anything
I can do to help.
There isn't.
Cheers.
[Elevator dings]
What do you got?
I couldn't find out
where Cameron's
got his witness hidden,
but I figured out
who it is.
What?
So now I know
why you wanted to meet me
at the elevator.
Pretty awesome.
Yeah, it is.
What are you gonna do
about Jessica?
I don't know.
Nothing ever changes
around here.
It's good to see you too,
Harvey.
Now what was so important
that you just had to see me?
I wanna talk to you
about extending my time
at the D.A.'s office.
Come with me.
Now what's Cameron Dennis
offering you?
Why does he have
to be offering me something?
Because he knows, if you wanna
keep someone in your house,
offer them
a better room.
Head litigator.
Do you wanna stay there
because it's a step up
or because you can see yourself
there in ten years?
Why do you wanna know?
Because I have a promotion
ready for you right here.
What are you talking about?
Daniel Hardman and I
are taking Gordon, Schmidt,
and Van Dyke down.
That's why we're up here.
Did you think
we were gonna make out?
Man can hope.
What?
Are you sure you wanna
take control in the night?
Nighttime's
when they're sleeping.
Telling them you're coming
shows them respect.
Not telling them
shows them more.
What about honor?
Harvey, we're lawyers.
We're not
in the honor business.
What did I always tell you
when you were here?
Don't judge a man till you've
walked a mile in his shoes.
Well, if you're ever
in these babies,
we'll see if you feel
the same way.
It's a little early
for batting cages,
don't you think?
I'm not going
to the batting cages,
and you know it.
Trevor, let it go.
I can't.
I need that money back.
What did you do?
I haven't paid
for the weed yet.
You took a loan
from a drug dealer?
It's called consignment.
Did you ever learn about
free enterprise in Econ 1a?
No, but I read about
not betting money I don't have
in Econ 1a.
You told me you had him,
smart guy.
I did have him,
and you know I did.
Well, I need
a thousand dollars by Monday,
or Omar's gonna beat
the living shit outta me.
Trevor,
him kicking your ass
doesn't get him
his money any faster.
He's not gonna
see it that way.
Okay, then we will think
of something else.
I've been thinking,
and the only thing
I came up with
you're not gonna like.
Why do I
have to like it?
Because I can't do it.
I told you before,
I'm not selling
any test answers.
It's not any test.
It's the test you just aced.
It's not out there yet.
Nobody has it.
I can make us 1,000 bucks
in one shot.
Tell me you haven't memorized
every question
and every answer, Harvard boy.
That's what this is about,
isn't it?
So what if it is?
Look, you're bolting,
and you're using
your brain to do it.
I'm just asking,
before you go,
use it to help me.
Please.
What the hell is this?
It's the paperwork
for the Mackenzie deal.
Type it up
and get it out.
No, that report was
supposed to be disclosed
during discovery.
If you type up
what I gave you,
you'd know
I'm disclosing it now.
No, you're sticking it
in there now
as if it's always been there.
It's called bluffing.
Okay, it's what I do.
That's how I got the confession
in the first place.
It's called bullshit,
it's what bullshitters do,
and it's how innocent people
sometimes end up in prison.
- Watch yourself.
- Excuse me?
That toxicology report
doesn't change the fact
that those two assholes
killed that woman.
And you being
an asshole to me
doesn't change the fact
that you are breaking the law.
I'm not breaking the law.
I put the goddamn thing
in there.
They can find it
if they can think to look.
Harvey,
you are making a huge--
That's enough!
I'm here.
You're here.
Do your job.
We know you have a witness.
Surprised it took you
that long.
And we know who it is.
The man from the video,
Colonel Mariga.
I don't have any prizes,
so you'll just have to accept
a pat on the back.
That's okay, Tom Selleck,
I don't need a pat on the back.
I just need to know
what bullshit story
he's gonna tell in court.
It's not bullshit.
He's gonna say
that Ava Hessington
paid him to kill
those people.
We're getting access
to him.
No, you're not,
because I'm gonna say
if she finds out
where he is,
what's to stop her
from killing him too?
You're not gonna bribe him,
you're not gonna threaten him,
and you're not gonna
talk him out of it,
because you're not gonna see him
until he gets on the stand.
But what I will do
is allow you
to take an offer
to your client.
15 years, no parole.
You're bluffing.
He's not gonna say she knew
about the murders,
because she didn't.
I'll tell you what.
Ten years with parole.
Ah, make it nine.
After all,
we used to work together.
- How'd it go?
- Don't.
Was she hot?
I sold her a math test
for $1,000.
I wasn't thinking
of whether she was hot or not.
Okay, I get it,
so, like, an eight?
No, a ten wouldn't even
do her justice.
- So six.
- Mm, she's a four.
But she paid me $1,000,
so I bumped her up to a ten.
Got it.
Thank you, Michael.
Came through.
Not yet.
I'm coming with you
to Omar's.
No, no, no, no,
you can't.
Yes, I can.
What's going on?
I owed him the money
yesterday.
How could you not
tell me that?
Because I couldn't make the
test thing happen until today.
I didn't want you
freaking out.
Well, I'm definitely
coming with you now,
and the only way you can
stop me is with that bat.
You wanted to see me?
What the hell is this?
- It's the Mackenzie file--
- I know what it is.
What the hell did you put
in the fine print?
You too?
You're gonna give me shit about
not disclosing this report?
Not disclosing it?
You gave it to 'em
on a silver platter.
I don't understand.
You want me to take it out?
I don't want you to do shit.
I've already taken it out.
And if I'd wanted it disclosed,
I wouldn't have misfiled it
in the first place.
You buried it?
Damn right I did.
Cameron, look,
I'm all for skirting the law,
but this is
breaking the law.
So was killing that woman,
and I'm not gonna let
those two assholes walk
because our eyewitness had
a few beers at the ball game.
They won't walk. That's why
I put it in the fine print.
You think you're the first guy
to have this idea?
Nobody does it
because it doesn't work.
Well, that's exactly
why it can work.
They won't think
to look at it
because nobody
has the balls to do it.
And what if they do
and these guys get out
and they murder your brother
or your father
or your cousin?
'Cause I'll tell you
right now,
they're gonna
murder someone's.
I don't feel comfortable
with this.
I don't give a shit whether
you feel comfortable or not.
This is my case.
We're not disclosing it.
It's done.
Cameron-
I told you this before.
Don't make me tell you again.
I'm here.
You're here.
Do your job.
- Keep the change.
- I need to speak with you.
Okay, let's talk
on the way up.
No, I prefer
to speak out here.
I know that Cameron's
offered Harvey a deal.
All right, I'm not going
behind Harvey's back.
I don't want you
to go behind his back.
I want you to go
to his face.
And do what?
It wasn't a deal.
It was an insult.
It was an opening.
Now he wouldn't
have offered anything
if he wasn't willing
to negotiate.
Maybe we can get him
down to five years.
That's exactly
what he wants,
to put Ava
in a position
where she has to choose
between five years and life.
That's a better position
than she's in now.
He wouldn't have offered
anything at all
if he wasn't bluffing.
We're not gonna fall
for that bluff.
Well, then Harvey's
making a mistake.
Then take it up
with Harvey.
You know as well as I do
Harvey is not interested
in anything I've got to say
at the moment.
You think Harvey's
making this call
because of what's going on
between you and Donna?
- It's clouding his judgment.
- Not about this.
Right now
Harvey cannot see reason
with respect to Cameron.
He can't hear reason
with respect to me.
Now you have a chance
to convince him
to make a deal, Mike.
Put yourself
in Ava Hessington's shoes.
Would you want that choice
or not?
[Muffled hip-hop music]
Okay, whatever happens,
just be quiet
and be cool.
Okay.
Who this?
My friend.
Hi.
Inside.
Don't move.
Where's Omar?
That's Omar.
How is that Omar?
He's obsessed
with The Wire.
[Chuckles]
Are you kidding me?
Come on.
I'm telling you,
he's no joke.
Yeah, well, I know
I'm supposed to be scared,
but I'm really not.
Don't touch anything.
Now unless my calendar
is messed up,
today be Monday.
- Omar--
- Shut up!
Okay, I'm trying to decide
why I shouldn't call
a couple of hard,
pipe-hitting negroes
to come and work on you
with a pair of pliers
and a blowtorch.
[Snickers]
I'm--I'm sorry, Omar.
I don't have a reason,
but I think the word
you be looking for
isn't "negro."
If you're gonna quote
Pulp Fiction,
at least have the balls
to quote Pulp Fiction.
- Omar--
- Shh, shh, shh.
♪
You know what they call
a quarter pounder with cheese
in France?
A royale with cheese,
mother flecker.
- I love this negro!
- Yeah.
Trevor,
you're off the hook.
Never again.
- [Clears throat]
- This be for you.
Not white boy.
Go in peace.
- Oh, uh, okay.
- Thanks.
Hey, thank you.
Mmhmm.
Who touched my alien?
[Chuckles]
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Come on,
it's nothing that some of this
and a royale with cheese
can't fix.
You do not know
what we just avoided.
Just call me the wolf.
I'll be over there directly.
Oh, you sending the wolf?
Both: Oh, shit, negro,
that's all you had to say.
Yo, put that away.
What?
Put what away?
If they find it,
it's mine.
Trevor Evans?
Yes, officers.
Come with us.
Hey, what's going on?
Your friend here
seems to be involved
in selling the answers
to a stolen test.
The Mackenzie deal
came back.
Two murderers down.
Don't you wanna ask me
if they saw the fine print?
Oh, no, of course you don't.
Because you know they didn't
because that report wasn't
in the fine print anymore.
Donna--
Cameron made you take it out,
didn't he?
How'd you know?
When I do my Donna shit
with you,
it's not just for fun.
It's my job.
Now why don't you tell me
why you didn't tell me?
Because you hated me
when I was working in the gray.
This is the black.
I didn't hate you.
I was trying to stop you.
And the truth is
what you were doing
was right on the line.
What he is making you do,
that's illegal.
It's one time,
and it's not my case.
It might not be your case,
but it's definitely
not just one time.
I was here all night
going through his past cases.
How many?
Too many.
And I'll tell you another thing.
I bet his first time he thought
would be his last time.
Donna.
If you want somebody
to just sit at her desk,
answer your phones,
and pick up your dry cleaning,
then put out a want ad,
because that's not me.
I'm gonna tell you
what I think.
And what I think is,
if you do this,
you're gonna keep doing it.
Donna, I need you to--
where the hell's Donna?
I don't know.
I was waiting for her myself.
Wait somewhere else.
- Harvey, listen--
- No, don't "Harvey" me.
You went to my guy
about my case behind my back.
So what you need to do now
is stay out of my face.
[Grunts]
They told me this is
where I'd find women's softball.
It is now.
All right, old man,
stand back while I knock
the cover off a few balls.
Easy, Reggie Jackson.
I think you're maybe
forgetting I hit .385.
Who doesn't hit
at least .350 in high school?
Marcus didn't.
Don't give
your brother shit.
He's not here
to defend himself.
Pussy.
Hey, if he's not here
to defend himself...
Yeah, he's not here
to hear it.
Both: Cheers.
So what's going on?
I don't know what to do.
Well, breaking the law
isn't worth it
no matter what the guy did.
How'd you know?
You're a prosecutor.
You told me you had a problem.
Well, it's not
that simple, Dad.
It's not just me,
and if I don't let it go,
I'll get fired.
If you do?
I tell him
I'm only doing this once,
and I'm only doing it
because it's his case,
and I'll never do it
on one of mine.
And then I keep knocking
the covers off the bad guys,
which is what I do,
and I don't bat .385,
I bat a thousand.
All right.
You know, I'm gonna
tell you something
I never told you before.
You might not wanna
hear it now,
but you know what
your grandmother said to me
when I told her I was gonna
ask your mother to marry me?
What?
Don't, because if she'll cheat
on someone else with you,
she'll cheat on you
with someone else.
We had a huge blowout.
I told her
to shove it up her ass.
Lily wouldn't do that.
She'd be different with me
because Lily loved me.
- Dad--
- No, no, let me finish.
Then, years later,
I found out the other guy
thought the same thing.
What I'm trying to say is,
even if Cameron believes
that he'll never
make you do it again,
he will.
Okay, out with it.
Drop the hammer.
They know Trevor
isn't in the class,
so they know
he couldn't have been the one
to steal the test.
And they won't expel him
if he gives you up.
How do you know that?
I watch Law & Order.
I'm not an idiot.
He'll never turn me in.
- But you feel guilty.
- I am guilty.
So you wanna
turn yourself in?
They'll fail me.
But I still have a 3.8.
You know, there's no way Harvard
rescinds my acceptance.
[Scoffs]
That goddamn kid.
I guess I know
where you come down on this.
Oh, he's an asshole
in the making,
no question about it.
But?
After you lost
your mom and dad,
the Evanses offered
to take you in.
They offered
because that little boy
cried all night
for a month.
He begged them.
I'm not saying
he's the same kid anymore,
but that kid
is in there.
[Sighs]
Harvey, just the man
I wanted to see.
Why is that?
'Cause I wanted you
to be the first to know.
I'm looking
at my new head litigator.
I'm afraid you're not.
And why is that?
Because after I show you this,
you're gonna demand this.
You disclosed that report.
That affidavit
says I made a mistake,
an honest mistake.
And this one says,
as my penance,
I'm resigning.
So you're just gonna put
two killers back on the street.
If you're half the prosecutor
you say you are,
you can still
put 'em away.
And I don't give a shit
whether you feel comfortable
with that or not,
because you said
it was your case,
but you made it my case.
I made it our case,
because I thought
you were about putting
bad guys behind bars.
Cameron, you asked
what if they got out
and killed my father?
Well, I think
the question is:
What if my father found out
what I did to put them in?
[Scoffs]
You goddamn pussy.
The only thing
that makes me a pussy
is that I didn't send
that affidavit in
the second I found out.
Sir, I know you
offered Trevor Evans
a way to avoid expulsion.
Well, the reason
he didn't take it
is he was trying--
he was trying
to protect me.
He's the one
who sold the test,
but I'm the one
who took it.
So please,
do not punish him
for his loyalty to me.
Truth is,
with the way his grades are,
I don't think
it'll matter anyway.
So I'll tell you what,
I'm not going to expel
your friend.
[Sighs]
Oh, thank you, sir.
There's just one thing.
You're his roommate.
And you scored perfectly
on that test.
I knew it was you.
I also know you're only
sitting here in front of my face
because you think whatever
I do to you won't matter.
No, sir,
that's not true.
Well, let me tell you
what is true,
you little piece of shit.
The young woman you sold
the test to was my daughter.
They're demanding
my resignation.
And as my last official act,
I'm expelling you
from this school,
and then
I'm gonna call Harvard.
Believe me when I tell you,
you're never going there.
[Buzzer]
I decided what kind
of attorney I want to be.
I heard.
You quit.
Did you hear I also turned
over the toxicology report?
You didn't.
Thought you were
supposed to know everything.
How'd you not know this?
Well, I knew that you were
either gonna take that promotion
or you were gonna quit.
And either way, I wasn't
sticking around to find out.
- You quit?
- Damn straight.
I'm not working at a place
headed by a viper.
Donna, I can't get you
another job.
Oh, well, that's gonna make
my decision easier.
What does that mean?
I'm choosing
between Bratton Gould,
Skadden Arps,
and O'Melveny & Myers.
If I had another one,
I don't know what I'd do.
You know,
it just occurred to me
that you and I
don't work together anymore.
Yeah, that didn't
just occur to you.
No, it didn't.
Do you know
how I know that?
'Cause you knew
I'd show up here
the second
you heard I quit?
Why do you think
I have this in my hand?
What are we waiting for?
For you to figure out
that it's time to come inside.
[Alternative music]
♪
So let me get this straight.
You turned me down before,
and now you're saying
you want to come back?
Yes.
And it has nothing
to do with our coup?
I didn't even know
you did it
until I saw your name
on the wall.
You got it up there fast.
Don't tell 'em
you're coming,
and slam the door
behind them.
Now why should I take someone
who waited for me to win?
Because I'm someone
you trusted with the news
in the first place.
I also trusted
all the people who voted for me.
Come clean, Harvey.
What changed your mind?
Instead of thinking
about what I wanna be doing
in ten years,
I started thinking about
who I want to be doing it with.
Me over him.
Terms are nonnegotiable.
You get what I give you.
Fine by me, but I'm getting
my own secretary.
Associates don't get
their own secretaries.
This isn't
about the associate.
It's about the secretary,
and I'm not coming here
without her.
She must be very special.
She is.
Difference comes out
of your pocket.
As long
as she never knows.
Welcome back, Harvey.
You start Monday.
Give it up.
Oh, no.
So what was so important
that you just had to see me?
I don't know how to say it,
so I'm just gonna come out
and say it.
But I don't want
to lose you.
Come work for me.
What?
Don't go to Skadden.
I took a job
at my old firm.
I was hoping
you'd be happy.
What? I am.
If this is
about your rule--
No, it's not about that.
Because if I had known
that this was gonna happen,
I never would
have come over.
Why didn't you know
that it was gonna happen?
Because I hadn't thought
about taking another job before.
And when I did...
I thought about who I wanted
to take it with.
Look, I don't wanna find out
what kind of lawyer
I'd be without you.
[Sighs]
Okay, I will come work with you
on two conditions.
First, we put it
out of our minds,
and we never
mention it again.
Second?
You're giving me
a huge goddamn signing bonus.
How do you know
that's enough?
Because you're the one
who's gonna fill in the amount.
Oh, my God,
you really do need me...
To stop you
from doing shit like this.
Oh, well...
In the future.
Hmm.
What?
We're gonna need
a new ritual.
Well, maybe we can think
of something to do
with a can opener.
Harvey, that's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard.
Jeez.
Actually...
What are you doing here,
Harvey?
It's 7:00 a.m.
I didn't know
you were gonna be here.
I love this place.
Really?
You've only ever been here
once before.
How'd you know that?
I know.
You and Stephen,
it bothers me.
I know it's not fair,
but it does.
Good.
What do you mean, good?
I mean,
we both knew it.
It's good that you finally
were able to say it.
You realize just
because it bothers me,
it doesn't mean
that I want us to be--
I know.
Jeez.
You know this is exactly
why I had that policy.
Well, then why did
you change it?
Because I have to live
my life, Harvey.
I've never apologized
for who I am,
and I'm not gonna
start now.
You don't need
to apologize for anything.
I know.
[Sniffles]
But you do.
For taking so long
to say that it bothered you.
Jesus.
And let's just
put an order in
for the valet
to hold my suit jackets,
and then we c--
Harvey.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
You're not due back
for another two years,
three months, and five days,
not that I'm keeping track.
Change of plans.
I'm back today.
[Chuckles]
Who's your girlfriend?
Oh, I'm not his girlfriend.
I'm his girl Friday.
[Laughs]
Associates
don't get secretaries.
I'm not like
other associates,
and she's not like
other secretaries.
- Bullshit.
- Donna?
Okay, listen, Rain Man,
you wear lifts in your shoes,
you want braces,
but you don't have the balls,
and you have a cat
that you love
more than it loves you.
- Good to see you, Louis.
- Mm.
[Elevator dings]
I need a day.
You going down?
All the way up, asshole.
I'll take the ride.
[Sighs]
Hey.
What's that?
This is my way
of showing you
that no matter
what you choose,
I support you.
And if your dream
is to go to Stanford,
then that's my dream
for you too.
How does it look?
I have to admit,
it looks pretty good.
So what changed
your mind?
You got into Harvard?
It's a--
it's a long story,
but I have to go
right now.
I wanted to be here
when you got home.
But if you let me,
I'd like to come
straight back here
and tell you
the whole thing.
Okay.
Any progress
getting to Mariga?
Cameron's not just bluffing
about what Mariga's
gonna say.
He doesn't even have him.
That means we--
We win.
It's over.
[Chuckles]
Ah, it's gonna be fun
telling Cameron that.
It's gonna be fun for Mike.
I've got
something else to do,
and it's not
gonna be fun.
Is that
why we're up here?
You remember
when you told me you decided
to take Gordon, Schmidt,
and Van Dyke down?
I guess that is
why we're up here.
You said,
take them in the night
because nighttime's
when they're sleeping.
And you thought
I was wrong.
And then you said
if I were ever in your shoes,
I might think differently.
What'd you do, Harvey?
I made a move
in the night.
I get Ava Hessington
acquitted...
Darby backs me
for managing partner.
[Soul music]
♪
I guess congratulations
are in order.
I'm here to tell you
I don't want it anymore.
Get out of my sight.
♪
[Elevator dings]
[Clears throat]
You look ready
to attack.
Does Harvey know his puppy's
off his leash?
Harvey said he didn't need
to waste a trip down here
just for me to tell you
I have my eye on the ball.
I'm afraid
I don't follow you.
Mariga.
You weren't lying
about what he would say.
You were lying about having him
in the first place.
This whole thing
was designed just to get us
to sign your bullshit deal.
You're right.
We didn't have him,
but we do now,
and he's on a flight
as we speak.
So you do me a favor,
and you tell Harvey
he can take that bullshit deal
and shove it up his ass,
'cause we're going
to trial.
No way.
If you didn't have
Mariga yesterday,
you don't have him today.
Why don't you ask
your friend Stephen Huntley?
He's the one who led me
right to him.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
for www.addic7ed.com