Lucille.
Hey!
Hey, it's looking good.
- Tell me you got good news.
- I do.
Stable shelters' bridge loan
has just been approved.
Harvey pulled
some strings at the bank.
Ah, good to see you, Harvey.
I figured you was allergic
to manual labor.
Oh, I'll get my hands dirty
if I have to, Lucille.
But I believe
charity begins at home.
Yeah, and based on
that rolex you wear,
I'd say that your favorite cause
is doing pretty good.
We're gonna need
your signature here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
15% interest?
They're worried about
stable shelter's solvency.
They're worried?
They should try being
executive director.
If you don't recover the money
that Anthony Mazlo
embezzled from us,
every one of these
projects goes dark.
Unless you got
a spare room or two
for a couple thousand families
in your condo.
I'm not really
a roommate kind of guy.
Oh.
Harvey's deposing
Elliot Perkins,
Mazlo's number two,
this afternoon.
Perkins had to have
knowledge of this,
and he's going
to give up his boss.
That's a promise. Excuse me.
Check it out.
Mazlo spent $500 a night
on doggie daycare
on his trip to Greece.
Greece.
What?
- Oh, nothing.
- Tell me.
My first time was in Greece.
My God, you're picturing that
right now, aren't you?
I have no choice.
I'm a visual person.
You two are really adorable.
We're 48 hours from trial,
and you're gossiping
like two 12-year-olds
at sleepaway camp.
Listen up.
Lucille Jackson's not just the
head of stable shelters, okay?
She also sits
on the board of directors
of several of
our largest clients.
So if we lose this case,
I doubt that her generosity's
going to extend to us.
- I would...
- In my office.
Bring the clarity-drilling IPO.
Jerome Jensen's here. Come on.
Lucille's case
is all hands on deck, Harvey.
- You can't just...
- I can, and I am.
I thought we're
working on this together.
Yeah, we are, Louis.
Same way a golfer
and his caddy work together.
Be that as it may,
we are deposing Elliot Perkins
in 15 minutes, so...
Perkins can wait.
Just make sure that my 9 iron
is nice and shiny
when I get there.
Okay? Come on, Mike.
Harvey.
Jerome Jensen, meet Mike Ross.
He's got the latest on the IPO.
- Hello, Mike.
- Mr. Jensen.
I'm not here to talk
about my business, Harvey.
Looks like my daughter might be
getting into some trouble.
Mildred Wisnewski.
What's Lola doing
with a fake I.D.?
Well, that's what I hope
you can find out.
It slipped out of her purse
when she was ordering a drink
at a friend's Bar Mitzvah.
Any idea what it's about?
My relationship with Lola's
been rocky for a few years.
If I asked her, she'd just lie.
Truth is, I don't need to know.
I just need you
to take care of it.
Thank you.
What the hell is Harvey doing?
He's supposed to be
deposing Elliot Perkins.
He's with a client.
I don't care.
We have a deposition.
Don't even try it, Louis.
I'm sorry.
Let's... Let's just start over.
Okay?
- Hi, Donna.
- Hi.
You know I like you, right?
But in the firm's food chain,
I am a humpback whale,
and you are phytoplankton.
June 3, 1997.
That date means nothing to me.
Doesn't it?
Who told you?
Is the important thing
how I know
or that I know?
Does Harvey know?
He can.
I'm going to pay you.
I just don't have
cash on me right now.
So I'm gonna just tell Norma
to run her old ass
out to the atm
and then bring it back
in a jiff, all right?
I don't want your money, Louis.
I just want you to...
I was not here. I was not here.
I was not here.
All right,
let's get started, shall we?
Isn't Harvey Specter
leading this deposition?
He sent me.
Now, Mr. Perkins,
my first question to you is...
Do you sleep well at night?
Of course you do,
'cause you have a roof
and a bed and running water,
and by contrast,
thousands of families
are gonna be sleeping
on the street
when stable shelters is forced
to suspend their operations,
all because of the money
that you stole.
I never stole anything.
You're Mazlo's number two.
Money was embezzled.
Do you deny that?
- Absolutely.
- Please, Robert,
I know as general counsel
you just basically push paper,
but please warn Mr. Perkins
about the penalties of perjury.
Look, I'm not aware
of any perjury.
We know about your account
in the Caymans.
$20 million.
Are you kidding me?
That transaction
was legitimate.
Oh, when I take this public,
you're gonna be disgraced.
Your wife, your children,
your whole family, disgraced.
Would you show my client
some respect...
And that transaction
had nothing to do with the firm.
Bullshit.
You either
took your cut from Mazlo,
or it was hush money.
Either way, you're gonna live
the rest of your life
as a pariah,
or you give up Mazlo now.
Is this a deposition
or an inquisition?
This is ridiculous.
I can show you the records.
Oh, sure you can.
Because you're the guy
who invented losses
in mortgage-backed securities
when you never even
bought them.
I had no part in that.
But you were aware of it,
and you did nothing about it.
Come on, Louis.
Can I get
a glass of water, please?
You can't get any water.
We don't have any.
You give up Mazlo now,
and this all stops.
All right, that's... That's it.
My client needs a break.
We can continue this
in ten minutes.
I'm just getting started.
I don't get it.
She looks so sweet.
Don't let the photo fool you.
She's less "girl next door"
and more
"girl with the dragon tattoo."
Mm.
Look, my plate's full
with stable shelters.
I need you to look
into Jerome's daughter.
Why didn't you just
hire a private investigator?
Because if there's a problem,
an investigator can't fix it.
I'm not just a lawyer
to Jerome, okay?
I'm... I'm more like
Robert Duvall in the godfather.
His consigliere.
Okay.
What?
Uh, nothing.
Just if you're
his Robert Duvall,
you're coming to me,
so technically
I'm your Robert Duvall.
You're my Fredo.
Fredo? No.
Robert, what the hell
happened to Perkins?
Ask that pit bull of yours.
Uh, oh, no, actually.
I prefer a female masseuse?
If that...
Can I call you right back?
Right back. Okay, bye.
Perkins just got
wheeled out on stretcher.
Well, he couldn't
handle the heat.
He's probably faking it.
What were you thinking,
starting that deposition
without me?
I don't know. Maybe if
you were doing your jo...
- Oh, no.
- What?
It's from Geller.
Perkins wasn't faking anything.
Our best chance
to nail Anthony Mazlo's dead.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Well, he blew f the deposition,
so I was just
picking up the slack.
I was letting Perkins sweat.
It was a tactic,
which you completely undermined.
Well, I believe
I made him sweat and then some.
Are you actually proud
of what you did?
As far as I'm concerned,
whatever happened to that guy
was a result of his own guilt,
and I will not apologize
for deposing a criminal
in a vigorous manner.
Losing Perkins
is a complication.
We're just gonna
have to work harder
to unearth Mazlo's money trail.
As for what happened,
I've spoken to the hospital,
and cause of death
was a pulmonary embolism.
It was nothing you did.
Would it be okay
if I took the credit?
Louis, I need
to have a word with Harvey.
Okay.
Financial crime
is that man's forte.
Yes, he overstepped his rank,
but I'm not about to throw
the baby out with the bathwater.
Louis is the bathwater.
Believe it or not, Harvey,
you can be a real pain
in the ass to work with too.
Oh, I get along
with me just fine.
Yes, well, I'm not about
to tell Lucille Jackson
that we didn't win because
we couldn't work together.
You need to figure out
how to collaborate with Louis.
So the name
on Lola Jensen's fake I.D.
Wasn't just pulled
from thin air.
Belongs to an
assistant controller
at clarity drilling.
You're telling me this why?
You wanted me to look into it.
I didn't ask you
to explain the problem to me.
I asked you to fix it for me.
Hey, did Louis
really kill a guy?
Is that what the associate
rumor mill's been churning out?
Actually,
I think he started it.
"Yeah, he also claims
that he's 6'2"
with a full head of hair.
Louis with hair. That's good.
How'd you get past Donna?
You waited till she peed,
didn't you?
I mean, the woman
retains water like a camel.
I see that the, uh,
greatest band of all time
is conspicuously absent.
And who would that be, Louis?
Oh, I don't know.
A little British band
called queen?
Should have seen that coming.
You know, real musicians,
they don't wear eyeliner.
Oh, really?
Why don't you tell that
to the artist
formerly known as Prince,
who's...
Once again named Prince?
What do you want, Louis?
Well, I think
now that we're working together,
we should set
some ground rules.
First rule,
never touch my records.
Or anything else
in this office.
Fine.
That includes the furniture.
I'm trying to build
a rapport with you.
Okay?
I mean, I think our relationship
needs a little work.
Let's hold off
the couples counseling
until our fifth anniversary.
Don't you think?
Look, Mazlo's lawyer
moved to push up the trial.
They know we need time
to cultivate another witness.
Well, I say we bluff.
I mean,
Perkins implicated Mazlo
the minute his lawyer
walked out of the room.
That's hearsay, Louis.
Not if it's
a deathbed confession.
Maybe while Geller
was making the 911 call,
I had a little
conversation with Perkins.
So you want to lie
about what Perkins said
and how he said it?
Well, what's your brilliant
solution, Harvey?
I'm having the money
in Perkins' account
traced as we speak, and I have
another witness in mind.
I get Anthony Mazlo
across that table,
you know I'll break him.
- The way you broke Perkins?
- Yeah, if need be.
You're not hearing me.
We need to hold off
on any meeting.
I don't...
That's final, Louis.
Question. Why would someone
named Lola Jensen
ever want to be known
as Mildred Wisnewski?
Who are you?
My name's Mike Ross.
I'm a lawyer.
Let me guess. Pearson Hardman?
You know, forging a government
document like this
after 911
is next to impossible.
God, there must have been
a glitch at the DMV.
Why'd you come here?
Your father came to us
'cause he's worried about you.
He's not worried.
He'd be here himself.
He wouldn't have sent
an empty suit.
You don't know anything
about me.
I, on the other hand,
know that you used this I.D.
To funnel payments
from clarity drilling
to some fake company
that you set up.
Locksley LLC?
You're stealing money
from your father's company.
Couple million so far.
I don't need to know why,
but I do need you
to return it. Now.
Actually,
you do need to know why.
This is ground water
from clarity's fracking
operation South of Tulsa.
It's got elevated levels
of dibutoxyethanol,
methane, and benzene.
This compares samples
taken pre-drilling
to levels taken last week.
How did you get that?
That's classified company data.
Let's just say
I'm good with computers.
Wait a minute. Locksley LLC.
As in Robin of Locksley,
as in Robin hood.
These toxins are known
to cause kidney failure,
liver cancer, and infertility.
The epa fines
were a slap on the wrist,
but the settlement
that your firm
negotiated with the victims...
It doesn't matter
how pure your motives are.
You're committing
a very serious crime.
Threaten all you want. Okay?
There's no way that my father's
gonna let this go public
right before his IPO.
I'm not giving the money back.
I'm giving it away.
In terms of living relatives,
I didn't find anything,
but when I looked into
the estates
of relatives who passed away,
e holding was originally
in the name of the aunt.
Your theory on Perkins
is right.
Harvey, what are you doing?
Rachel's services
are under my purview.
Sorry. I'm gonna change that.
Anthony Mazlo and his attorney
are in the conference room.
At whose invitation?
Oh, what,
you think I called 'em?
I... I didn't.
Then Mazlo feels
he has an advantage.
And he's pressing it.
Hey, fellas.
Thanks for meeting us
on such short notice.
I figured you'd be on a flight
right now, Mr. Mazlo.
Somewhere with no
extradition agreement.
Let's get to the point.
Without Perkins,
you don't have a case.
This report summarizes
an internal investigation
we conducted.
What Inez has just handed you
is hard evidence
of fraudulent investments
and fake losses
perpetrated by Perkins.
Guys have a real penchant
for fiction, don't you?
No, he duped all of us.
As ceo, he betrayed me
just as much as the investors.
We found an offshore account
worth 20 million.
Hold on a second.
Lucille Jackson trusts you
to manage
a $150 million endowment.
Perkins takes 20.
Where the hell's
the rest of it?
In light of these findings,
we'd like to offer
a settlement.
15 million.
Ten cents on the dollar?
That's a slap in the face.
Well, we advise all our clients
that investments carry risk.
You want a risk-free return,
buy treasury bills,
or, I don't know,
hide your money
under the mattress.
While you were writing
the great American novel,
I've been checking facts.
The 20 million
that Perkins had overseas
was legitimate.
He was innocent.
The money your firm embezzled
is still out there,
and this so-called
investigation
isn't worth the paper
it's printed on.
Well, Lucille Jackson
may beg to differ, counselor.
A bridge loan
means she's desperate.
Our offer is non-negotiable.
I won't accept this offer
today or a year from now.
Now since you've all
invited yourselves over,
feel free to see
yourselves out.
So first you attack me for
wanting to lie about Perkins,
and then you turn around,
do the same exact thing?
I wasn't lying.
What are you saying to me?
Harvey, what the hell
are you saying to me?
That Perkins had no
involvement whatsoever?
That's exactly
what I'm saying, Louis.
He was innocent.
It's no surprise
that Mazlo low-balled us.
I'm just passing along
this offer as a formality.
$15 million
is not insignificant.
But now's not the time
to settle.
We have to strengthen our hand.
All right, here's my problem.
Best-case scenario.
We go to trial,
the jury awards us a settlement,
obviously Mazlo appeals that.
It's three years
before I see any money,
and my foundation's
long gone by that point.
No, I'm not gonna let Mazlo
pocket the lion's share
of your endowment.
I'm not interested
in a pyrrhic victory.
Neither are we.
And to prove it, we're gonna
forego our usual fee,
and return to you the money
you've already paid.
I grew up
sleeping in my mama's car.
And in and out of more
halfway houses than I can count,
and one thing I realized
is that every penny matters.
So thank you.
What you gonna do?
Perkins may have been innocent,
but he was still
Mazlo's direct report.
I'm gonna find out
what he knew.
Your job is to verify
every detail
of Mazlo's
internal investigation.
It is not about the crime now.
It's about the cover-up.
This says Perkins acted alone.
Well, he's
the perfect scapegoat.
He can't defend himself.
You want to go to the bathroom?
You don't bother coming back.
By the way, that goes
for personal phone calls,
emails, and texts.
I detect a whiff of slacking,
you are done. Get it?
You find anything,
I'll be in my office.
Louis. Uh, I'm still
working on Harvey's case.
Jerome Jensen can go
screw himself for all I care.
Well, Harvey
explicitly told me...
I don't care if
a burning bush told you, Mike.
The only commandments
you need to focus on right now
come from me.
There's something wrong
with Louis.
It's not my problem.
I answer to Harvey.
Sitting home alone
with your kids, with no job.
Harvey.
You solve Jerome's problem yet?
Uh, about to. But I need
your corporate card first.
What for?
Well, I thought you didn't
want me to explain it to you.
You're right. I don't.
Okay.
It's killing you not knowing
what I'm gonna use this for,
isn't it?
Nope.
Please let me tell you.
If you bring that back to me
and it smells like stripper,
you're fired.
I don't... I don't go
to places like that.
You had to send someone?
Couldn't just call me?
If you wanted this
to be private,
should have just robbed me.
You robbed the company,
I had to involve other people.
Okay. Why don't we take a seat?
Why are you here?
I want to tell you
my side of things.
Okay.
I'm not proud of the fact
that we contaminated
people's water.
But we apologized.
We implemented safeguards.
We negotiated a payout
that was more than generous.
If that's what you think,
then you are lying to yourself.
I think that
we could keep this civil...
No, she's right. It's true.
I am lying to myself.
I thought this was a phase,
that it was hormones,
that it would pass,
but the truth is...
I raised a thief.
Okay, I think we're gonna
need a minute. Thank you.
A thief.
My research is making the planet
more habitable, okay?
You are making money
destroying it.
You have no respect for me,
that's fine.
But at least
respect the workers.
You're stealing from them too.
You think I'm such a criminal?
Arrest me.
So I organized this so that
you two could clear the air,
and it seems we've gotten
off the wrong foot...
You know what? It's the same
story as always, dad.
You duck your responsibilities.
Lo... Lola.
What if I paid the company
back with my own money?
I don't think that
would be a very good idea.
It would make you
a conspirator.
I'm not turning my daughter
into the police.
This is not about
the company image.
Well, the good news is,
she hasn't distributed
the money...
The money is irrelevant.
I came to Pearson Hardman
to take care of this.
Instead, my daughter and I
are further apart than ever.
I can't imagine
how hard it is right now.
People are saying the most
horrible things about Elliot.
They must think I've gone deaf.
Anthony Mazlo has been
dragging your husband's name
through the mud to make him
a scapegoat, Mrs. Perkins.
I'm here to help.
I don't understand.
You work for the other side.
I work for
a charitable organization
that had all its money stolen.
I'm on the other side of
Anthony Mazlo, not your husband,
and I don't want
to see his memory
painted with the same brush.
What would I have to do?
This isn't the time
or the place.
No, it's okay.
What would I have to do?
I'd like to know everything
Elliot has ever
told you about Mazlo.
Any details would help.
Miss Perkins,
uh, I'm Louis Litt,
and I just want to let you know
that I'm going to do
whatever it takes
to clear your husband's name.
His name?
My husband would be alive today
if it weren't for you.
Well, we don't know that.
I know what happened
in that room.
Well, at the time,
we didn't have all the facts,
but now we do.
I can't believe
that you have the audacity
to come here.
I don't ever want
to see your face again.
And you can forget
about me helping you.
What the hell are you doing?
I was deposing the widow,
just like you.
I came here to pay my respects
and initiate a relationship,
not aggravate a grieving woman.
Yeah, I brought flowers.
You just cost us
a potential witness.
Oh, really?
Well, maybe... Maybe if you shared
your game plan with me...
Oh, the same way that you
shared your game plan with me?
How do you expect her
to react to seeing you?
You need to get
your shit together
and find us a new witness.
Lola.
Wanted to apologize
for earlier today.
Can I come in?
Uh, yeah. Of course.
Nice gesture.
Botanical gardens.
Yeah, he said it was a pretty
special place for you guys.
It was. And then he became ceo.
But I'm not here to reminisce.
I must say I was, uh,
really impressed
you figured out
what I was doing.
Especially since you're
not even a real lawyer.
What... What are you
talking about?
I accessed Harvard
law school's alumni directory.
Every class that graduated
for the last ten years.
No record of Mike Ross. At all.
Yeah, the Dean's office
was supposed to fix that.
They... They put my name wrong
in the system.
I checked your
social security number
against the database.
How'd you get my social
security number?
Easily. Here's the deal.
Leave me alone,
or I expose you.
You don't really seem
that worried about this.
Threats like hers are a tactic.
They're effective
because they distract you
from what you're
supposed to be doing.
Are you crazy?
What we should be doing
is backing the hell off.
And how would that go, huh?
"Jerome, you came to
us with the problem,
"we discovered that
your daughter
"stole $2 million
from your company,
and our conclusion is
you're shit out of luck"?
I don't really care
how it would go.
All I care about is my life,
and... And keeping our secret.
I told you, it's a distraction.
She won't pull that trigger.
Why do you think she hasn't
distributed that money yet?
Why do you think Jerome doesn't
want us to go to the police?
I don't know.
It's because they both
want to bury the hatchet,
and if any of that stuff
happens, they can't.
Then what?
Figure out a way
to make them reconcile.
It's easy.
Yeah. It's easy.
Inez, right? Louis Litt.
I know who you are.
So is this what you do
for Mazlo?
You clean up his dirty laundry?
Leave me alone.
You know, you have
your whole career ahead of you.
Mazlo goes down and you're
part of this cover-up,
no one's gonna hire you.
I can't help you.
Listen, can I just
tell you something, Inez?
In my experience, people respond
to two things, okay?
And that's the carrot
and the stick.
Now, I prefer the stick,
and if you do not help me,
I will devote
my considerable expertise
to sticking it to you.
The same way
you stuck it to Perkins.
Inez, stop.
Let's go with the carrot.
Inez, Harvey Specter.
I appreciate you
coming forward.
I should have done it sooner.
What changed?
I can't be a part
of a company like that anymore.
Are you ready to testify
against Anthony Mazlo
in open court?
I am.
I assume you've documented
his malfeasance.
Because otherwise it's
he said, she said.
The entire paper trail.
From the beginning
all the way to last week.
Harvey asked me to fix
this problem with Lola,
but I can't.
Because your daughter's
not the problem, Mr. Jensen.
You are.
Are you trying to get fired?
No. I'm not.
I'm your attorney.
It's my job to give you advice.
But you're her father.
It's your job to raise her.
Now, you can go
to another firm,
but there's not a lawyer
in the city
that can do that job for you.
Please don't lecture me
on parenting.
Mr. Jensen, I had a difficult
relationship with my father,
so trust me when I tell you
that Lola wants to forgive you,
but she needs you
to take the first step.
Well, we tried it your way.
We went to lunch, and you saw
how well that worked out.
My daughter's not a child.
She's an adult.
She made these choices
as an adult.
If you just found a way...
You're my lawyer.
This is a legal problem.
My daughter
brought this on herself.
Now, I desperately do not want
her to go to prison.
But if she doesn't
return the money, she will.
Where's Mazlo?
He was afraid
to face us himself?
What do you want?
We know about
your entire scheme.
What scheme?
Oh, the scheme where
Mazlo's laundering money
through Dubai.
How do you know about Dubai?
We cultivated another source.
What kind of settlement
are you looking for?
One that includes
punitive damages.
Send Inez in here, please.
I don't think
you'll find her at her desk.
Why not?
'Cause she agreed
to testify for us.
I doubt that.
When your colleague
approached her,
she came straight to us.
He even tried to bribe me.
He said if
I ratted out Mr. Mazlo,
he'd get me a job as an
assistant to Jessica Pearson.
Everything she told you
is a complete fabrication.
There is no Dubai.
I seem to recall
you mentioning something
about penalties for perjury
at our last meeting.
Well, the penalty for bribing
a witness is just as severe.
And we're willing to overlook
that indiscretion
if you convince your client
to take our settlement offer.
Well, our revised
settlement offer.
- Revised?
- Yes.
Exactly half
of what it was before.
What the hell
were you thinking?
We needed a new witness.
You didn't think
to look into her story?
I don't know.
Did you look into it?
You were the one
who brought her in.
I assumed you had.
Like any halfway
decent lawyer would.
We were under the gun.
And I was under
strict instructions
from my golf pro
to get another witness.
No, I told you to get
another witness,
not bribe one.
That's enough.
As for the threat
against Louis,
no money changed hands.
I'm not concerned with Louis.
He brought your name
into it, okay?
The offer was to be
your assistant.
Now you're exposed
because of what he did.
Is that true?
She's an executive assistant
to the head of
a major investment firm.
She's not gonna work
for a junior partner.
So you tried to bribe her.
No, it wasn't a bribe, Jessica.
It was an incentive.
I thought she'd be
more likely to talk
if she wasn't worried
about getting fired.
I want you to go to Mazlo
and take their offer.
- I'm not ready to do that.
- I'm not either.
I waived Lucille's fee
because a certain
senior partner
said we'd never go to trial.
I said that before
you stuck me with Louis.
Not the point.
She can't afford it,
and neither can we.
Give me time.
Give it to me without Louis,
and we'll see who can
afford it and who can't.
You have until
the end of the day.
You come up empty,
I'm taking the offer
to Lucille myself.
Jessica. I went to Perkins...
Not another word.
You try something
like that again,
and it will be your last day
at this firm.
You said Jerome
wouldn't pull the trigger.
You were wrong. He's ready.
I don't have time
for that right now.
Harvey, when the police
show up at Lola's doorstep,
we're done.
Has she distributed
the money yet?
No, she hasn't, but she's...
She hasn't, and she won't,
because what she wants
is her daddy's attention.
Now sit down with me,
and let's deal with this.
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Why don't you tell me
what you need?
Mazlo was in Liechtenstein
the day that Lucille's
endowment evaporated.
Maybe he was skiing.
Nobody goes to
Liechtenstein for pleasure.
Why don't we subpoena
the bank records?
How many banks can there be?
Place is like
Switzerland on steroids.
We'll never see those records.
So what the hell
do you want from me, then?
What did you just say to me?
I once suggested
that we hack Harvard's records
to cover my ass,
and you laughed at me.
And now it turns out
that you were wrong,
and it's about
to cost me my career.
Where are you going?
You told me to fix my case.
Why don't you fix yours?
Hope you came here to tell me
Harvey's backing off.
I wish I could, but he's not.
That's too bad.
Had such a promising career.
Oh, my God. God, Lola,
you act like you care
about a higher cause,
but of all the companies
that exist,
you chose your dad.
Company that's trying
to make amends for what it did.
Really don't need
to hear another speech
from a wannabe suit.
God, you think
I'm your enemy, huh?
Well, I'm not.
I didn't even come here
to talk to you about me
or your father.
New York. Iowa. Kansas.
40 states that all
have housing projects
that will vanish if we don't
find out information
that only you can help us get.
So you can steal money
for your father's company
or you can blow the whistle
on me if you want to,
but if you
really care about people
the way that you claim to,
you're gonna do this first.
Are we close?
I'm accessing the banks
through a server in China.
Unless you'd rather
me use yours.
- Take your time.
- Done.
All right, there's 16 banks
in Liechtenstein.
This is every account
in every single one of them.
None of the accounts
is listed under Anthony Mazlo.
Forget about the name.
Find an account
with $150 million
embezzled from stable shelters
on that day.
Harvey, it's time.
Unless you have something,
I'm calling Lucille to settle.
Jessica,
you know how Liechtenstein
doesn't respond to subpoenas,
so I've responded for them.
Just trust me.
We've got everything we need
to find Lucille's money.
It's not here.
Sounds like you need more
than just another minute.
You need another person.
Someone whose expertise
is financial crime.
No. No.
Harvey, bring in Louis.
Or I'm calling Lucille.
Donna, I need to talk to Louis.
He's not in his office.
Huh. Norma wouldn't
tell you where he is?
Well, she didn't, um...
You didn't ask her, did you?
She gives me the creeps.
Ugh. You're such a wuss.
What did you just say to me?
I think we both know
what I just said.
Norma, where is he?
What? You're kidding.
- What?
- Shh.
I come here
when I need to be alone.
.44 Magnum?
Really?
Feeling lucky today, punk?
You know, I understand
that me pissing the bed
on this case
must be really, really
fun for you.
No. Louis, it's not.
The one thing
you and I have in common
is we need to win.
I noticed that.
I came here because,
even after everything,
we can win.
No.
I can watch while you win.
Louis, I'm not here
to give you shit.
Listen, I respect you.
I bribed a witness.
You incentivized her.
Went to see Perkins' widow.
To apologize.
I killed a man.
That you thought had it coming.
I don't think
you heard what I said.
I respect you.
You need my help.
I wouldn't phrase it
exactly like that.
Well, if you need my help,
you better phrase it
exactly like that.
Okay. You want me to say it?
I'll say it.
I'm under the gun,
and I need your help.
I've got information that you've
got the financial expertise
to break this case.
Now let's put the gun down
and go get 'em.
Okay.
First just stand over there.
Don't push it.
So what was the exact
amount of money
that was lost from
stable shelters' account?
Why?
$152,375,242.18.
I'm good with numbers.
Huh.
All right. What do you have?
We've compiled a printout
of every account
that had a deposit made
on the day in question
in all of Liechtenstein's
16 banks.
Okay. Well, we are going
to focus on, excuse me...
These five banks.
How can you be sure?
Watch this.
These four banks have a history
of capitulating to subpoenas.
So Mazlo would know.
These six
have U.S. corporate parents,
which would expose their
accounts to federal scrutiny.
Once again, Mazlo would know.
And then the one that he's got
right there is low in reserves,
therefore its solvency's
in question,
and there is no way in hell
that Mazlo would take
his stolen money
and put it into
some shaky bank.
So we can be sure.
Every person
who embezzles money,
they do it in their own way,
but the one thing
that they all have in common
is that they never put
all their eggs in one basket.
So we are going to be looking
at a combination of accounts.
Across banks.
Well, I mean,
maybe across banks.
Maybe the same bank.
But we're definitely looking
at more than one account.
How do we figure out
which accounts are his?
Because they're all
gonna add up
to the same exact
amount of money
that was lost from
stable shelters' account.
Well, how do you know?
When the account was drained,
it had to go somewhere.
What goes out from Lucille's
had to go into Mazlo's.
Simple law of mathematics.
So we just have to figure out
a combination of accounts
that adds up to...
$152,375,242.18.
I'm good with numbers too.
Thanks for meeting us
on such short notice.
Well, I assume you're ready
to take our offer.
I rushed right down.
Well, we just have
a few questions
before we get to any of that.
We didn't agree to answer
any questions.
No, no, Robert, it's okay.
I'm happy to play.
Have you ever been
to Liechtenstein, Mr. Mazlo?
You know,
I've been to many places.
Among them, Liechtenstein.
Really?
Well, of those many places,
did you open seven
different bank accounts,
the amounts of which add up to
exactly the same amount of money
that disappeared from Lucille
Jackson's endowment fund?
I doubt it.
Uh, what I don't doubt
is that if you trace the money
that went into those accounts,
you'll find that it came
from our corporate offices
in Sri Lanka.
It's completely legitimate.
I mean, I'm happy
to show you the records, uh,
whenever you'd like.
That's great. Isn't that great?
Well, after that,
can you show us the records
of the seven
safety deposit boxes
that you opened at those
same banks the same day?
I don't have to answer that.
This isn't a deposition.
You're so right.
It's more of a presentation.
We could make it a deposition.
- Or trial.
- Up to you.
We have pictures of you
entering those banks.
And we have enough
to crack their subpoenas.
Just a matter of time, Tony.
All right. What do you want?
What do I wa...?
Well, it's not about me.
It's about Lucille.
She wants your head on a stick
but she'll settle
for her money back.
And your resignation.
We agree right here,
no criminal prosecution?
Done.
If Lucille doesn't
get her money back today,
nothing's done.
Great. That's perfect.
You are back in business.
The wire transfer
just went through.
Girl, you came through.
That is what we do.
Harvey. Harvey, get in here.
Lucille wants
to thank you in person.
Always got time for gratitude.
Harvey,
you didn't let me settle,
and I appreciate your tenacity.
Truth is,
I didn't do this on my own.
Have you met Louis Litt?
You guys are doing
such good work.
I just want you to know it.
Have I told you how valuable
you are to this company?
'Cause you're not.
I'm just kidding.
Janice, I want you to take
the rest of the day off
because you're so good.
And I really mean it.
Harold, 9:30. Tequila shots.
You and me. Sharp. Be there.
Thank you.
- All right.
- See you later.
Louis. Luiz.
What's up?
What were you
just doing in there?
What? I was just...
Let me guess.
You were cutting me out.
- What are you talking about?
- The little impromptu meeting
you just had
with Jessica and Lucille
that you conveniently
left me out of.
I didn't leave you
out of anything.
I mean,
I thought we were a team.
I thought this was the start
of something, but I...
Now I see the truth
all too clearly.
Louis, I was walking by,
and they called me in.
Yeah, just in time to take
the credit for what I did.
I didn't do that.
Wouldn't even think
of doing that.
But you know what?
You would, and that's
your problem right there.
Got your email about Mazlo.
Not a bad way
for Locksley LLC to go out.
Looks like the
firm owes you one.
Think you owe me one.
Whoa.
Is this... The real thing?
Yeah.
Told the Dean's office
you'd lost yours,
and they were happy to oblige
for one of their top graduates.
I don't know if
you're awesome or terrifying.
Also I added a layer
of protection for you.
Uh, the Harvard law school
alumni database?
It's all there.
Your name, class rank,
social security number.
You do realize you just
made me party to a crime, right?
Can always call 'em up,
report it as a glitch.
Let me guess. Untraceable.
I'm not saying
you won't get caught,
but it won't be because
your story doesn't check.
Hey, um...
Thank you.
Seriously.
You're right.
Working things out with my dad.
Yeah.
Not the empty suit
I thought you were.
Who was that?
Uh, client's daughter.
Really? It's kind of late.
What's she doing
at the office at this hour?
You know, she was, uh,
just thanking me.
- Thanking you.
- Mm-hmm.
How'd she do that?
Easily.
She bought me
two tickets to Greece.
- Not interested.
- We leave Tuesday.