And you got your name
on the wall.
Now I want the respect
that comes with it.
Meaning?
I want one of harvey's clients.
(harvey)
my clients are my clients,
And if you don't get out
of my office
In the next three seconds,
Something's gonna happen
between you and me,
And I guarantee
it won't end with you
Keeping all of your teeth.
Avery mckernon
was the first client
I ever brought into the firm.
And they win, like me.
(mike) they know trevor
isn't in the class,
So they know he couldn't have
been the one to steal the test.
I'm not going to expel
your friend.
Thank you, sir.
I...
There's just one thing.
I'm gonna call harvard.
Believe me when I tell you
you're never going there.
Remember this?
No, you don't.
Because you can't remember
something you never knew.
You can't fire me.
Why would I fire you
when I can break you?
You see, I'm going to bury you
under a mountain of shit so big,
You're going to be begging me
to take it off.
First of all,
give me that manhattan
And go get yourself a drink
a man would order.
Come back here in 15 minutes,
And if I still remember
who you are, I'll be shocked.
Okay, so why are we really here?
I mean, you didn't just bring me
out to talk about khaleesi.
I did. Paul porter says
I look like her translator.
He's a throner?
Though he says
I'm a less-attractive version
Of her translator.
Okay, you're just trying
to get me to say
That you're hotter than her.
- Am I?
- You're way hotter.
But she has that accent.
Fair point.
You know, look, the reason
that I brought you here
Is to tell you that I know
that you told louis
That I got katrina a job.
- Look, I...
- Relax, I'm not mad at you.
But I do remember you
being the person
Who told me not to force things
That weren't meant to be.
Rachel, just because
a person gives advice
Doesn't mean that they have
to follow that same advice.
That's one of the core
principles outlined
In "the book of donna."
Seriously, though,
I didn't mean to tell louis.
It just came out.
I'm sorry.
Like I said, it's fine.
He actually ended up asking
if we could be friends again.
And?
And I told him that things would
never be the same between us
Unless he forgave mike.
And what did he say?
He said he couldn't do it.
(jessica) that's easy.
The jumper over ehlo.
Wrong, the switch-hand layup
over perkins and green.
I'm surprised at you, harvey.
The ehlo jumper
was a game-winner.
The layup was a statement.
"I can do whatever I want.
I own this league."
Are you talking about jordan
or yourself now?
Is there a difference?
A big difference,
Which brings me to why I'm here.
You can't do
whatever you want, harvey.
You want me to make things right
with louis.
He made things right
between jeff and me.
So I'm supposed to kiss his ass
forever because of that?
No, you're supposed
to make peace.
Jessica, I'm willing
to make peace,
But that's never gonna happen.
Why not?
Because louis
is never gonna forgive mike.
Then figure out a way
to make him forgive mike.
Donna, how many times
have I told you
I want you out front?
I'm the only associate
with a secretary.
It would be nice if people
could see my secretary.
Well, then maybe your next
secretary can figure out
Where to put this
without coming into your office.
- You're kidding?
- Not kidding.
You didn't forge this?
I am a lot of things,
but I am not a monster.
I would do that
to neither michael nor you.
- Oh, so he's michael now?
- Well, I'm donna to him.
He's michael to me, which
is what I told his airness
When he called.
Wait a second.
You're not kidding.
He signed with me?
Well, technically,
he signed with me.
Holy shit, donna.
We have to celebrate tonight.
Oh, I'm gonna celebrate.
You, on the other hand,
are having drinks with louis.
What?
We've been over this.
Whenever louis asks
to have drinks with me,
The answer's always no.
Listen to the words
that I'm saying.
You are getting drinks
with louis tonight.
Fairchild's retiring?
Fairchild's dead.
That's almost as good
as the jordan news.
Eh, not to fairchild.
Who gives a shit
about fairchild?
The real tragedy is
I have to get drinks with louis.
Which is why I got you
a secluded restaurant
With a table in the back
where no one will see you.
And you'll call a half an hour
in and say there's an emergency.
Already in place,
and if I can't get through,
Then I'll just have the waiter
spill drinks all over louis.
- You could have that done?
- Oh, please.
I could have louis held captive
In a tibetan monastery
if I wanted to.
Yeah, I don't think
you have that...
Now get the hell out
of your office.
I got work to do.
Hmm.
Excuse me. Can you tell me
where jim o'donnell's office is?
That depends. What do you know
about immigration law?
What, are we talking visas,
or are you trying to process
A labor certification?
You know about immigration law?
Doesn't everybody?
Okay, tough guy,
What do you think
about my strategy on this?
Hmm.
- I think it's a winner.
- Why is that?
Because everyone knows gonzalez
versus state of maryland
Was a kick-ass precedent,
but your case is better.
It was
a kick-ass precedent,
But I'm not sure that my case
is better.
Oh, it is.
Well, what
about viteri versus...
Trust me, it's better.
Viteri needed magic dust
and a sympathetic judge to win.
- Have we met?
- Nope.
But I'm mike, by the way.
Claire.
Are you sure?
Because you look very familiar.
Oh, that's probably because
I've been delivering packages
To your office
for the last two months.
But you haven't given me
the time of day,
Because you didn't think I was
smart enough for you.
It's 915.
Wait.
That worked?
It's working so far,
but I'm gonna need to know
Your full story
if it's gonna keep working.
Well, I'll tell you
the full story
Once you give me
your phone number.
I'll give you my number
when I know the full story.
How about this? I'll tell you
everything you want to know
At dinner tomorrow night.
In that case, I'll show you
where jim o'donnell's office is.
Jim o'donnell's office?
Where do you think
I just came from?
[knock at door]
I need you do something for me.
Okay, what is it?
Never mind what it is.
Unless you want to go back
to whatever you were doing
Before I hired you,
you'll be here at 9:00 a.M.
This is the address
for your car club.
Oh, yeah, your memory.
I'd remember this
even if I had your memory.
It was right before
our first case together.
You're right, mckernon motors.
So this time be on time
and put your seat belt on,
Because we're about to take
a trip down memory lane.
(man) ♪ see the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
(harvey) morning, sunshine.
- What are you...
- I think you call it a prunie.
Congratulations, donna told you
my favorite breakfast drink,
But what does that have to do
with the price of tea
In antarctica?
Donna also told me
that you were pissed,
Because you found out
I gave you a client
I didn't want
in the first place.
Hmm. And you think this is gonna
make up for that?
No, but I think giving you 50%
of mckernon motors will.
What's the catch?
The catch is, you and I
are about to take a road trip
To their corporate headquarters
right now.
You serious?
I don't joke
about mckernon motors,
And you know that as well
as I do.
To fairchild.
God rest his soul.
Screw his soul.
You know how they say
"heaven just got another angel"?
They ain't saying it now.
Why do you keep checking
your phone?
- No reason. I just...
- Please, I'm not an idiot.
We've been here 28 minutes,
and in 2 minutes,
Donna's gonna call
with some preplanned emergency.
Louis, that's not...
Look, why do you think I used
fairchild's retirement
To get you to have drinks
with me?
Because you knew I thought
it would never happen?
Because he doesn't have
an heir apparent.
Louis, if you're thinking
what I think you're thinking...
Hardman's not gonna make
one of us senior partner.
I'm not talking about one of us.
I'm talking about both of us
convincing hardman
That two kick-ass
junior partners are worth
As much as one new
senior partner.
Louis, that is the best idea
you've had since I've known you.
Yeah?
Here's another one.
When did you come up
with this one?
Of our half hour.
[chuckles]
[cell phone vibrates]
Don't you have to get that?
No, I don't.
Let's drink to this.
Asshole.
That was donna, wasn't it?
Trevor, this is so stupid.
It's not stupid, dickhead.
I want you to see it
for the first time
From the middle of the room.
It's your apartment, assface,
And don't even think about
giving me a wet willie.
You suck the fun
out of everything.
Go ahead.
Open your eyes, dickfoot.
- "Dickfoot"?
- I was gonna use "assface."
It's all I could think of.
How do you even manage
in the world?
Are you just gonna stand there
with your your eyes closed
And mock my "dickfoot"?
I'm definitely not gonna
open them to see your dickfoot.
That's a good point.
I wouldn't do that either.
Go ahead.
Open your eyes.
Wow.
Holy shit.
I thought you were getting
a studio.
Yeah, I was going to,
but then I realized
We can't both live in a studio.
What?
Welcome to casa evans and ross.
Trevor, I can't afford
half this rent.
That's the best part.
Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna pay
for your whole first year.
No, you're not.
I can't let you do that.
Michael, I start my new job
on Tuesday.
On top of that, I have
my friends and family business
On the side.
That doesn't mean I'm gonna
take charity from you.
Look, are you gonna
make me say it?
It's not charity.
I graduated, and you didn't,
Because you took the fall
for something I did.
I owe you.
[sighs]
Okay, I'll think about it.
All right, in the meantime,
think about this.
Ahh...
No, I can't.
- I got a date tonight.
- All right.
Wow, clubfoot, mustache,
all of the above?
First dickfoot
and then clubfoot?
Are words with "foot"
all you've got now?
All right, smart guy, describe
her with one of your sat words.
- Bigfoot.
- That's what I'm talking about.
For the record,
she's really hot.
(daniel)
let me get this straight.
Instead of promoting
an existing partner,
You want me to make both of you
junior partners.
Well, not make us.
We've earned it.
Earned partnership status?
That's a pretty bold statement
coming from two fifth-years.
Not just any fifth-years.
We're the best fifth-years
this firm has ever seen,
And you know it.
May I inquire whose idea
this was?
- It was both of ours.
- I was louis'.
(daniel) that's generous of you
To give him credit.
It was generous of him to come
to me with the idea.
The truth is, I wasn't
gonna make anyone partner.
But I do like admire
your gumption.
So here's
what I'm willing to do.
I will advance one of you
if you prove to me
Which one it should be.
No, see, that's the whole point.
We came in as a package deal.
You came in with a proposal.
I'm giving you a counter,
and it's take it or leave it.
What sort of proof
are we talking about?
Let's just say mckernon motors
is in play,
And landing them could go
a long way to making your case.
No way.
We're not gonna...
(harvey) all right, daniel.
You want mckernon?
I'll get you mckernon.
(louis) we're going to mckernon
motors, not your senior prom.
Why can't we just take
the car service?
Because we're going to
an engine manufacturer.
We need to show up
with a bad-ass car.
How about this little bad boy
right here?
That's no good.
Why the hell not?
Because it's not just
the two of us.
What do you mean?
You son of a bitch.
You said you and I
are going up there.
You lied to me.
Because if I didn't, you would
have never agreed to come.
There is no way I'm going.
Yes, you are.
I don't care if I have
to tie you to the roof.
By the time we get to mckernon,
You and mike are gonna
work your shit out.
I can't believe you did that.
The plan was to present
a united front.
And we did,
and he didn't go for it.
Then you stab me in the back?
I didn't stab you in the back.
I took what he gave us.
He didn't give us
anything, harvey.
He pitted us against each other.
Louis, we've been pitted against
each other since day one.
What are you talking about?
How many of the 50 associates
we started with
Do you think
are gonna make partner?
I don't give a shit
about the other associates.
We toasted to making
partner together.
I don't make the rules, louis.
Hardman does.
And as much as we say
he's an asshole,
I respect him for at least
telling us the deal out loud.
You want something out loud?
I'm gonna give you
something out loud.
No way on earth am I gonna
let you land mckernon motors.
[engine revving]
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
[music stops]
- Hey, what the hell?
- What the hell what?
This isn't a joyride, louis.
You don't want to talk,
you're gonna sit in silence
Until you're ready to talk.
Well, you can make me sit
in silence all you want,
But you can't make me
work it out with him.
- Then what can, louis?
- Excuse me?
You worked it out
with donna and rachel.
You lied to malone for jessica.
What's it gonna
take to work it out with me?
Well, I forgave those people,
because they were victims
Infected with the disease
known as mike ross.
Now I'm stuck in a car
with patient zero.
Okay, outbreak, patient zero
is the first person
Actually infected
with the disease,
Not the disease itself,
and for your information,
I'm stuck in the same car
as you.
At least you don't have to look
at the back of your own stupid,
Fat, balding head.
What's so goddamn funny?
You two are finally talking.
I think you earned
a little music.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
- That's it?
- Yeah.
All you have to do is pick one
of two characters.
And whichever character
I don't pick
Is removed
from film history forever?
It's like they never existed.
It's a piece of cake.
Okay, han solo or indiana jones?
- I'm out.
- What's the problem?
You just said it was gonna be
a piece of cake.
Of all time, so...
You're right about that.
I'm sorry.
Let me start with something
easier for you.
- All right.
- Butch or sundance?
Mm, check, please.
- [laughs]
- yeah, we're done.
No.
This is really nice.
Yeah, I'm having
a really good time too.
So when do I get to hear
the answer to what you do
Besides being a bike messenger?
Who says I do anything?
Look, mike,
there's nothing wrong
With being a bike messenger,
but I'm serious about my life.
I'm not going to law school
just to cash out.
I really want to help people.
Bike messengers
don't help people?
No, not in the way
that a man I want to be
In a relationship with does.
Well, then today
is your lucky day.
I knew it.
Where do you go?
Mm-mm, you first.
- Nyu.
- Columbia.
(both) I win.
[laughs]
- Good morning, jessica.
- Hi, daniel.
- I still haven't received...
- This year's budget?
I was just on my way
to give it to you.
And I thought maybe you hadn't
gotten around to it
Because you were too busy
pitting harvey against louis.
You disapprove.
I don't mind a little
healthy competition.
But I do mind the empty promise
of partnership.
What makes you so sure
there's no reward at the end?
The last time we discussed this,
You said harvey wasn't ready.
And you said louis wasn't.
Well, I'm giving them both
the chance to prove it.
So partnership is on the table.
Partnership was already
on the table.
What makes you so sure
it's gonna be harvey?
Because harvey will do
whatever it takes to win.
If doing whatever it takes
is the criteria,
My money is on louis.
What are you talking about?
I think we should continue
this conversation in my office.
[clears throat]
Hi, I've got a delivery
for a zoltan freastmeisterson.
I'm afraid there's no one
in this office with that name.
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Because I'm willing to bet that
there's no one on this planet
With that name.
Okay, fine, but if you could
just point me towards
Kumquat mcgillicuddy's office,
I'll be on my way,
Because I certainly
did not bike down here
With two fictitious deliveries
just to tell you
What a great time I had
last night.
Good, because I have a lot
of work to do.
So, if you could please just hop
on that little bike of yours...
- Claire?
- Yeah.
When you're finished flirting
with quicksilver here,
You might want to get down
to ins.
Hector suarez just got taken in.
Shit.
His visa's expired.
They're gonna send him back
to the dominican republic.
Wait.
Maybe I can help.
No offense,
I don't see how you can...
No, no, no, nathan,
he's not just a bike messenger.
He's in law school.
Really?
- Where are you in law school?
- Columbia.
And he happens to know visas
better than either one of us.
Well, I really
can't pay you, so...
No, I don't need any money.
I just want to help.
All right, columbia,
be my guest.
Got a hearing Tuesday morning,
9:00 a.M.
Mike, that is amazing.
Thank you.
Oh, no, don't thank me yet.
I haven't even done any...
Um, this might not be relevant,
but I actually saved
Kumquat mcgillicuddy's life
this morning, so...
I'm gonna go do some work.
Thank you.
Mr. Mckernon,
harvey specter.
Mr. Specter, would you mind
telling me why I have
Two different pearson hardman
lawyers on my schedule today?
I don't know, but after this,
You won't need to meet
the other one.
You're cocky.
I'm right.
You're also traveling
a little light.
Where's your
powerpoint presentation?
I don't need
a powerpoint presentation.
Why is that?
Because every lawyer in the city
has tried to dazzle you,
And you're still looking
for a date to the big dance,
Because they don't know
what you're looking for.
What exactly am I looking for?
Loyalty.
You're right.
I built this company
from the ground up,
And everybody that started
with me is still here.
And I know why.
You don't downsize
in the bad times.
They stick with you
in the good times.
And no other lawyer
has figured that out.
Not a single one.
Well, I'm the one, avery,
Which is why I know
you don't want me dumping you
For a bigger client
down the line.
How do I know you won't do that?
Because that's not the way
I work.
Well, it's a hell
of a nice sentiment.
But how do I know you're not
full of shit?
I'm glad you asked,
Because here's my
powerpoint presentation.
Okay...
I have a hearing tomorrow
against fletcher engines.
You win that, you're my lawyer.
(louis) seriously?
Okay, you know what?
Oh, jeez.
This is ridiculous.
You drive like a savage animal.
Louis, be a man and suck it up.
Suck it up?
I'm sitting in the death seat.
Fine. I'll pull over, and you
can sit in the back with mike.
Hey, I'm not sitting in the back
with a fraud,
And before you even think it,
you're not putting him up here
And sticking me back there.
Then what do you want, louis?
Because there is no way in hell
I'm letting you
behind the wheel of this car.
It's crystal goddamn clear.
You and I sit in the back, and
he chauffeurs the both of us.
Whoa, no. Even if harvey would
agree to that, which I doubt...
Shut the hell up.
You're not talking.
You don't get to refuse.
I'm not refusing, louis.
I don't know how to drive.
Holy shit.
You wanted to see me?
Uh, yes.
I heard you did well
with avery mckernon.
Well, then you heard wrong,
Because I killed it
with avery mckernon.
- Congratulations, harvey.
- Thank you, daniel.
You're welcome.
Unfortunately,
we can't represent
Mckernon motors after all.
Why not?
Well, it turns out
fletcher engines
Wants to sign with us.
Because they found out
I'm about to land mckernon.
Yes, and they're three times
the size of mckernon motors
Well, I don't care
how big they are.
I'm not dropping my client.
Yes, you are.
This was your plan all along.
Of course it was.
That's how the world works.
I don't give a shit
how the world works.
I gave my word
to avery mckernon.
Watch yourself, harvey.
I haven't gotten where I am
by watching myself, daniel.
And I don't appreciate
being used as a stalking horse.
Well, you may not appreciate it,
but let me remind you,
You work for me.
And I'm giving you the chance
to show me you understand that.
Let me remind you you said
partnership was on the table.
I'm gonna hold you to that,
and so will jessica.
[door bells jingle]
Hey, fart taster.
I thought you were coming over.
What, nothing?
It's a classic.
I'm implying your job
is to literally taste...
Hey, trevor,
I'm in the middle of something,
So I'll come over later, okay?
In the middle of what?
That girl I told you about,
She interns at a legal clinic,
And I am helping her
with a case.
Dickfoot gave you homework?
Okay, first of all, from now on,
her name is claire.
And second of all,
this is important, so...
Dude, what the hell
are you talking about?
I might have told her
that I'm in law school.
[chuckles] holy shit.
You will do anything
to get laid.
I am not trying to get laid.
I really like this girl,
and I have zero chance with her
If all I am is a bike messenger.
Yeah, well, you're definitely
gonna have no chance
If she finds out
that you lied to her.
Trevor, I don't want to talk
about this anymore.
You don't really want to talk
about anything anymore.
It's about the apartment,
isn't it?
- Yes it's about the apartment.
- Okay, you want the truth?
I haven't given you an answer
because of grammy.
You think I didn't know that?
Then you know
she's never forgiven you
For what happened in college,
And she is never, ever going
to let me live with you.
Then explain to her
that this is my way
Of making up for what I did
in college.
That is never gonna work.
You know what, michael?
If you're gonna do all of this
for some girl you just met,
Maybe it's time you stood up
to grammy for me.
How'd it go
against fletcher engines?
You cut them off at the knees
or put them in the ground?
They put me in the ground,
And on top of that, it was
in front of avery mckernon.
You lost in court?
I didn't just lose.
I looked like a fool.
Harvey, what happened?
The general counsel
for fletcher engines
Knew every move I was gonna make
before I even made it.
How could he...
Because hardman
must have tipped him off.
You really think
he would do that?
I wouldn't have yesterday,
but I sure as hell do today.
Then you have to go to jessica.
And say what?
Hardman's managing partner.
She's not.
I don't have any proof,
and I never will.
Well, then
what are you gonna do?
I don't know,
but I have less than 14 hours
To dig through 1,000 pages
of patent law.
[groans]
If only there was somebody
in the office who was an expert
On patent law.
Donna, I am not going to louis.
He'll never help me.
Well, that's too bad,
because if you can't figure out
How to patch things up
with louis,
Then you don't deserve
avery mckernon
Or that partnership.
What's all this?
Uh, a grandson can't order in
and set a table
For his grandmother?
A grandson can do
whatever he wants.
But the answer
to your question is no.
You haven't even heard
what it is yet.
I know what it is,
because I've been waiting for it
Since that kid graduated,
And you are not
gonna live with him.
That boy is the reason
you got kicked out of school.
You're the one that told me
to tell the dean the truth.
That was before I knew
it would cost you graduating.
And he's trying
to make it up to me.
He's gonna pay for my whole
first year's rent.
That will not make up
for putting your whole life
Into a tailspin.
- It's a head start.
- No, it's not a head start!
That boy is gonna drag you
back down with him!
Grammy, I'm never gonna let
that happen!
God damn it!
I forbid it!
[breathing heavily]
I'm sorry, michael.
I lost my temper.
But I know what he does to you,
And I know he'll
always be the same.
Has it occurred to you
that maybe I'm not the same?
What's changed?
I met someone.
And I'm gonna figure out a way
to finish school, and...
And then I'm gonna go
to law school.
Good.
Then do it from here
What's on your mind, mike?
You look lost in thought.
I was just thinking
about my grandmother.
We took a train trip
to d.C. Once.
[chuckles] we played I spy.
That's a nice story, mike,
but we are not playing I spy.
I'll play. It'll remind me of
dominating esther on our trips
To see our smelly aunt frida.
(harvey) all right, if it will
get you and mike talking, sure.
[clears throat]
I spy a fraud who probably
never even knew his grandmother.
All right, god damn it,
you got a problem with me,
Take it up with me,
but don't ever talk
About my grandmother again
Oh, I forgot, the poor orphan
From new york city
who I should feel sorry for
Because he never
learned to drive.
I'm telling you, watch yourself.
Why?
Because I hurt your feelings?
- Louis!
- I don't care.
For all I know, you're probably
not even an orphan.
It sure as hell wouldn't be
the first time a con man
Tried to make that claim.
- That's enough.
- No, it isn't.
Yes, it is.
Pull the car over right now.
I'm gonna beat the shit
out of him.
Hey, you got a minute?
Oh, wait.
Let me turn my back,
So I can give you the right
angle to...
You were right.
We should have stuck together.
I get it...
You need my help,
Because you got your ass wiped
in court this morning.
You're right. I did get my ass
kicked this morning,
But it wasn't a fair fight.
What are you talking about?
Hardman accessed my computer
And fed the other side
my game plan.
Okay, I'm still waiting
for the part
Where I'm supposed
to give a shit.
Hardman did it because
I refused to dump mckernon
For fletcher
after I gave him my word.
And why should I help you
When you couldn't live up
to your word to me?
I did live up to my word.
- We went to daniel...
- Oh, bullshit.
No, it's not bullshit.
I welcomed your idea
with open arms,
And by the way, when he asked
whose idea it was,
I gave you the credit.
You see, harvey, that's the part
you will never understand.
I didn't want the credit.
I wanted us to be a team.
Then let's be a team right now.
But you don't want to be a team.
You want me to help you
get mckernon
So you can make partner.
I want you to help me so I can
keep my word to avery mckernon.
And when I become partner,
I'll keep my word to you.
What the hell word is that?
That someday what you wrote
on that napkin
Goes up on the goddamn wall.
You seem to have done
a lot of work here, mike.
Oh, it's no big deal.
It is a big deal.
Mike found a loophole
in the immigration act of 1975,
And it's gonna blow you away.
I don't know about that,
But it may help hector suarez
stay in the country.
That's great.
And you're more than welcome
to stay and watch.
Unfortunately, claire, I need
you to run back to the office.
Marshall called in sick.
I need someone
to handle the walk-ins, so...
Okay.
Call me.
Tell me how it goes.
Yeah.
What the hell are you doing?
That's...
Gonna keep hector suarez
in the country?
Yeah.
Yeah, nothing's gonna keep him
in the country.
So what I'm going to do is
I'm gonna buy him some time
So he can get his affairs
in order,
And then I'm gonna give
his children a chance to stay.
[scoffs]
I'm just... I'm... I'm sorry.
Are you jealous of me
and claire or...
Hey, look, I'm not jealous,
and I was waiting
For her to leave to save you
the embarrassment.
The embarrassment of what?
That's good work.
I'm not talking about the work.
I'm talking about your
"bike messenger by day,
"Law student by night" bullshit.
All right, you don't know
what you're talking about.
What are you gonna tell me next?
Your roommate is a stripper
who's in medical school?
Tell me right now... I call
columbia, your story holds up.
That's what I thought.
Forget who I am,
and take a look at that folder.
- This is a man's life.
- Don't touch me.
If you know what's good for you,
You'll stay the hell away
from claire.
(harvey) daniel...
Did you know
that some of these species
Can live up to 200 years?
Fascinating.
Did you know fletcher engines
is picking up the pieces?
I guess congratulations
are in order.
I not here for a pat
on the back.
I'm here to tell you
you're making me partner.
Partner?
I never said signing mckernon
was the key to making partner.
Yes, you...
All I said was landing them
could go a long way
Toward making your case.
Bullshit.
You said partnership
was on the table.
And I said I was gonna
hold you to it.
And I'm going to right now.
You don't hold me to anything.
But I did say partnership
was on the table, and it is...
Just not for you.
What are you talking about?
Well, I can't very well
make you partner
After I just told louis
I'm making him partner.
What?
You don't get it, do you?
This isn't about
bringing in business.
This is about figuring out
who would do whatever it takes.
I did whatever it took.
You didn't do a thing.
You had the chance
to triple our business,
And all you had to do
was take a knee.
You mean bend a knee.
Yes, that's exactly what I mean.
But you're
an arrogant little boy
Who would rather win
than get in line.
Well, what the hell did louis do
to get in line?
He did whatever it took.
- Please get away from me.
- Claire, wait.
- Nathan told me everything.
- Just let me explain, okay?
No, explain what...
That you're a sociopath?
I'm not a sociopath.
I'm the same guy that you
hit it off with.
No, you're not.
You lied to me.
Yes, I am, and I didn't mean
to lie to you, okay?
I was gonna tell you the truth.
Then why didn't you?
Because you said you wanted
to be with a guy who was doing
Something good with his life,
and I wasn't.
So what, now you're here to
tell me that all of a sudden,
You want to dedicate your life
to helping people
Or some other lie like that?
It's not a lie, and what I did
would have helped hector suarez.
Yeah, but you only did it...
Claire, please,
you have to believe me.
After I met you, I decided
to get my shit together.
I am trying to get
my shit together.
Okay, mike,
you know what I hate more
Than guys who don't have
their shit together?
It's guys who lie about
getting their shit together.
Claire.
[car door closes]
Louis, fill up the tank.
I'll be back.
Well?
Well, what?
You heard what he said.
Fill up the tank.
Yeah, I did hear what he said.
He said,
"louis, fill up the tank."
Who fill up gas tanks.
Yeah, and where I come from,
If you take another step
towards me...
Oh, what, the tough kid from
the city is gonna beat my ass?
Louis, I'm telling you
right now...
You ruined my life.
You ruined my firm.
Louis!
[coughing]
[sobbing]
You son of a bitch.
Wait.
Harvey...
Tell me right now
you weren't the one
That gave fletcher engines
my game plan.
Hardman told me he wasn't gonna
make you partner anyway.
And once he offered it to me,
all I had to do was...
Sell me out.
How is what I did any different
than you going after
Mckernon motors
in the first place?
If you don't understand that
on your own, you never will.
So, from now on, you stay
on your side of the yard.
- I'll stay on mine.
- No, harvey, listen to me.
You told me you would fight
to get our names on the wall
Once you got on the other side.
I can do the same for you.
Did you hear what I just said?
I don't want you
doing shit for me.
Oh, so it would be okay
if you were the one
Who got there first?
It would have been okay
if you got there first
Fair and square,
Because then I would have
believed you
When you said you wanted
to be a team.
I do want to be a team, harvey.
That's why I helped you after.
No, you don't!
You don't want to be a team.
You just want to have it
both ways,
Because you're a disloyal rat.
You always have been,
and you always will,
No matter what it says
on your door.
Well, like you said, we've been
pitted against each other
Since day one.
You asked how many of the
50 associates we started with
Would make partner.
Well, you know what?
I don't give a shit
about the other 49,
Because I'm the one who did.
I'm the one who did.
And now get the hell
out of my face,
Because I have work to do.
You know he did that
on purpose, right?
Did what on purpose?
He asked you to fill the tank
because he knew what you'd do.
Knew what I would do?
What about what you would do?
He knew that too.
Louis...
You never even said
you were sorry.
I am sorry, louis.
I'm sorry that I lied to you.
I'm not a con man, louis.
Every single other thing
I ever told you was true.
Want to know something that I've
never even admitted to myself?
I never learned to drive
for the same reason
I never went to law school.
Both my parents were killed
in a car accident.
And ever since then,
I've never been able to...
Get behind the wheel.
And then harvey gave me
a license, and I took it.
You were 11 years old.
I mean, you must have felt
so alone.
I thought you said you
didn't believe I was an orphan.
I looked it up.
I had to once I found out that
you never went to law school.
You mean once you found out
that I'm a fraud.
You're not a fraud, mike.
You just never went
to law school.
Okay, frazier, you get a grape.
Ali, I got you a fruit punch.
You two work your shit out?
I'll take that as a yes.
Let's get the hell out of here.
I should never have lied to her.
Oh, screw her, man.
If she doesn't like you
for who you are,
She doesn't deserve you.
It's not claire's fault.
It's mine.
I know you were into her
and everything,
But trust me,
There are plenty of other fish
in the sea.
You don't know that.
For all you know,
I'm never gonna meet
Another girl like her again.
[sighs] michael...
Trevor, if I'm gonna have
to listen
To whatever you're about to say,
I'm gonna need a joint first.
Come on, I thought you were
trying to turn your life around.
I'll turn my life around
tomorrow.
But tonight
I'm a bike messenger, so...
- Dude...
- Trevor.
All right.
Fine.
And I know grammy
doesn't want you living here,
But you can crash here tonight
if you want.
[exhales deeply]
Donna.
Something wrong?
Why would something be wrong?
Because I don't believe you've
ever been in my office before.
No, nothing's wrong.
And I know it's not my place,
But I'm here to tell you that
I think you're making a mistake.
Is this about me not giving
people off for columbus day?
You know this isn't about that.
Harvey laid it on the line
with daniel,
And you didn't have his back.
Donna, I've had harvey's back
since the day I met him.
For your information,
when I found out
What daniel was up to,
I had him guarantee
Partnership was on the table.
And then you let him give it
to the wrong man.
That is on harvey, not on me.
What are you talking about?
Daniel was worried
that harvey couldn't put
The firm's best interests
ahead of his own,
And harvey proved him right.
Or maybe you're just
telling yourself that
Because you don't want
to stand up to daniel hardman.
Donna, there's a reason
why you are where you are
And I am where I am,
and that is because
One of us sees
the bigger picture.
You knew about fletcher engines?
What I know is that
harvey's time will come.
And if this little incident gets
him to think about other people
For a change, then I'll take it.
You're up early.
I'm up early,
because I couldn't sleep.
Where we you all night?
You know where I was.
I was staying
at my new apartment.
I thought we'd settled this.
You settled it.
I didn't.
[chuckles]
I'm telling you, that kid...
Grammy, for as long
as I can remember,
You've been calling him
"that kid"
Or "that boy" or worse.
His name is trevor.
And he's my best friend.
Look, I'm gonna do this thing
with our without your blessing,
But...
It sure would be nice
to have it.
Okay, michael.
I'm not gonna lie to you
and pretend I approve,
But...
You're a grown man,
and I respect your decision.
I love you, grammy.
I love you too.
Thank you.
I believe that's all
I need to know.
Thank you for your time,
ms. Pearson.
I will wait to hear from you.
Oh, one more thing...
Does your father know you came
to me for a job?
I-I...
Did you really think
I didn't know
You were robert zane's daughter?
Is that why
you're interviewing me?
Because if it is,
I would like to remove myself
from consideration.
If you don't want to work
for your father,
That's your business.
I'm hiring you
because I like what I see.
Hiring me?
You start Monday,
if that's not too much trouble.
I will be the first one in.
Aren't you gonna ask me
why I don't want to work
With my father?
I know why.
I have a dad just like yours.
He has his own law firm?
He's a surgeon.
But it's the same damn thing.
[giggles]
[exhales sharply]
- How are we on time?
- We're perfect.
But I'm not going in there.
You two are.
What are you talking about?
I said I was giving you 50%
of mckernon.
I didn't say I was keeping
the other 50%.
Oh, so you finally realized
they need an upgrade
In representation.
Easy, frazier.
You'd still be out cold
at that gas station
If I hadn't saved your ass.
Okay, I would have gotten out...
Eventually.
- Not from where I was standing.
- I'm slippery.
I told you...
I wrestled in high school.
- I checked on that. He did.
- See?
Oh, and now
you're fighting for him?
Okay, I guess
my job here is done.
Wait.
Where are you going?
I'm taking the car back
to the city.
Well, what the hell are we
supposed to do?
Ray's waiting on the other side
of the parking lot, isn't he?
He'll drive you two back
when you're done.
Wait. You know what?
I have a better idea.
How about you take ray,
we take the car,
And I teach mike how to drive
on the way home?
- You'd actually do that?
- Yeah, I would.
- No way.
- You don't trust me?
I don't trust you
as far as I can throw you.
You're a goddamn fraud.
- That's what I said.
- Harvey, seriously.
- Come on, I promise
- okay, I know you will.
Louis, you make one dent
in this car,
Mike's back on the street,
and your name's off the door.
You think he was serious
about what he just said?
Okay, well,
I'm just a little nervous,
'cause I feel like I drank
that power drink,
And it has a lot
of sodium in it.
Actually, it's like
drinking a hot dog,
But the doctor says it raises
my blood pressure, so...
(mike) I'm gonna need you to let
me do the talking in there.