Previously on "Suits"...
Your execution date
has been set.
- When?
- 30 days.
You said you were
gonna find Maria.
You have one week
to find a witness.
After that, his execution date
is set in stone.
We found the guy who's been
feeding Sutter his information.
Phillip Allen.
I know.
He came by to cut a deal
two hours ago,
so I gave him one.
- No you goddamn didn't.
- Relax.
As far as the SEC is concerned,
Mike lead directly
to the witness who's gonna put
that piece of shit away
for the rest of his life.
You have a small window
to come clean with the SEC
and save yourself.
I would never turn
on my own father.
I didn't take this deal
for that son of a bitch.
I took it for my wife.
And if you ever contact her
again without my blessing,
I swear to God, I will
beat the shit out of you.
Jim Rogers found
your missing witness.
She died three years ago.
You're informing on
your roommate.
I know it, and if you don't
get me out of here soon,
your bunkmate's gonna
know it, too.
They pulled Mike's deal.
Goddamn it,
I drove that guy to you!
If I tell them that,
they're gonna know what we did.
Sean, please,
there's got to be
another way
to make this happen.
I'm sorry, Harvey,
there isn't.
Jessica, can I talk to you
for a second?
Harvey, can it wait?
I just got some bad news
about our death row case.
No, it can't.
Cahill just pulled Mike's deal.
What?
I thought he was
a man of his word.
He's saying
it wasn't him.
It was his superiors, but what
difference does it make?
It makes all the difference
in the world,
because if it's him,
you can go over his head.
I go over his head,
everybody knows
we're in on
this thing together.
So what you're telling me is,
not only are they pulling
Mike's deal, but you're going to
lose this case for nothing?
Yeah.
I guess that's what
I'm telling you.
Then you're not gonna like
what I have to say.
[tense music]
But if Mike's not getting out,
you might as well win.
What?
Harvey, we're in the middle of
building ourselves back up.
You lose this case,
we take it in the knee.
- Jessica, the guy is guilty.
- And you're his goddamn lawyer.
And you took this case.
And I never would have
taken it if it wasn't
to get Mike out.
Well, you did take it.
And if it's just gonna kick us
back down the mountain,
then I don't care
what it takes.
You win that goddamn case.
♪ ♪
We're gathered to hear
the United States
versus William Sutter on
the charges of insider trading.
Is the prosecution prepared to
deliver its opening statement?
We are, Your Honor.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
William Sutter has been earning
outrageous returns for decades.
Now, I'm sure the defense is
going to try to
convince you Mr. Sutter
trades with his gut
or his instinct or some
mysterious explanation
that is impossible to verify.
But that isn't how
he makes his money.
And we can prove it.
We have a witness that can
document giving
inside information to
William Sutter time
and time again
over the last ten years.
And when we present
that witness to you,
you'll be leaping out of
your chair to convict
that man beyond
a reasonable doubt.
Mr. Specter.
What the hell witness
is he talking about?
Didn't it have to be
in discovery?
It sure as hell did.
What're you
gonna do about it?
I'm gonna stop it
dead in its tracks.
Mr. Specter, is the defense
ready to deliver
its opening statement?
No, Your Honor, but we are
ready to request
an immediate three-day delay
of these proceedings.
On what grounds?
The prosecution
knows what grounds,
because he just violated
the rules of discovery.
Your Honor, I have absolutely
no idea what he's talking about.
Yes, you do because you just
introduced a witness
into your opening
statement and this is
the first
I'm hearing about it.
It's the first you're hearing
about it
because the witness just came
forward yesterday.
I'm sorry,
did the Internet go down?
Did you go over the limit on
your friends and family plan?
Because we're required
to be notified
and I don't even know
what this person's name is.
His name is Phillip Allen
and he's prepared
to put that man behind bars
where he belongs.
Mr. Cahill, that's enough.
Your Honor, we need three days
to depose this witness.
This is ridiculous.
They've lost, they know it, and
they're just trying to stall.
Then you should have thought
of that before you decided
to drop this bomb
in my courtroom.
Mr. Specter,
you have three days.
♪ ♪
I wasn't expecting you
so soon.
We have some news
we wanted to give you in person.
We found Maria Gomez.
Leonard, she died
three years ago.
What does that mean?
It means that we have five
more days to find
something we can use
to get your case re-opened.
That sounds like a polite way
of telling me
that in 30 days, I'm gone.
And what if there was a way to
get us more than five days?
Let's take it.
You have the right
to have a family member
present at your execution.
If you have a relative
that's sick, who needs time
to get better to travel,
we can petition the court
for a delay
and they have to grant it.
The woman who raised me,
my Aunt Harriet.
She has MS.
But that's not gonna
do us any good,
because she doesn't want
anything to do with me.
She never came to visit you?
She thinks I'm guilty.
Says I brought shame
on the family.
Even if you did,
you need her now.
She has to see that.
I reached out to her, Rachel,
a thousand times
my first years here.
I wrote her that there's
nothing I needed more
than to know that
I had her support.
She didn't give it to me then,
and...
she's not gonna
give it to me now.
Well, maybe if she could see
that two women like us
believe in you, then she'll
be able to believe in you, too.
If you can make that happen,
that would mean the world to me.
Then we'll make that happen.
♪ ♪
That was nice work in there.
Think it was good enough
to get us a mistrial?
Mistrial? You're lucky they
didn't find you
guilty after that.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Enough bullshit, William.
This isn't the SEC asking
anymore, this is me.
Who the hell is Phillip Allen
and what the hell
is he gonna tell them?
He's an investment banker,
used to work for me.
He's not gonna tell them
shit about me
because he doesn't know
shit about me.
Then why were you so surprised
when they said they had him?
Because he can tell them
about my daughter.
I get it.
He gives inside
information to her,
so if this goes down,
she goes down instead of you.
No one's going down.
'Cause they can't prove
she told me what he told her.
Which means, if you do
your job, we both get off.
William, you're taking
a huge risk.
What the hell you think I
hired a gunslinger like you for?
So stop telling me I can't win
and go ahead and start winning.
♪ Suits 6x08 ♪
Borrowed Time
Original Air Date on August 31, 2016
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
You keep eating eggs
every morning,
you're gonna
have a heart attack.
Didn't you hear?
They're good for you now.
What happens
five years from now
when they become
bad for you again?
Worried something's
gonna happen to me?
I'm worried I'm gonna have to
deal with another roommate.
Took me long enough
to get used to you.
Kevin...
I'm sorry.
Water under the bridge.
All right? You had my best
interest in mind.
You want some bacon?
Man, that's always gonna
be good for you.
[chuckles]
Amen to that, brother.
Look who it is.
Frick and Frack.
We're in the middle of
a conversation, Gallo.
Oh, I bet you are.
Mike here's an excellent
listener, isn't he, Kevin?
- What do you want?
- Nothing.
It's just nice to see you guys
are such good friends.
Nice to know
you can trust each other.
I only wish I could trust that
Mike here was really
working on getting me
out on parole.
We are working on it.
Well, you're running
out of time.
- Would you listen to me, Gallo?
- No, there's no listening!
You got until 6:00 tonight
to get Harvey down here
or after that,
I'm gonna schedule
a little hearing of my own.
♪ ♪
- Can I help you?
- I hope so.
My name's Rachel Zane.
And I'm a lawyer working on
your nephew's case.
My nephew's case was over
a long time ago.
And thank God for that.
Ma'am.
I'm here because we believe
Leonard was wrongly convicted
of those murders.
Well, that's what
they all say, isn't it?
But just because he suckered
you, doesn't mean
he's gonna sucker me.
He didn't sucker anyone.
I looked at the evidence
and I got to know the man.
So you got proof
he didn't do it?
We're working on it.
But if we can't find a way to
push back the execution,
then in 30 days
it won't matter anymore.
What do you want from me?
I want you to
ask the court for a delay
so you can be with him
at his execution.
I'm not gonna
watch him die.
Ms. Deon, please.
You raised him.
I raised Leonard from
when he was 14 to 17.
I took him in,
I loved him,
He was no good then
and he's no good now.
Well, if that's the case,
you don't have to be
at the execution.
But if you could sign
this request that says
you're too infirm
to travel this month,
it will at least give him
the chance to prove you wrong.
♪ ♪
I'll sign your letter.
But I'm not
watching him die.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
There you are.
I've been on pins
and needles all morning.
How was dinner?
It was a complete
and total shit show, Donna.
Louis, what happened?
What happened was,
I found out the woman
of my dreams is spoken for.
- She's married?
- She might as well be.
She has this long-term boyfriend
who lives in California
and they have this arrangement
where they see other people.
And even though it was the most
wonderful night of my life,
I'm moving on.
I don't understand.
The most wonderful
night of your life?
Why did you even
stay through dinner?
Because she gave me some line
about being the only person
she'd ever done this with.
But now that I think about it,
what the hell difference
does that make?
Huh.
I think it makes
all the difference in the world.
What're you talking about?
Louis, if you're really
the only man she's ever
done this with, then that means
you've got something
that this other man
doesn't have.
How could you know that?
They've been together
three years.
I can't compete with that.
Because when you're happy, you
don't go looking somewhere else.
Donna--
Louis, I told you I broke up
with Mitchell,
but I didn't tell you why.
He wanted to see
other people.
He wanted to
move in with me.
And when he asked me, I started
picturing a life with him.
And that's when I knew
he wasn't the right one for me.
How can I know
I'm the one for her?
You can't.
But you'll never know
if you don't fight for her.
♪ ♪
[phone rings]
Harvey Specter's office.
You have a call from
Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept--
Yes.
Donna, it's me,
I need to talk to him.
I don't have him, Mike,
he's in court.
I don't care where he is.
I need to know what's going on
with Gallo's parole hearing.
Nothing's going on.
What the hell do you mean
"nothing's going on"?
Harvey was hoping that you
were gonna be out of there
before he had to
go through with it.
Goddamn it, Donna,
Gallo knows about
me and Cahill.
If he doesn't see some progress
by the end of the day,
he's gonna tell Kevin.
Mike, Harvey didn't want you
to know this yet, but...
there is no you and Cahill.
- What?
- Cahill pulled your deal.
What the hell
are you talking about?
His superiors said you didn't
hold up your end of the bargain.
That is bullshit!
I've been busting my ass to hold
up my end of the bargain.
I know that
and Harvey knows that,
and he's trying to
get your deal back.
Well, you tell him that
while he's getting around
to making Cahill honor his
goddamn word,
maybe he could take just
a minute to honor his word
and get Gallo
his goddamn parole hearing.
♪ ♪
- I got it.
- She signed it?
She did, and an affidavit
from her doctor, too.
All right, I'll go to court
and make this happen.
You start going back through
every piece of evidence we have
because this gives us
some breathing room
to find something,
but we have to deliver.
- Jessica...
- Look, Rachel,
I know you want
to go to court with me,
but we don't have the time--
- No, that's not it.
- Well, then what is it?
She signed
the request, but...
she wouldn't actually agree to
be there with him if--
Rachel.
It's not our job to
reunite him with his family
if it comes to it.
It is our job to make sure
it doesn't come to it.
I meant she doesn't
want to come
because she thinks
that he did it.
And if we can't convince his own
aunt that he's innocent,
how are we gonna convince
12 strangers?
Right now, I'd rather
focus on the fact that
we're getting the man another
30 days to save his life.
♪ ♪
Mike, sit down.
I need to talk to you.
You needed to
talk to me yesterday
when Cahill decided
to pull my deal.
He's saying it was
the people above him.
And I didn't want to
tell you about it
until I figured out
how to get it back.
Yeah, well the amount of
things you're not telling me
are really starting
to pile up.
I know you found out
about Gallo.
I'm sorry.
But I give you my word,
it's being taken care of.
Oh, like my deal was being
taken care of?
Listen to me.
I'm gonna neutralize
Phillip Allen so you still have
a chance to walk out of here.
But that's not gonna happen
if you don't get Jill Miller
to testify against her father.
Goddamn it, Harvey,
I've been down that road.
Jill's not gonna go for it
and neither is Kevin.
Well, then you better
figure out a way to make him,
because once I blow
Phillip Allen out of the water,
the next person up on Cahill's
hit list is Kevin's wife.
♪ ♪
[line trilling]
- Hello?
- Hey, Tara.
It's me, Louis Litt.
I know who you are, Louis,
you don't have to use
your last name.
Well, I don't like
to be presumptuous.
I mean, you can have
another man--I mean--
you can have another Louis
in your life.
Speaking of other men, Louis.
I'm glad you called back.
I had an amazing time
the other night,
but I wasn't sure
you were okay
with what I told you
about me having a--
Oh, please, Tara, it's 2016.
If a man can't be okay with
his woman seeing other men,
then what was Susan B. Anthony
even fighting for?
[chuckles]
Well in that case,
Louis Litt,
how'd you like to
go out tonight?
Tonight?
[upbeat music]
Um, I'd love to.
Then tell me where to be,
and I'll meet you there
at 7:00 p.m. sharp.
Okay.
Jessica Pearson in court.
I haven't seen that
in a while.
I like to get back in the ring
from time to time.
So what giant companies
are you merging today?
Behemoth Steel
and Global Everything?
That was Tuesday.
Today, I am here to save
a man's life.
We took over an
Innocence Project case.
Innocence Project?
So what're you trying to do,
rehabilitate your firm's image?
What I'm trying to do
is help a man get justice.
And if doing that helps my firm
look good, even better.
Fair enough.
How have you been, Jeff?
I've been good.
Listen, I know we talked about
me looking you up
when this whole mess
was over, but...
I want you to know--
It's okay, Jessica.
I understand.
No.
What I mean is,
it's not over.
I'm still in it.
You really are fighting to
rehabilitate your image,
aren't you?
I am.
It was good to see you,
Jessica.
It's good to see you too,
Jeff.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What're you doing here, Sean?
I'm here to protect
my star witness.
He's got his own
attorney for that.
I don't care.
And we're here for you
to get your discovery,
not lecture me
on procedure.
I'm here to demonstrate
how Mr. Allen's
cross examination's gonna go,
now sit the hell down.
Mr. Allen, what exactly
are you getting in return
for your testimony
against my client?
He's getting immunity for
the crimes he committed.
Are you gonna answer for him
when he's on the stand, too?
What were those crimes?
I gave William Sutter
inside information
over the course of a decade.
And how, exactly,
did you do that?
When my bank was hired to
review a transaction
and I determined
it was going through,
I'd call Jill Miller
and I'd give her
the relevant names
of the parties.
Jill Miller?
I'm confused.
You told the SEC that you were
feeding William Sutter
inside information.
- We had an understanding.
- Understood by who?
William Sutter.
Did you ever have a specific
conversation with Mr. Sutter?
I mean, when was the last time
you were even
in the same room?
Jill said
that he understood.
Bullshit, you can't testify
William understood anything.
It's called hearsay.
It's called the truth.
I don't give a shit
what you call it,
if you don't have proof,
the jury can never hear it.
Do you have proof?
Oh, I don't believe this,
you don't have a paper trail.
- I have the phone records.
- I mean to Sutter.
She's his
goddamn daughter!
Yeah, and every murderer
has a father, too,
doesn't mean they're
in on the crime.
Save your metaphors
for the trial, Harvey.
We don't need them here.
I don't need to save anything
for trial
because you made a deal with
this man for nothing,
you handed me my best witness,
and this deposition's over.
♪ ♪
You son of a bitch.
How dare you?
How dare I what, Sean?
Defend my own client?
Bullshit, you weren't trying
to defend your client.
You were trying to ruin my case
'cause you're
pissed off about Mike.
I sure as hell am.
We had a deal
and you broke it.
So now I'm breaking it, too.
Well, you know what, Harvey?
I don't care what you're
breaking, 'cause Phillip Allen
gets me the daughter and that
gets me right back to Sutter.
Good, 'cause that's exactly
what I'd expect you to do.
♪ ♪
Oh, I get it.
You weren't trying to
win this thing.
You just wanted to discredit
Phillip Allen so I'd have
no choice but to
reinstate Mike's deal.
You're damn right
that's what I wanted.
So instead of getting mad at me
for doing what you should have
done in the first place,
why don't you start turning up
the heat so Mike can get
this goddamn woman
to turn on her father?
♪ ♪
- Kevin.
- Oh, good, you're here.
You can help.
I know you made me promise
not to bring this up again--
- Mike, I told you--
- Listen to me.
I just talked to Harvey.
A man named Phillip Allen has
come forward and he's gonna--
Wait, you talked to Harvey?
Listen, this guy
cut a deal with Cahill.
All right? That means
he knows all about it.
What do you want from me?
I want you to convince her
that this is it.
She has a one-time chance
of getting immunity
if she turns on
her father now.
How the hell do you even know
this Cahill guy'll do that?
Because I know how bad
he wants Sutter,
and offering Jill a deal is the
best way to make that happen.
Or he promises her a deal,
then takes it away.
And no one's kissing my kids
good night
for the next two years.
Harvey wouldn't
let that happen.
He's William's lawyer.
He's not selling out
his own client.
You're his client, too.
Only to protect the guy
who's paying his bills.
He doesn't give
a shit about me.
Maybe not, but he does
give a shit about me!
What're you--
what're you saying?
♪ ♪
I'm saying that
offering Jill a deal
doesn't just get
her out of prison.
It gets me out, too.
♪ ♪
You've been
informing on me, Mike?
Yes.
Get the hell out of my sight,
you traitor piece of shit.
Kevin, listen,
I'm only telling you this
so that you'll see--
See what?
How full of shit you are?
Telling me you grew up
without a mom and dad
just to gain my trust--
That is not why I did that.
And I just told you the truth
so that you trust
that I care about you.
Bullshit, 'cause here you are,
willing to leave
two little kids all alone just
to get your goddamn freedom.
- Kevin, I'm sorry--
- No, you're not.
But you're about to be.
[blow landing]
Come on, fight!
Fight back, you traitor!
Fight me back!
You have to listen to me!
Come on, fight!
[both grunting]
[blows landing]
♪ ♪
- This isn't done, Mike!
- Get him out of here now!
- No, no, no--
- Get him to solitary now!
No, not solitary!
It's my fault, it's my fault!
You don't have to do this!
Ross, Ross!
Another word, and you're
going to solitary, too.
♪ ♪
[cell phone buzzing]
Harvey Specter.
You have a call from
Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept the charges?
- Yes.
- Harvey.
Mike, good.
I did my part and I took
care of Phillip Allen.
Tell me you did yours and got
Kevin to talk to his wife.
I tried.
Instead, I got him
put in solitary.
What?
How the hell did that happen?
I told him I was
informing on him
and then he started
beating the shit out of me.
Are you kidding me?
Why would you do that?
Because lying
wasn't getting it done
and I'm living on borrowed time,
so I thought I might as well
tell him, anyway.
Then you better figure out
a way to get him out of there,
because we need to get Jill
to turn on Sutter
before Cahill gets her to.
That's why I'm calling you.
I already have a way,
I just need to know
you did that other thing
you were supposed to do.
I need to know you got Gallo
his parole hearing.
[tense music]
Let's get to it.
What happened?
Good news.
The court granted our motion.
They pushed your execution
back a month.
I don't believe it.
You convinced my aunt
I didn't kill those people?
- No, Leonard, I didn't.
- I don't understand.
You said that she had to agree
to be there for me.
She agreed
to sign the papers.
But she's not gonna come.
Goddamn it.
Leonard, don't take
your eye off the ball.
This was about
buying us time.
Take my eye
off the ball?
Do you even
give a shit about me?
Of course we do.
Yeah, I know you do.
But I want to know
if she cares
whether I live or die.
I just got your execution
pushed back.
That's not
what I asked you.
You didn't even
go see her, did you?
I have a firm to run.
And only one of us
needed to get her signature.
But two of you
could've helped convince her
that I'm innocent.
Don't you get it?
The woman who raised me
wants nothing to do with me.
Leonard, I know you're
disappointed.
But it's not my job to repair
your relationship
with your aunt.
It's my job
to get you out of here.
I ain't never
getting out of here!
Don't you understand that?
So you go play your game
with the courts.
But whether it's
30 days or 60 days,
it doesn't matter, 'cause
I'm gonna die in here, lady.
The one thing I asked you
to do, you didn't.
♪ ♪
You didn't even
care enough to try.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Just get out.
♪ ♪
You better be here to tell me
I have a hearing.
That's exactly
what I'm here to tell you.
But you're not gonna
have anything
unless you do
something for me.
Bullshit.
Wasn't part of the deal.
I don't give a shit.
I'm tired of you
threatening me,
so if you even want a chance of
getting out of here early,
you're gonna
do something for me.
And by the way,
it's too late to tell Kevin that
I've been informing on him.
I already did.
What do you want?
I need you to get him
out of solitary.
You're kidding me, right?
I can't do that
That's bullshit.
You switched into my cell
the first night and ever since,
you've been bragging about
everything
that you can do in here,
so how about you stop
telling me that
you can't do it,
and just tell me
whether or not you will.
♪ ♪
All right, Mikey.
I'll get your ticket to freedom
out of solitary for you.
But if you get out of here
and I don't,
you should know, I can get to
you just as easily out there
as I can in here.
And when I say "get to you,"
you got to remember what I did
to make Harvey put me away
in the first place.
♪ ♪
Do you want to talk about
what happened at the prison?
No, Rachel, I don't.
Because whether Leonard
believes me or not,
I really do have a firm to run.
I know you do.
Then you know I have
ten other things to do
before I get out of
here tonight.
Then I will
leave it alone.
But for what it's worth,
you were there for me
when the victim's father
lashed out at me.
And so, if you want to talk
about it with someone,
I just want you to know
that I'm here for you, too.
I appreciate that, Rachel.
But right now, I'd rather you
spend your time
finding something to get
Leonard Bailey out.
I will.
♪ ♪
[line trilling]
Hello?
Hi, Jeff, it's me.
How would you like to have
dinner with me tonight?
I would love to, Jessica.
Just name the place.
♪ ♪
What?
Nothing.
I just haven't been in this
place since I was here with you.
I remembered how much
you liked it.
So how come you decided
to call me?
You said you were
still in it.
You told me once
that you think maybe
things happen for a reason.
You mean
running into me today?
I mean after
I ran into you.
I was pretty much
accused of being cold,
heartless, and uncaring.
And I can take it when it's
lawyers saying that about me.
But this was from the man
whose life I'm trying to save.
And you wanted
to be with someone
who knows a different
side of you.
I thought I wanted to be
with someone who knows
that's not a side
of me at all.
Jessica, I told you
I loved you once.
And when I said that,
I meant that one of the things
that I love about you
is your ability to
push emotion aside
and knock the shit
out of people.
So you think I'm cold,
but you love that about me?
I'm saying that's one of the
things that I love about you.
The other thing is
that in your heart,
you're not cold at all.
♪ ♪
What do you say after dinner,
you take me home?
I say...
I think that we should
take it slow this time.
♪ ♪
Listen, I know you hate me
right now,
but right this second,
we are on the same side.
I know.
- You do?
- Yeah.
'Cause they just
let me out of solitary,
and I went to call Jill.
I was gonna tell her
everything, but before
I got a chance
to do that...
she told me
she was indicted.
- Kevin, I'm so sorry.
- I don't need sorrys, Mike.
I need to find a way
to keep my wife out of prison.
- Then let me help you.
- You can help me.
But it can't be by trying to get
her to turn on him,
because I'm telling you,
there is no way in hell
she's gonna do that.
You really think she's willing
to go to prison for him, too?
Look, the night I found out
about her and her father,
I asked her how she could have
gotten involved
in something like this.
Turns out, she found out his
whole place was a Ponzi scheme.
She flipped out on him and he
gave her some bullshit sob story
about how the returns
were running dry.
He told her that if she got
inside information for him,
one time, it'd keep them from
losing everything.
And the next thing she knew,
it was too late to stop.
Yeah, he tricked her.
And when I tried
to tell her that,
get her to quit with me,
you know what she said?
She said
she'd never do that.
Because no matter what
he did with the business,
she knew he was willing to run
into a burning building for her.
So she was willing
to do the same for him.
♪ ♪
Kevin, I need you to let me
use your cell phone.
I need you to trust me.
[line trilling]
- Harvey Specter's office.
- Donna, it's me.
I need your help
and I don't have much time.
What do you need?
I think I have a plan
to get Jill to talk.
Mike, shouldn't you be telling
Harvey about this?
I'm calling him next.
But whatever we do,
we are not gonna be able
to get her to talk unless
you first get her to listen.
[tense music]
Hey Tara,
I know I called four minutes ago
and I know you said
7:00 p.m. sharp,
but now I'm thinking
you said 7:00 p.m. short.
And I don't know exactly
why that would be,
uh, but it's 7:12,
and I'm just wondering what--
Hello?
Goddamn it.
Louis.
I just saw
you called two times.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Tara, please.
There's no need to apologize.
I had them hold the reservation
for 15 minutes,
and it's only been 13 minutes,
so I'm sure it'll be fine.
Thank you, Louis.
The Litt party is ready.
Awesomeness, I'll have a table
for you as soon as one's ready.
As soon as one's ready?
I asked you to hold our
reservation for 15 minutes
and it's only been 13 minutes,
you hipster douche bag.
Excuse me, sir,
is everything okay?
No, everything is not okay,
this asshole gave away my table.
Hey, man, it's all good.
I'll get you another table.
"Hey, man," it's all bad.
I don't want another table.
I want the one I reserved.
So why don't you tell those
people that you gave them
something that belongs to
someone else,
'cause I'm not going to share
the most exquisite table
on the planet
with another man.
Louis.
♪ ♪
This isn't gonna work.
Louis--Louis.
Please talk to me.
Look, I know I said
I'd be okay with this,
but I'm not okay.
Because the whole time
I couldn't reach you,
I kept thinking that you were
on the phone with him
and laughing with him
and loving him.
And as long as you have
another man,
I'm always gonna think that
you're with him,
thinking about him--
- Louis? That's--
- Let me finish.
You are the most riveting
woman I've ever met.
You've cast a spell on me.
And I would never tell you
how to live your life.
But I will not
share you with another man.
And I don't understand
why any man would.
I want you,
and I want all of you.
But if I can't have that--
Louis?
Take me home.
♪ ♪
Here, let me
help you with that.
- Oh, would you?
- Of course.
Us redheads have to
stick together.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, Jill.
Who are you?
I'm the woman who tricked you
into going to Danbury.
I have nothing
to say to you.
Please, I came here in person
because I don't want to
trick you again.
Then say whatever it is
you're here to say.
I'm here to tell you
about my father.
He committed a crime years ago,
and before he did,
he tried to get me to put
my toe in the water with him.
I said no,
but I almost said yes,
because I loved him.
And I knew he was a good man.
What do you want from me?
Same thing that I wanted
the last time.
I want you to visit your husband
in prison tomorrow.
And I want you to
keep an open mind.
♪ ♪
Louis, I knew
you were passionate,
but I had no idea
how passionate.
That was magic.
Yeah, I take pride
in my work.
Well, you should.
[laughs]
Well, in that case,
there's another show starting
in about 15 minutes.
Okay, you know
what that means, don't you?
You're gonna be exhausted,
which means you're gonna
have to spend the night.
Well, then what do you say we
make the whole day of it, too?
What exactly do you
have in mind?
There's a dress rehearsal
of the "Barber of Seville"
at the Met tomorrow
and I could get us in
as patrons.
Louis...
[poignant music]
I would love to.
♪ ♪
- William, we need to talk.
- I'm here, just like you asked.
They indicted your daughter.
I know.
She told me.
And I told you, you were
playing a dangerous game
using her to shield you.
Jill's a big girl.
She can take care
of herself.
Take care of herself,
or take care of you?
Are you accusing me
of something?
I'm not accusing you,
I'm telling you,
you need to wake the hell up.
What did you
just say to me?
Do you know what Cahill's
gonna do once Jill's arraigned?
He's gonna sit her down
for as long as it takes
until she cuts a deal
to give you up.
She would never do that.
You have no idea what
she'll do when they get her
into that room.
And I'm telling you,
if my loser of
a son-in-law didn't cave,
then Jill sure as hell won't.
Listen to me, goddamn it.
This isn't gonna be what it was
like it was with Kevin.
What do you want from me,
Harvey?
I want you to give me
authorization
to cut you both a deal.
You turn yourself in,
you get maybe three years,
and you keep her out.
Why the hell
would I do that?
Because if she turns on you,
you're gonna be getting
a hell of a lot more.
I'm not cutting a deal.
And you think if you're
willing to do this
to your own daughter, she won't
be willing to do it to you?
Jill's a young woman,
I'm an old man.
She does a few years,
it hardly makes a dent.
When she gets out,
she can still play tennis
and go to Pilates
and do all the things
I always gave her
the money to do.
You knew it might
come to this, didn't you?
I love my daughter, Harvey,
but she'd be nothing
without me.
And she knows if
she does this for me,
she'll be taken care of
for the rest of her life.
So that's it?
No deal?
No deal.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, Jill.
I want to cut a deal.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Can you do that for me?
No, I can't.
Why not?
Because he represents
your father.
But I don't.
So I can.
♪ ♪
Tara, I didn't think today
could get any better,
But whatever you did to
that water pressure
is thing of beauty.
I haven't felt this fresh
and clean since--
Louis, I have to talk to you.
- What is it?
- Joshua called.
He's coming to town tomorrow
for two days.
But after last night,
I thought it was over
between the two of you?
Louis...
we've been together for years.
I can't just not see him.
So you're gonna
break up with him?
[tense music]
I don't know.
♪ ♪
Welcome to Danbury, Sean.
You know you're taking a big
risk that someone's gonna
recognize me and figure out that
you're up to something.
Well, I'd be taking an even
bigger risk
if I didn't hand this
to you personally.
You're not gonna weasel
out of my deal again.
What is this?
That is an iron clad agreement
between your office
and Jill Miller.
You're representing
Jill Miller now?
Yes, I am.
Does she know
that you're not a lawyer?
She does.
And she's okay with it
because I'm also the guy
who's keeping her
out of prison.
Let me save you the trouble
of reading that.
It says that she's gonna testify
against her father,
pleads no contest,
and receives full immunity.
But it also says that
you acknowledge that
I brought her to you.
Hmm.
Well, then I better bring it
to my office and sign it.
♪ ♪
Oh, and for what it's worth,
I didn't try to
weasel out of your deal.
I did everything I could
to keep it in place.
Well, now it's
back in place.
Because I just gave you
everything that you need.
No, Mike, you didn't give me
everything yet.
Because what I still need is
William Sutter behind bars.
[knocking]
♪ ♪
What the hell did you do?
Nice to see you, William.
Can I get you a drink?
You think I wouldn't find out
that you recorded me
and played it
for my daughter?
I didn't play it for her.
I played it for my other client,
Kevin Miller.
Jill just happened
to be there when I did.
And now she's turning on me.
Then I guess it turns out she
didn't want to wait five years
to play more tennis
like you thought.
Goddamn it, you broke
attorney-client privilege.
I didn't break anything,
William.
Because like I just told you,
Kevin's my client too,
and I had an obligation
to share the facts with him.
So instead of attacking me,
you should be thanking me.
Because I went to Cahill
and cut you the best deal
you're ever gonna get.
Why would you
do this to me?
You did this to yourself,
William.
You had me represent
both you and Kevin,
which means I had to choose
between two clients.
And you said it, yourself.
You're an old man,
and they're a young couple,
and I chose them over you.
I didn't have you
represent us both.
It was your idea.
I guess it was, wasn't it?
You son of a bitch.
You set me up!
And I'm gonna make sure
the world knows it.
You can tell the world
anything you want, William.
But you've got no proof
and you'll be telling it
from behind bars.
Either way, I suggest
you sign this deal,
'cause it's the best
you're ever gonna get.
♪ ♪
Jessica.
What're you doing here?
I had a great time
last night.
And I was going to
call you about
going out again next week
because I know
you want to take it slow.
But then I found out that
you want to take it slow
because you may not
be here much longer.
How'd you find out?
They called for a reference.
And what'd you tell them?
I said them they'd be
lucky to have you.
Thank you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I wasn't sure
I was gonna take it.
But now you are.
Jessica, if I thought there
would be a chance in the world
that you would come with me,
I would've asked you.
But we both know
that's not gonna happen.
Because you told me
it's not over yet,
but what you meant is that
it's never gonna be over.
It's my firm, Jeff.
It's the thing I spent
my whole life building.
And I'm not
judging you for it.
You are who you are,
and I love who you are.
But I've been thinking about
going back to Chicago
for a long time now,
and as much as seeing you again
makes me want to stay here...
This is something
I have to do.
Like I said.
They're lucky to have you.
♪ ♪
It's done.
Sutter took the deal.
Jill's safe.
Thank God.
I'm, uh...
I'm sorry that Jill had to
hear what she heard.
It was the only way, man.
Besides, you didn't say it.
No, but I did know
what I was doing
when I agreed
to inform on you.
I'm sorry.
You didn't deserve
any of that.
Hey, look, when we first met,
I let Gallo in here.
And that was as much a betrayal
as what you did to me.
Yeah, but you
didn't know me.
I knew you.
What, are you trying to
make me hate you?
[chuckles]
No.
It's just that I'm getting out
and you're not.
No, I'm not.
But you kept my wife
out of prison,
and as far as I'm concerned,
that makes us square.
♪ ♪
Thank you, Kevin.
Where you going?
Me?
I'm gonna give you a few minutes
to enjoy the fact
that you're getting out.
And to call Rachel
and tell her.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
Hey.
Donna,
I'm on to something.
I just need one second
to write it down.
What is it?
What're you so happy about?
I think I just
figured out a way
to get Leonard Bailey's
case reopened.
Rachel, that's amazing.
Come on, get your things.
We can talk about it
on the way out,
because we're going to
celebrate.
No, it's good news,
but I'm not ready to celebrate.
Yes, you are.
Because I'm not
talking about your case.
Rachel,
Harvey and Mike did it.
Mike's getting out.
What?
You heard me.
They did it.
Sutter's going away,
which means Mike's coming home.
[M83's "Outro"]
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
[chuckles]
Come on,
let's go have some fun
while you're still single.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
[cell phone buzzing]
It's Mike.
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
I know it's you.
It's over.
I'm coming home.
I just heard.
God, I love you so much.
I love you, too.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man