Previously on "Suits"...
- Robert Zane made you an offer.
- He did.
You begged me
for a second chance.
And now he's using you
to destroy us.
You waltzed in here thinking
this was gonna be
like some prison movie,
but it's not.
It's just prison.
Welcome to Danbury.
- Mike Ross.
- Frank Gallo.
We're being sued for every
case Mike Ross has ever touched.
You won't admit this whole
thing is your fault
in the first place.
My fault?
If I hadn't brought Mike in,
you'd still be here
sniveling around like
a Goddamn junior partner.
Your fiancée,
you want to call her?
Maybe I'll just send
Rachel a text.
We need to move the money
that we have
in every account
by tomorrow.
We don't need to move it.
We can use their buy-ins
to settle
the class-action lawsuits.
All right, let's go.
I'm in the right cell.
I'm in the one you gave me.
Yeah, but this isn't
the one they gave me.
You said you could've turned
on a guy to get out of here,
but you didn't
because you owe him.
Well, I owe that
son of a bitch too.
- You son of a bitch.
- Take it easy, Mike.
And remember,
I know about you.
And I got your
little girlfriend's number
right here.
[dark music]
You keep watching
that clock,
it's gonna be
a long two years.
Believe it or not, I've been
where you are right now.
You've been thinking about
how to get back
at that son of a bitch
all night.
Spit in his oatmeal.
Shit on his pillow.
Whatever it is, my advice
to you is don't do it.
I don't need any advice
from you.
- Excuse me?
- You're the one
that left me alone with that
psychopath in the first place.
Now I get
why you haven't
said a word to me
since last night.
How the hell did you
think I'd react
after something like that?
Hey, listen, man.
I don't have anything
against you,
but I sure as hell
don't have anything for you.
And I'm not gonna cause trouble
with a guy like that
for someone I've never even met,
so if he wants me
to switch for a few hours,
I'm switching.
To hell with
what happens to me, right?
- Hey, I didn't say that.
- No, you just did it.
♪ ♪
[door buzzes]
[doors opening]
♪ ♪
Donna, what are you
doing here?
I come bearing gifts.
That's really nice, but you
don't have to come over here
to check on me.
I'm fine.
Says the girl
in her fiancé's shirt.
Look, I know it's cheesy.
Rachel, you wanted to feel him
next to you.
It's not cheesy.
Thanks, Donna.
Well, you do owe me
a thank you,
but it's not for that.
Because in a couple of hours
it's going to be more
than his shirt
wrapped around you.
Are you saying that you got me
on the visitor's list,
because they said
that if I'm not family--
I don't care what they said.
You're his family.
And you're my family, and I
wasn't going to sleep last night
until I got you
on that list.
I-I don't know
what to say.
Say, "Thank you, Donna,"
and get your ass up there.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
What you got in your hand
there, tiger?
Dark roast, splash of cream,
no sugar.
And to what do I owe
the honor?
I was thinking this morning
about the day
you picked me
out of the mailroom
and how far we've come.
You know, it's funny.
I was thinking this morning
about how far we've fallen.
Then let's go put
these lawsuits to bed.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Excuse me, Officer?
I know the phones don't open
until 10:00,
but I was wondering
if it's possible for me
to make a phone call?
Get back in line
and eat your breakfast.
Please.
The only reason I'm asking
is 'cause it's an emergency.
I just need a little--
What, are you on fire?
Your leg broken?
'Cause it looks to me
like you're trying to call
someone out there about
something that happened in here.
You don't understand,
all right, my fiancée is...
No, you don't understand.
Unless there's a bomb
headed for us,
nothing that happens out there
has anything to do
with what happens in here.
You got that?
Yeah, got it.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Hey, I left in such
a hurry last night,
didn't get a chance
to say good-bye.
Well, I'll say it now.
Have a nice life.
Leave me alone.
Don't you want to see
a copy of the pictures
your fiancée sent me
last night?
♪ ♪
That's bullshit.
She didn't send you anything.
You're right, she didn't.
She sent 'em to you.
I mean, you're the one
who started it all,
telling her how much
you missed her.
How hard do you think it was
for me to get her
to send a sexy picture to you
after that?
I think that kids today
call it a selfie.
[scoffs]
There's no way she sent you
a picture like that.
You're right,
it wasn't sexy.
But what I did,
I photoshopped her face
onto a body that is.
I did such a good job,
no one in here
is ever gonna notice.
Yeah.
I made copies.
One for each guy
in the joint.
Usually, a situation like this,
I would charge a fortune.
But today,
I'm feeling so generous
I'm going to give them away
for free.
[grunting]
[all reacting]
♪ ♪
Get off him, Gallo!
What? I didn't do shit!
He attacked me!
That is bullshit!
I tried to tell you
that's the guy.
I don't care
what you tried to do.
You wanted an emergency,
now you got it.
Get 'em both out of here.
What?
[smooches]
♪ ♪
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 6x02 ♪
Accounts Payable
Original Air Date on July 20, 2016
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[elevator dings]
Good morning, Ms. Pearson,
Mr. Specter,
can I offer either of you
a hot towel?
Miss, would you mind
telling me who hired you?
I think we both know
who hired her.
[funky music]
♪ ♪
What the hell are you doing?
- I'm making copies.
- Goddamn it.
We don't bill you out
at 350 an hour to make copies.
Now get your ass
back to work.
That motion
isn't going to file itself.
Louis, what the hell
did you do?
What?
What are you talking about?
We don't have the money
to hire associates,
paralegals,
and support staff.
I know that.
I'm not an idiot,
they're not support staff.
Who the hell are they?
They're movie extras.
How much weed
did you smoke last night?
We have a settlement meeting
in an hour.
And if these offices are empty
when they walk in,
we are gonna look like shit.
Louis,
did it occur to you
that we're using the threat
of bankruptcy in that meeting,
and if these offices are filled,
it kills that plan?
Everybody drop whatever
the hell it is you're doing
and hand your timecards in
to my secretary.
And if they are marked
one second late,
I swear to God,
you will never be fake
associates in this town again.
[mellow rock music]
♪ ♪
Next.
- Hi.
- Inmate's name?
Mike Ross.
I'm here for visitation.
It appears Mr. Ross is not
receiving visitors today.
I-I don't understand.
I was told that I was on
the approved visitors list.
It says visitation
has been suspended for two weeks
because of an altercation
he had this morning.
No, that can't be right.
He just got here yesterday.
It can be right,
and it is right.
Well then, I need to see him
right away.
And I just told you
you can't do that.
Yes, I can because not only
am I his fiancée,
I'm also his lawyer.
It says here a Harvey Specter
is his lawyer.
And he works at Pearson,
Specter, Litt, and so do I.
This card says paralegal.
I don't care what it says.
You don't let me in there
and something's wrong with him,
I will make it
my life's purpose
to make your life
a living hell.
Ma'am, I worked maximum
security for ten years,
so if you think I'm gonna be
intimidated by the likes of you,
you've got another thing coming.
[tense music]
You know, usually it takes
prisoners a couple of weeks
to get their first violation.
You've been here
less than 24 hours.
That might just be
a record.
Yeah, I don't care.
I need to make a phone call.
You're not making anything
after what you just did.
I didn't do anything.
He set me up.
I don't care
what he did.
So all that stuff
about you helping me
become a "better version"
of myself,
that was bullshit?
No, it wasn't.
Then what exactly
did you mean?
Because if you won't even hear
my side of the story,
then how are you
gonna help me?
All right, what do you mean
he set you up?
I mean,
he paid off a guard,
then he posed as my roommate,
and the next thing I know,
he's about to hand out
pictures of my fiancée
to every inmate
in this entire prison.
There's no evidence
of any pictures.
But they were
all over the floor.
This is what
was all over the floor.
Listen to me,
there might not be any proof,
but I am telling you
that he paid off a guard
and you need to do something
about it.
Brother, I don't have
any authority over the guards.
Then what exactly
am I doing here?
You are learning how to deal
with the bullshit
life throws your way without
making your situation worse.
And how the hell
am I supposed to do that?
This isn't just a tea party.
The purpose of this meeting
is to decide
if you are worth
rehabilitating or not.
And if I am?
Then I get you a job.
♪ ♪
And if I'm not?
Then you never see me again.
And the next time
you have an incident,
you will go to solitary
confinement for a month.
So I suggest you go back
to your cell
and you think long and hard
about what you want
to accomplish
during your time here.
♪ ♪
I have to say,
I'm glad you've decided
to settle
rather than fight
these suits.
Well, as you can see,
things are a little tight
around here, so you have us
at a disadvantage.
What I have is the fact that
you don't want to be talking
about having hired a fraud in
court for the next six months.
No, we don't, so...
With all due respect,
this isn't an offer,
it's a typo.
And with all due respect,
this isn't a lawsuit,
it's a shakedown.
Bullshit.
This is a chance for you
to wipe the slate clean
with the clients
you defrauded.
And $10 million is a hell
of a Goddamn wipe.
It's ten cents
on the dollar.
If you don't take it,
it's going to be
zero cents on the dollar.
What the hell
are you talking about?
This money is from
our partner buy-in fund.
It's the only cash we have.
And once the partners find out
that we're using it to settle,
they're gonna come after it.
So you have about an hour
to sign on the dotted line,
or that money's gone forever.
So take a look around,
Arlene,
'cause once it's gone,
there isn't any more left.
You knowingly defrauded
your own clients.
You made a mockery
of the legal system.
And I won't let you
get away with it.
You want to know something,
Arlene?
We did something wrong,
and now we're paying for it.
But I'm getting a little
sick and tired
of people acting like
Mike Ross screwed them over.
He gave his heart and soul
to every client he ever had,
and if those cases
were reopened,
they would end up exactly
in the same place.
So, you can sign that deal
or not,
but I'm not gonna spend
another second
dealing with a parasite
like you.
♪ ♪
Donna, where's Harvey?
I need to talk to him.
He's finishing up
a negotiation.
- This can't wait.
- Why? What's going on?
I got up there
and they turned me away.
No, that can't be.
I got you on that list.
That's not it.
They turned me away
because he got into a fight.
- What? With who?
- I don't know.
All I know is that
I went to go and see him,
they said he got into a fight,
and then they wouldn't
let me in.
- Good.
- How is that good?
Because if they wouldn't
let you in,
it means he fought back.
You don't lose visitation
if you just got jumped.
Harvey, I don't care
if he fought back or not.
It doesn't mean
that he's okay.
Rachel, listen to me.
They have an obligation
to tell you
if he's in the infirmary.
Did they tell you
he was in the infirmary?
No.
Okay, then this is what
I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna call up there
and get to the bottom of this,
but it might take a while,
so I need you to be patient.
[exhales sharply]
Okay.
♪ ♪
Donna, cancel my afternoon
and have Ray meet me downstairs
in five minutes.
I thought you said
you weren't worried about Mike.
I only said that
so that she wouldn't worry.
They only take visitation away
if you're the one
who starts the fight,
which means something
Goddamn happened down there
and I'm gonna figure out
what it is.
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
Gretchen,
what can I do for you?
Well, I thought since
everyone was gone
maybe I could help myself to the
executive kitchen for a change.
For a change?
I wanted to let you know
that I had no idea
those people were leaving
or I never would have gone
to that appointment.
I know, Gretchen.
I would also like
to point out
that since they did leave,
between me, you,
and Rachel Zane,
this firm just got
a whole lot blacker.
Well,
as far as I'm concerned,
that has nothing to do
with anything.
Gretchen,
as long as you're here--
You want to know if I can
handle the reception desk
and Louis at the same time.
How did you know
I was going to ask you that?
Because that's what
good secretaries do.
Sure as shit is.
Well, there's one thing
about everybody being gone.
When would the three of us
ever find ourselves
in here
just shooting the shit?
And when would you have
thought that was a good thing?
This one is a keeper.
- [chuckles]
- I know.
Oh, and for the record,
I'm black in here.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here?
- What do you mean
what am I doing here?
I want to know what's going on.
What's going on?
Nothing's going on.
I'm in prison.
Nothing's going on?
Then why do you look
like that?
It is none of your business.
Well, I'm making it
my business
because Rachel came
to visit you this morning,
and they told her
you got in a fight.
Yeah, well, why don't you do
what you always do
and make up some bullshit
and tell her it's not true?
Because I'm busy trying
to survive in here.
Why won't you tell me?
Because you'll try
and handle it for me.
Well, maybe I should be
handling it for you
because you're too stupid
not to piss someone off
on the first day.
[chuckles] Okay, Harvey.
You want to know what happened?
It wasn't me who pissed him off.
It was you.
What are you talking about?
- Frank Gallo.
- Holy shit.
What's he doing in here?
I don't know.
I was hoping
you'd tell me that.
I put him away
for racketeering.
That doesn't make
any sense.
Last time I checked,
that doesn't land him in here.
You're right.
A guy like Gallo
only lands in here
for one reason: good behavior.
Why are you saying that
like it's a good thing?
Because bad behavior
can get him out.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna go to the warden.
Tell him the whole story.
We'll get him outta here
within the week.
That's exactly why
I did not want to tell you.
Look, these guards
are corrupt.
You go to the warden,
it gets back to Gallo,
he's gonna come after me
twice as hard.
It's one week
instead of two years.
Look, we got a chance to get him
outta here, I'm gonna take it.
He's got Rachel's
phone number.
Ye--that's all
the more reason to do it--
God damn it, Harvey!
You pushed me
to beat the shit out of you
so that you'd know I could
take care of myself in here,
now are you gonna
let me do that,
or are you gonna cut my legs
out from under me?
[tense music]
I'll stay out of it.
I want your word.
I won't go to the warden.
♪ ♪
Hey, I was wondering
when you'd show up.
Don't act like you don't
remember me, Harvey.
We both know why
you're here.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I'm here because
I represent the prison.
[scoffs]
Bullshit.
I pulled a string
and you came.
You think it's a coincidence
I'm standing here
while you're walking out?
Okay, Gallo,
you got my attention.
You want me to step inside?
Or you want to come out here?
We both know
that's not possible.
You owe me 13 years.
I'm gonna collect.
I didn't do anything to you
that that investigator
didn't start and you know it.
Well, if his little boyfriend
ever shows up in here,
I'll be sure to take it up
with him.
What do you want, Gallo?
I already have
what I want.
Which is knowing that every time
your phone rings,
you're gonna ask yourself is
this the call where you find out
that the guy who's in here
for you
is never coming out.
[grunts]
Listen to me,
you son of a bitch.
you think I can't hurt you
in here?
I'll put a Goddamn bounty
on your head.
I'll pay 'em whatever it takes
to break your legs.
And if that doesn't work,
I'll wait till you get out
and I'll kill you myself.
So unless you want that
to happen,
don't you ever even look
at Mike Ross again.
♪ ♪
Ring, ring, counselor.
Ring, ring.
I knew I'd find you here.
'Cause this is where you come
when you think
you just beat somebody.
What can I do for you, Jack?
You can tell me
you used your own money
to settle that lawsuit.
'Cause if you didn't,
we're gonna have a problem.
Then I'd say we have
a problem.
God damn it.
You used the buy-in fund.
Yes, we did.
Then I guess...
I'll see you in court.
[scoffs]
You're suing me personally?
- It's your name on the door.
- Oh, Jack.
I know corporate structures
were never your strong suit,
so I'm gonna explain something
to you.
We may use the word
"partnership,"
but this is a LLC.
And no judge in the world
is going to let you
pierce that corporate veil.
They will once they learn
you knowingly hired a fraud.
One has nothing to do
with the other.
And if you really did
find a judge who would do that,
then you'd be here with an army
of lawyers and a Brinks truck
instead of standing alone
with a flimsy piece of paper
in your sweaty
little hands.
You can talk tough
all you want, Jessica.
The fact is, I do have an army
of lawyers and you don't.
What are you talking about?
I took that job
with Robert Zane after all.
And I'm willing to drag
this fight out,
so the choice is yours.
Give us our money
or go out of business.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Can I talk to you
for a second?
About what?
Listen, a man's cell should be
the one place he can feel safe.
I took that away from you,
and I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, sorry doesn't do
shit for me in here.
I know.
That's why I want
to make it up to you.
Are you kidding me?
That's exactly what got me
in this situation
in the first place.
I know that.
But I also know
you wanted to call
whoever you wanted to call
this morning.
And I'm trying
to make it up to you.
Yeah, well,
this doesn't do that.
Hey, look,
I can get in a lot of trouble
for just letting you know
I have this.
Why don't you do
something else
that can get you
into trouble?
What are you talking about?
Tell them that Gallo paid
the guards to have you switch.
I can't do that.
Yeah,
because you're afraid of him.
You're damn straight I am.
And on top of that,
I'd make a permanent enemy
of everyone else in here,
because the worst thing
you can be known for, my man,
is as someone who would
do something like that.
Which means I get to deal
with this all by myself.
[dark music]
It's all right,
you can stay.
It doesn't matter
if he stays or goes,
I got nothing to say
to you.
That's okay, 'cause I got
something to say to you.
You want to know what my
favorite time of day is in here?
It's right now.
Got the TV going.
Guys are sitting around
playing cards, telling jokes.
You almost forget
you're in prison,
which is why
I came over here.
'Cause I want to make sure
you never forget.
There's gonna come a time
when this place isn't filled
with people,
and you and I are alone.
Then all those vicious threats
your boy Harvey Specter
made to me today
aren't gonna save you.
♪ ♪
[gentle music]
I heard today was a good day
for Rand, Kaldor, Zane.
If this is about me hiring
Jack Soloff's department,
I didn't do it
to stick it to you.
They were leaving anyway.
Maybe.
But if your first move
is to have them come after
their partner money,
then I must have been wrong
that we were on good terms.
Jessica,
I accepted your apology.
I wouldn't say that makes us
on good terms.
But I had nothing to do with him
coming after your money.
That's between you and him.
But you do have the power
to stop it.
And I am not in the habit of
telling my brand new employees
what they can and can't do.
Well, I need you
to do it anyway.
Jessica--
Robert...
I need this.
And I know it's not
your style
to tell your partners
what to do,
but if you don't make it
your style,
I'm dead in the water.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[phone vibrates]
This is Harvey Specter.
You have a call
from Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept the charges?
Yes.
I do not understand
your response.
Yes. God damn it.
Please respond yes or no.
Yes.
[line beeps]
- Hello.
- Oh, Mike, thank God.
Thank God what?
You looked me in the eye
and you said
you would stay out of it.
You couldn't even make it
to the parking lot
without threatening Gallo?
Mike, listen to me.
No, what,
so you can lie to me again?
Or are you gonna tell me
you didn't do that?
Look, I didn't do it
because I didn't think
you could handle yourself.
I did it because
he got under my skin.
I don't give a shit
why you did it.
You swore you wouldn't.
Instead,
you've made things worse.
Harvey, if I can't even
trust you,
then I do not stand a chance
in here.
Look, I can't talk
right now.
What do you mean
you can't talk?
Rachel's in my office
looking at me right now
and she's gonna think
something's wrong
in five seconds, so unless
you've changed your mind
about me not telling her,
I gotta go.
Harvey, you gotta get
the phone from her.
Sure, Rick, no problem.
8:30 sounds great.
Harvey, get the phone
from her.
First round's on you.
Rachel, good, you're here.
I was just gonna
come see you.
I didn't hear from you,
so I just figured--
He's good. There was an error
in the paperwork.
It's a different inmate,
same last name.
Okay.
So I can see him tomorrow.
Actually, he asked
that you give him a little time.
What?
Rachel,
prison is a big adjustment.
He'll be ready
in about two weeks.
So then, why do I have
about 50 texts from him
saying that he can't wait
to see me?
- What?
- Harvey, what's going on?
- Give me the phone.
- No.
- I said give me the phone.
- I'm not giving you anything
until you tell me
what's going on.
Those texts
aren't from Mike.
Then who are they from?
From a guy I put away
when I was an ADA.
Oh, my God.
Rachel, don't let
your imagination run wild.
It's gonna be okay.
You don't know that
because you're not in there.
You're right, I'm not.
Then what the hell
are you gonna do about it?
I'm gonna do
what I promised Mike.
I'm gonna have faith
that he can handle it.
I don't believe it.
So you're not gonna do anything?
You think I don't want to bust
him outta there right now?
Look, if I try and do something
and it doesn't work,
it makes it worse for him.
- Is he violent?
- Rachel--
- I made him a promise--
I don't give a shit.
He's in there to protect you,
so you better figure out
a way to protect him
because Goddamn it, Harvey,
if something happens to him
in there
and you didn't do anything,
I will never forgive you.
♪ ♪
Harvey, I know you don't
need me to tell you this,
but she's right, because
if something actually does
happen to Mike,
even if she forgives you,
you're never gonna
forgive yourself.
♪ ♪
What do you want, Harvey?
Five minutes of your time
and that's all.
Five minutes to catch up,
or five minutes to ask a favor?
Five minutes to help me
protect Mike Ross.
Protect him how?
'Cause last time I checked,
he was in the bosom of
the federal penitentiary system.
Sean, he's in there
with a guy I put away
and the guy is no joke.
I'm sorry to hear that,
Harvey.
But what am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to move
the guy to another prison.
I don't have the authority
to do that and you know that.
You can get the authority.
You're a federal prosecutor.
Then why the hell don't you
go after the prosecutor
that put Mike away
in the first place?
'Cause she doesn't owe me,
and you do.
You got a lot of balls
saying that to me
when the entire time
we were working together,
you knew the kid
was a fraud.
That kid helped you take down
Charles Forstman
and Eric Woodall
and put you on the map.
The map?
Bullshit.
I was on the map long before
I met either of you.
You're going to tell me
you haven't shot up the ranks
since that conviction?
[chuckles]
You know, Harvey,
when you first walked in here,
for a second I actually thought
you were gonna apologize
for lying to me
all that time.
I don't need
your forgiveness, Sean.
I need your help.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
All right,
I'll see what I can do.
But, Harvey,
now you owe me one.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
Jack?
I've had a long day.
What are you doing here?
You know
what I'm doing here.
You went to Robert Zane
and you had him shut us down.
I did what I had to do.
Now if you'll excuse me.
All I wanted was
my money back.
Well, the sooner you get used
to the fact that it's gone,
the sooner we can both
move on with our lives.
That's the problem.
I can't move on with my life.
What are you talking about?
I can't afford Zane's buy-in.
What?
How is that possible?
Jessica, listen to me.
You know what I did
that Hardman found out about,
but what you don't know
is why I did it.
I needed the money.
And now you want me
to give you your money back
out of my own pocket?
Jessica, please.
This is a chance for me
to have a new start.
Even if I wanted to,
I can't do that.
- Why not?
- You know why not.
I pay you
out of my own pocket.
I'm piercing
that corporate veil myself.
And if the partners find out,
it will cost me millions.
They won't find out.
Well, I can't take
that chance.
Jessica, I need this.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, Jack.
I can't help you.
♪ ♪
[elevator dings]
[mellow rock music]
Morning.
[chuckles]
What?
You know what.
Do I have something
in my teeth?
No, but you got
some bullshit in your brain.
- Excuse me?
- "Black in here."
Please, you're the whitest
woman I ever met.
Oh, is that a fact?
Tell me something different.
How about I show you
something different?
♪ ♪
- Is that...
- Yep.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Nope.
- What year was that?
- '96.
- How long were you together?
- Seven months.
That that, Mrs. Hater.
Before his last album
or after?
[scoffs]
Who do you think
that song was about?
Shit.
"Black in here."
She's black all over.
♪ ♪
I'm glad we came
to an agreement.
And it's usually not my habit
to court a dalliance
with opposing counsel,
but I couldn't help but notice
you don't have a ring
on your finger.
Not in a million years,
Mr. Litt.
Go back to your own side.
Wow, man puts himself out
there, the least you can do is--
Regarding the class action
against Pearson, Specter, Litt,
do both parties agree to
the terms of the settlement?
- We do, Your honor.
- We do as well, Your Honor.
Then unless there are
any objections,
I see no reason for this court
not to ratify--
I have an objection,
Your Honor.
- What?
- And you are?
His name is
A. Elliott Stemple, Your Honor,
and he has no standing
in this case.
Mr. Litt.
I have no standing,
Your Honor.
But I represent
Rothman Insurance,
a company not included
in the class of clients
misrepresented by a firm
that knowingly hired a fraud.
There's not one shred of proof
we knowingly did anything.
But there is proof
that you employed a fraud,
which is why you're settling
with Ms. Rosen
in the first place.
- Are you in on this?
- Are you kidding me?
All right, Mr. Stemple.
Submit your evidence.
The court will rule on it
tomorrow.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
We may have agreed to
ten cents on the dollar,
but if this goes south,
we're coming after you
for every penny you've got.
♪ ♪
You little son of a bitch.
Watch it, Litt.
We're in a court of law.
I don't care where we are.
Jack Soloff put you up to this,
and I know it.
So what?
So I'm gonna prove it.
And when the judge realizes
what you did,
he's gonna throw your ass
in jail.
Really?
Huh.
Because the way I see it,
the judge is gonna certify
that my client is a member of
this class because they are one
whether Jack tipped me off
to them or not.
And when that happens,
I kill the deal,
and your money goes back to the
partners that you took it from.
So, why don't you march
your fat feet
back to
the only two lawyers left
at that miserable little firm
and decide just how deep
you're gonna reach
into your own pockets
to pay me off.
Because as I see it,
phew,
you have about 24 hours
until you lose everything.
♪ ♪
What do you want now,
Harvey?
I wanted to apologize
for what happened with Gallo.
It was wrong.
Shouldn't have happened,
and I'm sorry.
But?
But I don't care
what I promised you
because I found a way
to get him out of here,
and I'm gonna take it.
[scoffs]
I told you,
you go to the warden--
I'm not going to the warden.
I went to Sean Cahill.
What are you talking about?
We had him for
conspiracy to commit murder.
And the police let the tape
of that bastard admitting
that he did it
out of the chain of custody
for 20 minutes.
So you went after him
for racketeering instead.
I used every trick I had
to put him away for 15 years
for three crimes that would have
added to five years at the most.
And that's why he hates you
so much.
It's also why I need you
to lay low
until I can get him
out of here.
Oh, I can appreciate that,
Harvey,
but I can't exactly hide
in my cell 24 hours a day.
Then I suggest you do
the complete opposite.
♪ ♪
You know, I don't normally
take walk-ins.
Sorry.
Well,
as long as you're here.
Well, I thought about it,
and...
I'd like a job.
And if it's not
too much trouble,
I'd like it to be in front
of as many people as possible.
And why is that?
It'll be easier for me to stay
out of trouble in a crowd.
Good.
Because I got you
a job in the kitchen.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
Thank yourself.
If you hadn't come in
to see me,
I never would have
told you about it.
Is that true?
You don't really take walk-ins?
Nah.
Just something to say.
♪ ♪
The billing records
are right there.
Mike was at the meeting.
Shit, you're right.
He's got us.
- You know what this means.
- I do.
Louis, I just got
your message.
What's going on?
Harvey, we got a problem,
and you're not
going to like it.
Elliott Stemple showed up
in court
with an excluded member
of the class.
Elliott Stemple?
Are you kidding me?
He ambushed me, Harvey.
The judge was about to ratify
the settlement
when he comes out of nowhere.
What was I supposed to do?
You prove his client
isn't part of the class,
and you shut this thing down.
I can't do that because his
client is a part of the class.
- What? That's not possible.
- Yes, it is.
Mike took one meeting
with Rothman Insurance.
Jack Soloff told Stemple
about it.
- No way.
- It's all right here, Harvey.
And if we don't pay him off
tonight,
he kills that deal tomorrow
and we're out of business
ten minutes later.
Bullshit.
That's blackmail.
I'm not giving in
to blackmail.
Oh, come on,
do you think I want to do this?
He's got us by the balls,
Harvey.
If we don't pay him, what was
everything we went through
the other night even for?
Which means right now,
we just have to figure out
how much we're willing to pay.
No, we don't.
Harvey,
what are you saying?
I'm saying Stemple
doesn't care about you two.
He just wants to get in a room
with me and see me bleed.
You are not paying that man
out of your pocket.
- Yes, I am.
- Harvey, Jessica's right.
No, she's not.
We all know
I got us into this mess.
It's time for me
to get is out of it.
All right,
you want him, you got him.
But you're gonna be tempted
to rip that man's head off,
and when that happens,
you're not going to do that.
You're going to pay him.
And then you're going to throw
his sorry ass out of here.
[dramatic music]
[tense music]
Harvey, do you have
a minute?
If it's quick.
Someone's on their way over.
I want to apologize to you
about earlier.
You don't need to do that.
Yes, I do.
I know that you're doing
what you feel is best.
I just...
I didn't think this was
going to be as hard as it is.
For me too.
And for what it's worth,
I took your advice.
I'm gonna get that guy
out of there.
Thank you.
Rachel?
He's gonna be okay.
♪ ♪
Aren't you getting
a little long in the tooth
for that hottie I just saw
in the hall?
Let's get to it, Stemple,
because I'm not in the mood.
How much?
How much what?
How much to let me
have my firm?
Do you mean to imply
that I'm simply here
on a mission to extort you?
Oh, we both know you're here
to get my money
so you can split it
with Jack Soloff.
I resent that you think
so little of me.
You saying that's not why
you're here?
I'm saying I don't give a shit
about your money or Jack Soloff.
I want a piece of you.
♪ ♪
Get your Goddamn hands
off that.
Harvey, Harvey, Harvey.
Relax.
I didn't come here to put
my gentle hands
on your precious balls.
I came here to take something
far more valuable.
'Cause what I want is that
piece of shit duck painting.
♪ ♪
What?
That right there.
I was right.
If that didn't mean something
to you, you would have
jumped right out of your chair
and said okay to me.
- Stemple, listen--
- Not to mention,
you've had that thing
as long as I've known you,
and there's no way a guy like
you has a painting like that
unless it means everything
to him.
How much money, Stemple?
Because you are not
getting that painting.
- $10 million.
- Elliott.
- 15 million.
- Goddamn it.
20 million.
Do you want to keep going?
Or have you had enough?
Because in ten seconds,
I am walking out of here
with $20 million
or that thing in my hands.
Or tomorrow morning, I'm putting
your firm in the ground.
♪ ♪
Take the painting.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, hey.
I know you don't trust me,
but look who's headed this way.
On top of that,
people are leaving.
You should leave, too.
No.
That's what he wants.
He wants me to go somewhere
where those guards
don't have a view of me.
And for all I know,
he sent you to help him.
You don't know
what you're talking about--
Leave me alone.
Hey there, Mike.
What you reading?
"Outliers"?
[tense music]
I don't know what you think
is gonna happen here, Frank,
but I'm not gonna let you
trick me into leaving this room.
I don't need to trick you.
This room will do just fine.
Oh, yeah?
Why don't you tell that
to the two guards
sitting behind me?
You mean the ones
who let me into your cell?
♪ ♪
They took a little
cigarette break, Mike.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So that's it?
You're gonna let
these guys kill me?
Who said anything
about killing you?
We're just gonna hurt you
a little, or a lot.
No, no, no, no, no.
What I meant was,
are you really too much of a
pussy to take me on by yourself?
You think they won't
come at you
just because you called
me out?
Oh, no, I think that
men respond to leaders.
And if you're too afraid
to take on a guy like me,
you're not gonna be a leader
for much longer.
Okay, tough guy.
You want me one-on-one,
you got it.
One little thing:
I'm gonna use this
and they're gonna hold you.
No, no, no!
No!
What's going on here?
Huh? What?
Nothing.
You have the same story?
[panting]
Yeah.
Yeah,
nothing's going on here.
Then why don't you three
get away from him,
and go to your cells?
And I don't want to see you
back in here
for the rest of the night.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I just saw Stemple
walking out of here...
with a canvas that looks
about the same size
as that empty space
on your wall.
He won't be back.
So it's done?
It's done.
Harvey?
I remember you told me
that painting
was the one happy memory
you had of your mother before--
Like I said, Jessica,
I was the one
who got us into this mess.
I'm the one who needed to
get us out of it.
♪ ♪
Well?
It's done.
Thank God.
So, you want to go get Harvey?
Have a drink and celebrate?
Harvey needs to be alone
right now, Louis.
How about you and me?
I would,
but there's something
I need to take care of.
I understand.
Louis,
you had the right idea.
The wrong execution.
What do you mean?
I mean, if we're going
to look like a real firm,
then starting tomorrow,
we need to do something
about subletting
these offices.
I'll take care of it.
♪ ♪
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Why'd you come back
with the guard?
Now Gallo knows it was you.
He would have found out
it was me anyway.
But I might not have.
I didn't do it
to get you to forgive me.
I did it 'cause I never
should have
let him in here
in the first place.
What?
I just realized that
I don't even know your name.
[chuckles]
Kevin.
Kevin Miller.
Mike Ross.
Thank you, Kevin.
[serene music]
Lights out, gentlemen.
[buzzer buzzing]
♪ ♪
Robert, can I talk to you
for a second?
Yeah, what do you need?
I just found out I'm not
going to be able
to buy in as a partner.
- What?
- I don't have the money.
And I was wondering--
I don't need
a 50-year-old associate, Jack.
I know that.
If you could just let me
pay it off out of my salary.
You know as well as I do,
if I let you do that,
I might as well waive
the buy-in for everyone.
Please, Robert--
Why can't you get a loan
for it?
He can, but it's gonna be
a little complicated.
Because I'm actually
loaning you this money.
And you're gonna loan it
to him,
and if nobody ever repays
anybody,
nobody's gonna give a shit.
Why are you doing this,
Jessica?
Because I'm the one
that got you into this mess.
I should be the one
to get you out.
Thank you.
The truth is, Jack,
the older I get,
the more I'd rather
have friends out there
than enemies.
[Charles Bradley's "Changes"]
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man