No, Mike, stop.
Whoa.
Smooth.
You woulda made
a nice ballerina.
I'm not gonna apologize
for my lithe physique, okay?
And, by the way,
I was on the wrestling team
in high school, so...
Is something funny?
I'm just trying to imagine
you fighting someone.
Oh-oh-oh. I would kill you.
- You wouldn't touch me.
- Why not?
Because you'd be too busy
staring at me in tights.
No, I wouldn't.
You're doing it right now.
You're not wearing any tights.
I'm not wearing any underwear.
I'm... you...
Okay, so, Mrs. Williams,
we're gonna take you
to the deposition
as soon as Kenny Verdasco's
finished, all right?
You two draw the short straw?
I'm sorry?
You're in charge of
corralling the cancer patients.
It's not the most glamorous
duty in the world.
I supposed you two
don't mind working together.
- How long you been dating?
- Oh!
No, no, I'm sort of
seeing someone...
It's gonna happen
sooner or later.
- Excuse me.
- Excuse me for a moment.
Yes?
Hi, I'm sorry,
I think I'm in the wrong place.
Are you here for the Emerson
Petroleum deposition?
No, no, I'm an old friend
of Harvey Specter's.
This place is huge.
I always get turned around.
Maybe you can point me
in the right direction.
Uh, no problem.
You just see
those doors right there?
Go through to the elevators,
then up two floors,
and then you're gonna
take a right,
and down the hall,
and you'll see Donna.
Donna. Great, thanks.
Travis Tanner.
Mike Ross. Good to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you too, Mike.
Take care.
My wife Emily and I,
we saved every dollar
I made in the army,
and we moved here from
Apple Creek, New York,
six years ago.
We bought a brownstone,
and planted a tomato garden.
We had barbecues
with the neighbors.
It was... it was
a dream come true.
After being diagnosed
with lung cancer,
I couldn't work anymore.
I mean, there's times
I have difficulty
even going up the stairs
to my daughter's room.
You attended Apple Creek
High School, is that right?
All four years.
Your high school was built
in 1985.
What was there before?
An oil well,
owned and operated
by Emerson Petroleum.
Now, Kenny, why was
the high school shut down?
Because 200 people
who taught at
or attended Apple Creek High
were diagnosed
with some form of cancer.
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
That's for you, Larry.
Trust me, it's good. Use it.
How do you know my name?
It's all in there, Larry.
Hey, are you Donna?
Yeah, can I help you?
Yeah, Mike Ross
told me to find you.
We were in the library and
one of the plaintiffs fainted,
hit their head. Oh, my gosh.
Okay, I'm on it. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wrong office.
Harvey, I have to admit,
great job making Kenny Verdasco
the face of your
class action suit.
I don't know
who Kenny Verdasco is.
Oh, well, you better find out.
How 'bout for starters
you introduce yourself
or I'm calling security. Donna!
Relax, relax.
Name's Travis Tanner.
You're Travis Tanner?
You've heard of me.
No.
I'm a senior partner
with Clyde-MacPhee.
- We're based in Boston.
- So are the Red Sox.
I don't give a shit
about them either.
That's funny.
You know what's not funny,
is what's happening
to Kenny Verdasco.
At this moment, they're
asking him about his parents,
both heavy smokers.
Nasty habit.
Yes, a pack a day each.
I lived with them
till I was 18.
And then they'll ask
how in the army
he was exposed to nickel.
Chromium, and hydrocarbons.
I was an infantry soldier.
I didn't have much choice
in the matter.
Not to mention
the frivolous lawsuit
he filed ten years ago against
the Shriver Grocery chain.
It wasn't frivolous.
I slipped and shattered
my elbow.
If they're doing such
a great job down there,
what are you doing
up here in my office?
'Cause I gave them all that.
And when they walk
out that door,
I'm gonna be the one
who fires their asses.
So you coming to me
for a pep talk?
You're gonna do great, kiddo.
No, you see, Emerson Petroleum
was gonna lose this case.
So they called me in
to fix the situation.
And when I beat
Pearson Hardman,
I don't want anyone saying
it was because
they didn't send in their best.
Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you,
but Jessica Pearson's
handling this case herself.
And if you think
that she's not the best,
why don't you take
a run at her and find out?
All right, look,
I hear what you're saying,
but here's the thing.
I know that you know who I am.
And I also know
that during your senior year
you missed out on playing
in the state championship
because of your shoulder.
You can't pitch
with a bad shoulder.
And what do you know,
they won without you, Harvey.
Now ask yourself something.
Are you gonna let
Jessica Pearson
play the big game for you, hmm?
What's so funny?
I'm just thinking
about how I'm gonna enjoy
kicking your ass.
I'll see you in court.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
It was an attack
on my history, my family,
everything I care about.
I told you this was coming.
They're just trying
to rattle you.
Yeah, well, they're doing
a hell of a good job.
Kenny, you're our
lead plaintiff.
You've got to keep
your composure.
I don't care about composure.
I want to make a settlement.
That's exactly what they want.
Kenny, I'd like you to meet
Harvey Specter.
He's my right hand.
Can your right hand
please tell me why
we shouldn't ask
for a settlement?
I'm not against
settling one bit.
But if we go to them,
we're weak.
They come to us, we're strong.
Harvey's right.
They came after you because
they're running scared.
Trust me, they'll come
to us soon enough.
Okay.
One more thing,
I'm gonna postpone
the rest of the depositions.
Don't tell the rest of the
plaintiffs what happened.
What the hell was that?
I need you to let me
take over this case.
The guy that came into
my deposition.
- He called you out?
- Yeah.
- He's good.
You think I can't take him?
He brought up
the state championship.
- Oh, shoulder.
- Yeah.
Oh, take him.
- Be careful.
- I will.
Bringing up
state championships,
that's just... that's wrong.
Nothing I wouldn't have done.
♪ ♪
Thanks.
I need you to dig into
Travis Tanner.
Find out where he's worked,
where he's gone to school,
what cases he's won.
Why, you thinking
about starting
a Wikipedia page for him?
I don't know anything about
how this guy operates.
And before I make a move,
I need to know everything
about how this guy operates.
Right, for his Wikipedia page.
You think the Mavericks
didn't watch game film
on Lebron before
they played the Heat?
You're Harvey Specter.
You don't need
to watch game film.
Do you know who's watched
more game film than anybody?
- No. Who?
- Michael Jordan.
What? How do you know that?
You don't believe me?
Let's call him.
You have Michael Jordan's
phone number.
Yep.
If I hit this button
right here,
I call Michael Jordan?
That's kinda how a phone works.
Speed dial 23.
- I'm doing it.
- Go for it.
I'm gonna ask him
about baseball.
Do not ask him about baseball.
Ahh! Wrong... wrong number.
You're kidding me.
Oh, my God.
Who are you?
Everybody stop
what you're doing,
stand up, and follow me
in the library.
Mike, that goes for you too,
up and at 'em.
Uh, yeah, Louis, I'd love to,
but I have some work
to do for...
His majesty can wait.
All associates
in the library now.
Let's go.
Rumor is we're getting
our annual raises early.
People are freaking out.
That's great, Harold.
I'm thinking about
getting a tattoo.
You need a raise for that?
I'm really overpaying
for my apartment.
Good morning, everyone.
Many of you seem to think
this is about
getting your raises early.
- It isn't.
- Suck.
We've discovered a breach
at the firm.
A confidential witness list
was leaked to a rival firm,
Wakefield-Cady.
Now it's entirely possible
that this was
an honest mistake.
If so, we urge
the responsible party
to come forward.
If not, we'll find out
soon enough.
Either way, we will get
to the bottom of this.
Louis.
Jessica seems to think
a mistake's been made.
I don't believe so.
I also don't believe
this is a matter of ethics.
It's a matter of loyalty.
Someone in this room
has betrayed us all,
and it makes me sick.
The fact that it went to those
holier-than-thou pricks
at Wakefield-Cady, you know
what, that makes me sicker.
Now, you all work together,
in the trenches,
shoulder-to-shoulder,
which means one of you
must know who did this.
Now if y'all harbor knowledge
of the perpetrator
and do not turn him in,
you're as bad
as the perpetrator himself,
you along with the perpetrator
will be fired.
He's doing George W. Bush.
You're either with us
or against us, folks.
He sounds like Bush,
but he looks just like Cheney.
You got something
to tell me, Harold?
- Uh-uh.
- No?
Not that dermatological problem
that you were talking
about earlier in my office?
No, not that one? No.
To show you how serious I am,
I have an incentive.
Whoever turns this traitor in
receives $10,000.
You're welcome.
Feel free to go back to work.
$10,000, that's a big tattoo.
Yeah, it'd be huge.
Why?
- Louis, there was a...
- I don't care.
Tell me what you learned
about Travis Tanner.
It's all in there.
Travis Tanner went to Yale,
undergrad in law,
honors in both.
He was a junior tennis champion.
Tennis. Just like Louis.
Yeah, he played in college too.
- Oh, my God.
- More importantly,
he was the youngest senior
partner at Clyde-MacPhee.
This guy's record
is off the charts.
Really?
He specializes in breaking
class action lawsuits.
Harris Tobacco, Bell Pesticide,
Gravtech Securities,
he broke 'em all.
How come I've
never heard of him?
Evidentially, he doesn't
like to take public credit.
Stays off the radar,
he avoids the press.
I only found this stuff by
looking through court records.
Now it makes sense.
What?
Why he thinks I know him.
I know those other attorneys.
He thinks they've
told me about him.
- They never did?
- No.
- Why not?
- Because he beat them.
This guy's kind of a badass.
You want me to get you
an autograph?
No, I'm just
respecting our foe.
- Foe?
- It's from The Art of War.
No?
No, look, I need to know
how those other cases
are different from ours.
Well, those other cases
were spread out
geographically,
economically, socially.
Ours is in a single town,
a single school with
a single cluster of plaintiffs.
That tennis-playing douchebag
Travis Tanner's on the phone.
You know I listen.
Travis, what can I do for you?
Yeah, I'm happy
to discuss the case,
on one condition.
You're gonna meet me
at Apple Creek High School.
See you in an hour.
Why do you want to meet there?
Because that's ground zero.
And I want the emotion
of that school under my feet
when I negotiate.
I thought you were
against emotions.
I'm against having emotions,
not against using them.
Come on, I thought
we were homies.
Jimmy, I didn't leak anything.
You know, I remember you said
you hated Louis Litt
and you were second-guessing
your decision
to become a lawyer.
I told you that in confidence
over six cosmopolitans.
It doesn't mean
you're not the guy.
Harold, really?
You drink cosmopolitans?
Stop doing that
unless you're with girls,
which you never are.
And, Jimmy, are you kidding me,
going after Harold?
What, how do you know
he didn't do it?
How do we know
you didn't do it?
Maybe you're the guy.
Oh, my God, guys,
this is ridiculous.
All right, has it occurred
to any of you
that maybe this is all
just a big test?
Wow, wow, spoken like a person
with something to hide.
Louis was talking
about loyalty.
Maybe this is just some test
to see how loyal we are
by not turning on each other.
Are you kidding?
Jessica would never play along
with something like that.
Even if it's not a test,
this is a law office,
not Lord of the Flies.
Everybody get back to work.
Are these the Galusska briefs?
You guys, Louis has been
hounding us for these.
Why hasn't anyone
taken them to him?
Are you serious?
Wow. You're scared of him.
He's Louis Litt,
he's not Darth Vader.
This is what courage looks like.
Jimmy, pay attention.
Please.
Louis, the Galusska briefs.
Sorry they're late.
Hmm, only two days late.
- Sure you're ready for this?
- I'm here, aren't I?
I've been looking into you.
You're an elusive man.
Yeah, well,
when you're number one,
you don't need to broadcast
your victories, Harvey.
That's funny.
Where I come from,
number one doesn't usually
challenge number two
to a fight.
This school
was Apple Creek's pride.
Parents felt safe sending
their children here,
and teachers felt safe
teaching here.
You know what Apple Creek
High School is now?
A bunch of trailers
on the outskirts of town.
All because 30 years ago
your clients failed
to cap an oil well
and gave them all cancer.
You see all these
power lines around here?
They crisscross
the entire town.
Two miles down that road,
paint factory.
You got a microwave tower.
And all this grass
that you see?
It's been treated
with pesticide every week
for 20 years.
You say it's our fault.
I say you're wrong.
That office, Mitch Rosewall,
soccer coach, brain cancer.
Library, Monica Dodd,
volunteer.
She ran it for years.
Stomach cancer.
They both died last month,
and they sure as hell didn't
die from pesticide.
- Can you prove it?
- If we go to trial,
it won't be
about proving anything.
It'll be about Monica,
Mitch, and Kenny,
and you won't stand a chance.
Ah, this is fun, Harvey.
I'm just sorry to say
that we won't get
to do this in court.
Against my advice,
Emerson wants to settle.
You're kidding me.
After all this,
you want to settle.
No, I don't,
but those are my instructions.
Call it a draw.
Mike, get over
to Kenny's house.
Tanner's gonna try
and make him cave.
I came as soon
as I got the message.
Kenny.
It's Harvey Specter.
Was Travis Tanner here?
I was just with him.
He couldn't have beaten
me by much.
Sweetie, why don't
you go inside, okay, baby?
Okay.
No, it wasn't him.
It was someone else.
He wouldn't tell me his name.
He said he was
with Pearson-Hardman,
so I let him in.
Did he mention Tanner's name?
No, but it was obvious
that's who he worked for.
He said me
and the other plaintiffs
were gonna get
a settlement offer soon.
- What else?
- He said if we don't take it,
that they're gonna go after us.
That they have dirt
on everyone.
He mentioned
Eva Williams' arrest
for public intoxication,
Bernie Rutherford's
shoplifting arrest
when he was in college.
That's criminal intimidation.
If they want
to go after me, that's fine.
I can handle it.
But the others,
I don't know if they can.
You have to stay strong, Kenny.
You cave,
everything falls apart.
One more thing,
what did this guy look like?
I don't know,
he was average height,
brown hair, brown eyes.
Thanks.
Want me to start figuring out
who this guy is?
No. We'll never find him.
How'd you know Tanner
was going after Kenny?
'Cause if I was the type
to go out of bounds,
that's exactly what I'd do.
- You're not?
- No.
So what's our next move?
I'm calling in reinforcements.
What do you mean?
If Tanner sent a guy
to intimidate Kenny,
he's got something else
up his sleeve,
and I want to know what it is.
What?
Nothing, you guys are like
two sides of the same coin.
What are you saying,
he's another me?
No one is another me.
I mean, you told Donna
I was another you.
I never said that.
You said you were looking
for another you,
and then you hired me.
So see how that works?
Logic.
Mike, let's go.
In my office now.
Oh, damn, Mike.
Tell me you didn't
leak the documents, man.
Are you our Benedict Arnold?
Benedict Arnold,
nice reference.
You helping your
high school girlfriend
with her homework again?
Okay, not cool, Mike.
You know Darla's
in community college.
I don't even know why
you laughing, Harold.
You don't have a chick.
She's of age.
I am so very proud
of you, Mike.
Wow, I really wish you
weren't touching me right now.
You are what loyalty
looks like.
You rooted out
the person responsible
for leaking the witness list
to Wakefield-Cady.
Louis, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
It was almost cute
how you hid the evidence
in the Galusska briefs.
Like you didn't want
to take the credit.
What?
Louis, I didn't hide anything.
Don't worry, no one's
gonna label you a snitch.
Snitch?
We didn't even think
to check the fax machines.
That was brilliant.
The list was sent from
right here in this firm.
This is a copy
of a fax submission form
sent from three days ago.
This doesn't implicate anybody.
That's the confidential
employee code.
She must not have known
that the machine recorded it.
She?
Wait, why am I being suspended?
I didn't leak any documents.
Who told Louis I did this?
Get your arms...
No, no, no, Louis.
You have to stop this.
I didn't turn Rachel in.
That's so sweet
how you didn't really mean
to hand someone in.
Wait, Mike, stop.
You did a great thing.
And because
of that great thing,
$10,000, and don't spend
it in one place.
You say, "Thank you, Louis."
And then,
"You're welcome, Mike."
- Rachel.
- I don't want to talk to you.
- Hey, come on.
- You want "Come on"?
Why would you do that to me?
I didn't do anything to you.
I didn't fax that goddamn list.
And I didn't turn you in.
Then why was I just
suspended, Mike?
All I know is that I gave
Louis a stack of briefs
and there was some fax with
your confidential code on it.
Do you think that if I was
gonna leak firm documents,
I'd be dumb enough to fax
them with my own code?
No, I don't,
but whoever did this
must have framed you.
Yeah, well, it worked.
Rachel, look, you just...
they're gonna investigate this.
They're gonna clear your name,
you know that.
I've worked there
for five years,
and this is how they treat me?
I'm suspended, Mike.
I'm probably gonna be fired.
I should sue them.
Okay, let's not
do anything rash, okay?
It's not rash.
It's standing up for myself.
Rachel, you...
you're over-react...
Excuse me.
You wouldn't happen to know
what sort of wine
pairs well with
a Duck I'Orange, would you?
Try something
with a full fruit flavor,
like a cabernet sauvignon.
Eh, sauvignons are a little
bit oaky for my palate.
This article right here
is all about the resurgence
of Pinot Noir.
You know, you could just pay me
right out in public.
But then I wouldn't
feel like James Bond.
Oh, who's that make me?
Pussy Galore.
Octopussy?
That's enough, Harvey.
What do you have for me?
Nothing.
On paper, Tanner's clean.
He may break the rules,
but he covers his tracks.
You've never come up
empty for me before.
I didn't this time either.
Tanner booked a conference room
at the Waldorf
tomorrow at noon.
Divide and conquer.
He's gonna gather
my plaintiffs,
scare them, and then
give them a lowball offer.
And that's illegal.
What?
You've used me
for a lot of things.
You've never asked
me to investigate
another attorney before.
This guy's good.
If he called your plaintiffs,
I can get his phone records
to prove it.
He didn't make
those calls himself.
He's not gonna be
at the Waldorf either tomorrow.
But I will.
Donna, can you tell me
about these confidential
employee codes
that Louis says Rachel used
to fax the witness list
over to Wakefield-Cady?
I have a thousand things
to do before lunch.
Hold Mike's hand
while he crosses the street,
not one of them.
Donna, this one's for Rachel.
What do you need?
I know we use the billing
codes to charge the clients,
but what do we use
the employee codes for?
They're special codes
for when you need to use
the firm's resources
for personal reasons.
We can do that?
- You can't, but Rachel can.
- Why?
Because a fifth-year paralegal
is more valuable to the firm
than a first-year associate.
Okay, so do you have
a personal code?
- I have two.
- So where do you get them?
They're generated
by the I.T. Department.
We have an I.T. Department?
The computers
don't run themselves.
At least until Skynet
goes active.
Sarah Connor.
No.
- No, I'll work on that.
- Really bad.
Yeah.
What?
Uh, hi, excuse me.
I'm looking for Benjamin.
You found him.
Oh, great, I'm Mike Ross.
We just spoke on the phone.
Man, this place is like
Battlestar Galactica.
Where do you guys
keep the Cylons?
What do they pay you guys?
Pearson-Hardman
takes care of us
because we're on call 24/7.
If a server goes down
or a partner's computer crashes,
people die.
That's a little dramatic,
don't you think, Ben?
It's Benjamin.
I'm sure you don't like it
when people call you Mike.
Actually, I prefer Mike.
Well, Mike, six months ago
I was at Connolly White,
the network went haywire,
and we were in a breach
of contract litigation
worth $400 million.
They needed it fixed
in an hour.
No one thought
it could be done.
I had the network up and
running again in 23 minutes.
Is that dramatic
enough for you?
Wow, you're like
a regular Zuckerberg.
Z-zuckerberg?
Zuckerberg couldn't code
his way out of a paper bag.
You called about
the employee codes.
You're a first year.
You can't have one, sorry.
Okay, well, I don't need one.
I just want to know
if it's possible
for someone to gain access
to somebody else's code.
Sure. For one person, me.
I have access
to all of the codes.
Okay, so in your short
tenure here,
has anyone ever
asked you for access
to someone else's code?
Once. Last week.
- Who?
- I can't tell you that.
Why not?
I.T. Officer/client privilege.
Does that even exist, Ben?
It does in here.
All right, Ben,
why don't we make a bet?
I think you mean a wager,
Michael.
Yeah, sure.
I'm gonna tell you every single
number on this piece of paper,
and you're gonna
give me that name.
And if you can't?
Then I'm gonna give you
this check for 10 grand.
You get one number, one comma,
one decimal point wrong,
and that money is mine.
Oh, and when I win,
I'll also take
one of those computers.
And for the record,
there's not
a single comma on there.
You ready?
Rachel, it's Mike.
I figured out who leaked
the list to Wakefield-Cady.
It was Louis. Call me back.
Hi, I'm Rachel Zane.
I'm here for my job interview.
- Welcome to Wakefield-Cady.
- Thank you.
Okay, as soon as we get inside
I need you to find
every plaintiff you interviewed
and tell them they're here
under false pretenses.
- Done.
- Kenny's meeting us here.
We need him to identify
the man who came to see him,
and we're gonna wait
for that guy to approach
any of our plaintiffs.
And if we connect
that guy to Tanner,
then we have him
on criminal intimidation.
And Emerson Petroleum will
have no choice but to settle.
Hey, Kenny. Good to see you.
This is gonna be fun.
You were right,
he called every one of them.
You see the guy?
No.
Start looking.
Mrs. Williams,
do you remember me?
I'm Mike Ross, from the office.
I remember you.
Do you mind if I ask you
what you're doing here today?
We were invited to come
and hear a settlement offer.
Really?
Um, excuse me
just for a minute.
He came here himself.
Big mistake.
Sorry to ruin
your little brunch,
but I think you know damn well
that you can't legally
address my clients.
Hey, I just came for the juice.
Mmm.
Pulp free.
I know I can't talk
to your clients directly.
But thank God
you're here, Harv.
Because what I can do
is I can talk to you.
Harvey, Emerson Petroleum
is offering $25,000 to each
and every one of your clients.
They don't take that,
this trial stretches out
for years.
Cross-examinations
will be brutal.
You take our settlement,
and this whole thing
will be gone tomorrow.
Now if any of your clients
want to get in touch with me,
here's my number.
Mr. Ross.
Harvey.
Erase that number.
You're not gonna get away
with what you're doing.
You know that, right?
What?
I just addressed you
with a raised voice.
Sometimes my ears
aren't so good.
If other people heard me,
I apologize, Harvey.
I'm just glad
you were smart enough
to figure out
I booked the Waldorf.
Mmm, I think I need
to take this.
I'm guessing
it's one of your clients
wanting to take
my settlement offer.
Hello.
Tanner. I'm coming after you.
Oh, I got your number.
Plaintiffs are scared.
They're talking about accepting
Tanner's lowball offer.
Those floodgates open
and we're done.
That's why I went
to go see Clarkson.
The legal finance guys?
If we can get
our plaintiffs a loan
against a future jury award,
it'll close the floodgates
and buy us more time.
Those loans
aren't cheap, Harvey.
Well, it's better than settling
for pennies on the dollar.
- Then do it.
- I tried,
but they won't give us anything
without collateral.
They don't think you can win.
They're wrong.
That's what I like to hear.
I need a million dollars
to get that loan.
Are you talking
about firm money?
- Yeah.
- No way that happens.
You don't think I'm a good bet?
That has nothing to do with it.
This was your case.
And I gave it to you to win.
Which I will do if you just
show some faith in me.
You can have my faith,
but you're not
getting my money.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here?
I left you three messages.
Louis framed you.
We can take him down.
I don't want
to take him down, Mike.
Why not?
Because I want a fresh start.
So you don't wanna work
at Pearson-Hardman anymore?
I applied for a job
at Wakefield-Cady.
They offered it to me
in the room.
I start Monday.
You took a job at the company
that ended up
with the leaked list?
Do you know
what that looks like?
I don't care
what it looks like.
I'm not guilty,
and I need a job.
So the going gets rough,
and you just quit?
No, I'm not quitting.
I was fired, remember?
No, you were suspended,
and you could still
save your job.
If Louis wants me gone,
I'm gone.
Rachel, Louis tried
to frame me once,
and I fought back.
Why aren't you doing
the same thing?
Because except for you,
no one from Pearson-Hardman
has contacted me at all.
Why would I fight
to stay there?
They're accusing me
of spilling secrets?
I'll show 'em spilling secrets.
I'll tell
Wakefield-Cady everything.
I may not have
a photographic memory, Mike,
but I sure as hell know a lot.
Rachel.
Moneypenny.
- Don't call me that.
- Why not?
Because she had
a thing for him.
This is the other way around.
You don't like me?
Like you enough
to give you this.
What's that?
I tapped the phones
at Emerson Petroleum.
This is a conference call
between Travis Tanner
and several high-ranking
Emerson executives.
I hope they're talking about
more than just the weather.
They're talking about Tanner
intimidating your client.
Both you and I know
that without a warrant
this recording's
not admissible in court.
It is if you testify that you
don't know where it came from.
Why'd you do this?
Because you need it.
I'm not gonna commit perjury
to win a case.
Oh, weird, look what I found.
Oh.
You are a prince among men.
I don't understand
why you use skim milk
and then put whipped cream
and sugar in it.
Because I use skim milk,
I can put whipped cream
and sugar in it.
Ah.
What's wrong?
- Can we talk for a second?
- Yeah.
Last week Louis got
Rachel's confidential code
from the I.T. Department.
And?
And it's a smoking gun.
He's the one that set her up.
Why would Louis
betray the firm?
I don't know,
maybe he's still upset
that he got passed over
for senior partner
and leaked the list
before he jumped ship.
Mike, Louis is a lot of things,
but he's not a traitor.
That man bleeds
Pearson-Hardman.
He's probably wearing
Pearson-Hardman underwear
right now.
I went to the tennis club
with him.
Trust me, he doesn't
wear underwear.
I care about Rachel too.
Louis didn't do this.
Okay.
And if you ever mention.
Louis' underwear situation
to me again...
You're the one
that brought it up.
- Go.
- Okay.
74 plaintiffs.
I can't believe they're willing
to cave for $25,000.
Slow down.
We need to figure out
how to beat Tanner.
Guy's been a step ahead of me
this entire time.
- It's pretty obvious why.
- Why?
You told me that you knew
he'd go to Kenny
because that's what you'd do,
if you were willing
to go out of bounds.
You anticipated him by
thinking about what you'd do.
And?
And that's exactly
what he's doing to you.
Maybe the only way
to get ahead of this guy
is to, I don't know, think
about what you wouldn't do.
Surprise myself. I like that.
You're welcome.
You wanna tell me
what you're doing?
Nope.
Doesn't seem fair to the person
whose idea it was.
You're gone.
- You wanted to talk, talk.
- I did.
I want to put
this competition aside,
call it a draw.
Tapping out, Harv?
This isn't about that.
This is about real people.
You make them
a reasonable offer,
I'll get them to take it.
Real people?
You're standing there
in a $12,000 suit
asking me not to do my job.
You care so much
about those real people,
I suggest you give them
your lunch money
but don't ask me for mine.
Vanessa, I'm gonna need
that wiretap after all.
- Is there any more of that?
- Last cup.
- Did you make...
- Nope.
Dude, that's common courtesy.
You finish a pot,
you make another one.
You gonna turn me
into Louis if I don't?
Hmm? Get me fired too?
Michael.
Benjamin,
you got something for me?
Wager's a wager, fair is fair.
Here's your GX-9000.
You're a good man.
Use it for porn, and I'll know.
Weird.
Hey, Louis, how you doing?
Why did Benjamin
just call you Louis?
I don't know. Made a mistake.
Oh.
No, he didn't.
He called you Louis because
he thinks you are Louis.
Because you posed as Louis
to get Rachel's employee code,
didn't you?
Look, Mike,
it's not what you think.
It's exactly what I think.
Go on. Start talking, Jimmy,
or I'll get get Benjamin
and we can all go see
Jessica together.
Listen.
Wakefield-Cady offered me
a junior partnership
if I leaked the witness list.
No, no, listen, Mike.
I have huge law school debts.
Okay? I mean, don't you?
I can't wait
for Pearson-Hardman
to make me a partner.
So what are you still
doing here then?
After I gave them the list,
they reneged on the offer.
Big surprise.
I didn't see that one coming.
Just don't turn me in, Mike,
please.
I came from nothing.
I worked my ass off
to get into Harvard Law
and become an associate here.
You know who else
worked their ass off?
Rachel Zane,
the paralegal who got fired
because of what you did.
I didn't know it was her code.
I just needed
some numbers, man.
I didn't think
I was gonna get caught.
Look, Mike, I made one mistake.
Okay?
I mean, haven't you
ever cut some corners?
Done some things you regretted?
Jimmy, I like you, man, okay?
But to clear Rachel's name,
they have to know
she wasn't the one.
If you come forward,
maybe they fire you.
If I turn you in,
it's gonna follow you
for the rest of your career.
It's up to you.
Harvey, I'm gonna
do you a favor.
Why don't you tell Mike Ross
to take a hike?
He can stay.
Okay.
You see, 95 of your plaintiffs
have already called me
about the settlement.
It's just a matter of time
before the rest of them
see the light.
I win.
I don't know
the last time you checked,
but as of this morning
all 200 of my plaintiffs
are staying with me.
Bullsh...
I got them an advance
against their settlement.
No finance company
in their right mind
will back your suit.
I don't know if they
taught you math at Yale,
but that's 5 million.
$25,000 a plaintiff.
Exactly what you tried
to buy them off for.
You know what this means?
I'm gonna hammer them all
one by one,
break them down,
and it's gonna get ugly.
No, you're not.
What the hell is that?
It's a conversation between
you and Emerson Petroleum
discussing how you sent a man
to intimidate Kenny Verdasco.
Take a listen.
Don't worry,
it's not gonna give you cancer.
No matter what that is,
it's not admissible.
Unless of course you had
a warrant, which you didn't.
Showed up on my doorstep.
And I declared that
in this affidavit
which I'm about
to send to court.
Hmm.
So you're gonna
perjure yourself
just to win this case?
No, I'm not gonna
perjure myself.
Even if I were, it wouldn't be
just to win this case.
It'd be to get your ass
thrown in jail.
See, you have
power of attorney,
and you're gonna accept
this settlement,
$2 million a plaintiff.
You're gonna take it.
And you and that
shit eating grin
are gonna fly back to Boston
and never come back
to my town again.
You can use mine.
Told you I'd get his autograph.
I can't believe you.
You were gonna perjure
yourself just to win.
I thought you didn't
cross lines,
that that's the difference
between guys like you and him.
I had no intention
of submitting this affidavit.
I'm not gonna perjure myself,
but Tanner doesn't know that,
and he never will.
How do you know?
Because a man who's willing
to break the rules
can't imagine
someone else wouldn't.
You said that
you took my advice
and that you
surprised yourself.
I did.
That loan I got
for the plaintiffs,
I put up a million dollars
of my own money to get it.
If that's not having emotion,
I don't know what is.
- Get out.
- That seemed a little angry.
Feeling good? Satisfied? Happy?
All right.
Emotional.
Okay, maybe a little happy.
$2 million?
Didn't I tell you
he was my right hand?
- I don't know what to say.
- Don't say anything.
Tell me what it's like when you
deliver this news to everyone.
Thank you.
Told you I'd win.
And it's a good thing too.
Because if you hadn't, oh...
What, oh?
There's no way we're gonna
cover that million dollars.
- None of it?
- Nope.
Hey, how's your shoulder?
Amazing.
You called me?
Sure did.
Have a seat.
I prefer to stand.
Fair enough.
Uh, I made a mistake.
You were unfairly punished,
and I would like to officially
just welcome you back.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Are you kidding me?
You think I'm gonna make it
that easy on you?
I want a raise.
- 3%.
- 10%.
- 7%.
Fine.
And Pearson-Hardman
pays for law school
when I decide to go.
Agreed.
And one more thing.
This shoulda been the first
words out of your mouth
when I walked in here.
You need to apologize to me
right now
or I'm gonna file a lawsuit
against you
first thing in the morning.
You're right.
I should have apologized.
But don't you threaten me.
I followed procedure
to the letter,
and you have no basis
for a lawsuit.
No, I don't.
Not about this.
But if you don't think
I have a basis
for all the shit you've pulled
over the years I've been here,
think again.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
How'd it go?
I don't know if you
had plans tonight,
but you're gonna cancel
and help me put
my office back together.
Sure thing.
So long as you don't quit
halfway through.
Thank you, Mike.
Yeah, sure thing.