Why am I being suspended?
I didn't leak any documents.
You were unfairly punished,
and I would like
to officially welcome you back.
- I want a raise.
- Fine.
And Pearson Hardman pays for
law school when I decide to go.
Agreed.
- I fronted your buy-in.
- How could you do that?
You were about to take
a job somewhere else.
We need to start being honest
with each other.
You want me off this case,
so I don't get anywhere
near the spotlight.
In your position,
the spotlight can become
an interrogation lamp
pretty damn fast.
This is always
how it's gonna be, isn't it?
I thought you knew that.
I guess I did.
I need you to use your power
to give me this case
over Scottie.
Are you asking as a friend,
or are you calling in a chit?
Calling in a chit.
Does this have something to do
with that favor he did you?
- Yes.
- Tell me what it is.
I can't.
Guess we're not
sharing everything
with each other after all.
[Funk music]
♪
Time to wake up, sweetie.
Oh, five more minutes, mom.
Did you just call me mom?
What? No.
Louis,
I've said it before.
The bedroom
is a no-mom-talk zone.
Understood.
- You have to catch your train.
- [Groans]
I'll take the later one.
Who are you,
and what have you done
with my boyfriend, Louis Litt?
Oh, you mean the guy
who sweats profusely
before closing arguments?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that guy's gone.
[Laughs]
Really?
Oh, my God.
You're completely dry.
Your love has made me dry,
Sheila.
[Both laugh]
I'm a changed man.
In fact...
I'm gonna rock your world
for one more hour, and then I'm
gonna kick some ass in court.
'Cause today
nothing can go wrong.
Today is my goddamn day.
Yeah. It is.
[Giggles]
♪
[Sighs]
Can you pass the sugar?
Yeah, of course.
Okay, how 'bout that milk?
Sounds great.
How would you feel
about me dating other women
now that we're
living together and all?
Pizza's perfect.
[Snaps]
Rachel.
What's going on?
I got my tuition
payment schedule, and...
Wow.
That is a big bill.
Yeah, and that's
not even the problem.
Remember when Louis fired me
because he thought
that I was leaking information?
I never told you about
negotiating the terms
of my return.
Yeah, you did.
He gave you a 10% raise.
That's not all he gave me.
He agreed that the firm
would pay for me
to go to law school
when I got in.
So what's the problem?
It's gonna be
an awkward conversation.
Rachel,
you want to be a lawyer,
you're gonna have to have
a lot of awkward conversations.
Yeah, but not like this.
I mean, "Hey, Louis,
do you remember when I demanded
"that you pay for me
to go to law school?
"I get that since then you've
now tried to help me get in
"and that we're friends,
but I would really
like my money now."
Okay.
So don't talk to him.
Just get ready to write
a check for $200,000,
because that's what it's gonna
cost for the next three years.
- Awkward conversation it is.
- Best of luck.
Oh.
Norma, it's Louis.
Louis Litt, your boss.
Don't play your games
with me now, woman.
I'm due for closing arguments
30 minutes,
and I need you to stall.
No, you do not pull the fire
alarm as a tactic, okay?
I need you to just
buy me ten minutes
without committing a crime.
Taxi!
There we go.
Come on, baby. My man.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
don't you upstream me.
That's my cab.
That's my taxi.
This is my cab.
Hey, I'm gonna sue you.
I'm gonna sue you for sucking.
I'm gonna sue you
for not being--
okay, I need your name,
date of birth, and I need--
all right, let's Litt this up.
[Elevator dings]
Uhoh.
What did you do to Scottie?
- Nothing.
- That is not nothing.
That is a soy caramel latte with
a double shot of fear and guilt.
That is an apology coffee.
Why can't it just be an
"I'm a great boyfriend" coffee?
If you're
such a great boyfriend,
why don't you know that
your girlfriend is on her way
to Chicago
for the Wexler deposition?
- Oh, shit.
- So I repeat, what did you do?
I overruled her
on Franklin Courier.
I made her give the case
back to Louis.
[Sighs]
You got in the middle of it?
Why would you do that?
Look, I don't want to get
into it right now, Donna.
Okay.
But, Harvey, if you really did
do that to her,
coffee isn't gonna cut it.
For the record,
this was not my goal.
Mr. Litt.
Sorry, Your Honor.
Sorry I'm late.
Are you ready
for closing arguments?
Yes, I am.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
opposing counsel has accused my
client of a great many things.
But you see,
here's the problem.
They don't have one single fact
to back up their claim.
I mean, not one.
So you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna challenge you.
Actually, no, scratch that.
I'm gonna dare you
to find dispute
with the facts of this case
as we presented them.
'Cause are you a good person?
Yes.
Are you a good person?
Are you--actually, you took
notes, so I can see you care.
You see, this is the kind
of jury that they teach about.
This is the kind of jury
that's gonna hear me
when I say these four words.
Do you know
what those four words are?
Because I want you
to remember these four words
to your dying breath.
He didn't do it!
He didn't do it.
[Heart beating]
Mr. Litt, are you okay?
I'm all right.
Yeah, I'm fine.
[Groans]
Bailiff, call an ambulance.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Suits 3x14 ♪
Heartburn
Original Air Date on March 27, 2014
♪ all right
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Well is that it?
Are we done.
Harvey, you've signed
three checks.
And?
Just go.
Oh, by the way,
how's Mike Ross doing?
What are you talking about?
He just came up
with the huge Stemple solution.
He's doing great.
So I guess he didn't tell you
about our little conversation?
What conversation?
The one where he ran
into the fact
that he has a glass ceiling.
Mike knows he has
a glass ceiling.
He knows,
but he didn't know.
We have a problem
with William Beck.
Who's William Beck?
Division head
of Coastal Radiance Sunscreen.
He's trying to break
his contract.
I assume he has
a non-compete.
No, Harvey, I was dumb enough
to let him do whatever he wants.
Why is he trying to leave?
He has some ideas
about the product line
that we're not implementing.
Does he have another offer?
- Neutrogena wants him.
- They can't have him.
He can go work at Starbucks, but
he's not touching this market.
Excuse me,
but maybe there's a solution.
Coastal Radiance is a division
of Pure Moisture Skincare.
Spin them off.
Beck gets to run
his own company,
both stocks go up,
everybody wins.
If I had wanted
the junior associate
to come up with an idea,
I'd have asked
the junior associate
to come up with an idea.
Tony, he's not wrong.
Coastal Radiance is undervalued,
and this fixes that.
Beck has been with us
for ten years.
Maybe it's worth running
the numbers on the spin-off.
I don't want
to run the numbers.
I want him out now.
So have your boy work up
the exit paperwork.
Jonathan will sign off.
Your company, your call.
You want to talk about
what just happened in there?
Not particularly.
Look, it was a good idea.
He should've listened to it.
I know it was a good idea.
What I don't know
is why you didn't push back.
Were you in there?
I did push back.
When you push back,
you change people's minds,
which means either
you didn't agree with me
or you don't care enough
to change his mind.
Look, I know when it's time
to change someone's mind
and when it isn't,
and all pushing harder
in that meeting would've done
was make him dig in.
We had an ally.
Jonathan agreed with me.
Yeah, and then he agreed
with his boss,
which is what we're gonna do,
because it's the way
the world works.
- Come on, Harvey.
- Mike.
This man goes through lawyers
like a hot knife through butter,
and I wasn't
about to get us fired
to protect some guy
I don't even give a shit about.
Now are you on board
with that?
I'm on board.
Can we move on?
- I have nothing to move on to.
- I do.
Have you called Scottie
and apologized yet?
Apologize for what?
What are you,
the apology police?
If you're the one
under investigation,
I'll sign up for that.
Jessica, if you need me
to sign any more checks,
now would be a great time.
It's Louis.
Let me guess.
Even though he didn't
show up to the meeting,
he's feeling left out
and throwing a hissy fit.
He had a heart attack
in court this morning.
Oh, my God.
He's okay.
I made a call, he's got the best
cardiologists at Mount Sinai,
and they say
he's going to be fine.
We should go see him.
He told Norma
he didn't want anybody to come.
That means he's embarrassed,
but he wants me there.
I'll be back
when I'm back.
We handle
all his cases personally.
Nothing with Louis' name on it
falls through the cracks.
No client finds out
this happened.
- Done.
I'll send him flowers
from all of us.
No.
He's allergic.
To flowers?
All of them?
How do you even know that?
I used to send them
to his desk every day
when we were associates.
I know.
I'm an asshole.
Hey.
He's gonna be okay, right?
Oh, my God.
This is awful.
Yeah, I know.
All morning all I've been
thinking about is how
I don't want to talk to him
about the tuition, and now--
Hey, Rachel, Rachel.
Hey, come on.
Look at me.
He's gonna be okay.
He'll be back, and you guys
can have a lifetime
of working together,
going to the ballet,
having really awkward
conversations.
[Chuckles, sighs]
Rachel,
I'm gonna say the thing
that I know
you don't want to hear.
I don't care
about that right now.
It doesn't have to be
a big deal.
We've all got Louis' back
right now,
and Jessica handles
this stuff anyway.
Just talk to her.
You are never allowed
to have a heart attack.
Okay?
Understood.
Louis.
Is this heaven?
I can understand
why you would think that,
but no.
I don't know
how this can happen.
I...Treat my body
like a temple.
And you've also been
commuting every weekend,
and you let the associates
raise your blood pressure.
- It's because they're stupid.
- Okay, Louis, relax.
The doctors say
you're out of danger,
but you shouldn't
get worked up.
- The doctors need to let me go.
- You had a heart attack.
If my blood supply had been
cut off for a half-second less,
it would've been classified
as a minor cardiac event.
And what if it would have
lasted half a second more?
It didn't.
And I need to get to work.
Louis, I'm serious.
You have to cut back.
You could have died.
And if anything
were to happen to you...
Harvey would be a total mess.
Okay?
I'll cut back.
Good.
Excuse me.
It's Mike, right?
Yeah. Did you
still need something?
Because I haven't
finished yet.
I did. I've been
trying to find Louis.
He wasn't at the meeting.
- Louis isn't here.
- Where is he?
What did you need
to see him about?
I want to talk
about what happened.
Yeah, um, look,
I know that we both agreed
that a spin-off
was the better way to go, but--
I don't want
to talk about that.
I want to talk about me.
I want out.
You want to leave
Gianopolous
because of what happened
this morning?
What happened this morning
happens every day.
He keeps people down
when they reach a certain point,
and I'm pretty sure
I'm at that point.
- Yeah, I get it.
- No, you don't.
You don't. No.
In a place like this, your whole
future's laid out for you.
You'll be running
the place before 40.
[Chuckles]
Jonathan, we work
for Tony Gianopolous.
And I know I don't
have to tell you,
but you're working
under the same non-compete
that William Beck is.
But you work for me too.
Louis is my personal attorney.
I know.
But if there's
a conflict of interest,
we're gonna choose him.
I know
that you have a conflict.
I'm just asking,
is there any way
that you can help me
without...
Helping me?
I'm sorry.
Then where's Louis?
Louis is away
on business right now,
so he can't help you either.
Then I'll find
someone who will.
Let this serve as formal notice
I'm letting him go.
Michigan Court of Appeals.
What?
There was a ruling
a few years ago
that established a weak link
in the non-compete.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Do you have a minute?
What can I do for you?
The timing on this
is terrible,
and I-I apologize for that.
What is it?
I need the first check
for my law school tuition.
Excuse me?
Maybe you don't remember, but
when I was wrongfully dismissed,
one of the terms
of my rehiring
was that the firm
pays for my law school.
I remember just fine.
And the only term
of your rehiring
was a 10% increase
in salary.
What?
No, I'm--I'm telling you this
was an agreed-upon term, and--
And I'm telling you
I know nothing about that.
And if I had heard about it,
I would have never approved it.
I was scapegoated
by this firm.
And when you agreed
to come back,
you were given a 10% raise.
That's standard.
My situation
was not standard.
In what way?
Louis accused me
of being disloyal.
And?
And he turned out
to be wrong.
The problem, Rachel,
is that you have no record
of what you're saying.
He agreed to it.
He is your agent.
You're bound by this.
I don't know that.
And the man just had
a heart attack.
And I'm not going
to call him and ask him.
I know that,
and I don't want you to.
Then this conversation
is over.
Dr. Iverson
to the cardiac lab.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Sheila.
I'm so sorry.
You should be.
I don't know
why I had a heart attack,
but I promise
it won't happen again.
You think I'm mad
because you had a heart attack?
It's a sign of weakness.
You hate weakness.
No, I hate
that you're doing work.
- Sheila--
- No, Louis,
do you know what I was thinking
about the whole way down here?
I was thinking
that if you died,
I'd want to die too.
So you better start
taking care of yourself,
because I don't want to--
- Sheila--
- No. No more work.
Okay, but this isn't
what you think it is.
Don't fight me
on this, please.
- Okay, but I need that--
- Don't fight me on this!
"Sheila, as long
as I've known you, I've had a...
"I've had a feeling
of completeness.
[Sighs]
Romeo and Juliet.
Antony and Cleopatra."
You crossed out
Jaime and Cersei Lannister.
I thought they were
too controversial a couple.
- Too controversial for what?
- A proposal.
What?
Sheila, I could've died.
And I don't want my life
to have ended without--
Louis, I don't want you to ask
me what you're about to ask me
because you're afraid
to die alone.
No.
It's not about that.
It's not about dying alone.
It's about living
without the woman I love.
Sheila Amanda Sazs,
you are the love
of what I hope will be
my very, very long life.
And I can't spend one more
second of it without you.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Yes, I'll marry you.
Tony,
what can I do for you?
You screwed me over.
By figuring out how to fire
the guy you told us to fire?
By telling my number two
how to break his non-compete.
- I did nothing of the kind.
- Then it was Louis Litt.
No way.
That did not happen.
That's bullshit, Harvey,
we had a meeting.
Jonathan stuck around
for the paperwork.
Then suddenly he comes back
with his resignation
and some Michigan
Appeals Court precedent
for breaking our deal.
Well, he couldn't have
met with Louis
because Louis wasn't even
in the office.
Then it was someone else.
Tony, what exactly
do you want?
You want me to fire him
like we're firing Beck?
I'll tell you
a little secret.
I don't give a shit
whether Beck goes or not.
But can you understand
why I want him crushed?
Because you want
people like Jonathan Sidwell
to know what happens
when they try to leave.
Ah.
Finally my lawyer shows up.
Oh, I've been here
the whole time.
You see it
how you want to see it.
But if you can't figure out
a way to make Jonathan stay,
you'll be the one who's gone.
Tony.
I'm gonna fix this,
but let's get one thing clear.
I'm not like the other lawyers
you've burned through.
So the next time
you go stomping around
like a four-year-old
throwing tantrums with me,
I'll be the one
getting rid of you.
I guess you were
never really onboard after all.
What?
I did the paperwork for Beck.
I'm not talking about Beck.
I'm talking
about Jonathan Sidwell.
Michigan Court of Appeals
sound familiar?
[Sighs]
Harvey,
he was gonna fire Louis.
If that's the advice
he was looking for from Louis,
he'd have fired him anyway.
And Jonathan would've
found that loophole anyway.
But instead
he got it from you.
What do you want from me?
Louis had a heart attack.
Jessica told us not to--
don't hide behind that shit.
Let's get
into what this is really about.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
your conversation with Jessica.
So that's why you were
telling me my idea was so good
after our Gianopolous meeting.
Yeah.
We had that conversation.
And yeah, it sucks.
But this has nothing
to do with that.
- Then prove it.
- Prove what?
He's unhappy
with his situation.
When people are unhappy,
they find a way out.
Which brings me
back to my point.
You weren't really on board.
I told you,
I took care of Beck.
Well, now you're gonna
do the same for Jonathan.
The Michigan ruling
clearly states that he has--
Don't quote precedent to me.
You figured out how he could
break the non-compete,
now figure out
how to enforce it.
- Harvey--
- Enough.
You're a pretty good lawyer
when you want to be,
so maybe try doing it
for our side this time.
Bad night?
Only if you call
figuring out a way
to crush
someone's hopes and dreams bad.
What about you?
You, uh, take care
of that awkward conversation?
Yeah, it wasn't awkward.
It was...
Humiliating.
Louis never
actually told Jessica.
What?
That's bullshit.
He made a promise to you.
He's an agent of the firm.
You know,
I never thought about that.
Maybe I should just
rush to his hospital bed
and get him to admit
that he screwed me over.
[Sighs]
How could he
lie to me like that?
Rachel, why he lied
to you doesn't matter.
- It matters to me.
- Well, you said it yourself.
Do you really want
to upset him just to find out?
Of course not.
Then take the emotion
out of it.
- What are you talking about?
- It's a contract problem.
Figure out a way
to enforce the contract.
I have someone
here to see you.
Donna, I don't have time
to see anyone right--
oh, look who it is.
Where the hell have you been?
Harvey, don't be a dick.
He had a heart attack.
And you think
having a heart attack
gives you the right
to take the day off?
I'm alive.
[Chuckles]
[Quietly]
Help me.
Hug him back.
I'm gonna let you two
be alone.
Okay, not that I'm not
enjoying this, but...
Shouldn't you be home?
No, the doctor cleared me
to come back.
Sheila's allowing me
half days.
The other half of the day...
I'm at home
planning my wedding.
You're engaged?
It's the happiest moment
of my life.
I'll send my condolences
to the bride-to-be.
That kind of sense of humor
is exactly what I want
of my best man.
Louis, are you asking me
to be your best--
Harvey, before you answer,
I am sorry my fight with Scottie
put you in a bad situation.
And I know calling in
my chit with you
jeopardized our friendship,
but...
- Louis--
- Let me just finish.
You said I can't
have it both ways, but--
I'd be honored.
Thank you, Harvey.
You're welcome, Louis.
- Mr. Kovacs.
- Yes?
Mike Ross.
Pearson Specter.
Do we have business
together?
Jonathan Sidwell.
I understand
you made him an offer
to run
your investment division.
Jonathan reached out to me
with a proposal, and I liked it.
Did he happen
to mention the fact
that he's under a non-compete?
Yes.
He also mentioned that
the Michigan Court
of Appeals decision
makes his contract breakable.
I had my lawyers look into it.
He's right.
Did you also have
your lawyers
look into the theft
of intellectual property?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking
about the algorithm
that Jonathan developed
to identify
companies ripe for takeover.
- My employee, my algorithm.
- Wrong.
Jonathan developed it
while under contract
with Tony Gianopolous,
which makes it his property.
- What do you want?
- I don't want anything.
I just came down here
to let you know
you can go ahead
and do whatever you care to
with Jonathan Sidwell,
but if you use
his algorithm,
we're gonna sue you for
every penny that comes from it.
- Hi.
I heard you were back.
Should you be doing that?
Prescribed.
Light walking.
Need to get the blood flowing.
Okay.
Good.
Look, Louis, I am--
I'm sorry about what happened.
I really am.
Well, I'm gonna
be fine, Rachel.
Good.
I actually wanted to talk to you
about a contracts issue.
- Shoot.
- Okay.
A friend of mine
entered into a verbal agreement
with an agent for a corporation,
and now he's reneging on it.
Wait a second, why verbal?
Why not?
Verbal contracts are binding,
and she knows it.
She have it on tape?
No.
Well, then he can lie about
it, or he can argue the wording.
No, he made a clear promise.
Well, maybe it was
a promise to try,
or maybe it was a suggestion.
No, it wasn't.
What's the contract?
Employment bonus.
Lump sum
or payable over time?
- Three-year term.
- Well, then verbal ain't shit.
If it's paid over a year
or more, it has to be written.
My friend made life decisions
based on this promise.
She could sue
for promissory estoppel.
Well, she could sue
the dick who made the deal,
but she can't sue the company.
- She doesn't want to do that.
- Let me ask you this.
Why wouldn't she get it
in writing if it was legit?
Because she trusted him.
She doesn't know
why he would lie to her.
He did because he could.
He wanted what he wanted
when he wanted it,
and it cost him nothing.
You know?
Yeah.
Maybe she should go after him.
She could try.
But I mean, realistically,
she'll lose, and she should,
because stupidity
shouldn't be rewarded.
So glad you came to see me.
You really got my juices going.
Make me feel glad to be back.
[Chuckles]
- This is nice, fiance.
- It is nice, betrothed.
So where should we do it?
Sheila, are you serious?
I just had a heart attack.
I'm talking
about the wedding.
I say we do it here.
Get married in New York?
It's where
our relationship began.
I think it's only fitting
that we tie the knot here.
I love you.
Good, then it's decided.
We'll do it here
and then move
straight to Boston.
What do you mean
move to Boston?
I'm not moving to Boston.
You have to. You know
what Harvard means to me.
You know what
Pearson Specter means to me.
Okay, Louis,
there are a dozen firms
that would snap you up
in a second there.
Same goes
for law schools here.
Yeah,
but they're not Harvard,
which means
they're second tier.
You seriously expected me
to drop everything
and move to New York?
Yeah, I did.
Okay, well, I think
that's a little presumptuous.
Me?
What about you?
You're the one who has us
buying a place on Bacon Hill.
Okay, it's "Beacon Hill,"
and I thought you liked it.
To visit.
I mean, not to live.
And what are you talking about,
our law schools are second tier?
Your city is second tier.
Well, maybe my city
is second tier.
But it's also the home of
the woman you supposedly love.
Oh, Sheila,
come on, please.
I mean, everything I have
is in New York.
Everything except me.
It's usually easier
if you look at the screen.
With your eyes.
I'm...I'm sorry.
It's just been
one of those weeks.
You know Louis
is gonna be okay, right?
Yeah, I know
he's going to be okay.
But at the moment,
I hate his guts.
I hear congratulations
are in order.
Jessica.
Another eligible bachelor
bites the dust.
Yeah.
I mean, no, it's--
[chuckles]
It's amazing.
How are you feeling?
Better, thanks.
I wanted to get you
a little welcome-back something.
It's not much.
You know, you gave me
quite a scare this week.
I love it.
The Pearson Hardman retreat
five years ago.
And do you know what I
remember most about that night?
What an amazing dancer
you are.
Five years,
Long Island School of Ballet.
[Laughs] You weren't
dancing ballet that night.
Well, they say ballet is
the foundation for everything.
Well, sir, you have
an amazing foundation.
I just thought you could
add that to your collection.
Somewhere between you and...
Bruno.
It means so much to me
that you...
Louis.
Come on.
After everything
we've been through...
You're family.
- Holy shit.
- I know.
He betrayed me.
Maybe, but, Rachel,
you didn't even give him
a chance to explain himself.
I didn't want to upset him.
Even if he was
bullshitting you back then,
the Louis I know
is a man of his word.
And if you went to him
honestly--
It wouldn't matter.
He would just say
he agreed to it,
and Jessica
would still say no.
He might offer to pay.
Absolutely not.
I wouldn't let him.
And you know what,
that's not the problem.
What is the problem?
The problem is
he made me a chump.
- Rachel--
- Donna, I went in there
as a paralegal trying
to negotiate with Louis Litt,
and I left with the money
to become a lawyer,
and for the first time
in my life,
I felt like
I could actually be one.
And now I realize that...
[Chuckles]
When I left that room,
he was probably laughing about
how he pulled one over on me.
Maybe you're right.
But I'm telling you, the Louis
of today would never do that.
Well, the Rachel of today
certainly wouldn't
let him get away with it.
And the Donna of today
is a genius.
Well, the genius of Donna
is every day.
[Laughs]
What are you saying?
Just because
you can't go after Louis
doesn't mean you can't
still make your case.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
You gave me the map to escape
and told the guards
where I'd be.
- Jonathan--
- Kovacs rescinded his offer.
He said I'm not worth it
without that algorithm.
- Listen, I'm sorry.
- Sorry?
You gave me that advice
in the first place.
Because you threatened
to leave Louis.
Bullshit.
You did it because you knew
what I was up against,
and you were
trying to help me.
Whether that's true or not,
that advice was
off the record,
and it turns out that on the
record it's my job to stop you.
Well, congratulations.
You ripped away
the thing I value the most.
That algorithm--it took me
ten years to develop it.
It's how I look
at valuing companies.
It's how I look at the world.
If I can't take it with me,
even if someone thinks
I'm worth something, I'm not.
- Jonathan--
- Please.
You did your job
on the record.
Now off the record,
what do I do?
It was my job to make sure
there's nothing you could do.
Then check in with me
in ten years.
'Cause I promise you
I'll be at the same desk
punching the same clock.
Can't move up,
can't move out.
It's on you.
You were right.
This isn't about William Beck
or Jonathan Sidwell.
It's about me.
- Mike--
- I want to go legit.
- You can't.
- Harvey, listen--
Do I need to state
the obvious?
I can go to law school now,
all right? Get a real degree.
Even if it didn't matter
that you've already
presented yourself
as having gone to Harvard law,
you'd have to take
the bar again.
Okay, I passed it once,
I'll pass it again.
Not under your own name.
And if you take it now,
you'll draw attention
to yourself in a major way.
Then I get Lola Jensen
to hack into the bar
and just put me in there,
just like she did with Harvard.
Are you insane?
Hacking into the bar
is twice the crime
you've been committing.
Rule number one
of not getting caught,
you don't move
the goddamn body.
You do if they're
about to find it.
They're not
They're always
about to find it!
Mike, committing another fraud
to cover your fraud
isn't going legit.
It's just covering your ass,
and it doesn't undo
the fact that you've already
committed the crime.
You think I haven't thought
about all of this?
Harvey, I'm stuck.
There's no way up,
there's no way down.
[Chuckles]
I can't live
my whole life like this.
Okay.
You want to be legit,
there's only one way.
You go to a small town
in Iowa
where nobody's ever heard
of Harvey Specter,
Jessica Pearson,
or anybody else,
you go to law school,
hang out your shingle.
Nobody will ever know.
I guarantee you'd be
king of the hill.
But you could never
come back to the mountain.
Not here in New York,
Chicago, or L.A.
Someone'll know someone,
and it'll all be for nothing.
I can't do that,
and you know it.
I do know it.
Mike, you're in
the major leagues,
and you get to go toe-to-toe
with the best there is.
And I can't tell you
if that's enough for a lifetime,
but if you want to stay,
there's nothing more you can do.
My advice is hold on tight
and enjoy the ride.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help you.
You said there was no way
to stop what you did.
This isn't a legal solution.
It's a business solution.
One where everybody wins.
Everybody wins?
That's what you said
about Beck.
So you want me
to spin off my own company,
I run it, he owns it?
I never said that.
Well, he didn't
go for it with Beck.
Why would he go for it
with me?
Because he doesn't give
a shit about William Beck.
What are you saying?
You develop your algorithm
every day.
Of course.
It's useless if I don't.
Right, but that's not
why you do it.
You do it because you love it.
Well, he can
force me to stay,
but he can't force me
to love it.
And that's exactly
where your leverage is.
If you don't love what you do,
it costs him a fortune.
And he knows it.
This isn't a sure thing.
Which is why
I'm trusting he won't know
it came from me
if it doesn't work.
Why are you doing this?
Let's just say
I love my job...
but I know what it feels like
to be trapped.
Donna said
you wanted to see me
about some more
managerial bullshit.
What?
Don't you think I learned
my lesson with the checks?
- Then why am I here?
- You're here to listen to me.
Do you know
what this is about?
Yes.
And I already told you--
I am not here to ask you
to honor Louis' contract.
I am here to ask you
to make a new one with me.
Our contract with you
is a promise of a job
when you get out,
not paying for you
on your way in.
I have a list here
of the signing bonuses
of the top three associates
who have come into this firm.
Give me an advance on mine.
The last time we negotiated,
you said,
"never sign something without
getting something in return."
What you're getting
in return
is that I keep working here
part-time.
The advance, plus my salary,
will cover my tuition.
Paralegals
don't make that much.
Those numbers don't add up.
I'm not proposing
being a paralegal.
Summer associates
work as lawyers,
and I can do the same.
You came up with that
pretty fast.
It's almost
as if you wanted me
to ask you
what I get in return.
- Do we have a deal?
- One problem.
You already asked me
to break precedent once
when I waived
the Harvard rule.
I'm not breaking it again
to pay for law school.
I'm not asking you
to break anything.
You already established
precedence, with him.
When you paid
for his law school.
That is not
common knowledge.
No, it's not.
That's why
she wanted me here.
I'm exhibit A.
You made an investment
in Harvey,
and I think
that turned out pretty well.
I could argue that point.
No, Rachel's right.
I'm pretty awesome.
I assume you have this
in writing.
I wouldn't be worth it
if I didn't.
Let me guess.
He went for it.
He did.
You want me to set up
your new corporation?
I want you to join
my new corporation.
It's an offer letter.
I don't understand.
You said you know
what it's like to feel trapped.
Thought maybe
you'd like a way out.
- I also said I love what I do.
- Maybe.
But let me tell you
what I once told Louis Litt.
We're not lawyers.
We're investment bankers.
Our job blows yours
out of the water.
Wait a second.
You're not asking me to be
your in-house counsel.
You kidding me?
Most people don't even know
what an algorithm is.
You used it to strong-arm me
and Tony Gianopolous.
You have a mind for this.
Jonathan...
You don't have
to answer right now.
Just think about this.
You're in
the minor leagues here.
I'm giving you a chance
to play in the majors.
I'm glad you came.
I hope you don't mind.
I thought you might like it.
[Both chuckle]
- Sheila...
- It's just a gesture.
It's a beautiful gesture.
You're so...
You're everything.
Oh, no,
is this where you tell me
that you're not gonna
move to Boston?
Not everybody sees me
the way you do.
Most people take a very,
very long time to figure me out.
It's taken me years and years
to get the people here to see
past my short temper
and my...
Weird obsessions.
Your love of mudding
is not weird.
Well, you see, I know that.
You know who else knows that?
Donna,
Jessica, Mike, Rachel,
and Harvey.
They appreciate me.
They're my family.
I'm asking you...
Please don't make me
leave my family.
I'll move to New York.
Yeah.
- You won't regret this.
- I know I won't.
I promise I'm gonna
give you the best life.
We're gonna be
a New York power couple.
Law by day,
love by night.
And when we have kids,
world, watch out.
Sazs-Litts,
they're gonna be ridiculous.
Wait, what?
I mean, let's face it.
Our kids?
They hit the genetic lottery.
Louis, I don't want kids.
What?
They don't get me.
What? I mean, what--
what are you talking about?
I don't like kids.
I like when they're 22
and going to law school,
but I just...
Those would be adults.
Exactly.
No, no, no.
You may think that now,
but when it actually happens,
when--when they're yours,
it's so--
Louis, I'm never
gonna think that, ever.
- How can you--
- How can I what?
It's who I am.
Sheila,
I'm gonna be a father.
Louis, we're so happy.
We can be happy.
Just us.
I was willing to give up
Harvard for you.
You can't give up
something for me?
[Soft rock music]
♪
[Sobs quietly]
[Sniffles]
♪
Well?
Call her.
Call her and apologize.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man