- It's not woodall
coming after us.
It's...
- Sean cahill.
- Welcome to the new s.E.C.
We target law firms.
- Mr. Forstman.
- No.
- You'll miss the opportunity
to get back at harvey specter.
- You've got my 230 mil.
Once the deal closes,
you cut sidwell out.
- What happened to "you think
I'm staying if you leave"?
- Yeah, that was before I knew
You were gonna
screw over sidwell.
- Forstman doesn't throw
money around
Without getting something
in return.
- So we're just gonna go
back and forth trading favors?
- Are you my lawyer or not?
Seriously, rachel, I couldn't
have done it without you.
- [whispers] logan, I should go.
[cell phone vibrating]
- Mike?
- Did you turn off my alarm?
- I did.
- It's after 9:00.
I have been sleeping for...
- Almost six hours.
And the truth is, you need more.
- Why would you do that?
- Rachel, you've been
running back and forth
Between school and the firm
like a maniac.
I don't even remember
the last time
- It doesn't give you
the right to do that.
Plus, harvey's gonna kill me.
- He'll get over it.
- And I've got three briefs
to write,
Plus a paper for torts
And a contracts exam tomorrow.
I don't have the luxury
to sleep in.
- Then you need to ask harvey
for a day off this week.
- Did he ever give you time off
because you were overworked?
- No, he didn't.
- Exactly.
I don't want to be
any different.
- Mr. Jamieson,
you are hereby remanded
To the federal penitentiary
in danbury, connecticut.
[gavel bangs]
- You might want to call me
about an appeal.
The prosecutor has a reputation
for bending the rules.
- You must be
the infamous harvey specter.
- And you must be the chump
eric woodall ordered
To come after me.
- Chump's my name
on my mother's side.
- And I prefer you stop
manufacturing bullsh...
To get my clients to turn on me.
- I'm sorry, I'm not in
the manufacturing business.
I'm just a humble civil servant.
And if you're as clean
as you say you are,
Your clients won't have anything
to give us.
- Unless you bully them
into making things up.
- Oh, see, now I think
you've got us confused,
Because that sounds like
something that you might do.
- The point is, sean,
you had a secret little plan,
And I've taken away
your element of surprise.
- Have you?
You may know I'm coming,
But do you know where or when?
See, while you're battening down
the hatches at b-4,
I might be at d-12 or h-3,
And before you know it,
I have sunk your battleship.
- That's a cute game.
I was more of a rock 'em
sock 'em robots guy.
- So you think you can knock
my block off, harvey?
- I know I can, because I had
eric woodall fired.
So stay the hell away
from my clients,
Or I'll pave
the same career path for you.
- Okay, your hands weren't full
with eric.
They will be full with me.
Harv.
- You want to talk about it?
- That 10,000-pound weight
on your shoulders.
What are you gonna feel like
when you cut sidwell out?
- If I cut him out.
- What are you talking about?
- I've been thinking about it.
I haven't actually
taken forstman's money yet.
If I can get harvey
to back off before I do,
Then I might not even need it.
- You want to use the idea
of forstman's money
To cut a deal.
But, mike, they have money too.
- Yeah, which they can't spend
until their t.R.O. Expires.
- Yeah, but that's next week,
and it's not like
There's some huge block
of shares available now.
Wexler's merging
two of their funds.
- So their investment parameters
don't allow
For more than 4%
of their holdings
In any one industry.
- They have to sell
a block of something.
But how do you know
it's gonna be gillie industries?
- Because I did the math.
That's what I would do.
- You think harvey
will go for it?
- There's only one way
to find out.
- Hey, I don't have
any cash on me,
But if you want
to bring my luggage up,
I'll get you on the way back.
- Nah, you know what?
That's okay.
I don't need a tip
now that I have enough money
- Yeah, what are you doing here,
mike?
- Well, you came to give me
some friendly advice.
I thought
I would return the favor.
- [scoffs]
I don't remember asking.
- Mm, yeah, neither did I.
Walk away, harvey.
- Excuse me?
- You're gonna lose.
- If you think you getting
a little loan is gonna stop me,
I didn't teach you much.
- It's not a little loan.
I've got one of the most
powerful players in the world
- Which is exactly
where he needs to be
To stab you in the back.
- Well, wherever he's standing,
This is what I'm prepared to
offer logan sanders to go away.
That you're legally required
to run that by your client.
- I just ran it by him.
No deal.
- Harvey.
- You haven't taken
forstman's money yet.
He's got some kind of gun
to your head,
And you're just trying to use
his promise of cash
As leverage against me.
[elevator dings]
- This isn't a bluff, harvey.
I came here to give you
a way out.
You came here to give yourself
But I wasn't born yesterday,
and I'm not giving it to you.
- ♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All that time imagine this ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
- Did you go to see sean cahill
in court this morning?
- I'm not in the mood
for a lecture.
- I'm not lecturing.
I'm asking you a question.
- Yes, I did,
and before you tell me
This is what we brought
malone in for...
- I'm not going
to tell you that.
- Good, because...
- Now cahill's coming
directly after you.
- Exactly.
To tell malone
to concoct some bullsh...
To legally get us
that wexler block.
- Look who's been
reading the papers.
- I'm not the only one
who can read the papers, harvey.
So can you.
So can mike ross.
He's gonna go
after those shares.
- He is now.
- What are you talking about?
- He tried to buy us off.
- And you turned him down.
- Yes, which is why
I'm going to see malone.
- No, you're not.
- Jessica, we have to...
- I'm not saying we don't.
I'm saying I'm going to be
the one to do it.
- You know
he's not gonna like it.
- He doesn't have to like it.
He has to do it.
- Therefore, prepare thee
to cut off the flesh.
Shed thou no blood,
nor cut thou less nor more.
But just a pound of flesh if...
Louis, how long have you been
standing there?
- Long enough
to become part of you.
- Okay, you know what?
I don't have time
for you to be creepy.
- So does this mean
you're doing theater again?
- Yes, I am playing portia
in merchant of venice.
- Holy sh..., donna,
that is a meaty part.
- Yeah, it's 588 lines,
which I have yet to memorize.
- Wait.
So you're not off book?
- Louis, if I were off book,
Would I be pacing around
the copy room
With a script in my hand?
- All right, just calm down.
No need to panic.
When do you open?
- Tonight.
- Tonight,
and you're not off book?
What the hell's wrong with you,
donna?
- Okay, this isn't helping.
- I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to be...
- I knew it.
- No, no, no, no, no, no,
just relax, okay?
I don't care
if it takes all day.
We are gonna memorize
these lines together.
- Thank you, louis.
- No need.
For one canst choke
on the joy of life
Without thy mouth full.
- Is that the bard?
And roughly translated,
it means,
When we're done, you're gonna
kick shakespeare's ass.
Milady.
- I take it it didn't go well.
- Because I know you,
and you don't have your usual
"I'm super cool mike ross" face.
- If you knew me that well,
You'd know I'm not in the mood.
And I don't appreciate
being treated like I am.
- I know.
I'm sorry.
- So what did harvey say?
- It's not what he said.
It's what he did.
He knew what I was trying to do,
And he called my bluff
right there.
- He didn't even share the offer
with logan?
- No, he didn't.
- But you said he had to.
- You want me to sue him
for that?
- So what are you gonna do?
- You know what I'm gonna do.
- Mike.
- I don't want to hear it.
I just want to make sure you've
exhausted all your options.
- I have.
- Then maybe you can...
- Amy, the second I bid
on that block of shares,
I've already taken
forstman's money.
[phone rings]
- Mike ross' office.
I'll tell him.
- Sidwell?
- He wants to see you.
- You look good.
- This isn't a social call.
- All right, I take it back.
- Wexler is divesting
A huge block
of gillie industries,
And I need you to find
a creative way
To buy them for logan sanders.
- If I'm not mistaken,
logan sanders has a t.R.O.
That actually prohibits him from
buying any additional shares.
- Which is why
you're going to set up a trust
For us to buy it for him.
- That's called parking,
jessica.
- I know what it's called.
- Then maybe you also know
it's illegal.
- I know it can be illegal,
And I need you to figure out
a way to make it questionable.
- And here I thought
you came in here
To tell me how much fun
last night was.
- Oh, speaking of last night,
You said you blamed yourself
For helping cahill
drop those cases.
So here's your chance
to make up for it.
A moment of self-reflection
around you.
- I'm not using this
as ammunition.
I am using it as motivation.
So figure out a way
to set up the trust,
And do it quickly,
Because we're running
out of time.
- You wanted to see me?
- Come here.
I want to show you something.
- Lionsdale electronics,
3 million shares,
Bought out by management.
- My first lbo.
I was right out of school.
All I wanted was that first
tombstone because it meant...
- Your first deal.
- Broke my cherry.
- Must have been nice.
- It was.
But you know what the difference
between you and me is?
I was just an analyst.
I mean, sure,
I did all the work,
But I didn't do any of the work.
Know what I mean?
- Jonathan.
- Don't be modest.
I know I've been on your case,
But the truth is,
you made this all happen.
- I haven't made
anything happen yet.
- No, you haven't.
And there's a rule against
giving out tombstones too early.
- You're not
supposed to jinx it.
- But there's no rule
against this.
We'll fill it in later.
- Thank you, jonathan.
- You're welcome.
Now go bring this bad boy home.
[cell phone vibrates]
- Rachel, they loved it.
We are gonna go after piedmont
in a week.
We're gonna have
a lot of work to do.
Give me a call when you get in.
- Harvey,
can I help you with something?
- Yes, you can help
by telling me
How much longer it's gonna take
For you to find me a way
to bid on that stock.
- It's going to take
as long as it takes.
- Well, it better not be
more than a day,
Or I won't need it at all.
- It's so good to hear this
from the horse's mouth.
- It means the next time
you want me to break the law,
At least have the balls
to ask me yourself.
First off, jessica insisted
on asking you herself,
And I agreed with her,
because we're on the same page.
And nobody's asking you
to break the law.
We're telling you
to sidestep it.
- That's not the job
I signed on for.
- The job you signed on for
Is the job we tell you
you signed on for.
- Well, that's
a bullsh... justification,
And you know it.
- What I know is,
there's a reason
We make the kind of money we do.
It's because we figure out a way
to get things like this done.
So stop questioning my integrity
and start doing your job.
- Harvey, do you have a second?
- That's about all I have.
- All right,
I was wondering if...
If maybe I could possibly just...
- Time's up.
- Could I get a day or two off?
- A day or two?
- A day.
I just need one day away.
- Are you sure
that's all you need?
- Would you also like me
to make your bed?
- Maybe I can triple your salary
while we're at it.
- No, really, what can I do
to make your life easier?
I have been juggling work
and school for months now,
And I-I haven't asked
for any special treatment.
- You're asking now.
- I'm not asking for time off
To go to the hamptons.
This is law school
I'm talking about.
You didn't say anything
about law school.
- Well, it's for law school.
- Well, this is your law school.
This, right here.
And by the way,
we're paying you for it.
- I know, and I'm grateful.
- If you're grateful,
then you'll stop complaining
About how much work
you have to do,
And you'll figure out
how to best manage your time,
But as far as getting time off,
that's not gonna happen
If you still plan on
working for me.
Now, you still need
a day or two off?
- No, I can manage.
- Thou shalt have nothing
but the forfeiture
To be so taken
at thy peril, jew.
- Why, then, let the devil
give him good of it.
I'll stay no longer question.
Come on, let's go.
This be-eth awesome.
- Where's your script?
- I don't need a script.
I'm off book.
- How can you be off book?
You're not even in the play.
- Because I know
all of willy's work by heart.
- All 37 plays?
- Mm-hmm.
- For to be wise and love
exceeds man's might.
- Vengeance is in my heart,
death in my hand.
Blood and revenge
are hammering in my head.
What... what's the matter?
- Are you kidding me?
You have every word this man's
ever written memorized,
And I'm on
in an hour and a half,
And I'm gonna
make a fool of myself.
- Donna, forget
about my extraordinary gift
And focus on yourself.
We have done this whole play.
You know your part.
It will be fine.
- It's not gonna be fine.
- Donna.
- I haven't been on the stage
in years.
- So you're nervous.
All great performers
get nervous.
It brings out the genius.
- What if I'm not genius?
What if I'm not even good?
I was pretty damn good, louis.
I was.
But I knew the odds
of somebody making it
Were close to zero
no matter how good they were.
My father lost our money
when I was 13,
And I-I found out
what it was like to struggle,
So instead of pursuing my dream,
I chose this...
And that let me pretend
That maybe I was good enough
to make it.
But what if I wasn't?
- Mm-mm, all right, look,
I'm gonna tell you
something about myself
That I never told anyone.
I have stage fright.
Got it when I was
in third grade.
Let it get the best of me.
I never got over it.
And I cannot let you
make the same mistake.
- But...
- Look at me.
Donna victoria paulsen,
You have never been
more beautiful
And talented
And perfect than you are
at this very moment.
Your time is now.
And you're gonna kill it.
- Thank you, louis.
- No.
Thank you.
- My middle name is roberta.
- I'm so sorry for that.
- Hey.
- Were you working late?
- You really have to ask?
- Thought maybe it would be nice
for us to lie down a little bit.
Together.
But if I lie down,
I probably won't get back up.
- I know you don't want
to hear this,
But I was thinking about it,
And harvey did kind of
give me special treatment.
- Mike.
- He let me skip law school.
- Yeah.
Maybe if you just find
the right time to ask, you know.
- I did, and he bit my head off.
So please just let it go.
Okay?
- Okay.
Just wish all this harvey
and logan bullsh...
Would be over.
- Yeah, me too.
We can get out of town
for a weekend.
- I would love that.
- I've checked
with everyone I know.
- Me too, which is exactly
why I'm worried.
If I have to look over
my shoulder every 15 seconds,
- Okay, but it doesn't mean
you stop looking altogether.
[knocking]
- Hey, do you have a minute?
- Did you set up that trust?
- No.
- In that case, we don't.
- I did something better.
- We're listening.
- One of the biggest red flags
at the s.E.C.
Is a stock purchase with money
kept in trust for clients.
- We've gone over this.
- Let him finish.
- On the other hand,
There's nothing unusual
about a retainer.
- A retainer?
This takeover is
a massive undertaking, right?
Now, I don't know how you've
structured logan's payments,
But I think it's time he pay
this firm a hefty fee up front
And something on the order
of $20 million.
- And we use $20 million of
our own money to buy that stock.
- There's nothing
that prohibits us
From investing as a firm.
- And when the bulk
of our legal work is done,
Turns out
he has money coming back.
- We may just end up
giving him the shares
Instead of his unused retainer.
Or even discuss
with logan sanders in advance.
- And that makes it legal?
- No.
It makes it questionable,
Because they still might
figure out what we did
And make a case.
- We?
- You tell me, harvey.
Am I on the team now?
A little bit of a dickhead
about this whole thing,
So I'd say yes.
- Louis?
Do you have a minute?
- Oh, no.
It could not have been that bad.
- Oh, it wasn't.
It was amazing.
I mean,
it was like riding a bike.
I got two standing os,
And I got you to thank for it.
- Well, that's great.
Fell down a flight of stairs,
and broke his ankle,
Which means the show
won't go on.
- No, no, no,
the show must go on.
- Well, the show can go on.
- No.
- Louis.
Come on, you're the only one
who can do it.
- No, I can't.
I wanted to be a molar.
But that teacher's pet,
dorothy mchale, got the part,
So I was forced to be plaque.
Had to wear this ridiculous
flesh-colored unitard
And drape myself
over my classmates,
And every parent in the audience
laughed at me.
- And then the next year,
I got a bigger part.
Walked right out onstage.
Tommy gallup screams out,
"plaque man!"
Once again,
everyone laughs at me.
So right then and there,
middle of the stage, I...
I peed my pants.
So I ran right off the stage,
Never went back,
And I am not going back again.
- Louis.
A part like this doesn't
come around very often.
You gave me a gift,
and I killed it because of you.
- Donna, please.
- I'm not a lawyer, louis.
This is my chance to shine.
But I'm about to lose
two more glorious nights.
I've never asked anyone
for anything like this,
But there's no other choice.
Please do this for me.
Please.
- You want me to sell
directly to you?
- I don't want you to.
You're going to.
- Why would I do that?
- Because I'm the only one
Who's gonna buy your block
at a premium,
Instead of you flooding
the market with shares
And ending up
getting a discount.
- That's funny.
That's exactly what someone else
just told me an hour ago.
- And now I'll tell you
what I told him.
I'll shut everyone else out,
But you two are gonna
have to go head-to-head.
- You're talking
about a dark pool bidding war.
- That's no different
Than what you were
talking about.
You just wanted to be
the only one bidding.
Thanks for the scampi,
mr. Ross.
It was delicious.
I'll be in touch
with the details.
- Who's the other entity?
- If you can't figure that out
for yourself,
To come out on top
of this whole thing.
- What the hell
do you think you're doing?
- I think I'm washing my hands,
Which I'd like to do
without you bothering me
About whatever bullsh...
you're here for.
- Bullsh...?
We'll see if the s.E.C.
Thinks it's bullsh...
That you're
buying stock illegally.
- You're throwing some
pretty big accusations around
- You think I didn't do
my homework?
The registered bidder
traces back
To a shell corporation
We used six times last year.
- We're allowed to play
the stock market
- You think
because you're using firm money,
That makes it legal?
- Damn right I do,
Because we have no plan
to do anything
Other than keep those shares
ourselves.
- Now who's talking bullsh...?
- What are you gonna do, mike?
You gonna run to the s.E.C.?
- You think I won't?
These aren't your daddy's tapes,
harvey.
These are the rules of the game.
- Then let me dial their number
for you,
Because if you report us,
They'll put a freeze
on this sale,
And by the time we get it
all straightened out,
My t.R.O. Will be expired,
To where we're headed
this afternoon.
- You're a sore goddamn loser.
- I would be if I ever lost.
See you at 6:00.
- Guess what
piece of sh... lawyer
Just got himself a seat
in the wexler pool.
- Mike, what are you doing here?
- What do you mean?
The sale's not until 6:00.
- Didn't you check
your messages?
- No. Why?
- Columbia university called.
Rachel was taken
to the hospital.
- Rachel zane.
- Sorry?
- You have a patient here,
rachel zane.
What room is she in?
- Miss zane is resting and can...
- What room is she in?
- As I was saying,
she can't have any visitors.
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
- Mike.
She's in 1024.
- You've seen her?
- It's locked.
- I don't care.
- What are you gonna do?
You gonna break the door down?
- Yeah, if I have to.
- I spoke to her doctors.
They said she fainted at school.
She's fine.
- If she fainted,
she's not fine.
- They said she's run down
and a little dehydrated
- Because she's sleeping,
and she needs it.
Mike, she's fine.
She's gonna be fine.
- What are you even doing here?
- I'm one
of her emergency contacts.
They called me.
- Yeah, I know, but...
- What's a heartless sh... head
like me
Doing in a place like this?
- Yeah, something like that.
If you ever worked hard enough
to pass out, but you never did.
- [scoffs]
- Look, there's a steakhouse
across the street.
Why don't you and I
go get something to eat?
What, you gonna break
the door down and wake her up?
- No, I'm gonna wait
outside of it
And be there when she does.
- Yeah, which won't happen
Because they sedated her
to make sure she got some sleep.
Come on, let's go get some food.
- Don't you need to be
at an auction?
- Right now, I don't want
to be at that sale
Any more than you do.
- You're saying you're willing
to postpone it?
- I'm saying I already did.
Come on.
- No, I'm telling you,
dr. Lipschitz,
This is like the whole
plaque incident all over again.
Yes, I have told you
about the plaque incident,
At least twice.
I've... no, that...
you know, it doesn't...
You know what, forget it.
That's not the point.
The point is,
is that I'm supposed to be
Leaving for the theater
in ten minutes,
And I am a complete wreck.
I have the worst case
of cottonmouth
In the history of...
What? No, you can talk
with cotton mouth.
That's frickin' lockjaw.
You know something, doc?
Sometimes I just think
that I've wasted
Every single Monday, Wednesday,
and Friday
For the last 14 years.
- You know,
this is the first time
We've ever had a steak dinner.
- I didn't know
you were keeping a tally.
- It's pretty easy to do
when the grand total is zero.
- I know.
I said I wanted to take you out
The night you told me
you were leaving.
- We never got around to it.
- I never got around to it.
- What's the real reason you
were at the hospital tonight?
- The truth?
Rachel asked me
for some time off,
And I all but spit in her face.
- So you felt guilty?
- Pretty much.
Plus,
I knew you needed something
But I can see this dinner
with me isn't working, so...
Here.
- Holy sh...
What is this?
- Louis is in a play.
- You wanted to cheer me up,
And you didn't
start the night with this?
- I wanted to save something
for dessert.
- Oh, my god, that's got to be
a codpiece, right?
I don't want to know if louis
is packing that kind of heat.
- You think I do?
- You're the one
who went mudding with him.
- It was covered in mud.
- How much mud?
- Stop.
- Why would I ask that?
- Oh, man.
I shouldn't be laughing at him.
He still hasn't forgiven me
for using sheila against him.
- Mike, you did
what you had to do.
- You don't think
that was crossing a line?
- It was way over the line.
But I got to tell you,
it was brilliant.
It was harsh,
but it was brilliant.
- You know, harvey,
I-I never told you.
What you did with gillie...
I know you had to do it.
- Like I said before,
we do what we need to do.
- Louis, you're almost up.
Oh, christ, you're sweating
more than nixon.
- I've gone through
four elizabethan collars
- Okay, just breathe.
You're gonna be fine.
- Louis, we are
in the middle of the play.
- You'll have to ad-lib.
Make something up.
Say that he went to israel.
- Oh, my god.
Wow!
I don't even know what...
you know what?
I never thought
you'd be so weak.
- Okay, why do you got to say
something hurtful right now?
- Oh, screw hurt!
Turn that into rage.
- Why would I do...
- You always turn hurt into
rage, you idiotic piece of sh...
It is what you do.
- Okay, now I'm mad at you.
Now, imagine you're in court.
- Court, how?
It's too hard with the curtain.
- Just do it, dipsh...
You happy now?
- No, I'm not happy, you idiot.
Now, you're in court,
And you're enraged,
and you are fit to kill.
Now, do you see
that audience out there?
That's your jury.
- They're a bunch of morons.
- Yeah, they're beneath you,
aren't they?
- They're beneath everybody.
- What else?
- They're a bunch
of civil servants
- I want to rip out their stupid
brains from their stupid heads.
- Exactly.
Now, get out there
and make your case.
And you were meant to play
plaque your whole life.
- 3,000 ducats.
- I'm gonna head back.
- Hey, tell rachel she should
take the day off tomorrow.
- Thanks for this, harvey.
- Excuse me.
Which one of you is franklin,
And which one of you is bash?
Did you boys have a nice date?
- Couldn't be better.
He even paid.
- Oh, I guess
he's flush with cash
In order to do
investment banking.
- No, but I know you.
Mike ross.
And he's using his position
to harass my clients
On behalf of eric woodall.
I decided to take your advice
and focus on you.
- Are you following me?
- Then you also better have
authorization
From the justice department.
- Getting authorization
was easy,
Are on opposite sides
of a takeover battle
And that your girlfriend
is your associate.
- Are you trying to say
that we're colluding?
- Oh, you went right there,
didn't you?
- Well, in the six hours
that I've been there,
Your girlfriend, who I just
mentioned works for you,
Faints at law school
for five minutes.
You guys meet at the hospital.
Then you have dinner
for two hours
Where you cancel
a private stock sale
That you both arranged,
and one hour ago,
That stock mysteriously
gets bought
By some shell corporation
set up last year.
- Wait, what?
- Bullsh...
Where you feign outrage
and you feign ignorance
To help sell the whole story.
Anyway, I just wanted
to give you a little heads-up.
Smile for the cameras.
Harvey.
- You gave me your word.
- And I kept it.
- Oh, yeah,
then what about this stock?
- Jessica must have done it.
- Bullsh...
- I didn't know about this
until five seconds ago.
- There are only so many things
I can buy, harvey.
- Listen to me, we can deal
with this guy's bullsh... later.
Right now, let me deal
with the stock situation.
I'll make it right.
- You can't make it right.
- Mike, you used to trust me.
I need you to trust me
right now.
- [whispers] rachel, wake up.
- Hey.
Where were you so late?
- I was out, thinking.
- Thinking what?
- I don't want to be a fraud.
- What?
- I love you.
I'm married to her,
But I don't want
to do that anymore.
I want to be married to you.
- Logan.
- Rachel...
Will you marry me?
- I can't.
- Why not?
- Because you'll always be
a fraud.
- How can you say that to me?
- [gasps]
- Hey.
You okay?
Hey.
Come on, go back to sleep.
I'll be here when you wake up.
- Who told you
to buy that stock?
- Excuse me?
- Let me start again.
I just found out
we bought the wexler block.
Would you by any chance know
how that came to happen?
- It came to happen
when I found out
The dark pool had been canceled
and I couldn't reach you.
- So you took it upon yourself
to make a preemptive bid.
- Of course I did.
If I hadn't,
forstman would have.
So why are you here?
- I gave mike my word
we'd postpone the sale.
- Well, I didn't give
mike anything.
- Do you even want to know why?
- It was because rachel
passed out at school
And was in the hospital.
- Is she all right?
- Do you care?
To be the villain in this,
harvey.
I am sorry rachel fainted,
But our obligation
is to our client,
And I'm not undoing that sale.
- We can't tonight anyway.
- Why not?
- Because cahill
came out of nowhere.
He's been having me followed.
He thinks mike and I
are colluding on gillie,
And if we undo that sale,
it'll just fuel the fire.
- I told you
I was still worried about him.
Have myself tailed
to pick up a possible tail?
- What did you come in here
to tell me, harvey?
- Now that sean cahill
is involved,
We also can't ever transfer
those shares to logan.
- Which conveniently helps
fix your deal with mike ross.
Doesn't matter.
We don't need to transfer them.
We'll just vote logan's way
when the time comes.
- Jessica, I gave mike my word.
- Harvey, I don't care
if you took a blood oath.
Our duty is to our client,
not a handshake with mike ross.
And this discussion is over.
- Checked you out.
You're free to go
on your own recognizance.
- How much was bail?
- Oh, it's okay,
I took care of it.
How are you feeling?
- You know,
I'm actually feeling...
I'm feeling pretty good.
In fact,
I think that I'm going...
- Rachel, no,
you can't do any work today.
- I'm just gonna
stop by the office
And put away just three files,
send four emails.
I have to do this
just for my own peace of mind.
- No more.
I won't even tell anybody
that I'm there.
I won't.
- Louis, can I talk to you
for a minute?
- First of all,
you were remarkable last night.
- Who said?
- Everyone in the cast.
- Um, you know, I don't
actually read the local...
- You should, because they said
I was a shock to the senses.
I bought six copies
this morning.
Because she thinks
she's such a great singer.
Louis, what I came in here
to say...
- Donna, I'm retiring.
- You're what?
- You helped me get over a fear
That I never thought
I'd get over.
But I don't want to see
the audience as the jury.
I don't want to have disdain
for them.
I am the audience,
And I want to love them.
- Louis.
- Donna, I'm sorry.
Because I know I'm taking away
Your last glorious night
from you,
But I can't go on again.
I, um...
I can't do it.
- It's okay, louis.
It's okay.
It turns out
that the other shylock
Only sprained his ankle.
Looks like he's gonna be able
to go on tonight after all.
- Wait a minute.
He never hurt his ankle at all,
did he?
A lot of things going on lately
with harvey and malone,
And sometimes the best way
to deal with disappointment
In one arena
is to accomplish something else.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, louis.
- Hey, remember when you said
that you're not a lawyer?
You could be.
- Got donna's message.
What's going on?
- How's rachel?
- She's good.
Resting.
- Mike.
- God damn it, I knew it.
I knew you wouldn't fix it.
- I tried.
- You tried?
- And she's the managing
partner, and you know it.
- That wouldn't have
made a difference
- I fought jessica for you
and won more than once,
But this isn't
one of those times, mike.
- My mistake was believing you
when you gave me your word.
- No.
I made the mistake
by not believing in you
The second you brought me
your takeover plan.
Look, I don't have
a lot of regrets.
It's just not who I am.
But this is one of them.
If I could go back
and change it, I would,
But I can't.
- Is that supposed to stop me?
- No, I just wanted you
to know it.
Do what you have to do.
- Mr. Ross,
what can I help you with?
- Actually, nothing.
- Nothing?
What do you mean nothing?
- I mean I made a mistake.
I'm gonna find another way
to win this thing.
I'm grateful, but I'm not gonna
need your money anymore.
- You may not need my money,
but you've got it.
- What are you talking about?
- You think I didn't know
what you were up to?
You tried not to fund the money,
So you could leverage specter
out of the deal
And get out of our deal.
- How...
- Did I know?
I've done the same thing
a hundred times.
Because now I know the kind
of person I'm in bed with.
A sneaky little sh... like me.
- [chuckles]
Yeah, do you know the difference
between you and me?
Because I don't want
to screw over my partner.
- And if I were you,
I wouldn't want
to screw him over either.
That man has nothing
but wonderful things
To say about you.
- You had him take the money,
didn't you?
- He couldn't believe
it hadn't happened already.
He told me he's having a little
tombstone made up for you.
Mike, we are partners on this,
Whether you like it or not.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here?
- I'm here to deliver these.
- Who are those for?
- Who do you think they're for?
For you, for your dressing room.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- You think I'm gonna miss
your closing night?
- I didn't know
you were a shakespeare fan.
- I'm a donna fan.
- You know, harvey,
you don't have to do this.
- The only thing I got going on
tonight is you.