Previously on
Suits...
I want to work with you.
Come to Pearson Specter.
If all you want to do
is work with me,
I can find a job
somewhere else.
Scottie,
that's not all I want.
- Then say it.
- I want you in my life.
It's over, Mike.
I'm onto you.
And I'm going to expose you
for the lying piece of filth
that you are.
Louis, I went to Harvard.
I just changed my grade.
You cheated,
and now you're looking at me
to help you get away with it.
- No, Louis--
- Get out of my sight.
Louis, he did it
so that he can practice
the thing that we all love.
And if you don't let it go,
he's never gonna be able
to practice it again.
You make Mike confess,
you might as well throw his life
down the toilet.
You say we're friends.
A friend wouldn't ask me
to do this.
No, Louis.
A friend just won't hold it
against you if you don't.
Hey.
Where did you race off to
so quickly this morning?
I went to see my mistress.
Mm. Mm-hmm,
and what's her name?
Felony.
Really?
And how would you feel
if I said the same thing to you?
It depends.
Is she hot?
Mmhmm, you realize
you're just digging yourself in
deeper now, don't you?
Well, then it's good that I
was really out getting you...
This.
Minnie Mouse.
[Laughs]
I got a copy from your dad.
I thought
it would complement Panda.
It's perfect.
Good, because I have
a new lease on life.
And I wouldn't
if it weren't for you.
I am not the only one
who helped convince Louis
to let it go.
I know.
So are you gonna get
something for Harvey?
I want to,
but what do you get
the man
who has everything?
The same thing you got me.
A picture of him
dressed as a mouse?
No.
Something money can't buy.
Hmm.
[Groans]
What do you need?
- Advice.
- That tie has got to go.
I've been wanting
to say something for months.
It's not about the tie,
is it?
You know
it's not about the tie.
You're just giving me shit.
We take our opportunities
where they present themselves.
Now what can Donna do
for you?
- I need the perfect gift.
- Mm. Who is it?
Rachel?
Something personal,
preferably a picture
from her father.
How could you possibly--
- Jessica?
Simple and elegant.
Or wild and crazy,
the choice is yours.
Louis?
Oh, God, doesn't matter.
Just get him anything.
He'll cry for days.
What about Harvey?
There is no gift for Harvey.
He gets what he wants,
and he doesn't want
what he doesn't get.
And my knowing that is the only
gift he'll ever need from me.
Donna, ever since
I've been here,
every morning, I step
off that elevator wondering
if this is going to be
my last day.
Last week, that day came,
and Harvey said, "not today."
I...
I just--I need
to get him something
to let him know
what that means to me.
- Okay.
- What?
There is one thing that Harvey
has been wanting to get
for years,
and he hasn't been able to.
- What is it?
- No, it's too personal.
And I don't see
how you're going to be able
to make it happen
when he couldn't.
Whatever it is,
it'll make the perfect gift.
Before we do anything else,
I'd like to officially welcome
our newest senior partner,
Dana Scott.
I'd like to thank you all
for bringing me in.
And I assure you, I will be
hitting the ground running.
Well, that's what
we like to hear.
Harvey, where do we stand
on Franklin Courier?
They just announced plans
for the acquisition Friday.
I'd like to take lead
on this one.
I guess the ground
has been hit.
It's yours.
Shit.
I am so sorry.
I had an incident at Logan.
Did I miss anything?
Not really.
Scottie's going to be handling
the Franklin acquisition.
You're kidding, right?
Franklin's my client.
I was five minutes late.
Ten minutes, actually.
Well, I don't care
if I skipped
the whole goddamn meeting
to get a full-body wax.
I landed that company when
they were a regional shithole,
and I don't need
some interloper to--
Scottie's a senior partner,
Louis.
Oh, this is bullshit.
Then I guess you're saying
the bylaws are bullshit.
My bylaws are a work of art.
I know.
And the bylaws clearly state
that if a senior partner
is more than ten minutes late
to a meeting,
he or she has no standing.
Well, that rule doesn't take
into consideration
a partner being late due
to reasons beyond his control.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
"This rule shall not be abridged
by any circumstance,
"including but not limited
to family illness,
"criminal detention,
and travel delay.
For without punctuality,
we are animals," right?
How dare you quote me to me?
This isn't over.
Yes, it is.
They're still
your client, Louis,
but it's Scottie's transaction.
Moving on.
Boom.
What's this?
Oh, it's only the greatest
gift you've ever received.
Better than M.J.'s jersey
from the 63-point game?
If this folder had played
in that game,
it would have scored
80 points.
Okay, I don't even know
what that means.
Neither do I.
Just open it.
A run-of-the-mill
corporate case.
I don't get it.
Just look at the attorney
of record on the other side.
A. Eliot Stemple.
How did you know?
I talked to Donna.
She told me everything.
- Define "everything."
- Oh, I don't know.
He kicked your ass in moot court
three years running at Harvard.
You're kind of upset about it.
It keeps you up at night.
Yeah, well,
if she told you everything,
you'd know he's been ducking me
for the past ten years.
Harvey, I just told you
this gift is
better than M.J.'s jersey.
Do you think
I'd make that kind of claim
if I couldn't deliver
on it?
What are you saying?
I'm saying
that A. Eliot Stemple
is not ducking you today.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x13 ♪
Moot Point
Original Air Date on March 20, 2014
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Louis, if this is
about Franklin Courier,
I've made my decision.
- It's not.
- Okay.
Then what's this about?
- It's about Franklin Courier.
- Louis.
Jessica, I want to know where
I fall in the pecking order
with regard to Dana Scott.
There is no pecking order.
I don't look at things that way.
Great.
That means I'm behind her
because she's banging Harvey.
I'm going to pretend
I didn't just hear that.
Well, unfortunately,
I can't pretend that
you didn't just screw me over
on behalf
of your partner's girlfriend.
Louis,
I didn't screw you over.
Your own bylaws did.
And if the shoe
were on the other foot
and you'd taken
the case from her,
you'd be sleeping
like a baby.
What does that have to do
with anything?
All right, you know what, don't
bother answering that question.
As far as I'm concerned,
Dana Scott is dead to me.
Louis...
Did it ever occur to you
that these situations
may sometimes be a result
of your own doing?
What on God's green earth
are you talking about?
You have an opportunity
to bond
with our newest
senior partner
or make a permanent enemy
of her.
And I'm saying, in the past,
you've generally chosen
the enemy route.
Can you give me
a specific?
- Off the top of my head?
- Mm-hmm.
Pemberton, Yates, Cohen,
Duffner, Ramirez...
That's
five isolated incidents.
Robinson, Jenkins, Gardner.
Okay, okay, fine.
What's your point?
My point is,
if you let this thing go,
you can change
the entire course
of your relationship
with Scottie...
And who knows,
maybe even redefine yourself
within the firm.
Words to live by.
Jessica,
you may have just changed
my entire outlook on life.
[Sighs]
Is that a bomb?
It's a gift.
You're giving me a gift after
what happened this morning?
You're right.
You did poach my client
on a technicality.
And worse than that,
you used my own precious words
against me, and normally,
I'd declare war, but--
But what?
It's been pointed out to me
that I have certain proclivities
that need to be adjusted.
Louis,
what are you saying?
I'm saying I would like us
to be friends.
It's very sweet.
- Thank you.
- So we're friends?
- Friends.
Great.
Give me my files back.
Excuse me?
You accepted my friendship.
Give me back my case.
Uh, sorry, Louis.
That's not how it works.
What the hell
kind of friend are you?
I'm a friend who is not going
to give you my case
14 seconds
after you give me a scarf.
No, no, no,
it's not a scarf.
It's one
of the world's finest pashminas.
I don't care if it's
the world's only pashmina.
You're not getting this case.
Well, then you leave me
no choice
but to institute
article 19.5/b.
There is no article 19.5/b.
There is now.
All new hires must be
accompanied to client meetings
by the existing attorney
of record.
You son of a bitch.
You just want to start a fight.
Excuse me?
I tried to make friends
with you,
and you just told me
to go screw myself.
I am warning you, Louis.
This is a fight
you do not want.
Oh, no, I want it,
and I'm gonna win it.
And when I do, you better not
go crying to your boyfriend.
Well, look who it is,
the ghost of Christmas past,
Harvey Reginald Specter.
Speaking of the past,
A. Eliot, F.D.R. called.
He wants his bowtie back.
[Chuckles]
Oh, if you'd had rebuttals
like that,
maybe you would've gotten
past me in moot court just once.
Trust me, Archibald,
I'm way past you.
Oh, I guess you are.
Look at you, huh?
Tom Ford suit,
$1,000 hairdo.
What happened
to the skirt-chasing degenerate
I knew back at Harvard?
Oh, him?
He's a name partner at a firm
ten times bigger than yours.
Bigger? Sounds like
somebody's trying to compensate
for three huge losses.
Or somebody's living
in the past and too afraid
to take me on
in the present.
You're the one
who's afraid.
I think you've got
a little PTSD--
post-traumatic
Stemple disorder.
Why don't we go head-to-head
right now?
Oh, I'd love to.
But unfortunately,
my case is up on the docket.
But let's do this again
really soon, okay?
Call me.
AYZ Technologies
versus Janus Microprocessors.
Mike Ross for the plaintiff,
your honor.
A. Eliot Stemple
for the defense.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I forget to put the name
of my firm on the complaint?
I work at Pearson Specter.
That's Specter,
as in Harvey Reginald Specter.
I'm ready
to hear pretrial motions.
Motion to substitute counsel,
your honor.
On what grounds?
On the grounds
that he's a pussy.
- What's that, Mr. Specter?
- I was just wondering
if he has a copy of his motion,
because we never got one.
Not with me, your honor.
Something suddenly came up.
My niece, she took ill.
Well, when your family's sick,
you have to tend to them.
Your honor, Mr. Stemple may
not have a copy of his motion,
but we do have a copy
of his family tree.
He has no nieces.
I meant "niece"
figuratively.
She is actually
my goddaughter.
And what exactly
is her name?
Sandra Silverstein.
Your honor, that's
the same fictitious goddaughter
that's taken ill
every time Mr. Stemple's
needed a continuance
in the last five years.
Sounds serious.
Have you tried acupuncture?
They are completely
out of line, Your Honor.
The only thing out of line
is you.
Mr. Stemple, not only will you
not be replacing yourself,
you'll be paying the court
a $2,000 fine.
[Bangs gavel]
[Clears throat]
We got him.
The cage match is on.
Two men enter,
one man leaves.
We don't have anything yet.
What?
Come on, you need me to try
this thing for you too?
Listen to me.
This isn't thunderdome.
I need you to look at every case
he's worked since law school.
Relax, Harvey.
I'm all over it.
You better be,
because you don't know this guy.
I'm telling you,
once it sinks in
that there's no way
out of that cage,
he's gonna
come out swinging.
You wasted a trip.
Harvey's gone for the night.
I'm not here to see Harvey.
I'm here to see you.
Please, what I have to say
is important.
I'm not interested
in what you have to say.
In law school,
I had nothing.
Nothing.
No friends, no girlfriend,
no respect.
The truth is, I was hanging on
to not flunking out by a tread.
Look at me.
I'm not married.
I don't have children.
I'm not particularly successful.
Why are you
telling me this?
I have a little piece of glory
that I've been holding on to,
and I don't expect Harvey
to care about that.
But you're still first chair.
You can still let me out.
And I thought
that maybe you would.
[Sighs]
I'll think about it.
That's all I can ask for.
Except for one thing.
That's the exact same speech
that your plaintiff gave Harvey,
year one.
Doesn't mean it isn't true.
You think
I'm gonna let you play me?
A man can try.
Stemple, you've been ducking
Harvey long enough.
Now you're either gonna win,
or you're gonna lose.
What you're not gonna do
is avoid him anymore.
Oh, and you forgot.
I looked up your family tree.
You are married,
you do have children,
and your firm is top tier.
Please, I hate my wife,
my children are anchors,
and the only reason
I stay at that firm
is to pay for them
to leave me alone.
[Elevator dings]
Get the hell on the elevator,
Stemple.
I'm not leaving you
in our office.
Good call.
[Sighs]
[Rolling dice]
Eliot Stemple,
that's a blast from the past.
You should have seen
his smug face
when he realized
he couldn't duck me.
Need my help?
No, I am taking this one
all for myself.
Harvey,
it was three times.
You remember
what it did to you?
Yeah, I remember.
But instead of offering help
where it isn't needed,
you should be focused
on Louis Litt.
After what you did
at that meeting,
he's going to come at you
full-bore.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
You picked a fight
with him on purpose.
- Of course I did.
- What happened to the whole
"we need to be open
and honest" thing?
I didn't think we needed
to be open and honest
that one plus one
equals two.
I get it.
You don't want to be seen
as my girlfriend,
so you picked a fight
with the biggest,
baddest prisoner
in the yard.
I win this, I'm the partner
that beat Louis Litt,
not the partner sleeping
with Harvey Specter.
Okay, I respect that.
But Louis just did me
a huge favor,
and I don't want to get caught
in the middle of it.
I don't need you
Good.
Although...
What did you do?
Well, it's not really
what I did.
It's, um...
[Clears throat] What you did.
What did I do?
Louis,
what are you doing here?
Hey, I got your email
last night.
- Yeah, about that--
- No, no, no.
I was happy to get it,
happy to do the work.
Nothing makes me happier
than to spend all night
helping out a friend.
You were up all night?
Caught a power nap
between 4:30 and 4:45.
I'll be fine.
Well,
what'd you come up with?
Per your instructions,
I went through eight years
of Pritchard Holdings
corporate returns
with a fine-tooth comb.
That's a remarkably long
time frame.
Yeah, you ask for four,
I give you eight.
It's what I do.
And I caught every mistake
there was to find.
Great.
File the amended returns.
With any luck,
Jenner Pharmaceuticals
will be none the wiser.
Jenner Pharmaceuticals?
This suit's
against Miller Trucking.
That's what I meant,
Miller Trucking.
Ah.
What are they
suing them for?
Trucking?
God damn it.
You sent that email
just to screw with me.
Louis,
I didn't send the email.
Scottie did.
She used my computer.
I didn't even know.
Oh, bullshit.
She came running to you.
You played on our friendship.
And just now
you had me go on about it
to continue the mockery.
Look, I wasn't mocking you.
I was trying to keep you
from finding out.
I thought if you didn't know,
no harm would be done.
No, you know what,
harm was done.
And if you value
this friendship at all,
you would stay out of it,
because I'm going
to the mattresses
against Dana Scott.
Mattresses?
Have you been watching
The Godfather?
Yeah, I've been trying to
come up with some common ground
to expand our friendship--
sue me.
[Sighs]
Tell me you finished
the proposal
for Franklin Courier.
No.
What do you mean, no?
I mean I didn't do it.
What, did your mother die?
Because if she didn't,
you know--
Louis,
you told me not to.
We're at war, Bennett.
Why would I do that?
I don't know,
but I got a note from you
telling me that you were gonna
be the bigger person
and let Dana Scott handle it.
The bigger person?
You should've known
that was not from me.
[Knocking on door]
Good morning, Louis.
Great day.
Oh, you look a little tired.
I'm not tired.
I don't get tired.
What do you want, Dana?
I'm just dropping this by.
You sent Franklin
a proposal?
Well, I couldn't meet them
without you,
so I figured that I would
send this over instead.
You did this
behind our backs.
I don't believe in doing
things behind people's backs.
That's why I c.c.'d you both
on this letter.
No, you c.c.'d us, so they'd
know that it came from you,
and we had nothing to do
with it.
It did come from me,
and you did have nothing
to do with it.
Yeah, you want to play it
this way, fine.
But if you think
you can outsmart me,
you're gonna get Litt up.
Litt the hell up.
Litt up?
Litt. Oh.
[Laughs]
Oh, my God, that is so cute.
I'm gonna go make fun of it
on my Facebook page right now.
Thank you.
Okay, we're gonna take
this thing apart limb by limb
so that little Miss Bullshit
wished she'd never heard
the name Louis Litt.
Louis,
she's an excellent attorney.
What if we can't find
anything wrong with it?
We're not gonna find
anything wrong with it.
That's why we're gonna
take it apart,
to make something wrong
with it.
Mr. Walker,
in October of last year,
you made a pitch to the chairman
of Kyoto Computers.
How did that pitch go?
It went amazingly,
right up
until when they told us
there was no way they could
actually buy our product.
And why was that?
Because Janus threatened
to withhold their microchip
if Kyoto did even $1 worth
of business with us.
And my next-door neighbor says
he saw his next-door neighbor
cheating on his wife.
Turned out to be nothing
but a vindictive lie.
These are sworn affidavits
from the CEOs of Kyoto, Griffon,
and Howland all backing up
Mr. Walker's claim.
This isn't your next-door
neighbor, Archibald.
Mr. Walker, the truth is
that we control the market
because our product is
better than yours, isn't it?
No, it isn't.
Jake, come on.
The cameras are on.
We're all under oath here.
We are?
He is.
And I have
independent analysis
and sworn testimony
from other CEOs
disputing everything
your client just said.
Those things aren't worth
the paper they're printed on.
My point is
that you can go to court,
spend years fighting
a battle you may not win,
or you can take
this settlement.
This is actually
pretty fair.
More than fair.
The only thing is, he's trying
to get us to sign it,
so he can use it against us
in court.
Just like he did last year
against Micron
and the year before that
against Suntech.
You're just a one-trick pony,
Archibald.
And once you've been
to the show, it's not that good.
Hmm, you're a one-trick pony
too, Reginald.
Only my trick doesn't end
with my own client suing me.
- This deposition's over.
- What do you mean, it's over?
Don't you want
Mr. Walker to know
that you were just sued
for malpractice?
That client
dropped that suit.
And before she did,
she stated on the record
that she got shafted because
you had a personal vendetta
against your opposing counsel.
He likes to pick fights
with other lawyers,
and he doesn't give a shit
what it does to his clients.
- Okay, that's a lie.
- It is?
I think you and I both know
why he took this case,
because he lost this case
and this case
and this case to me
15 years ago.
Go ahead, ask him.
He's not under oath,
but you'll know if he's lying.
And these cases,
they were all in moot court.
Imagine what he'll bring down
on you when the stakes are real.
I can tell you this much,
it'll be a hell
of a lot more expensive
than that settlement.
Stemple, we're done.
Reginald,
you did a great job
making it so I couldn't
get out of it,
but you should have picked
a better case to trap me in.
Because we both know
that my independent analyst
will come up with anything
that I want him to say.
Did you hear
what he just said?
I sure did.
And if you did, and I did...
Maybe it did.
♪
I already had breakfast, Michael.
Maybe, but that's a bag
completely filled with bacon.
Crispy?
To quote my friend Benjamin,
"if it's not crispy,
it's not bacon."
I don't deserve it.
Benjamin.
Michael, I can enhance
the sound of a bee
making pollen recorded
from a satellite.
How can you possibly
know that?
It's been done.
But what I can't do
is enhance sounds
that weren't picked up
by a used camcorder,
because this firm is too cheap
to go with my recommendation
of the $63,000 ZR-X90.
You didn't really
recommend that, did you?
It's also good for making
independent films on weekends.
Okay, Benjamin,
I need this audio,
or we're screwed on a huge case.
Michael,
look at these sound waves.
Okay.
There's nothing there.
No, nothing.
And that's after 12 hours of
maximum enhancement on the tape
and six Red Bulls in me.
Whoa, you shouldn't be having
that many Red Bulls.
I did it for you, Michael.
What do we have?
Uh, nothing.
Then we go
with what we got.
What's he talking about?
He's saying Stemple bluffed,
so now we're gonna bluff.
What exactly are we
talking about here, gentlemen?
We want access to the raw data
from his independent analysis.
And I wish I would've had
a vasectomy ten years ago.
But raw data is work product,
and he has no right to it.
The work product doctrine
is fairly clear on this,
Mr. Specter.
Except in cases of misconduct,
Your Honor,
is fairly clear on this,
which is the situation here.
What exactly
are you accusing me of?
At the end of our deposition,
Mr. Stemple basically boasted
that he plans to fix
the findings of his analyst.
That is a lie.
I never said anything
of the kind.
What you mean to say is
you didn't think our microphone
would pick it up.
So let me get this straight.
They're doctoring a tape to
accuse me of doctoring a report.
Mr. Stemple, you have
a history of lying to me.
So if you're on that tape
saying anything close
to what they're claiming,
I'll not only sanction you,
I'll report you to the bar.
I'll give them what they want.
[Scoffs]
I have to admit,
when I read 600 million Euros,
I thought it was a typo.
It wasn't.
Baltic Freight can get
a bottle of Riesling
from an Alsatian Vineyard
to a Dubai hotel in six hours.
This is a steal.
I agree. The proposal-
most riveting thing I've read
since Fifty Shades of Grey.
Both: But--
But the real upside for you
is that I...
- We.
- Not exactly.
Structured the deal
to avoid U.S. taxes.
By setting up a subsidiary
with headquarters in Cyprus.
Where the rate
is only 5.7%.
Wait a second,
doesn't that mean they would
have to build in Cyprus?
Mmhmm, and I've already
locked up a developer.
Yeah, I see that,
the Whitner Group.
Whoa, I'm so sorry.
Did you just say Whitner Group?
Right now
they're being investigated
by the FTC for fraud.
What?
Yeah, it was just announced
this morning.
Well,
those are bogus charges
concocted
by a jealous competitor
who will stop at nothing--
I'm so sorry, Tom.
As Dana mentioned,
I was c.c.'d on this,
but I didn't exactly
have a chance to vet it.
Tom.
Our reputation is everything,
Ms. Scott.
We can't be in bed
with criminals.
I will have another proposal
over to you within the hour.
Thank you, Louis.
Oh, and, Tom,
Scottie's new, okay?
So just cut her some slack.
Because when
those training wheels pop off,
she's gonna be
really, really good.
- What the hell did you do?
- Nothing.
I just called a friend
at the FTC.
You made up charges
against a company
just to get back at me?
I did nothing of the kind.
I simply alerted a friend
to some possible misdoings.
These are people.
You are hurting their business.
Oh, please,
give me a break.
They're not publicly traded.
They don't have a stock price
that'll fall.
And if they're as clean
as you say,
I'm sure they'll be exonerated.
But not in time for me
to get Franklin's business.
Oh, I don't give a shit
when they're exonerated.
You're never getting
Franklin's business.
You really are a dick.
I'm Moby goddamn dick,
and you just swam in my waters.
Per your request,
this is everything.
You didn't just come over here
to deliver work product.
I've got
a revised settlement offer.
And before you say anything,
it contains a provision
prohibiting me
from using it against you.
After what happened today,
you think I'm going to settle?
Please, Harvey,
just take a look at it.
So now that
you need something,
it's Harvey, not Reginald.
Settling is what you do.
Not with you.
And the reason I'm not gonna
settle with you--
I get it.
I ducked you.
Look, I could take the losing,
the gloating, and the taunting.
But what I can't take
is losing to a coward
who's too afraid to stand up
and try to beat me again.
I didn't beat you
the first time.
What the hell
are you talking about?
It was rigged.
I bribed the jury.
- What?
- That's why I keep ducking you.
You're telling me
you cheated all three years?
[Sighs]
Once I won,
I was the guy
who beat Harvey Specter.
There was no going back.
And you think admitting that
now is gonna make me settle?
I'm coming clean because
it's time to put it to bed.
Put it to bed?
You gonna take an ad out in
the Crimson saying you cheated,
just like you did
when you beat me back then?
- Harvey.
- No, no, I remember it.
Muhammad Ali standing
over Sonny Liston.
Your face on Ali,
mine on Liston,
every day for a week.
You know who my hero was,
Eliot?
Ali.
That's right,
you piece of shit.
You want to know
why I did that?
Because you were
an arrogant bastard
who skated through life
without a care in the world,
getting everything you wanted
from anyone you needed!
And you know what,
if I had to do it again,
I would do
the exact same thing.
I'm not settling.
You so much as think about
breaking the law on this case,
I guarantee
you'll end up in jail.
Is this--
Yes.
- With extra--
- Yes.
- To what do I owe this honor?
- Dana Scott.
- No.
- Hear me out.
You won.
I'm not saying you have
to give in to her.
I'm saying,
make amends with her.
Mm, and why would I want
to do that?
Well, it would help
if you tried
putting yourself
in her shoes.
The same shoes that tried
walking away with my client?
Louis, all I'm saying is,
she came here
from Darby International
to be Harvey's girlfriend.
I'd say that's enough baggage
to deserve you
cutting her some slack.
But I did cut her
some slack, Donna.
I bought her
the world's finest pashmina,
and she wiped her ass
with it in return.
Okay, I got it.
You're never gonna like her.
Forget I said anything.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait a second.
Did Harvey send you here?
No, Louis, he didn't.
Harvey doesn't care
about this.
Why do you?
[Sighs]
Because I know Harvey,
I know Scottie, and I know you.
And if somebody
doesn't back down,
this isn't gonna end well.
Are you saying
that you or Harvey
are gonna hold this
against me?
No, Louis,
I'm not saying that.
Good, because then
I'll tell you what I told him.
If our friendship
is dependent on this,
then we do not have
a friendship at all.
It's not.
I was just trying to help.
Mr. Morris,
please tell the court
what the raw data indicates
about the two companies'
microprocessors.
And I remind you,
you're under oath.
Both products operate
at the exact same rate.
What you're saying is,
our product is just
as good as theirs.
I'm saying their performance
is identical.
And yet Janus dominates
the marketplace.
Why is that?
Objection.
Calls for speculation.
Oh, I'll tell you why.
It has nothing to do
with product superiority
and everything to do with Janus
bullying its competitors.
That's not a question,
nor is it Mr. Morris' area
of expertise.
No, it isn't.
Bullying is his client's area
of expertise.
No further questions.
Mr. Morris,
you just testified
that the microprocessors'
performance was identical.
Is it possible that they are
actually identical?
- Anything's possible.
- How would that be?
Either it's
a one-in-a-billion event,
or one of them stole
the other one's design.
Mm.
Your honor, based on evidence
introduced by opposing counsel
and Mr. Morris' testimony,
I would like to file
a countersuit
against AYZ
for patent infringement.
That is outrageous.
His client stole
my client's design.
I am the one
who is outraged.
This case has nothing to do
with patent infringement.
It does now, Reginald.
Move!
We need to talk.
Not now, I'm carbo-loading.
For what?
For you!
We're still at war.
No, we're not.
So what,
you're telling me
you're waving the white flag?
No, I am waving this,
bylaw 19.5/b,
in clear violation of 139/j.
I got ratification per 139j.
There wasn't
a quorum present.
Big deal,
technical violation.
Not for you.
You're on the bylaw committee.
And you know what the bylaws say
about a member of the committee
implementing an amendment
without approval?
Immediate removal.
So back the hell
off my case.
This won't stand.
Louis, I am warning you
to not keep pursuing this.
I've beaten you before,
and I will beat you again.
- You've never beaten me before.
- Haven't I?
Who do you think it was
that assigned Nigel
to go against you
in the dissolution talks?
Meow.
- You're the devil.
- No.
I'm not the devil.
I'm a strategic thinker.
Louis Litt,
you are hereby notified
that your services
are no longer needed
on Franklin Courier.
And if you go around me,
I will invoke 139j on your ass.
- He set us up.
- You think I don't know that?
He made our client
look like a thief.
It's not true.
It doesn't matter
if it's not true.
Now we're on the defensive.
Gentlemen,
that settlement offer
is about to get flipped
on its ass.
And thank you for introducing
that evidence,
'cause it wouldn't have been
as credible coming from me.
You dropped that comment
on purpose.
Mmhmm. I knew that camcorder
wouldn't pick it up,
just like I knew you would bluff
to get that data.
You made us work for it,
or we would've seen it coming.
[Laughs]
He would never have seen
anything coming
once I fed him that bullshit
about bribing the jury.
I've got your number,
Reginald.
I haven't been ducking you.
I've just been setting you up.
I took a page
from your hero's playbook,
rope-a-dope.
I heard about today.
If you hadn't,
I'm sure there'll be an ad
about it in the paper tomorrow.
What?
Stemple says he's got
my number, and it's true.
I don't know what to do.
What are our options?
For all I know, this deal's
the best I'm ever going to get.
Stemple's been outthinking me
ever since I met him.
You're the only other person
who's ever done that.
I need your help.
Have I ever told you about
my high school tennis career?
I didn't even know
you played.
I was 38 and 3.
You know who handed me
every one of those losses?
Eliot Stemple?
Marsha Myers.
[Sighs]
A 5-foot-nothing math geek
with a 20-mile-an-hour serve.
I should have left
a Marsha Myers skid mark
on the court
and never looked back.
But instead, the little bitch
was a human backboard.
And I think about it
to this day.
You're saying
I should take the deal
because I can't beat him?
I'm saying
I know what it's like
to have an Eliot Stemple.
So I'm going to ask you
a question,
and I want you to give me
an instant response.
Do you want to beat him,
or do you want to settle?
I want to leave
an Eliot Stemple skid mark.
Then there's your answer.
If he's got your number,
then what you want to do
is what he wants you to do.
Harvey, I've been looking
at Stemple's cases.
Doesn't matter.
What do you mean
it doesn't matter?
We're taking the settlement.
- You're just gonna give up?
- Jessica has a plan.
Fighting is stepping
into a trap.
We'd be giving him
exactly what he wants.
Jessica was wrong.
Is that a fact?
You looked at it
the right way.
You just came
to the wrong conclusion.
Stemple wants us to fight,
but I know why.
He was on this case
long before you and I
came into the picture.
What he wants--
what he really wants--
has nothing to do
with you.
Don't you look ready
to rumble?
We're not.
We want to take your deal,
with one small change.
- I'm not lowering the amount.
- No, don't worry.
Instead of $10 million,
we'd like to give you
100 million.
Because that would
still cost us less
than if we fought you
and you got this.
- I have no idea what that is.
- Yes, you do.
It's the glue
that enables AYZ
to stack more microchips
than you,
and you've been after it
for a year.
And when you saw me coming,
you used the opportunity
to bait me
into introducing evidence
so that you could turn it around
and manufacture a suit
to get your hands on that
during discovery.
You can't prove that.
I can when I ask
your analyst
why you hired him
in the first place.
He's gonna say
that Janus needed the technology
and was willing to do anything
to get it.
You don't know
that he'll roll over on me.
Ali versus Liston.
I'm gonna make him
roll over on you.
So here's
what's gonna happen.
You're gonna drop the suit,
publicly admit to wrongdoing,
and pay us this.
This'll cost my client
a fortune.
Yeah, but it's better
than being convicted
of corporate espionage.
Eliot, I'm giving you
a dignified way out,
a chance to really
put it to bed.
Now the judge is gonna bang
that gavel in 30 seconds.
And when that happens,
it's gonna be too late.
We'll take the deal.
I'm just saying,
if you're gonna quote a movie,
quote a movie.
I got one word wrong.
It changed the entire meaning
of the quote.
- Not to me, it didn't.
- [Laughing]
That's what I thought
the quote was.
Okay, fine.
You want to be disrespectful
to Martin Scorsese,
you go right ahead.
Martin Scorsese didn't even
write the damn movie.
If anything, it's disrespectful
to the writer.
Harvey, who cares
about the writer?
I guess
you're right about that.
- Where have you two been?
- I took him to dinner.
Oh, that's never
happened before.
Well, he's never beaten
A. Eliot Stemple before.
No, he hasn't.
What could be different
about this time?
I didn't work for him then.
Yeah, but didn't
he duck Harvey
the whole time
you did work for him?
Okay, fine.
You were responsible
for beating Stemple,
but I was the one who told you
about Harvey's shameful losses
in the first place.
What does he always say?
0 and everything, Donna.
0 and everything.
- Are you finished?
- Yes, thank you.
Oh, and Jessica wanted
to see you
as soon as you got back.
She say what it's about?
No, but I was talking
to Mike.
Hmm.
[Knocking on door]
I heard you won.
- Oh, we didn't just win.
- I know.
You got a Fortune 500 company
to publicly admit wrongdoing.
Doesn't happen every day.
So why don't you
look happy?
I am happy about the win.
But I got a call from the editor
of New York Lawyer,
and they want to interview
the man responsible
for making that happen.
And you want to give Harvey
the credit.
I want you
to take your name off.
I already did.
This case was never for me.
It was for Harvey.
I took my name off
as first chair
the second
we trapped Stemple.
I appreciate that.
But because of this interview,
you can't be any chair.
So you don't want me
off this case
so that Harvey
can get the credit.
You want me off this case,
so I don't get
anywhere near the spotlight.
In your position,
the spotlight can become
an interrogation lamp
pretty damn fast.
I understand.
No spotlight.
This is always
how it's gonna be, isn't it?
I thought you knew that.
I guess I did.
Hey, can I talk to you?
Sure, Louis.
What can I do for you?
Um, I'm sure you heard about
Dana Scott's throttling of me.
I haven't.
You both wanted me
to stay out of it, and I did.
Right.
See, after Scottie took my case,
I went to Jessica.
I was after blood, and...
She told me--
[chuckles]
She told me that I bring
these things on myself,
and she was right.
And that got me to wondering,
what would've happened
if I hadn't shown up
to that meeting late?
So I went to the library,
and I found a copy
of the bylaws.
Scottie underlined
six different traps.
She deliberately picked a fight
to embarrass me,
and I want to know
if you knew.
She didn't do it
to embarrass you.
She wanted to beat the meanest,
toughest guy at the firm.
- Okay.
- It's a sign of respect.
See,
the problem with that is,
when that guy loses...
He's done.
He is no longer the meanest,
baddest guy in the firm.
He's nothing.
Louis...
What do you want from me?
I need you
to use your power
to give me this case
over Scottie.
I can't do that.
Harvey, she can survive this.
I can't.
- Louis--
- Listen, you came to me
and said I was your friend
when you needed a favor.
Well, I am now coming to you,
saying that I need a favor
in return.
The last time we talked,
you said if I value
our friendship at all,
I'd stay out of it.
I don't care.
I know how you operate.
I let it go with Mike
for you.
And what I'm asking for
in return
doesn't even come close,
so...
I do operate that way, Louis,
but not with my friends.
So I'm only gonna
ask you this once.
Are you asking as a friend,
or are you calling in a chit?
I'm calling in a chit.
So be it.
- Are you mad?
- I'm disappointed.
Harvey, I--
You can't have it
both ways, Louis.
[Sets keys down]
[Soul music]
♪
Hi.
The furniture came.
Look, I know we said that
we'd go with all my choices,
but it turns out you have got
pretty good taste.
Yes.
Yes, I do.
- So?
- Hmm?
What do you think?
I think
that I can't believe
you did all of this
in one day.
Well, I've been working on it
since I got home.
I just wanted to have
all of it ready,
so we could celebrate
your big win.
- [Laughs]
- Was Harvey appreciative?
Yeah, are you kidding?
He took me out to dinner.
Oh! Dinner.
Next thing you know,
you'll be getting a promotion.
Yeah. Next thing.
- Hey.
- Hey, yourself.
I hope you don't mind
that I let myself in.
You ready to celebrate?
- I'm ready for a drink.
- Well, hurry up.
Because underneath
these clothes,
I am entirely naked.
Scottie.
What's wrong?
You were in such
a good mood earlier.
What happened?
- I was.
- But?
Scottie, I need you to give
Louis his transaction back.
What?
He figured out that
you set the whole thing up,
and he came to me.
So what?
What does that have to do
with anything?
You can survive this.
He can't.
Wait, so let me get
this straight.
Louis tells me
that if I lose
I can't go running
to my boyfriend,
and then he turned around
and does the exact same thing?
Scottie,
I need you to do this.
Does this have something to do
with that favor he did you?
Yes.
Okay.
Tell me what it is.
I can't.
Guess we're not
sharing everything
with each other
after all.
Scottie.
Harvey, before you say
what you're about to say,
I need to know.
Am I talking
to my boyfriend,
or am I talking
to a name partner?
That depends
on your answer.
You can't have it
both ways, Harvey.
Then you're talking
to a name partner.
[Soft music]
♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man