Previously on "Suits"...
- What you thinking about?
- Just thinking about names.
It's just that if
I'm gonna help raise them,
I'd like to give them something.
You're gonna be the one
who gave him his last name.
My little guy--he got asthma.
The window in the living room--
it's been broken
for seven months.
His client hasn't paid
her rent in three months.
She's had no heat,
and a broken window all winter
despite repeated
requests for repair.
We don't have it in writing,
which is what
the court requires.
I'd like to request time
to confer with my supervisor.
- You have to help him.
- I can't.
We are requesting
permission to evict
if we don't have a check
by 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
- $3,600.
- Should be enough
to cover your rent
for the last three months.
I don't what to say.
- This is a job offer.
- When you graduate,
you're gonna have to pass
the Character of Fitness test.
And you think
working at your firm
looks better than
working at mine.
You're gonna tell me
you had nothing to do
with Harvey asking me
to help you get a law license.
I wasn't even on her radar.
I had one thing I wanted to do,
and you ruined it for me,
just because you can't
accept the fact
that I don't wanna
come back here.
I wasn't trying
to get you back.
I was trying to help you.
I don't believe you.
Stop messing with my life!
[tense music]
[Frank Sinatra's
"New York, New York" cover]
♪ ♪
[knocking on door]
Hey. Mike,
what are you doing here?
I came to apologize
for yelling at you
about going to Gibbs.
- You don't have to do that.
- Yes, I do.
I know you only had
my best interest at heart.
You always do, and...
I shouldn't have snapped at you.
I shouldn't have gone to her
behind your back.
That's okay.
It kinda worked out.
Come on in.
Let's have a drink.
You can tell me all about it.
♪ ♪
You kidding me?
A legal clinic?
- Mm-hmm.
- I thought Gibbs told you
she'd never let that happen.
Yeah, by telling people
I was a fraud.
Turns out the one guy
who knew I was a fraud
from years ago
runs the clinic.
Not only was he
willing to hire me,
he was happy about it.
Seems like crime does pay.
- You bet your ass it does.
- [chuckles]
What?
You're never gonna believe it,
but they have me supervising
this third-year law student.
She thinks she knows
more than me.
- You mean you have a you.
- She is so much worse than me.
Is she constantly
talking about
what a great memory she has?
Dresses shitty?
She have man purse?
Are you done?
Why? You have
someplace you gotta be?
Actually,
I am supposed to stay away
from our apartment for awhile.
So anyway, I said to Louis,
"I don't care
"if most of the associates
start in the bullpen.
I'm not giving up
my office."
That's great, Rachel, but I'm
on my third glass of Chardonnay,
and I don't think
you called me over here
to tell me you submitted
your application to the Bar,
or that you're putting
your foot down with Louis.
[chuckles]
You're right.
I called you over here
to tell you that...
I put my foot down with Mike.
You finally told him to pick
a hairstyle and stick with it?
No. [laughs]
I finally told him
that he made me a promise
before he went away,
and now that he's back
and gainfully employed,
it's time for him to make
an honest woman of me.
Rachel,
I'm so happy for you.
And the answer's yes.
What answer?
I didn't ask you a question yet.
Yes, you did,
and I'd be thrilled to be
your maid of honor.
Thank you, Donna.
Mike, that's great.
I'm happy for you.
Still up for being
my best man?
Wouldn't miss it
for the world.
We going back to the church?
No, we're gonna do it
at our place this time.
No, you can't do that.
Yeah, we just wanna keep it
small, intimate.
I understand, but what kinda
best man would I be
if I didn't offer for you
to have it here?
Pretty shitty one
if you ask me.
So basically
you came here to apologize,
so you didn't have to
get married
at your shitty
little apartment.
You think that I'd ask you
to be my best man
if we had a better location?
- Congratulations.
- [laughs]
Thanks, Harvey.
♪ ♪
Now all we need to do
is make sure
you don't skip out on this one.
Yeah, it's funny.
We also need to make sure
that you don't--
[coughs]--Donna at the wedding.
- What did you just say?
- Huh?
You got something
caught in your throat?
No, I'm all good.
♪ Suits 6x13 ♪
Teeth, Nose, Teeth
Original Air Date on February 8, 2017
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
What's this?
We're celebrating.
Louis, you know
I can't have champagne.
I know, which is why
we're having
the best sparkling apple cider
money can buy.
Well, in that case...
What are we celebrating?
The fact that it's
your first sonogram this week.
Louis, about the sonogram...
Joshua asked
if he could be there.
- What?
- He's the baby's father.
He wants to be in its life.
Or wants to be in your life.
Louis,
I chose you over him.
You don't have to be
worried about that.
And if you want me to say
he can't be there for this,
then I will,
but he asked me, and I thought
it was a fair request,
so I'm asking you.
[mellow percussive music]
Yeah, he can be there.
♪ ♪
- Are you sure?
- No, I'm not,
but I know it's
the right thing to do.
♪ ♪
[whispers] Thank you.
Um, excuse me,
I just need to--
Oh, hello, Benjamin.
Have you come to manipulate
my hard drive?
Debug my processor?
Reboot my motherboard?
Please, I just need to
update your VOX in peace.
If I wanted my VOX updated,
I'd be talking to someone
with a lot more
experience than you.
Ms. Paulsen,
I know you know this
but I will remind you
for the 37th time--
that VOX is our computer's
operating system,
and it needs to be updated
once a quarter.
Once a quarter?
[groans]
What, are we married?
'Cause I got news for you.
This main frame
needs a new memory stick
a hell of a lot more than
once a quarter.
That's it. I'm finished.
I would walk you through
the hard restart,
but I'm afraid you'd focused
on all the wrong words
in that sentence.
[sighs] No, right now
I'm just focused on the fact
that you're finished.
Now leave your money
on the table,
so I can watch you walk away.
Mmm!
Mind telling me
what that was all about?
You mean me making
sexually suggestive comments
to our IT guy?
He has a name, you know.
I do, but I'd be shocked
if you knew what it was.
That's not the point.
No, Harvey,
the point is,
I'm not doing
anything to him,
I'm doing it for him.
And how exactly
do you figure that?
I figure that,
because Benjamin updates
everybody else's
computers remotely,
and once a quarter
he's down here,
pretending not to like my act,
so unless you want me to focus
my rapier-like wit on you,
I suggest you walk
your pretty little self
back into your office.
Benjamin.
I knew it.
No, you didn't.
[dynamic music]
[indistinct chatter]
Mike, thank God you're here.
Sofia Price just called.
She's been in the hospital
since last night with her son.
- Is he okay?
- I think so, for now.
It was an asthma attack, but
she wanted me to tell you that--
She couldn't drop off
the check for her rent.
Damn it, um...
Call her back.
Tell her I'm on it.
Mike, wait.
You covered what she owed
with your own money, didn't you?
Because that's above and beyond.
We can talk about
how awesome I am later.
Right now, I need to
make sure that Sofia's rent
is paid by 10:00.
[tense music]
Louis,
can I talk to you?
Of course.
I--I don't even know
what to do.
My hands are shaking.
Rachel, what's going on?
I'm not getting into the Bar.
- What? That's ridiculous.
- Read this.
[indistinct] After careful
review of your application,
the Character
and Fitness committee
will not be granting you
an interview?
This is bullshit!
I know,
because I knew I was gonna
have to defend myself,
but I didn't think
I wasn't even gonna have
the chance to defend myself.
- Okay, calm down.
- How can I calm down?
This is exactly
what my dad was afraid of.
He said that they'd hold
my relationship with Mike
against me.
You don't know
this is about Mike.
Of course it's about Mike.
What--
what else would it be about?
It could be a mix-up,
some kind of clerical error.
You could've filled out
the paperwork wrong.
I went over it ten times.
Rachel, there is
an explanation for this,
and I'm gonna get to
the bottom of it.
- You don't know that.
- Look at me.
I promise you will get
your interview, okay?
[whispers] Okay.
♪ ♪
Harvey, we have a problem.
What is it?
This is about Mike.
Of course it's about Mike.
That's why I came
here the second
Rachel left my office.
- What'd you tell Rachel?
- What do you think I told her?
I told her that it must be
some kind of mistake,
but you and I
both knows it's not,
which means
you need to fix this.
Yeah, I do need to fix it,
and I will.
Normally,
instead of coming to me,
you'd go full steam ahead
and do something
that makes the situation
significantly worse.
Possibly.
What are you getting at?
Why did you come to me?
Because we said
we'd run this firm together,
and if we're gonna do that,
then I have to
be honest with myself
of what I'm good at
and what you're good at.
And you know I'm better at
this kinda thing than you are?
I do.
Louis,
that shows real growth.
Thank you, Harvey.
And it shows growth on your part
not to make light of the fact
that I just admitted
something that was...
very difficult for me to admit.
You mean that I'm better
at everything than you.
- That's not what I said.
- Too bad,
because that's what I heard.
Okay, Harvey, seriously,
this is not about you
having fun with me.
This is about Rachel.
I know it is,
and if I weren't confident
that I could take care of it,
I wouldn't be
giving you a hard time
for admitting
how much better I am
at everything than you.
God damn it.
Sorry, Louis, gotta go be
better at something.
See you later.
[dynamic music]
♪ ♪
- Can I help you?
- Yes, you can.
My name's Mike Ross.
I'm here on behalf of
Sofia Price,
and this is every dime of rent
she owes your client.
And why exactly are you
bringing that to me?
Because you're an attorney,
not a landlord,
and I don't want there to be
any misunderstandings.
What I understand
is that it's 10:18,
and your client had till 10:00.
You have got to be
shitting me.
I most certainly am not,
and maybe your client
should have thought of that
before not paying her rent
all those months.
You think I don't know
what's going on here?
You're trying to get her out,
so that you can get this place
out from under rent control,
but I'm not gonna let you
get away with it.
No, what's going on here
is that my client is sick of
having a troublemaker,
who doesn't pay her rent,
as a tenant.
Listen to me,
you cannot evict her now.
Her son is in the hospital.
I have a job to do.
Now, I am sorry about
your client's son,
but the court was very clear,
and there's nothing more
that I can do.
[somber music]
Mike, what happened?
Got there 18 minutes late.
What does it matter?
You had three months back rent.
They wanna kick her out
to get out of rent control,
and now that we've missed
the deadline,
there's nothing
we can do about it.
Wrong, there is.
I got to thinking--why would
they be in such a hurry
to evict somebody who can
actually come up with the money?
They're not just trying to
get her out.
They're trying to
get everyone out.
Exactly.
They're gonna demolish
that whole building.
I was over there last night.
The workers were already there,
which means
they've already started.
I get it. You wanna hit 'em
with a countersuit.
I wanna nail their asses
to the wall.
Now you guys get to work
on the suit.
I'm gonna go talk to Nathan
about stopping Sofia's eviction
from happening in the meantime.
Mike.
You don't need to go to Nathan.
I can handle this.
- Listen, I appreciate that--
- I get it.
I shit the bed the other day.
- Oliver--
- Look, Mike.
I admit, sometimes I get
flustered in court.
But the law's clear on this.
It's a layup.
If we have a pending lawsuit,
it puts an automatic hold
on the eviction.
I'm telling you
I can handle this.
Please, let me make up
for the other day.
[pulsing music]
Well, what are you
waiting for?
Get your ass down to court.
Let me know
as soon as it's done.
♪ ♪
All right, Benjamin,
playtime's over.
What the hell did you do
to my computer?
I didn't do anything to it,
other than increase
its performance.
If that's your idea of
increasing performance,
then you ought to
rethink your career,
because that thing
has crashed more times
than Mel Gibson on his way home
from a Saturday night.
Wait a second,
are you smiling?
Of course not.
You're yelling at me.
Why would I be smiling?
Don't bullshit
a bull-shitter, Benjamin.
You're up to something, and you
better come clean right now.
Okay.
I was hoping to do this
in a more formal
environment, but...
Allow me to introduce
The Donna.
What the hell is that?
It's a digital version of you,
with approximately
10,000 of your best quotes,
witticisms, and zingers,
packed into five gigahertz
of computing power.
That's why you've been
personally updating my computer
and nobody else's?
Yes, I've been
secretly recording you
for the better part of
two years.
Two years?
Why me?
Because everyone always wishes
they could say the right thing
at the right time,
and you are the one woman
in the universe who says
the right thing every time.
Now to mention,
you are without a doubt
the most amazing legal secretary
in the history of everything.
Benjamin,
that's the sweetest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
Okay, but you said it
about yourself two weeks ago.
- That I did.
- In that case,
Donna Paulsen,
I wasn't gonna ask you this
for another few weeks,
but how would you feel about
pursuing this with me
as a business opportunity?
Let me think about it.
But first, let me borrow
that thing for a few days.
[mellow bass music]
♪ ♪
Wanna tell me
why you're playing games
with my associate's
admission to the Bar?
- You're Harvey Specter.
- In the flesh,
and if I don't walk out of here
with an appointment in my hand,
you're gonna find out
what that means,
because Rachel Zane
deserves to make her case.
Rachel Zane.
This is clearly
a scheduling error.
Sorry.
I will, uh,
set her interview for
two weeks from today.
I'd say thank you,
but you should've done that
in the first place.
I don't think
she's gonna pass, though.
- What'd you say?
- I just thought you should know
the vote has to be unanimous
among the members of
the committee,
and I have a sense that
at least one
isn't gonna say yes.
Well, you could've
just rejected her,
but you went to the trouble
to get me down here,
so get to it.
Well, I'm just saying...
that if someone were to, say,
sue my biggest competitor
for enough money so that
their stock price plummets,
perhaps Ms. Zane's chances would
take a turn for the better.
Let me get this straight,
you're on the Ethics Committee,
and you're asking me to do
something illegal.
It's not illegal
if you can find
a legitimate reason to sue them.
Then there's gotta be
more to the story,
or you wouldn't be
calling me in here,
blackmailing me into doing this.
The more to the story is,
you have a history of
ethical ambiguity,
and that's what this requires.
And you're either gonna do it,
or you're not.
Either way, like I said,
Ms. Zane's interview
is in two weeks.
[tense music builds]
♪ ♪
Reckless endangerment?
Is this a joke?
I guarantee you,
Sofia Price isn't laughing.
Well,
any judge in his right mind
is gonna laugh you out of court,
because you don't
understand the law.
No, you're the one
that doesn't understand the law,
Ms. Johnson.
You started demolition with
tenants still in your building.
You sent a three-year-old
to the emergency room.
You pursue this, I'm going
straight after the mother,
and I'll turn her into
the negligent party,
and she'll be lucky
to keep her son.
You do that,
and I'll show the court
that you filed construction
plans with the city,
claiming that
the building was empty,
which is punishable
under the criminal code.
No, Mr. Ross,
you won't show them anything.
He will.
Did you think I wouldn't
check up on you
when all of a sudden,
a Queens legal clinic
starts acting like
a Midtown law form.
Well, I did.
And if this goes to trial,
he's the one I'm up against,
and we all know
what happened last time.
You wouldn't be here if that's
all you wanted to tell me.
[chuckles]
So why don't you
give me a number,
and I'll take it to my client.
$10,000.
Not a penny more.
You see, all my experience
at a Midtown law firm
tells me you're authorized
to go to 20,
so let's say 25
and call it a day.
$25,000?
Criminal charges, Linda.
So if I were you,
I'd cut that check,
consider it a bargain,
and hope to hell
that little boy
doesn't get worse.
[tense music intensifies]
♪ ♪
Hey, any luck?
Depends on your
definition of the word.
I met with the asshole
that sent the letter to Rachel.
Let me guess,
you couldn't convince him
to give her an interview.
No, I got her the interview,
but the vote has to unanimous,
and he's putting
a price on his vote.
What does he want?
He wants us
to fabricate a lawsuit
against his biggest competitor.
Jesus Christ,
that's not an ask,
that's a criminal action.
You think I don't know that?
Okay, Harvey, if we find
a legitimate suit,
it doesn't have to be illegal,
which means,
under the circumstances,
maybe it's worth doing.
I'm not doing shit
until I know
the full story on this guy.
Harvey, this is Rachel's
future we're talking about.
Yeah, I know it is,
but I'm telling you
this isn't all he wants,
and I'm not going to
agree to anything
until I know
what the hell it really is.
Well, what are we gonna do?
I'm not doing anything.
You are.
I don't understand.
Louis, you were man enough
to admit to me
that I'm better at
fixing things.
Well, you're better at
something than me,
and it's called
financial transactions.
I appreciate that, Harvey,
but what does that matter?
This guy's doing this
to drive down
someone's stock price,
and I wanna know why.
I'll take care of it.
What do we tell Rachel?
The truth--
that it was a mix-up,
but now she's got
a date on the books.
And you and I need to
fix this before then.
[tense music]
[exhales]
Sofia.
How is he?
He's okay.
They said he should get out
in a couple of days.
[sighs]
I have some good news.
We can stay in our place?
No.
But you have a month
to find a new place,
and a check for $25,000
to help you find it.
[sighs]
Mr. Ross, I'm grateful for
everything you've done,
but Marissa told me that
if we could prove
what happened to AJ
is their fault,
they'd have to pay.
They are paying.
Shouldn't they pay at least
enough for his treatment?
His injections
next year are gonna be
$25,000 right there.
Sofia, going to court
is always risk.
[poignant music]
Our lives have been
one risk after another.
This check isn't a risk.
This is real money.
♪ ♪
How much could we get
if we win?
Absolute best case--
$500,000--
but I'm telling you--
Please, Mr. Ross.
They did this to him,
and if we have a chance
to change his life,
we need to take it.
♪ ♪
[whispers] Okay.
Louis, can I help you?
I was just thinking about
when I stood here years ago,
and I had to tell you
that you weren't gonna
get into Harvard.
You thought you'd
never be a lawyer,
but I knew you'd find a way.
You got me my interview.
I did.
Turns out...
[laughs]
It was just a mix-up.
Thank you, Louis.
Do you think I'm still gonna
have to defend myself
about my relationship with Mike?
I don't know, Rachel,
but I do know we're gonna do
whatever it takes
to make sure
you become a lawyer.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
[tense music]
I'm seeing someone.
These aren't for you.
They're for my fiancée.
But if it'll get you to close
this deal, you can keep 'em.
I'll just buy her
another bouquet.
- I already closed this deal.
- Turns out you didn't.
- That is bad faith.
- Circumstances changed.
What the hell changed
between today and tonight?
My client found out that
her son needs more treatment,
which means
she needs more money.
I think what happened
is your client's seeing
an opportunity for
a bigger payday,
and you can't control her.
Well, what you think
doesn't really matter.
If you don't raise
your offer to $100,000,
we're going to court.
Are you out of your mind?
This isn't Wall Street.
We don't give out
that kind of money.
If you lose,
you're going to be giving out
a hell of a lot more than that.
And if I agree to this,
you'll be right back here
tomorrow, asking for more.
Look, I'm telling you,
I can get her to agree to this.
And I am telling you,
you've had your offer.
That's all your gonna get,
and if you don't take it
right now, we're going to trial,
and I am gonna
wipe the floor with this kid.
I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Listen to me,
if you think
you're gonna pull
some kind of trick
to get you to be able to
sit next to him
and hold his hand,
there's no way
that's gonna happen,
because you were deemed a fraud,
and no judge in the world
is gonna let you
turn his court into a joke.
♪ ♪
Jesus Christ,
Harvey's handwriting is so bad,
he makes my doctor
look like a calligrapher.
The Donna:
You're telling me, sister.
That handwriting's sloppier
than Mel Gibson
on a Saturday night.
Holy shit,
you can adjust my phrases
to the situation at hand?
The Donna: Of course I can.
Who do you think
you're dealing with?
As a matter of fact,
I just incorporated
"holy shit" into
my vocabulary right now.
No way, that had to have
already been in there.
The Donna: Well, look who
finally showed up to the party.
"The Party,"
written by, produced by,
and starring The Donna.
I like the way you think.
The Donna: Of course you do.
I'm you.
And you know what you are?
both: Awesome.
Hey.
You want to take a coffee break?
The Donna:
I think we've earned it.
Yeah.
Me too.
The Donna:
And none of that Keurig shit
that Gretchen likes.
Fresh brewed, or nothing.
When did you get so sassy?
Harvey, good, you're here.
I got your message.
Did you find something?
You tell me.
Explains a lot, doesn't it?
It does.
Good work.
I'll take it from here.
- Wait, where are you going?
- Where do you think I'm going?
I'm gonna see that asshole
and set him straight.
But I ordered you a sandwich--
turkey, no mayo, extra pickles,
like you like it.
Do you want me to fix
Rachel's problem or not?
I do.
It's just...
I thought we could talk.
What do you mean talk?
Harvey, please, I need to
talk to you man-to-man.
It's not about business.
Did you really get me
extra pickles?
Donna once told me
that's what you like.
[stirring music]
Okay, Louis,
I got a few minutes.
♪ ♪
You really can tell
if it's fresh brewed or not?
The Donna: Please,
this isn't my first rodeo.
[laughs]
You're telling me.
Donna, could I talk to you
for a second?
The Donna: Of course you can.
What do you need, hot pants?
What--what is that?
It's a device
called The Donna
that Benjamin's working on,
and it's awesome.
Go ahead, ask it something.
I don't wanna
ask it something.
I wanna ask you something.
No, that's the whole point.
It is me.
The Donna: If by you, you mean
much better than you.
See?
What did I tell you?
Donna, I'm serious.
Look, this is
a really cute joke,
but can I please just have
a conversation with my friend?
The Donna: If by friend,
you mean--
Of course you can, Rachel.
What do you need?
So let me
get this straight,
you're in love with a woman
that you've known
for about ten minutes.
She's having another man's baby,
and yet, you're gonna marry her,
and raise it as your own.
In a nutshell.
What exactly
do you want from me?
I need your advice.
The guy's gonna be at
the sonogram tomorrow,
and I'm afraid
I may cause a scene.
Louis, I don't understand
what you're coming to me for.
What do I know about--
Here, this is why.
Yeah, you get it?
This is why I'm coming to you.
Oh, he's good-looking.
He's not just good-looking.
He's a goddamn
Renaissance statue.
And I need to know
what he's thinking.
Louis, I don't speak
for all handsome men.
What do you see
when you look at me?
What?
I wanna know what you see
when you look at me.
Right now, be honest.
Say the first three things
that pop into your head.
- Teeth, nose, teeth.
- God damn it! Be serious.
I am being serious.
Well, you know what--
Never mind.
I shouldn't have come to you.
Louis, it doesn't
matter what I see.
What matters is
what this woman sees,
and she obviously
sees something,
or she wouldn't be with you.
She'd be with him.
Look, I appreciate that,
Harvey, but you know me.
I'm gonna be in
the same room as him,
looking at an image of
what he made with her.
How do I not lose my shit?
You're right.
It is his baby.
But it's yours too.
And you're gonna want it to have
as much love as it possibly can,
and that means having a good
relationship with its father,
because there's nothing
more important than family.
[laughs]
You're right.
Thank you, Harvey.
[dynamic music]
Hey, Mike.
How's it going out there?
What can I do for you?
I want you to take
a look at this.
Let me get this straight,
you want Oliver
to petition the court
to let Marissa argue his case.
Yes, I do.
- Well, that's not gonna happen.
- Why not?
'Cause he's
a full-fledged attorney,
and she's a third-year
law student.
He gets flustered in court.
And she's never even
been to court.
I'm telling you that I don't
think that he can handle this.
She can, and this woman's
future is on the line.
Then convince her
to take the deal.
She doesn't want the deal.
Putting me in a hell of
a spot here, Mike.
Nathan, you hired me
for a reason.
You told me to run
the associates,
and I'm running them.
Now, are you gonna let me
do that or not?
You're gonna do it, do it,
but you're gonna be
the one to tell Oliver.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
You wanted to see me?
Yeah, I, uh--I did.
Come in.
I want to talk to you about
the, uh, Sofia Price case.
Great, because I actually
wanted to tell you about
five similar cases in New Jersey
that won huge settlements.
That's good work,
and we can use that.
But listen, I need you
to do something for me.
You want Marissa
to be first chair.
I think it's for the best.
Mike, I know why you think
this is the right choice,
but I can do this.
I'm sorry, Oliver,
but at this point
in your career,
I don't think you can.
- Mike.
- Oliver--
you said it yourself--
you get flustered in court.
I know that, but if
I'm going to be a real lawyer,
I have to get better in trial,
and the only way to do that
is to get back on the horse.
And I'm telling you
that when the right case
comes along,
I promise
I will let you do that,
but this is not the case.
This one's Marissa's,
and I need to know
you have her back.
I do.
Good.
I'll go tell her.
You don't have to
do that, Oliver.
Yes, I do.
It's better for the clinic
if she thinks I have
confidence in her,
not that you don't have
confidence in me.
♪ ♪
- You're back.
- You better believe I'm back,
because I looked into
what you're doing
and why you're doing it.
There's really not much
to find, Mr. Specter.
Well, let me
lay it out for you.
Velocity Data Solutions
stole your technology,
and they're
rushing it to market,
so you want to
orchestrate a takeover
and get back what's yours.
That sound about right?
My company is gonna go under,
because of what they did.
People are gonna
lose their jobs.
Then go to the FBI.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Because I can't.
Yeah, I'll tell ya
why you can't.
Because a squeaky
clean guy like you
doesn't come to a guy like me
unless he's got no choice,
and you need me
a hell of a lot more
than I need you,
so why don't you give me a call
when you're ready
to tell the truth.
[sighs]
They got it from me.
I'm listening.
I had an affair.
I was stupid and careless,
and she got access to my laptop.
And you're married,
and your wife
can't find out about it,
and that's why
you can't go to the FBI.
There, now you know.
What I know is Rachel Zane
deserves to be in the Bar,
so you're not only gonna
stop blocking her,
you're gonna run
interference for her
if someone else does.
I don't have
the power to do that.
Bullshit.
You had the power to stop it,
and you better believe
that you can turn it
the other direction.
And in return,
you'll do what I want.
No.
You're gonna do it, because it's
the right thing to do.
But I'll do what you want
for something else.
I need to talk to you.
What's going on?
Oliver just gave me
all the case files for Sofia.
He said I'm the one
who should bring this home.
Yeah, I know.
We talked about it,
and I agree with him.
Mike, I know this wasn't
Oliver's idea.
It was yours.
'Cause you don't
think he's ready.
Which is why I'm coming to you.
- Marissa, you can handle this.
- I know I can,
but the problem is
I can't do it.
What are you talking about?
Um, my father's been sick,
and I haven't talked about it,
because I don't like to...
But now he needs surgery,
and I put in for
the time off weeks ago,
and I have to be there for him,
but now that
I'm telling you this,
I'm thinking maybe I could
fly back a few days early,
or I could get there
a day later--
Stop, stop, stop.
[poignant music]
It's okay.
- I wanna help Sofia, Mike.
- I know you do.
But you need to be
with your father.
♪ ♪
What are you gonna do?
I'll figure something out.
♪ ♪
Donna, hey,
how did you like the--
It's a no.
What do you mean it's a no?
I mean it's a cute joke,
but I'm not interested
in pursuing it as
a business opportunity.
I don't understand.
I thought you liked the idea.
I did, but that was
before I realized
that it was nothing but
quippy lines and sassy remarks.
But that's who you are.
No, Benjamin.
That's part of who I am,
and that's the only part
you've ever seen,
but that's because we don't
really know each other.
But if we did, you'd know that
what really makes me special
is my intuition and my empathy
and my heart,
and this doesn't have
any of that, so...
I'm sorry,
but it's a no.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Mike.
I'd love to chat right now,
but I can't.
I'm actually going to a movie
for a change. [chuckles]
Yeah, I just need a second.
What's up?
I need you to argue
the Price case tomorrow.
What'd you just ask me?
Because it sounded like
you want me to take the case
that you begged me
to give to Marissa.
I did give it to her,
but you didn't tell me
that her father had surgery.
Because I didn't know
her father had surgery.
She put in for it.
And I don't pay attention
to that shit.
Give it back to Oliver.
I told you he'll lose.
Then he'll lose.
Now I'm sorry, but I have to go.
God damn it,
this is a woman's life,
and you're going to
a goddamn movie.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Are you f--
Listen, we work in a clinic.
Every one of our client's lives
is hanging by a thread,
and if they lose,
they're out on the street,
they don't get the surgery,
or they get deported.
That's life.
And I haven't had a life
in five years,
which is why I hired you,
so don't you ever
say that to me again.
[tense music]
Look, Oliver's the kind of
lawyer we get here.
If he can't handle it,
he can't handle it.
That's how it goes.
Then I wanna
petition the court
to sit at the table with him.
No.
We can ask for
a special exemption, and--
And I said no, all right?
You're not
an officer of the court.
They will not grant it,
and that is not your place here.
Then at least I can
sit near him, and I can--
You hear me right now!
I gave you a chance,
because I needed it,
but if you risk
the reputation of this clinic
over one housing case,
I will fire you
and make sure that
you are banned from
ever sitting foot
in a courtroom again.
Is that clear?
♪ ♪
Yes.
It's clear.
♪ ♪
This is a nice place
you got here.
When are they condemning it?
What are you
doing here, Harvey?
I need to talk to you.
Now's not a good time.
I gotta figure out how--
What if I told you
I have a way
to get you into the Bar?
What?
Someone came to us
trying to play games
with Rachel's Character
and Fitness interview and--
Wait, what--what the hell
are you talking about?
Relax, I handled it,
but now we have a chance
to get you in.
What's the catch?
Mike...
Harvey, there are
no free lunches.
What's the catch?
We need to come up
with a lawsuit against
Velocity Data Solutions
to drive their stock price down.
Are you kidding me?
No.
What do you mean no?
What--what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me is
I don't particularly feel like
going back to prison,
and the last time I checked,
fabricating a lawsuit to
manipulate a stock is illegal.
It's not illegal
if we find a legitimate suit.
[sighs]
That is such bullshit
that we'd just be
telling ourselves that,
just like we told
ourselves we weren't
colluding with Cahill.
And that got you
out of prison,
so let's finish the job,
and get you back to
being a lawyer.
Harvey, I'm more a lawyer now
than I ever was.
Oh, bullshit, you're
a babysitter and you know it.
Hey, I'm doing what I wanted,
and I'm helping people,
so if you wanna
call me a babysitter,
you go right ahead, but
right now the house is on fire,
the kids are in the bedroom,
and I'm about to
goddamn save them.
Mike, we have
an opportunity right now.
It's not gonna
present itself again.
I appreciate that, Harvey.
I do.
But I'm telling you,
my answer is no.
[dramatic music]
Hey, what's going on?
What's the emergency?
Where's Marissa?
Marissa's gone.
What do you mean gone?
I mean that you're
first chair tomorrow,
and we need to get you ready.
What?
- Oliver, it's not a big deal.
- Not a big deal?
We can't risk having me
mess up in court again.
This case is too important.
You know how I know that?
Because you told me.
I know what I said.
But we don't have time
to find anyone else.
The trial's tomorrow.
Now, are we gonna
do this thing or not?
It happened at
my first mock trial.
I was so prepared.
And then trial started,
and the other side
threw a wrinkle in.
And I thought I could
think on my feet,
but all of a sudden,
I felt everyone watching me,
and my mouth went dry,
and my mind went blank,
and I froze.
Oliver...
we can get through
this together.
Except now you told me
I can't handle it,
and that's gonna be
boring a hole in my brain,
making this thing
a thousand times harder.
Well, I can't
take back what I said,
but what I can do
is stay here all night
to make sure you prove me wrong.
[stirring music]
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
I want you to say it.
We're gonna win this.
We're going to win this.
Say it again.
One more time,
but this time mean it.
We are going to win this.
[chuckles]
Now, the first thing
they're gonna do
is file a motion to dismiss.
Actually, they already did.
♪ ♪
Good.
Let's work on that.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
I had to stop off
and get Joshua a present,
'cause I wanted to welcome him
into the family.
Louis, that is so sweet,
but it turns out
Joshua can't make it.
What do you mean
he can't make it?
He was gonna fly in,
but something came up with work,
so he canceled his flight.
What the hell
kind of father is that?
- Louis--
- This is bullshit.
It's his flesh and his blood,
and if he's gonna be father,
he needs to be a father.
What are you talking about?
You didn't even want him
to be here in the first place.
Well, I want him here now.
Louis, I thought you were
a more forgiving
person than this.
And I thought you wanted
our baby to have a relationship
with its biological father.
And he's going to.
But if you're gonna get
this worked up
about something like this,
it makes me think
I don't really know you.
Louis, can you honestly tell me
that you really know me?
Are we ready
to take a picture?
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
No, I don't.
And now I feel like
I'm ruining this, so...
if you don't want me
to come in with you, I won't.
Maybe it's best
if I just do this myself.
♪ ♪
Your Honor, this incident
occurred three nights ago,
yet the boy has
a history of asthma,
proving one has nothing
to do with the other.
These hospital records show
friable construction
material in his lungs.
How did it get there?
It could have gotten there
from a hundred different places.
This case is based
entirely on speculation,
and it should be dismissed.
This case is based on
the fact that your client
started construction
while tenants
were still in the building,
in violation of
the Real Estate Code.
And what if I told you
Ms. Price signed off this?
I'd say that's not possible,
because she didn't.
Well, you've got documents,
and I have one too.
This is a copy of
a certified letter
from my client
to the remaining tenants
three weeks ago,
stating that
construction will begin,
giving fair warning
to the occupants.
Your Honor, my client's
never seen that.
Well, she might not
have seen it,
but she got it.
It doesn't mean she opened it,
or--or even read it.
According to the city,
that doesn't matter.
Building Code 305-A:
"Tenants are required
to be notified
of all construction
by certified letter."
Is this a certified letter
or not?
[whispering] God damn it,
Oliver, say it's inadmissible.
Yes, it is, but--
So you admit that
she was notified,
and therefore my client should
be absolved of all liability.
I--I don't--I--
[tense pulsing music]
♪ ♪
Objection!
Your Honor, this is
the fraudulent attorney
I spoke with you about
before trial.
We ask that he either
refrain from speaking,
or be removed from the court
with an immediate ruling
for the defense.
Request granted.
Sir, open your mouth
in my courtroom again,
and you will be removed,
and this case will be dismissed.
Mr. Grady,
do you have an objection
to Ms. Johnson's
statement or not?
♪ ♪
I don't.
I'm sorry, I don't.
Then the court has no choice
but to dismiss this case
with prejudice.
♪ ♪
Benjamin, before you ask,
I already told you--
What if I could make it
more like you?
What do you mean?
You said what
makes you special
is your intuition, your empathy,
and your heart.
What if I could
make it have that?
How could you
possibly do that?
The same way
I gave it the ability
to learn from your quips,
I might be able to give it
the ability to learn
from your heart,
but it would require your help.
You really think
we could do that?
I don't know,
but I know we can try.
Well, then the first thing
that you need to learn
is never, ever, ever
sit in my chair.
Oh, I'm sorry, I--I was--
[chuckles] Relax, Benjamin,
I'm just messing with you.
- [nervous laughter] Oh.
- But get out of my chair.
Yeah.
[mellow guitar music]
♪ ♪
Louis, what--
what are you doing here?
I need to bring you
a few things.
What is all that?
High school yearbooks,
childhood photo albums,
and six out of seven
of the highlight reels
my mother shot of us growing up.
What happened to the seventh?
Oh...
summer of D&D.
And if it's all the same to you,
I would like to still
be able to have sex again.
[laughs]
Louis--
You were right.
We don't know everything
about each other,
but that just means we need to
get to know each other better,
and what better way
to get to know each other
then by preparing to bring
our child into the world?
Louis, if this is
your reaction
to what we went through today,
I feel like I know you
better already.
[gentle guitar music]
Speaking of what
we went through today,
how'd it go?
Why don't you take me home,
and I'll tell you all about it.
♪ ♪
Harvey, can I talk to you
for a second?
Sure, Rachel.
What's going on?
It's about my interview with
the Character
and Fitness committee.
- What about it?
- Louis tried to lie to me.
He said it was
some sort of mix-up,
but when I asked Donna about it,
she told me that
you were the one
who went to see that man for me,
not Louis.
Look, Harvey, it's okay,
you can tell me.
It was about Mike,
wasn't it?
No, it was about leverage.
What do you mean?
The guy holding up
your interview
was trying to get us
to do something,
because he thought he could.
Are you going to?
Yes.
He is.
Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
Yeah.
[percussive music intensifies]
I'm in.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man