I don't know anyone that has ever made
a long-distance
relationship work.
But I can't stand
that I put you in this position,
and the only way I can see out of this
is for you to go to Stanford.
Come after me, Tanner.
That's what you're here for.
You actually care about her.
You think he didn't say
some things in there
that got to me too?
Well, I'm not bringing them up,
because right now,
we need to stick together.
Sticking together means telling the truth.
I can't stand to see them come after you.
You think I can't take it!
Look, you're not listening to me, okay?
I can't take it!
If all you want to do is work with me,
I can find a job somewhere else.
Scottie, that's not all I want.
Then say it.
I want you in my life.
I don't want her to go,
and there's nothing I can do about it.
I finished my list.
And?
You're staying?
Just try and stop me.
This place has every
Harvard law student file ever.
Do not touch any of the files in here.
Mike Ross...
he's not here.
What are you thinking about?
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
What are you thinking?
That your furniture's really old.
I think the word you're
looking for is "antiquey."
That is not a word, and
this sofa is Ikea circa 1994.
Okay, I get it.
So you get up early just so you
can do a thorough critiquing
of my furniture?
Actually, I got up early,
so I could figure out
if there's anything around here
that I could stand living with.
Ah... I'm sorry... do you want
to move in together?
Yeah, I mean, if the offer still stands.
Are you kidding me?
[Laughs]
So is that a yes?
Oh, no, this is a yes.
[Upbeat rock music]
♪
I figured out what we can bring.
- What?
- You.
Panda, right here.
That's my favorite piece of art.
That is not art.
Grammy gave that to me.
Oh, I love it.
Panda can come.
And the chair.
Oh.
That was Grammy's favorite chair.
I don't... I don't...
No, no, no, no, no,
I'm telling you, Rachel,
she used to sit in that chair every Sunday
and drink her hot cup of Hershey's cocoa
and tell me all about growing up
on the mean streets of Philadelphia.
When you lie, try less details.
Got it.
♪
Looking for me?
No.
The woman I'm looking for
is a lot more in my bed.
What can I say?
My schedule stops for no man.
Yes, but we've got a little unfinished...
Business.
I wouldn't call last night
"unfinished."
And I wouldn't call it
"business."
I was talking about breakfast.
Harvey Specter makes breakfast?
You never heard of the Specter special?
I think I just had the Specter special.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
The Specter special is...
Let me guess.
It's two eggs, over easy,
with a side of "Scottie,
I want you in my life."
Bacon.
And now I'm reconsidering
the "in my life" thing.
Oh, no, I saw your face.
You had your serious face on.
"Scottie, I want you in my life.
Scottie...
I want you in my life."
You know what?
You don't deserve my bacon.
Oh, that's fine,
'cause I have to go anyway.
Where could you have to go?
You're unemployed.
Well, actually a top-tier
law firm offered me a job
last night, and I thought it might be best
if I negotiate the terms of my agreement
with the partner I'm not sleeping with.
There's a slight problem with that plan.
You offered her a job before talking to me?
I didn't offer her a job.
I asked her if she wanted one.
I didn't want to waste
your time, and for the record,
we'd be lucky to have her.
I know that.
But my question isn't
why I should want her here,
it's why you would want her here.
She's the best lawyer I know, after me.
And you.
Are you sleeping with her?
Excuse me?
You have history with this woman,
so I just want to know
are you doing this
because you feel sorry for her
or because you want to pay her back
or because you love her or what?
- It's none of your business.
- It is my business.
It is literally my business.
I want a relationship with her.
Well, I'm happy for you.
I hope you two make a run at it.
Thanks.
I'll pretend you meant that.
Your track record isn't great.
You've had three name partners
in two years.
Let's talk about your commitment issues.
I'm not asking you
to give my commitment issues
a corner office.
You don't need to give her a corner office.
Any regular office will do.
Harvey, I get it.
She's a catch, for you and for this firm.
But what happens when you two break up?
Who says we're gonna break up?
♪ See the money, wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive of your mind ♪
♪ me and missus
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x11 ♪ Buried Secrets
Original Air Date on March 6, 2014
♪ all that time imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Foreman versus Heart Med...
I want it.
"Good morning, Harvey.
What can I do for you today?"
I'm serious.
They're pushing for a settlement
because they know our client can afford it.
I know they are.
You haven't even looked at the file.
My name is on the door.
You think I don't know our cases?
So why are we settling?
Because regardless
of the merits of this case,
it's not worth our time.
Harvey, listen...
Heart Med's in-house lawyer
negotiated this
because the bad PR costs them
more than the settlement.
We'd have to get the thing
dismissed to make it worth it,
and that's not gonna happen.
The lawyer is Nick Rinaldi.
- Who the hell is Nick Rinaldi?
- You don't remember?
I was 11 years old,
a little boy, powerless.
I watched him boil my parents'
lives down to a few dollars.
Yes.
I'm not gonna let that piece
of shit get a penny from us.
I said yes.
Thanks, Harvey.
You want to thank me,
why don't you go beat
the shit out of this guy?
Monday, 2:20 p.m.
[Sighs]
This conundrum is burning a hole
in my brain.
Think.
Logically.
I mean, Sheila is professional
and meticulous
and wonderfully anal,
and if she says that nothing gets misplaced
in her inner sanctum, then I believe her,
which leaves the national security option.
Is Mike Ross CIA?
[Scoffs] Please.
There's a better chance
that Esther's in the KGB.
I mean, I can ask Sheila,
if I'm no longer fond
of my testicles, which...
wait a second,
missing testicles, missing file.
It can't be missing if it doesn't exist.
Holy shit.
What if Mike Ross never went
to Harvard at all?
What if he just went to some
crappy third-tier law school,
like Fordham or Arizona State?
"Yeah, hey, bro.
"Yeah, no, I'll see you at the party.
"I'm not going to study for the bar.
"Damn straight, that's right,
bros before hos.
Oh, yeah, you know..."
all right, that's enough.
He's been peeing directly into
our pristine pool of eliteness.
He's been... oh, shoot,
it's blinking out.
Norma, really quickly,
I need you to get a pack
of rechargeable AAA...
shit, it's out.
So I guess I'm just talking to myself.
Harvey convinced me, so let's get to it.
- I want a relocation fee.
- Done.
And a 10% increase on my signing bonus.
7%.
You gave Harvey 10%.
Do you think you're worth
as much as Harvey?
I'm less of a pain in the ass.
10% it is.
Now, no one ever opens with the big stuff,
so why don't you tell me
what you're really after?
You know what I'm after.
The name of the firm is Pearson Specter.
It's changed too many times, and
it's not going to change again.
Never?
I never say never.
- That's all I'm looking for.
- Of course.
After all, who knows where any
of us will be in a few years?
You, me, Harvey.
I think we just changed the subject.
We did.
Now it's time for me to tell you
what I'm really after.
You want to know how committed
I am to Harvey.
I want to know how committed you are to me.
- How serious are you?
- About what?
Me.
We had this conversation.
We had this conversation
before it was going to cost me $500,000.
Jessica's making you pay
the buy-in up front?
- Yep.
- Sh...
What did you say?
Well, I said I don't want to have to pay
a Harvey-Specter-girlfriend tax.
You're not exactly paying a tax.
You're just buying in early.
Harvey, there's a reason
that firms are designed to have
a six-month trial period.
Yeah, to see if it's going to work out.
- Exactly.
- Which you don't think it will.
I'm saying that I need to know
what "I want you in my life" really means.
You know what it means.
It means I want to have a relationship.
But it doesn't mean that
I'm ready to give you a ring.
You think I'm ready for a ring from you?
Then what are you ready for?
I'm ready for it not
to cost me a $1/2 million
if it doesn't work out.
So if it doesn't, are you
saying you're going to leave?
Would you want me to stay?
I don't even know what
you're gonna do to break us up.
Harvey, I'm not kidding.
I'm...
I'm scared.
You know, I just got an offer
from Latham & Watkins in Chicago,
and I don't want to take it, but...
I need to know that
you're serious about this.
Scottie, I am.
Yeah, but nobody's asking you
to put up $1/2 million.
Maybe we can make it
so nobody's asking you to do that either.
Rinaldi.
You remember me?
James and Nina Ross.
That's good.
Finally know my parents' names.
What you maybe don't know
is that I'm a lawyer,
I work for Pearson Specter,
and we're not going to be
settling this Foreman suit.
We had an agreement.
Yeah, maybe, but instead,
we're gonna be filing this.
There's no way you're getting
this case dismissed.
You know, I actually wanted
to believe that whole sob story
about being reformed, but...
My client is a widow, not a drunk driver.
Oh, so you don't actually
bully the little guy anymore,
you just try and capitalize on him.
Do you even know the details of this case,
or are you just coming after us
because I'm on the other side?
No, I'm coming after you
because you're
a worthless ambulance chaser,
and I'm not gonna let you take
my client's money.
This is the second time
you've come after me
from out of the blue.
I apologized to you once.
I will not apologize to you again.
You don't have to.
And we're not going to court,
because I'm gonna prove
you're full of shit.
You ready for the deposition?
Yeah, of course I'm ready.
- Your fly is unzipped.
- No, it's not.
[Chuckles] Didn't even flinch.
That means you're ready.
Then why are you still walking with me?
'Cause I'm coming to your deposition.
What?
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
You said that I could take this case.
You told me I could kick this guy's ass.
It's my deposition, not yours.
- I know.
- You know?
Why are you babysitting me?
I'm not babysitting you.
I want to watch you kill this guy.
That's why I brought snacks.
You can't bring peanuts into my deposition.
- Why?
- It's unprofessional.
So is that tie,
but I've made my peace with it.
Look, I don't give a shit
whether you made your peace with it or not.
You want in my room?
You're not bringing peanuts.
You really are ready.
Here.
What's this?
Harvey's interviews
the day Mike Ross was hired.
But Mike Ross isn't on it.
Where'd you get this?
Doesn't matter where I got it.
The fact is I did.
Are you asking me
why Mike Ross isn't on it?
Yeah, Donna, that's
precisely what I'm asking.
How exactly did Harvey find him?
We didn't find him, he found us.
What are you talking about?
[Sighs]
Mike hadn't signed up
for the interview on time,
so he pretended to be
one of the other associates on the list.
He talked his way past me
and impressed the shit out of Harvey,
whose main requirement was
somebody who had the balls
to do something like that
in the first place.
Okay.
What if he had the balls to do something
a lot bigger than that?
What are you talking about?
I think Mike Ross went
to a subpar law school
and has been lying about it the whole time.
Louis, listen to yourself.
You're talking about Mike.
You're insane.
I'm...
Okay, I was in the Harvard
file room with Sheila.
Don't ask details.
And I noticed Mike Ross' file
was not there.
You specifically looked for his file?
Yes, and I looked for Harvey's too,
and his was there.
And by the way,
he looked like a major douche.
So you looked at a grand total of two files
out of tens of thousands,
and this is the conclusion you jump to?
What is wrong with you?
You don't know Sheila.
She's like a surgeon,
and the files are her patients.
She doesn't make mistakes.
- You told her about this?
- Hell no.
She told me not to touch
any of those files,
and she'd kill me
if she found out that I did.
I just asked her about it generally.
Well, of course she's
gonna say she never loses one,
but I can tell you
from personal experience,
anything can happen to a file.
I don't know.
Well, I do. I know Mike,
and I know he's for real.
But if you still doubt it,
there's an easy answer.
Just call up Harvard and ask
for a copy of his transcript.
And what if it's not there?
Then I will apologize
for calling you insane
and personally help you escort
Mike Ross out of the building.
Good-bye.
In 2002, you were sued
for the malfunctioning
of an earlier model of the heart stent.
Is that correct?
Yes, and we admitted wrongdoing.
The stent that was installed
in your patient was a new model
developed through three years
of extensive trials.
Making it outside the scope,
and frankly, not a good argument
for establishing pattern.
They saw a problem, and they fixed it.
How horrible, we should sue them.
We're not in court.
Opening statements are made before a judge,
or have you never been in court before?
I just wanted to give you a taste,
seeing as we're never
actually gonna get there.
A dismissal is never gonna happen, son.
Sorry for your loss, son.
What?
I'm saying, don't hope for a dismissal.
Please direct your questions to our client.
That wasn't a question.
It was a comment.
Here's a question for you,
Mr. Dimond.
What is this really worth to you?
You may think you have a defense.
Your lawyer certainly thinks you do.
But I just want to be clear
about the facts.
What is this really worth to you?
There's no question,
this was a terrible accident.
But let's be clear about the facts.
His blood alcohol level is an issue here.
If you pursue this in court,
there's no guarantee
you'll receive anything.
Think about the boy.
Think about what he needs.
[Breathes tremblingly]
Something is better than nothing.
[Pen clicking]
Stop stalling, Mr. Ross.
- Um, I...
- He's not stalling.
And we're under no obligation
to disclose trials from an earlier model.
It's beyond the scope.
Our expert will place
that study within the scope.
Um, uh...
If there isn't a trial,
your expert won't have
any scope to place it in.
And since you insist on asking questions
we're under no obligation to answer,
this deposition is over.
What the hell happened in there?
You said you wanted to watch,
not hijack my case.
You said you were going to kick his ass,
not drift
into never-never land.
- I'm handling it.
- Handling it?
I could've eaten that whole bag of peanuts
in the pause you took
to answer that question.
You got thrown, and I bailed you out.
Harvey, this is my case.
This is not your case.
It's the client's case.
And after what happened in there,
they're in a worse position
than when we started.
Look, I know I got thrown,
but I can still recover.
Maybe, but they're gonna call
in a half an hour
wanting to take the deal,
and when they do,
I'm gonna buy you one day,
and then I'm pulling the plug.
Hey, do you have a minute?
- I'm a little busy right now.
- We have a problem.
Scottie's not going to be a problem.
I thought it through...
Louis might be onto Mike.
He found out that Mike doesn't have a file
in the Harvard file room
and that he wasn't
on your original interview list.
What did you tell him?
Well, I handled the list.
- What about the other?
- What could I tell him?
I mean, I told him if he was so curious,
he could order a copy of Mike's transcript.
Then we don't have a problem.
Well, don't you think maybe
we should do something else?
Anything else is just going
to make him more suspicious.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Okay.
Oh, wait a second.
Where did you say Louis was again?
Oh, he was in the Harvard file room.
How was he in the Harvard file room?
He has a relationship with Sheila Sazs.
What?
Yeah, never mind.
We're good.
Oh, thank you,
but I'm sorry, I don't have time.
It's food.
It's not going to stop you.
It's going to keep you going.
Yeah, I don't need food.
I need to find something I can take
to this dismissal hearing tomorrow.
Mike, it was a pretty decent settlement.
Would it really be so bad to just take it?
[Soft rock music]
My dad was one of those guys
who liked to celebrate everything...
the half birthdays or first time
I struck someone out at Little League.
And the last time I saw them,
they were celebrating
the anniversary of their first date.
They were so excited, all dressed up,
and I was annoyed,
because I didn't want to spend the night
at my grandmother's house.
So before they left,
my dad came upstairs
to say good-bye,
and I told him that celebrating
a first date was stupid.
[Chuckles sadly]
And he just looks at me like,
"Michael, you have no idea
how important
a first date can be."
Theirs must have been a great one.
[Laughing] No, no, no,
it was a total disaster.
He spilled wine all over her.
He forgot his wallet.
[Both laugh]
And then, for some reason,
this woman, you know...
this woman who he knew was just perfect...
agreed to a second date.
And a third.
[Sniffles]
And everything after that.
I wish I could have met them.
He tried
to hug me good-bye...
But I didn't hug him back.
♪
I didn't even go downstairs
to say good-bye to my mom.
♪
[Sniffles]
And then they were gone.
And then the next morning,
Rinaldi shows up at our house,
and he offers my grandmother
the equivalent of one year's rent.
Rinaldi didn't kill my parents,
but he did try to tell me
what their lives were worth.
And I'm sorry, but I know that
my mom and dad were worth...
A lot more than that.
Forget the food.
Give me half the files.
♪
What about a hedge fund guy?
It's big money.
Think bigger.
Obama.
I'm not going to land the president
as my first client.
Fine, if you don't think you can.
You're not going to manipulate
me into trying to land Obama.
Well, it better be somebody like that,
or Jessica won't give up
on her early buy-in bullshit.
What if I got myself a sports guy?
The very fact that you call it
"a sports guy" means it's a no.
Harvey, just because I don't know sports
doesn't mean I don't know you.
What are you talking about?
If I'm going to change Jessica's mind,
I can't just land someone,
I have to land someone you couldn't.
There's no one I couldn't land.
You think I don't know about Beijing?
That's his word against mine.
Oh, well, um, I guess
we can clear that up right now,
because look who just walked in.
You knew he was coming here tonight?
You think I like Argentinean food?
I just need you to stop him for a second.
I get it.
You got the idea from Working Girl,
when they crash the wedding
to get to Trask radio.
Harvey, I'm not
a 14-year-old girl.
I don't get my ideas from movies.
Michael.
Harvey.
I have no interest in talking to you.
Hi. Dana Scott.
I work with Harvey, and I don't blame you.
I wouldn't want him to represent me either.
But he's not the only lawyer there.
Let me guess.
You've done your research on my record,
and you're here to impress me.
That's what every other lawyer would do.
- I didn't do that.
- Harvey, shut up.
I don't give a shit
about how fast you used to swim.
I only care about how fast
I can make you money.
How fast is that?
Why don't you sit down, and I'll tell you?
- All right.
- Okay.
Harvey, you mind?
- Actually, I...
- Great.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good to see you, buddy.
So what really happened in Beijing?
- Let's get a drink first.
- [Laughs]
Sounds good.
Doctor, how routine is this procedure?
Sid Foreman should have been dancing
at his daughter's wedding a week later.
Instead, he went into heart failure.
Dr. Lombard,
on December 7, 2006,
did a patient die on your table
during a routine angioplasty?
Objection, Your Honor.
Relevance?
It speaks to his qualifications
as an expert witness, Your Honor.
I'll allow.
Yes, a patient died.
And was a malpractice suit
filed against you for physician error?
That case was sealed.
I didn't ask you if it was sealed.
I asked if it was filed.
It was.
- And settled?
- For almost nothing...
Objection, Your Honor.
Move to strike.
The case is sealed.
The witness isn't allowed to testify
to the details of that settlement.
Sustained.
Have you practiced medicine since?
Yes, I've been practicing.
I'm sorry, what I meant to say
is have you performed surgery,
the job you spent seven years
training to do?
No.
What, loss of confidence?
They wouldn't let you?
Objection.
Speculation.
I want an answer to my question.
I chose to do other things.
Other things that don't involve the chance
of you killing people?
- Objection!
- Withdrawn.
What's your primary source of income?
I work as an expert witness.
So you testify now to make a living,
because you don't trust yourself
to do the job
that you were trained to do?
I can speak to the facts of this case...
Yes, you can speak to them,
but how are we supposed to trust
your opinion about them
when you clearly don't trust yourself?
You raised some doubts about my expert.
That isn't gonna get this case dismissed.
Maybe not, but if that's the best expert
you can come up with, then your client
just got a taste
of how this trial is gonna go.
My client is not gonna drop this case,
and neither am I.
Well, then you are forcing me to use this.
It's a picture of Mr. Foreman
at his daughter's wedding.
drinking alcohol
It's a toast.
It was one sip.
One sip two hours before his
stent supposedly malfunctioned.
Alcohol was strictly forbidden
following his surgery,
which makes him liable for his own death.
This is a total twisting of the facts.
You can't prove this caused anything.
You can't prove it was only one sip,
and it doesn't matter,
because I submit this,
it's contributory negligence,
and your case is gone.
And you say I'm a monster.
Being a monster would be
putting your client
on the stand and making her testify
that her husband's death
was his own damn fault.
Hi, Donna.
Hi, Louis.
I'm nothing if not a big man,
and I am not ashamed
to admit when I am wrong.
You got Mike's transcript.
Arrived this morning.
Imagine that, Mike Ross went to Harvard.
What a shocker.
You were right.
Never should have doubted it.
You know, it's just hard to imagine a world
in which Sheila made a mistake, though.
Well, it's just good
you can put this to bed
once and for all.
Yeah, see, that's the thing.
If Sheila's competence
is that important to her,
I need to tell her about this,
so she can fix it.
You know what, Louis?
It occurred to me after we talked
that I'm the only one who has
the list of associates
that interviewed with Harvey that day.
That can't be right,
'cause I got a copy off the general server.
You got a copy by bullying Benjamin
into accessing my private files
off my hard drive.
- That doesn't sound like me.
- Louis...
Okay, I did it, but that was
only 'cause I was concerned.
So your concern gives you
the right to invade my privacy?
I... what?
No, it was just a file.
How dare you?
You pretend to be this gallant man.
You make a big show of how you
would never cross into my area
without my permission.
I am gallant, and I would never dare.
You wouldn't dare, because
you'd have to do it to my face.
But you have no problem breaking
my trust behind my back,
and that not only pisses me off,
but it makes me question...
Whether I want to have
a relationship with you at all.
I'm so sorry, Donna.
No, Louis, you know what...
- No, no, no, Donna, I'm sorry.
- No, I can't.
- No, no, no, no.
- I can't... I can't even...
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- No, shh! Don't speak.
I cannot even look at you right now.
And I don't even know
why I'm gonna tell you this,
but if you pissed me off that much,
what do you think Sheila's gonna do
when you tell her you violated her trust?
Huh?
You're right.
Thank you, Donna,
for putting your anger on hold
long enough to help me salvage
the single most important
non-feline relationship
of my life.
- Someone's been a bad boy.
- Sheila.
You thought I wouldn't find out?
I hoped you wouldn't.
If you wanted a pair of my underwear,
you should have just asked.
Oh, that, Sheila.
God, what are you doing here?
Aren't you happy I'm here?
[Laughing nervously] Of course, absolutely.
- You don't seem happy.
- I'm overjoyed.
I'm just, you know...
I'm just surprised.
But you're all nervous and sweaty.
Come on, you know
my sweat ducts get excited
when they see you.
Good.
Because your sweat ducts are
going to be working overtime.
What?
The Chilton, room 305, tonight.
[Both chuckle] [Kisses]
[Sighs]
You didn't have to come
all the way over here
just to drop the case.
I came here to tell you
you're doing the wrong thing.
I don't need a lecture
from you on right and wrong.
You once asked me how I live with myself.
Well, somewhere along the way,
I realized I had a choice
not to be on the side
that made me feel like shit.
You're on that side now.
Yeah, I don't feel like shit.
That's because you're telling
yourself you're doing your job.
And I'm telling you
that you're bullying someone
who deserves your sympathy.
You really want to play the bullying card?
My grandmother lost her only son.
You used her grief against her.
This has nothing to do with that.
Look, I know, you need me
to be the villain...
No, no, no, no, no.
You are the villain.
Well, then congratulations,
because you just became me.
What are you talking about?
Your father had two drinks
on the night he was killed.
That was the reason I was able
to get your grandmother
to settle.
It's not every day I get off the elevator
and find someone in my firm
that makes me look short.
So you've seen our newest client?
You mean Scottie's newest client.
Michael Phelps may be her client,
but we're gonna get Speedo.
And why should that make me change my mind?
Because their fee
is worth more than her buy-in.
You still think this is about money.
I told this to Scottie, and now
I'm going to tell it to you.
We've had too much turnover.
We can't have any more.
Jessica, I'm telling you she's in.
Then she shouldn't have
any problem putting her money
where her mouth is.
It's not right.
Harvey, it's time you and I had the talk.
I know where babies come from.
But do you know how couples stay together?
What are you getting at?
When Daniel and I took over the firm,
we had a heart-to-heart.
He had a philosophy
that I agreed to live by.
Daniel was a piece of shit.
Doesn't mean his philosophy was.
I'm listening.
He told me, for a partnership to work,
there has to be trust between
number one and number two.
You don't have to agree with me,
but you have to trust that I listen to you,
that my decisions are reasoned,
and that I am doing what I think is right.
Jessica...
You can't have two presidents, Harvey.
Now I chose to trust you when you said
you didn't want to be managing partner.
Was that true or not?
It was.
Then I need you to accept this.
What if I had an idea
where maybe we can both get what we want?
I'm listening.
That's never happened to me before.
- It's okay.
- No, it isn't.
Black Hawk Down.
First of all,
that's an amazing movie,
and you should be proud
that you are associated with it.
And second of all, I think
I know what the problem is.
You do?
It's about what happened in the file room.
Listen, Sheila, I can't tell you
how that's been weighing on my mind.
No, I get it.
Now that we've declared our love,
you think of me as a good girl.
And you need me to be bad.
- What?
- It happens all the time.
We're in a relationship now,
and you think that changes
the nature of our sexual relationship.
But I am here to assure you...
I can be bad.
Okay, that's not actually what...
Liar.
Whoa.
Take it easy.
I am being serious right now.
You think I'm not being serious?
I'm deadly serious.
Ow.
- Say it again.
- Ow.
Ooh.
[Gasps]
Well, what do you know?
The Dark Knight Rises.
[Soul music]
♪
- She went for it.
- She did?
One catch.
What?
You have to sign an ironclad noncompete.
You can't represent
any Pearson Specter clients if you leave.
- Including Phelps?
- Including Phelps.
How is that any different
than paying in early?
It's $1/2 million different.
Harvey.
Scottie, this is the best we're gonna do.
Phelps brings in the money.
But if you leave and take him away,
what good does that do Jessica?
Jessica or you?
Are you kidding?
Are you questioning me?
You've been known
to manipulate situations before.
If it were up to me,
I'd waive your whole buy-in.
[Laughs] Now I know you're full of shit.
You're right, I am.
So get your check ready, 'cause
in six months, you're paying it.
[Sighs] Are we really doing this?
Sign it.
Give it to Jessica.
Tomorrow we'll celebrate
with dinner at my place.
Where did you get this?
Rinaldi.
Mike, I know what you're thinking,
but your father wasn't legally drunk.
Yeah, but he wasn't sober either.
And how do I know those two drinks aren't
the split second that he needed not to...
You don't know that this had
anything to do with the accident.
Rachel, do you have any idea
how many times I have wished
that they hadn't gone out that night
or that they had taken
a different route home
or any one of a thousand other things,
but the one thing... the
one thing that I never wished
is that my father hadn't been drinking
the night that he got killed by a drunk...
[sighs]
I know he wasn't perfect.
But he was.
He was perfect to me, and...
I don't want to have to wonder
if this is all his fault.
Mike.
[Soft rock music]
He is just trying to get to you.
Well, he's got to me.
I mean, how am I any different
than him, Rachel?
Because it's a bullshit claim.
I don't know.
I know I'm gonna win.
But I don't know.
Ah, there you are.
Been looking all over for you.
Why?
I just wanted to apologize once again
for crossing the threshold
of your electronic area.
It's okay, Louis.
No, no, I breached your mainframe.
No excuse.
Why is your face so red?
It's because you gave me the
greatest advice in the world.
What are you talking about?
Let's just say that I'm never
gonna tell Sheila what I did
in that file room that night, ever.
[Chuckles]
Apology accepted.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I need to put some peas on my face.
Your move didn't work.
I didn't go into a tailspin.
I wasn't trying to send you
into a tailspin.
I was just trying to get you to understand.
Well, I do understand.
That doesn't mean
I'm gonna sell my client out.
Then why are we here?
You want to sue someone,
you should sue these people.
They're the ones that make the medicine
that stent was coated with.
And you know that medicine has
something to do with this case?
I know there's
as much evidence against them
as there is against my client.
That's why you're pointing me there,
because they're not your client.
You know, nothing's gonna
bring Mr. Foreman back.
Just like there's nothing
that's gonna bring my parents back.
This is the best way I can see
to get your client compensation.
If you think you're doing
the right thing, you're wrong.
I'm trying to help,
but I'm not gonna sell my client out.
It's a half measure.
All right, then here's the other half.
I pointed out your achilles' heel
when I found that photo,
and I found it on Facebook.
Do your client a favor,
and have them take it down
before you file that suit.
So you're gonna fly back to
London, get your life in order,
and move back in two weeks.
Tickets are booked.
Here's to your new partnership.
I just have one question.
Why did Jessica specifically
make me agree to something
that's a standard part of your contracts?
You checked up on me.
I didn't check up on you.
I'm thorough.
What's the difference?
God damn it, Harvey,
don't change the subject.
What did you do?
I fronted your buy-in.
I knew it.
You bought me.
I didn't buy you, I bought us time.
That is a lawyer's response,
and it's bullshit.
How could you do that?
Scottie, you're acting
like I killed someone.
I didn't.
You paid so that I could sleep with you
and be here at the same time!
Do you know what that makes me?
Lucky?
- That's not funny.
- I didn't mean it to be.
I paid because I want you to stay.
I did it as a romantic gesture.
Yeah, well,Pretty Woman
may have been a romantic movie,
but Julia Roberts was still a hooker.
Now you come up with a movie reference?
Harvey, can you imagine
how that makes me feel
to find that out?
Well, what do you want me to say, huh?
I'm not perfect at this,
and you don't have to believe
that was romantic,
but it would be nice if you
believed that I thought it was.
Harvey, it would have been romantic
if you had begged me to stay
when Jessica wouldn't budge,
but this, this is not romantic.
This is manipulative.
You were about to take
a job somewhere else.
That's what makes it manipulative!
Are you telling me you've
never been manipulative with me?
Not since I've been back.
I had to learn the hard way,
and I'm afraid that
you haven't learned that at all.
So you're saying I'm an asshole?
Yes, that is what I'm saying,
that you are an asshole,
but what I'm really saying
is that we need to start
being honest with each other.
- About everything?
- Everything.
You know that paper you had to redo,
because Professor Gunn
said he never got it?
Mmhmm.
He never got it.
Son of a bitch.
How was I supposed to know
you didn't save it to your hard drive?
Because I told you that.
You know I don't listen
when you say things.
You are an asshole.
This is good.
Honesty is good.
I told Rebecca Carlin you were gay.
She slept with me anyway.
Once.
Yeah.
Why did she only sleep with me once?
Because I also told her that you had crabs.
- That's not cool.
- [Laughs]
This is good.
It is.
I am in this, Scottie.
Okay.
So am I.
Well, let's see what you got,
Michael James Ross.
Magna cum laude.
[Chuckles]
So Mr. Smarty Pants couldn't
even manage summa cum laude?
Yeah, well, so what if I couldn't either?
What? No Law Review?
Well, either you weren't asked,
or you didn't serve.
Either way, I win.
"A."
B-plus in International Law?
Oh, come on, I aced that class
with my eyes closed.
"A" in contracts.
That's legit.
A-minus in Estate Planning?
Remind me to not die intestate
with Mike Ross around.
[Knock on door]
Tape measure, as requested.
You look really excited.
- Long day.
- I know.
Is there any chance we can punt this,
maybe go grab some dinner?
We could, or we could accept
that moving in together
sometimes means we have to
just shake off our crappy days
and deal with things
like furniture negotiations.
Yeah, that doesn't sound
like anything I want to accept at all.
Too bad.
This is your life now.
Rachel, look, I'm trying...
You said that your dad liked
to celebrate the little things,
and I thought maybe we
should start doing that too.
You mean like furniture negotiations?
Mmm, I mean our first date.
So does that mean I'm not
gonna be able to eat anything?
'Cause I didn't like anything
on the menu that night.
That wasn't our first date.
Our first date was in the law library.
- Sushi.
That was my first case.
[Laughing] I know.
Oh, you were so green.
[Chuckles]
Harvey came in and told us
to stop playing footsie.
Oh, I remember that.
I wanted to do a lot more
than play footsie with you.
I know.
I caught you staring at me five times.
Oh, so I guess you didn't
catch all the other times then.
No I did, just trying to let you
off the hook.
Rachel...
This is perfect.
Not yet.
[Laughs]
Now it is.
So where's the chair?
No.
[Both laugh]
You wanted to see me?
Professor Gerard's
legal ethics class... you take it?
Of course, everyone had to take it.
What'd you get?
Killed it.
I got an A-minus.
Out of curiosity,
did you ever hear of anybody
ever getting an A-plus?
What? No.
He's famous for never
giving higher than an "A."
He doesn't believe in it.
Thank you, Simon.
That'll be all.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man