Previously on "Suits"...
This isn't "Westworld."
I can't make her human.
I'm just asking you
to give her a little compassion.
Well, I don't know
how to do that.
Just got off the phone
with Carly Donahue.
She fired us, Donna.
This isn't your fault.
You couldn't have known.
It's okay, I just need to go.
You filed a complaint
alleging life-threatening
health problems,
and I wanna help you
get the compensation
that you deserve.
Even if I wanted
to sue those bastards, I can't.
- We can shatter those NDAs.
- What do I have to do?
I wanna know if
you're using this case
to get back to Pearson Specter.
You said Pearson Specter
would never take on
a case like this when
you were there before.
We brought the suit so that
I could get into the Bar.
- 100 million.
- With an admission of guilt.
Sure, where do I sign?
I'm willing to cut
your clients a check
that'll change their lives
and you're too stupid to see it.
Are you ready
to take responsibility or not?
You think I won't
go after you
for stealing from
Seidel's company?
I don't give a shit
about his marriage.
The reason he hasn't come
forward has nothing to do
with his marriage.
You didn't have to
keep this quiet
because you're married.
You kept it quiet because
you're in on it.
My employees are gonna lose
their jobs because of me.
We need to keep this suit going.
You're not just
getting Mike an interview,
you're gonna block anyone
who tries to vote no.
See you at the Bar.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Mr. Stamos.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to get you
the authorization
to our medical records.
Thanks.
But, uh, you didn't
come all the way down here
just to hand me
some paperwork.
You're right.
I came to find out
what's going on with our case.
We should hear something soon.
- How can you know that?
- 'Cause Harvey is negotiating
with James Palmer as we speak.
What do you mean?
Why is Harvey Specter
negotiating this?
I told you
when we took him on,
he's the best negotiator
in the city.
I don't care who he is.
You're the one that came to me.
You're the one I trusted.
I know that, but we've got
a good cop/bad cop strategy
to get the offer up.
An offer?
You didn't tell me
there's an offer.
- That's because things are--
- How much?
The number on the table
is a hundred.
But we're hoping to get
a lot more.
Jesus Christ, 100 million?
Take it.
I know it seems like
a lot of money--
- It is a lot of money.
- Not when you have to
split it between 150 men
who have cancer.
Do all the math you want,
Mr. Ross,
but 100 million is a hell of lot
better than zero,
which is what we've been
walking around with.
Mr. Stamos,
you have to trust me.
We know what we're doing
and I am not gonna let you down.
Fine.
You do your
good cop/bad cop thing.
But if that number doesn't go up
in the next two days,
I'm telling my guys to take
the offer that's on the table.
♪ ♪
Benjamin, the Donna is ready.
- What do you mean she's ready?
- I mean, five minutes ago
she expressed empathy to me.
But it wasn't working before.
I was convinced it never would.
I don't know what you did,
but you said it could
learn from itself, and
that's exactly what happened.
Oh, my God.
Maybe I really am a genius.
Yeah, maybe you are.
Well, then it's a good thing
I didn't throw this away.
- What's this?
- I've compiled a list
of everybody who's invested
in products like this
in the last five years.
That's great,
but we're not gonna need this.
Why not?
Because the thing that
makes the Donna special is me.
Which means we need to look
into investors who know me.
Yes, correct, and nobody
knows you better than Harvey.
Do you think he'll
make calls on our behalf?
He would, but I'm not gonna
ask him to do that
because I want his clients
to see this
as coming from me and not him.
Then what's the next step?
The next step for you is
get ready to present that thing,
because I'm going to get us
some meetings.
Boom shakalaka.
♪ ♪
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
I do, but it couldn't wait.
Where's Rachel?
She's at her parents' house.
Why?
Because I have some news
and she's gonna wanna hear it.
What is it?
We got it.
You're in.
You're going to be a lawyer.
What? How?
Seidel was in on it.
He got paid.
And I got proof.
Which means we don't have to
worry about tanking
Velocity's stock anymore.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe it.
Oh.
I'm going to be a lawyer.
I know.
There's just one thing.
Palmer figured out that
we're doing this with Seidel.
And unless we drop the lawsuit,
he's gonna come after us
for collusion.
Wait, what?
No, this is bullshit.
I'm not giving up
on those miners.
- You have to.
- No, I don't.
- Mike.
- Look, the only thing
we did wrong was make a deal
to get me into the Bar.
If I pull out of that hearing,
Palmer can't touch us.
Are you--think about
what you're saying.
I don't need
to think about it.
I'm not going to throw
those guys under the bus.
- Mike, we've come too far--
- I don't care.
Tell Seidel the deal's off.
♪ ♪
What if there was another way?
Harvey, if you're talking
about somebody else
handling this case--
No, I'm not.
Listen to me, there's no way
Seidel came up with the idea
to sell that shit
to Velocity himself.
The woman he had an affair with
has to work for them,
which means we can leverage her
to sink Palmer.
- Are you kidding me?
- No, I'm--
Harvey, listen to yourself.
You're talking about out and out
extortion and blackmail.
I'm not going to do
any of that shit
just to get into
the God damn Bar.
You were the one that told me
that after
watching that kid lose,
you never wanted it
to happen again.
And now that same kid
is telling us that
what we're doing is wrong.
And he's right.
Mike.
No, Harvey, it's enough.
You promised Rachel
that you'd pull the plug
if things got too risky.
Well...
it just got too God damn risky.
♪ ♪
♪ Suits 6x15 ♪
Quid Pro Quo
Original Air Date on February 22, 2017
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Mm. Hey.
What's going on?
You got out of bed
before it was light out.
- Mm.
- And you never came back.
I want to talk to you
for a minute.
About what?
I know you went to Harvey
and you made him promise
to pull the plug on
my getting into the Bar
if things got too risky.
He wasn't supposed to
tell you that.
Did you really think
he wouldn't?
Mike, I only made him promise
because I care about you.
It's okay.
I know why you did it.
And I understand it.
And last night, I ended up
pulling the plug myself.
- So it's over?
- It's over.
Not gonna be a lawyer.
[tense music]
- Mike.
- [chuckles]
The thing is, I was fine with it
until Harvey started
dangling it in front of my face.
♪ ♪
I think the problem was,
I actually started
believing it could happen.
Do you want me to
stay with you today?
No.
♪ ♪
I'll be okay.
Besides, you've got
a lot of work to do
and I've got a big case to win.
♪ ♪
Harvey, there you are.
Louis needs to see you
right away.
Donna, whatever it is,
I don't have time right now.
Well, you need to make time.
Because he came looking for you
last night and he's upset.
Well, I'm sorry, Donna.
But I'm too busy to hear about
another crisis with
his girlfriend or drama
in his canasta club or how
his mouth guard doesn't fit.
Couture Apparel fired us.
- What?
- Carly got upset that
Louis brought Rachel and Katrina
to the meeting instead of you.
And when he stood up to her
about it, she fired him.
Shit.
[phone clatters on desk]
Harvey, he feels terrible
about it.
He thinks he let you down.
Well, he didn't.
I let him down.
And it turns out
it was all for nothing.
What do you mean, nothing?
What happened?
Palmer figured out
what's going on with Seidel
and Mike would rather pull
his deal than drop the case.
But then he'll never
get into the Bar.
Why do you think I said
I don't have time
for anything else right now?
So you're telling me
that asshole's
holding all the cards, and
Mike's never gonna be a lawyer?
No, no one's ever
holding all the cards.
And I don't give a shit
what Mike said,
I'm not going folding
when I know we can win.
♪ ♪
Louis, before you
say anything,
Donna told me what happened.
- Harvey, I am so sorry--
- I know you are.
But I didn't
come here to scold you.
I came here because
I need your help
or Mike's deal
is gonna fall apart.
- What? How's that possible?
- Let's just say
someone's got leverage on us and
I need to get leverage on them.
- What kind of leverage?
- There's a woman
who works at Velocity.
She had an affair with Seidel.
I need to know who she is.
Thousands of people
work at Velocity.
Yeah, I know that.
But to do what she did,
she'd have to be
a top corporate officer.
Well, that narrows it down.
But it's still gonna require
huge amounts of research
and hundreds of phone calls.
No, Louis, it'll only require
one phone call.
Because what I need
is access to their database.
No, Harvey, there's got to be
someone else.
Vanessa doesn't do this kind
of thing and you know it.
I swore that I would
never do business
with that son of a bitch again.
I know that, Louis.
But if we don't do this...
All right, get out.
Close the door behind you.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oliver.
- What's up?
What's up is
we got work to do.
Mike, I don't mean to be
an asshole,
but I'm not doing anything
until you tell Nathan
exactly what's going on.
There's nothing to tell.
Are you kidding me?
You said you were
doing this case as a way
to get into the Bar.
And I just withdrew
my application.
There's no deal anymore.
So whatever it was I was
gonna tell Nathan, I don't have
to tell him anymore.
Just like that.
You're giving up your chance?
Look, I heard what
you said to me last night
about setting an example.
So instead of telling Nathan
that I was up to
something shady,
I'm telling you that I'm not.
What do you need me to do?
I need you to get down to PSL
and grab half a dozen
of those associates
and bring them back here.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna do whatever I can
to make sure
this thing isn't over yet.
Yeah, screw those assholes,
they're nothing but
a bunch of dickless losers.
Yeah, I'll break them into
little pieces for you,
you have my word on it.
All right, I got to go.
I love you too, Mommy.
- Stu.
- Donna.
Gotta say,
I didn't figure you for a guy
who called his mother "Mommy."
What can I say,
if a man doesn't
have the confidence to do that,
then he's not really a man.
But I'm guessing you didn't come
all the way down here
just to evaluate
my relationship
with the greatest woman
on Earth.
No, I didn't.
I came here to show you this.
- What's that?
- It's a game-changer.
And I'm letting you in
on the ground floor.
That's a bold statement.
Turn it on.
Keep it for as long as you want.
And then when you're blown away,
come back to me with an offer.
Because my partner and I,
we're gonna go wide with this
and we're going to need
an investor.
Why are you coming to me
with this?
Because I wanted to give
someone the chance
to take it off the market.
And it needed to be someone
with the confidence
to call his mother "Mommy."
♪ ♪
It's typical you would
have us meet you here.
Gambling's for suckers,
you know?
It's only gambling
when the results are unknown.
There's nothing wrong with
tilting the game in your favor.
[chuckles]
I like this guy, Louis.
Why haven't I met him before?
You know why.
So why don't we just get to it?
We need you to hack
into Velocity Data's
personnel records.
Now, can you do it or not?
You want to say that
a little bit louder
so the Fed over there
can hear it?
Relax, Jerry.
What Louis is trying to say
is there's a woman who
works there who has information
we need to make a deal.
Make a deal?
Ah, I don't know.
That's starting to sound
like blackmail, which is
a little bit out of my league.
Bullshit.
It's in your league.
And it's starting to sound
like you're renegotiating,
like you always do.
You know what, Louis?
I just about had enough of
your bullshit over the years.
I renegotiate 'cause
you low-ball me.
- No, I told--
- Jerry, you're not dealing
with Louis on this one,
you're dealing with me.
So why don't you tell me
what you need
and let's get this thing done?
If I'm gonna access anything,
I need to know more than
you just told me.
'Cause I don't get
what you want,
there's no going
back a second time.
All right, there's a woman
who works at Velocity
who slept with
the in-house counsel
at my client's company
and convinced him to sell
confidential information.
Let me guess,
she promised him the Moon,
then hung him out to dry.
Yeah, why?
You don't need to
access Velocity's records.
She doesn't work there.
How do you know?
Because I know who she is.
And the price just tripled.
Tripled?
You hypocritical piece of shit.
You don't even have
to access anything.
Well, you know what they say.
You don't pay the plumber
for banging on the pipes.
You pay him for knowing
where to bang.
Yahtzee.
And I'm telling you,
where I'm banging,
a whole lot of shit's
gonna fall out.
So you're either gonna pay up
or you're not.
Am I interrupting?
To tell you the truth,
I've just been
staring at this screen
for the past 15 minutes.
That's what I do all day.
I call it working.
But I'm going to guess
that's not why you're staring.
I was thinking about Mike.
He told you
he gave up the deal?
He did, and, um...
he said that he's okay
not being a lawyer.
But the look on his face
didn't say that at all.
Then you might be interested
in what I have to say.
Because it involves getting Mike
into the Bar after all.
Harvey, why are you telling me
this instead of Mike?
Because you asked me to
pull the plug
on this whole thing
if it got too risky,
and what I'm talking about
is gonna make it
a hell of a lot riskier.
And what did Mike say?
- He doesn't want to do it.
- Why not?
You know why not.
It's not 100% legal.
And you can say no
if you want to.
But that look you saw
on his face,
that's not going away
any time soon.
Okay.
I'm in.
But this time,
if something goes wrong,
you take the fall.
Okay, I will.
Now, you gonna go back
to staring at that thing
or you want to help me
get Mike into the Bar
and have some fun
at the same time?
What do you need me to do?
I need you to go home,
put on something
a hell of a lot nicer,
and meet me at this address
in an hour.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Hi.
- Hey, sweetie.
I'll be done in a few minutes.
- How's your day?
- Fine.
Louis, we talked about this.
You can share your day with me.
I'm here to cheer you up.
It's not that.
It's just that sometimes,
I have to do
some less than great things
with less than great people
and I'd rather wash
the memories from my brain.
What do you mean,
less than great things?
Nothing, it's not
that big a deal.
Are you talking about
hurting an innocent person?
No, of course not.
Then how bad can it be?
Well, it's not that bad
at all, Tara.
As a matter of fact,
I'm doing it all
to help someone
I care deeply about.
And sometimes to do good,
you gotta get a little dirty.
Well, then maybe
you can take me home
and get a little dirty with me.
Oh, sweetie, I want to
but I'm just not in the mood.
Are you sure
this isn't something
you wanna share with me?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- Okay.
But I want you to know,
you can tell me anything.
Tara, I'm sorry, but I'm gonna
have to meet you at home.
Oh, what is it?
Nothing, I just have to
go see Harvey, okay?
Okay.
♪ ♪
Louis, I've got about
two minutes.
I'm gonna meet Rachel.
Well, take two minutes
to look at this.
What is it?
It's a letter
from Allen Fields.
Shit.
He's putting us in review based
on our recent affiliations.
- You know what that means.
- Yeah, I sure as hell do.
Well, then you should know
that I just got ten more
from ten other clients
and they all say the same thing.
That son of a bitch.
Louis, I'm not gonna be bullied.
No, I don't care
what you're gonna be.
Now, we lost Couture Apparel
because you were
too busy with Mike.
This is the same exact thing
in different clothes.
- Louis--
- Harvey, I just had to lie
to the woman I love
because I didn't want to admit
the whole truth about Mike.
Now, I'm willing to go with
the Hail Mary of using Jerry.
But what I am not willing to do
is risk our survival.
- Louis--
- Harvey, that is enough.
You know what
needs to be done.
Do it, or I will.
♪ ♪
Mr. Palmer.
I take it you didn't
get the memo.
This case is over.
Well, that's because it's not.
What the hell is this?
That's a copy of my letter
to the New York Bar,
removing myself
from consideration.
No interview,
no application,
no quid pro quo,
which means this case
is far from over.
You have got to be
kidding me.
You're gonna give up your chance
to be a lawyer
for some miners you didn't even
know existed before last week?
Well, I know they exist now.
And I know they're dying
because of you.
So, we're gonna settle
this thing
and we're going to settle
it right now.
Well, I'll tell you
what I'll do.
I'll write you a check
for ten million right here.
Ten million?
[laughs]
The hell are you talking about?
Oh, you told them you'd
get them a hundred, didn't you?
Yeah, you did.
I can see it in your face.
Well, I suggest you tell them
you accidentally added a zero.
Because you're not getting
a nickel more.
Let me remind you, Mr. Palmer.
We filed 150 suits against you.
And we are gonna fight them all.
And that shook me before.
But who's gonna supply
the manpower
to fight those suits now?
You know who.
Oh.
[laughs]
I guess you really didn't
get the memo, did you?
Because Pearson Specter Litt
just withdrew from this case.
♪ ♪
I'll find someone else.
I highly doubt it.
Hey, listen to me.
Your company hurt these people.
You were willing to settle for
a hundred million before.
This is your chance
to do the right thing
and clear your conscience
at the same time.
Sounds to me like a chance
to clear yours.
This is a take-it-or-leave-it
offer, Mr. Ross.
And whether you take it or not,
I don't ever expect
to see you here again.
♪ ♪
- Ms. Cromwell?
- Yes?
My name's Michelle Ross
and I was hoping to employ
your services.
- My services?
- Yes, I'm a junior partner
at Rand Kaldor, and I'm looking
to make a change.
I'm sorry, I don't really do
much work with the legal sector.
Actually, I was hoping
to use my experience
and parlay it into
the business world.
Well, I can take your résumé,
but to be honest,
I don't have a client
who's looking for a candidate
like you at the moment.
I know you don't.
In fact,
since we're being honest,
I know exactly what kind of
candidate you're looking for.
What kind is that?
One that can be manipulated
into selling
their employer's products.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who I am.
What matters is
I know what you do.
You don't know anything
about me.
I know that you're officially
a headhunter,
but unofficially, you meet
your exclusively male clients
at places like this.
I also know that at the end of
each of those meetings,
you say to them,
"I never do this,
but would you like
to have dinner?"
And then dinner leads
to dessert,
dessert leads to sex,
and sex leads to them
falling for you,
and that leads to--
All right, I've heard enough.
And you don't have proof
of anything.
Actually, I do.
But you know what?
I don't need it.
Because one of two things is
going to happen.
Either I'm going to hire someone
to tell every one
of your male clients
when they meet them
that you're going to rob them,
and then your cushy job making
a million dollars per sucker
is going away--
Or?
Or you're gonna tell me
about every time
you've done this
for James Palmer,
and you're never gonna hear
from either one of us again.
I can't do that.
My job requires
a reputation for discretion.
You're gonna do what we want,
or you're gonna find out
how much
your reputation
protects you in prison.
Oh, I get it.
You're not worried
about Palmer knowing.
You're worried about
word spreading.
Trust me,
he'll never tell a soul
and your business
will stay intact.
How can you be sure?
The same way I'm sure
that you don't have a choice.
The question is,
are you gonna go against him
or are you gonna go against me?
Okay, I'm in.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
This thing is damn impressive.
But before we move forward,
I need to make sure
you're good with one thing.
What's that?
I want 90% ownership.
90%?
Are you out of your mind?
No, I'm not.
And I'm not in
the venture capital business.
I invest in the stock market.
Which means I'd be using
my own money on this.
Money that
you'd earn back in spades.
I hope it turns out that way,
but this thing
has a lot of risk,
and I'd be taking all of it.
Then maybe you should take
none of it.
Donna, as good as
this product is,
I'm telling you--as one business
person to another--
you have no credibility
to do this.
Believe me, these are
the best terms you're gonna get.
Well...you see,
that's where you're wrong, Stu.
Because like I told you
once before,
I'm Donna, this is awesome,
and I can do better.
[tense music]
Well,
I hope you prove me wrong.
But in the meantime, I won't be
used as a stalking horse.
Which means
if you walk away now,
you can't come back to me later.
Oh, you don't have to
worry about that, Stu.
Because
once I walk out that door,
I promise you I'm not
coming back.
♪ ♪
I can't believe you.
Listen, Mike,
before you say anything--
I know you didn't give a shit
about those miners,
but the least you could've done
is stuck around long enough
to give me some leverage.
We had no choice.
Palmer pressured
ten of our top clients
to drop us unless we pulled out.
So it's either them or me?
Unless you can replace
30 million in billings,
you're damn right it is.
Harvey,
without you backing me,
those miners are screwed.
And there is nothing
that I can do about it.
There's something
you can do about it,
you just don't wanna do it.
You're talking about
that woman.
You want leverage on Palmer?
She's the one who's got it.
Harvey, we've been over this.
I'm not gonna use that woman.
And what if I told you
we already did?
- What?
- Mike, we not only found her,
we got enough to force
that bastard into a settlement.
The question is:
are you willing to use it?
What do you mean "we"?
- Mike--
- No, no, you just said, "we."
Who the hell is "we"?
Rachel.
Me and Rachel.
You dragged Rachel into this.
I didn't drag her
into anything.
I went to her for permission
because I knew how you felt,
and she jumped at the chance
since you're too stupid to.
You had no right.
- Mike, listen--
- You had no right!
♪ ♪
Good night, Johnny.
Benjamin?
Donna.
Uh, I hope you don't
think it's weird
that I came to your place.
Well, I find it
a little weird that
you know where I live.
I work in IT.
I know where everyone lives.
But that's not what
I came here to talk about.
What did you come here for?
Um, I'm freaking out
about tomorrow
and what if we're not ready?
Relax, Benjamin.
It's gonna be fine.
How can you know that?
Because I already did
a practice run.
- What are you talking about?
- There's a guy I know
who I thought might invest,
but he's not really
in this business
so I brought the Donna over
to him and I gave him our pitch.
And it went okay?
It went more than okay.
He made us an offer.
Then what in God's name
do we need
to put ourselves through
this torture for?
I turned him down.
Wait--what?
Donna, this is our dream.
I know that, Benjamin.
But wanted to own 90% of it,
and I'm not willing to give up
90% of our dream.
Now go home and get some sleep,
because we've got
our first meeting tomorrow
and you and I
are gonna kick some serious ass.
♪ ♪
[door opens, closes]
- When were you gonna tell me?
- Mike--
Were you ever gonna
God damn tell me?
- Don't speak to me like that.
- You went behind my back
when you knew how
I felt about this.
No, I went behind your back
because I knew
how you felt about it.
Is that supposed to
make it okay?
No, look, I was the one
that didn't want to
let things get too risky,
but when Harvey
laid it out for me,
I decided that it wasn't.
Then why didn't you come
to me first?
Because you're the one
that says
forgiveness is easier to ask for
than permission.
That's a bullshit reason.
Then how about focusing on
the fact that I did it for you?
- Rachel--
- Mike, this morning,
when you told me it was over,
the look on your face--
I don't want you to have that
look for the rest of your life.
Rachel, I was upset.
It had just happened.
No, Mike, that's just it.
It hadn't.
You've been living with this
for so long,
that's why you gave Harvey
the go-ahead to begin with.
I did that because I had to
watch Oliver fail
and there's nothing
I could do about it.
And if it wasn't Oliver,
it was going to be
someone else.
Or something else.
There's always gonna
be some reminder
that you weren't a lawyer.
And it would eat away at you,
because it's what
you're meant to be.
You shouldn't have done
what you did.
I know you're mad at me
for going behind your back,
but I'm not gonna apologize.
Because I don't wanna spend
the rest of my life with a man
who gave up on his dreams.
And I know that you don't
wanna be that man either.
♪ ♪
Louis?
What are you doing in here?
Rachel, can I talk to you
a second?
Of course.
I heard Mike had a problem
involving that woman.
Yes, he did.
We actually got into
a fight about it last night.
- What's he gonna do?
- I don't know.
But thank you
for doing whatever you did
to find her, anyway.
Of course.
So...
what are you doing in here?
You ever wish
you hadn't found out?
- What?
- You ever wish
you never known
about Mike's secret?
Or, for that matter,
never even met him?
Louis, what's going on?
Tara and I have been
sharing a lot lately.
But there's still things
I haven't told her.
Yesterday, she asked me what
I was having a bad day about.
And the truth is,
it was pretty much about Mike.
And I want to
tell her about it, but--
You don't know
how she'll react.
No, I don't.
I still haven't even told her
I knew about Mike's secret
before he got caught,
let alone the fact that
I used it to get made partner.
- Louis--
- Rachel, when Sheila found out,
she said I wasn't
her soul mate anymore.
But that was Sheila, Louis.
And the key phrase is
"she found out."
You didn't tell her.
So you were okay
when Mike told you?
No, I wouldn't say
that I was okay with it.
But I love him.
That's why I forgave him.
I can't guarantee
that Tara will forgive you,
but I can tell you that
if she finds out some other way,
then she won't.
[tense music]
[laughs]
♪ ♪
Thank you, Rachel.
I appreciate your time.
♪ ♪
Thank you for
sitting down with us.
Ah, it's our pleasure.
I'm Andrew and this is Russell.
- I'm Donna.
- And my name is Benjamin.
- Mind if I call you Ben?
- Yes, actually,
I mind very much.
But you open up
that checkbook of yours,
and you can call Ben here
whatever the hell you want.
I appreciate that,
but before we get started,
you should know
that we get pitched
six personal assistant devices
a month.
And you should know
that our device
makes Siri and the Alexa
look like toaster ovens.
Well, that may be the case,
but I'm concerned
that the market
is already saturated.
If you were so concerned,
you wouldn't be
sitting here
in the first place.
- Is that a fact?
- Yes, it is.
Because you're the head
of the investment team,
and the head of the team
doesn't waste his time
unless he thinks there might be
something in it for him.
There might be other things
in it for me
than just investing.
Yes, there could.
Like marking your territory.
Because anybody can see by the
way you two are sitting there
that he's gunning for your job
and you don't like that one bit.
- That's not--
- Who told you that?
No one told me that.
Just like no one told me
that you can't fire him
because that'll make you
look weak.
Which is why
you took this meeting.
Because you didn't want him
taking it without you.
Okay, how in the hell
are you doing all this?
I'm doing this
because I'm Donna.
And if it hasn't
dawned on you already,
so is this device.
Now, do you wanna puff up your
chest and play office politics,
or do you wanna hear about
an opportunity
that could vault you both
to the top of the ladder?
Why don't you tell us about
your product?
♪ ♪
Can I get a black coffee?
Make it two of whatever
he's having.
You here to tell me
what a dick I am
for going behind
your back again?
No, I'm here
to find out what time
your meeting with Palmer is.
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Well, I wasn't gonna do it
without your permission.
Which means there is no meeting
with Palmer.
Well, I'm giving you
my permission.
Mike, I'm not trying
to be an asshole,
but we went to a lot of trouble
to get that shit on Palmer
and you looked like
you wanted to kill me.
So how do I know you're not
gonna wanna change your mind?
'Cause I wanna be a lawyer.
I don't care how we do it.
[stirring music]
Take out your wallet,
pay for this coffee,
and let's bring this thing home.
♪ ♪
Well, that was
the most amazing 27 minutes
of my entire life.
Hm.
Which part?
When you sat there
with your mouth glued shut
or when you shit the bed
describing the operating system?
Oh, my God,
I knew I should have stopped
after the design specs.
Benjamin, I'm teasing you.
Now I don't know
if I should believe you.
Then listen to me carefully.
You killed it.
Thank you.
But, in fact, we killed it.
You're damn right, we did.
Now get going, I'm gonna see you
back at the firm.
Where are you going?
I accidentally forgot my pen
in the conference room.
Oh, I have one you can borrow.
Benjamin,
when I say accidentally,
I mean intentionally
because it gives me an excuse
to go back in there
and eavesdrop on what
they're saying about us.
Oh, that's a great idea.
Can I come with you?
- No, I need to do this alone.
- Why?
Because when they
see me without you,
they're gonna think
it's two against one
and they'll make me
an offer to cut you out.
Wait, you actually think
they would do that?
Of course they will.
These guys are vultures.
Well, then shouldn't I go
with you so we can stop it?
Do you trust me?
Yes, I do.
Then trust
when they make me the offer,
I'm gonna act outraged,
tell them we'll never
do business with them,
and they'll give us
an extra 5% right there.
[tense music]
[elevator bell dings]
♪ ♪
- So what'd you think?
- I thought it was impressive.
Oh, then I think
you're easily impressed.
- You didn't like it?
- I liked it just fine.
But do you know how much
it costs to roll out
a piece of tech like that?
Between the engineering design,
and beta testing.
It costs a ton of money.
Hey, you're the one
who says you gotta
spend money to make money.
I also said
when you fund a project,
you fund the person.
And the truth is,
I'm not funding that woman.
So,
why'd we take this meeting?
Took it as a favor
to Harvey Specter.
Now, if she was starting up
a lemonade stand,
I might throw in a few bucks.
[laughs]
But there is no way in hell
I'm getting into business
with a career legal secretary.
[laughs]
You don't have to
tell me twice.
You wanna grab some lunch?
Yeah, and maybe a drink.
I feel like I deserve it
after having to
sit through that
with a straight face.
♪ ♪
Hey, Jimbo, nice club.
A little heavy on the wood
for my taste.
A little heavy
on the douche bag for mine.
How did you get in here?
I told them I was your cousin.
We had some bad news and you
were gonna wanna hear about it.
- Bullshit.
- Maybe not the cousin part,
but here's the news:
we got your balls in a vice.
There's only one way out.
The hell you do.
And since you decided
to just wade back into this,
those six clients of yours
are gone.
Mm.
Don't think so, Slim Jim.
See, the only reason you almost
got to us in the first place
was you found my Achilles Heel.
But then we found yours.
I gotta say,
she sure is pretty.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Maybe this'll jog your memory.
Names, dates,
phone numbers, emails,
bank statements,
wire transfers.
Proof of over a dozen instances
of you committing
corporate espionage.
Lucky for us,
she isn't just pretty,
she's a hell of a bookkeeper.
What do you want?
For you to do what you should
have done in the first place.
You're gonna settle with
those miners for 200 million.
You're gonna forget you ever
heard of us or Ms. Cromwell.
And you're gonna honor
your original agreement
with Craig Seidel.
What do you care about
that weasel's future for?
That's between me and him.
Oh, one other thing.
This really is
a take-it-or-leave-it offer.
Expires in 15 seconds.
And once it's signed,
I never wanna hear about
your shitty little company
doing something like this
ever again.
♪ ♪
There you are.
Where have you been
since that meeting?
I've been doing
some thinking.
And I've been wondering
if my partner sold me out
all day.
Well...I hate to
break it to you, Benjamin,
but that's actually
the opposite of what happened.
What do you mean?
I mean...they don't want to
make us an offer.
In fact, they don't want
anything to do with the Donna.
- It's my fault, isn't it?
- Benjamin--
You don't have to
protect my feelings.
A chain is only as strong
as its weakest link,
and I know that's what I am.
No, you're not.
It turns out I am.
Listen to me.
You have designed
an incredible product.
And I don't want to
hold you back.
Which is why, as of right now,
I am dissolving our partnership
so you can take it
out on your own.
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
We're partners--I'd rather
throw the Donna into the ocean
than move forward without you.
Benjamin, please.
Don't be a martyr.
I'm not being a martyr.
I'm being a partner.
We're in this together
or not at all.
So it's up to you.
Are we gonna give up
on our dream
or live to fight another day?
[stirring music]
Live to fight, Benjamin.
Live to fight.
Again?
What the hell is it this time?
Same thing
as it was last time.
I need you to get
that hearing back for me.
Are you kidding me?
You know how much trouble
it was the first time?
I don't care
how much trouble it was.
You're gonna do it again.
Unless, of course, you don't
want the original terms
of your deal with Palmer upheld.
What are you talking about?
We had him guarantee
to pay you what he promised
and to hire you over there
at the end of the quarter.
- Why would you do that?
- 'Cause I don't just want you
to set that hearing,
I want you to bulldoze anyone
who stands in my way.
Look, it's up to you.
You take the job and the money
and you get me in
or you stay on a sinking ship
and wait for them to figure out
that you're the one who sank it.
♪ ♪
I'll make it happen.
Yeah, I'm not surprised.
♪ ♪
I would've thought you'd be
at happy hour by now.
These days my happy hour
is the 60 minutes
from the time I get home
to the time I pass out.
You're a hard worker, Stu.
Turns out they don't just give
you money for your looks.
But you didn't come
all the way back here
just to tell me how hard I work.
I came to see
if you'd reconsider.
You couldn't beat it,
could you?
No.
But that's not why I'm here.
Then why are you here?
Because even though
I didn't like your terms,
you spoke to me as an equal
and you treated me with respect
and that's the kind of person
I want to be in business with.
What would you say
if I told you the offer
was back on the table?
I'd say my assumption is
the terms won't be as good
as they were
the first time around.
The terms aren't gonna change.
Why not?
Because I don't want to
go into business with someone
who feels like
I'm giving them the shaft.
I wanna go into business
with someone who's happy
with my partnership.
Thank you, Stu.
You're welcome, Donna.
Oh, and just so you know,
when I put my money
where my mouth is,
I throw everything
I have into it.
I wouldn't expect
anything less
from a big mouth like you.
♪ ♪
Done?
Done.
I gotta say,
the world's gonna be
a better place
with you as a lawyer.
Why? 'Cause we just
strong-armed some jackass
into doing what what we want?
No, because you did
what it took
to get those miners
what they deserve.
Speaking of which, you wanna
come with me after this?
- Where you going?
- To tell those miners
that the world's best lawyer
just got them what they deserve.
- Second best.
- Ah, potato/potahto.
Seriously, Mike,
you go tell them.
Besides, after that,
you've got some preparing to do
for that hearing.
What are you talking about?
I just told you,
Seidel's got it in the bag.
And if you think there isn't
gonna be some kind of hitch,
I haven't taught you shit.
If you think whatever it is,
I can't handle it, then you have
not been paying attention.
You mean like when you handled
yourself into going to prison?
No, I mean when I came out
smelling like a rose.
Hey,
I was there when you came out.
And rose wasn't the aroma
you were emanating.
[snaps]
You're right.
I was emanating awesome.
You really are like me,
aren't you?
Unfortunately.
[poignant music]
Welcome back to the Bar, Mike.
Thanks, Harvey.
♪ ♪
Technically, I wasn't really in.
Actually, you weren't really
in the Bar, ever.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
I'd ask how your day was,
but last time I did that,
it didn't go very well.
Tara,
can I be honest with you?
Of course.
You can tell me anything.
It's part of getting to know
each other--I told you that.
Just not sure that
this is what you had in mind.
Louis, what is going on?
The other day,
when I didn't want to tell you
what I was upset about,
I was trying to figure out
a way to get Mike Ross
into the Bar.
You mean the fraud
who worked at your firm?
It's a long story,
but we're friends now
and we're past it.
What do you mean
it's a long story?
I mean I knew Mike was a fraud
before he was arrested.
And I didn't just know.
When I found out about him,
instead of going to the police,
or going to the Bar,
I leveraged it
to get my name on the wall.
♪ ♪
[sighs softly]
Tara, say something.
Say what?
You just told me you found out
you were working with a criminal
and you turned it
into a promotion.
I know that, but you said we
should get to know each other.
What do you want me
to say, Louis?
I didn't know what
your favorite movie was.
Or what side of the bed
you like.
But I thought at least I knew
what kind of man you were.
Tara, please.
This is the thing
I'm most ashamed about
in my life and I'm telling you
to show you that I'm never gonna
hide anything from you.
Well, maybe you should
hide some things from me.
What?
[sighs]
You heard me.
I heard you.
♪ ♪
How dare you say that to me
after what I had to
find out about you.
What is that supposed to mean?
It means you're sitting there
like you're the high priestess
of moral authority,
when the first time
we slept together,
you were with another man.
How can you say that to me?
I was up front about it
with you and with him.
You were up front about it
with everybody
and then you wanted me to be
up front with you about things.
And now you're looking at me
like I'm a monster!
You know what?
That's it.
That's it--
well, where are you going?
I'm sleeping
at my place tonight.
Look, Tara, please.
If I knew that
you were gonna react this way,
I never would have
told you any of this.
But you did tell me, Louis.
♪ ♪
Good night.
Tara, wait.
I'll give you a call
when I've had a chance
to figure things out.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man