Previously on "Suits"...
I don't have anything
against you,
but I'm not gonna cause trouble
with a guy like that
for someone I've never even met.
So if he wants me to switch
for a few hours, I'm switching.
If something happens
to him in there,
I will never forgive you.
- What do you want, Harvey?
- Help me protect Mike Ross.
He's in there with a guy I put
away, and the guy is no joke.
What am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to move
the guy to another prison.
You got a lot of balls
saying that to me
when the entire time
we were working together,
you knew the kid was a fraud.
I don't need your forgiveness,
Sean.
I need your help.
You want me one-on-one,
you got it.
I'm gonna use this,
and they're gonna hold you.
- No!
- What's going on here?
Why'd you come back
with a guard?
I didn't do it to get you
to forgive me.
I never should have let him
in here in the first place.
I don't even know your name.
Kevin.
Kevin Miller.
Louis,
you have the right idea,
but the wrong execution.
If we're going to look
like a real firm,
we need to do something
about subletting these offices.
I'll take care of it.
[upbeat music]
So, is everything
on my application in order?
- Yes, it is.
- Good.
Because in that case, I'd like
to get down to the particulars.
Forget the application.
I need to know what the hell
kind of man you are.
Excuse me?
What's your firm's
carbon footprint?
- Louis, not again.
- Carbon footprint?
- We're a law firm, why would I--
- Jesus Christ.
Miami's gonna be
underwater in five years,
and you don't have
a goddamn green policy?
You know what?
This interview's over.
Interview? This was supposed
to be a lease negotiation.
Tell your story walking,
jerk-off.
Goddamn it, Louis.
That is the fifth tenant
you have scared away
because of some bullshit.
- This isn't bullshit, Jessica.
- Really?
Since when do you care
about the environment?
Or genetically modified
cucumbers?
Or the plight
of the LGBT community?
Those are legitimate causes
close to my heart.
You're being ridiculous.
Yeah, well, had the French
been more ridiculous,
they wouldn't have the Nazis
goose-stepping
through their streets
for six years.
Are you really
comparing this to that?
I stand by that statement.
Then stand by this.
You don't find a new tenant
by tomorrow,
then the rent is coming out
of your pocket.
[tense music]
So do we eat together
in the cafeteria from now on
or how does that work?
You know this isn't
high school, right?
Yeah, of course I know that.
You are going to the pep rally,
though, right?
Seriously, Mike, Gallo's not
going to forget about you,
and now me, which means--
We need to have
each other's backs.
Exactly.
So from now on,
we don't just eat together,
we stick together
as much as possible.
The only time I see
that being a problem
is afternoons
between 2:00 and 4:00.
I took a job working
in the kitchen.
Then starting from today,
I'm gonna be doing something
very public from 2:00 to 4:00.
Ross,
you're coming with me.
Why, is there a problem?
That's not for me to say.
Well, where are we going?
The counselor wants
to see you.
Yeah, we're on our way
to breakfast, man.
Well, then you can
save him a biscuit,
but he's coming with me.
Let's go.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
What are you doing here?
I heard what happened.
So you know that Jessica
was being an asshole?
What I heard was that
you interviewed five tenants,
and you found a way
to turn them all down.
So why don't you tell me
what the hell's going on?
Everything's going on.
What are you talking about?
Donna, nobody's gonna be
taking these offices
without taking the bullpen.
It's the heart and soul
of this space.
And it's also the heart
and soul of you.
Exactly, which is why
I will not stand
for another firm to stick
their promiscuous associates
in my innocent incubator.
Okay, I'm gonna choose not to
respond to that except to say,
did it ever occur to you to rent
to someone without the bullpen?
Donna,
that's never gonna happen.
It could.
You've only been looking
at law firms
and law firms need
communal spaces, but--
Other firms don't.
Oh, my God.
Why didn't I think of that?
We can go with
financial planners
for high net worth individuals.
That's it.
They're old school.
They have privileged
conversations.
- They're pussies.
- Again, I'm not gonna engage.
And best of all
they're not legally savvy,
and I can shove any fine print
down their throats that I want.
Donna, you're a genius.
The only thing left
for me to do
is make sure you don't shit
the bed in another interview.
What makes you think
I would do that?
Every conversation we've
ever had, including this one.
Fair point.
Set it up.
[lively music]
You wanted to see me?
Yes,
and maybe you can explain
why you haven't
come to see me yet.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the fact
that Frank Gallo
pulled a knife on you
in the common area.
Look, I appreciate
your concern, but I'm fine.
Fine?
Mike, you are lucky he didn't
cut you into a million pieces.
What difference does it make?
I didn't come to you
because there's
nothing you can do about it.
- I'm here to help you.
- Yeah, but you can't, can you?
Look, I already told you
Gallo has guards in his pockets,
and you told me you have
no authority over the guards.
Then file a formal allegation.
No way I am doing that.
Listen to me, you have had
two incidents with this man.
Now, if it goes on record,
it triggers an investigation.
And then every single guard
and inmate
in this place
will know what I did.
And would you rather have
a hypothetical problem
or deal with your real problem
that isn't going away by itself?
What I'd like is to not have
to choose either one.
Well, I've got news
for you, bro.
One way or another,
you're making that choice
whether you like it or not.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 6x03 ♪
Back on the Map
Original Air Date on July 27, 2016
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Well, you seem to be okay.
I'm guessing that wasn't
some trick by Gallo
to split us up before?
No, it wasn't.
Then how about you tell me
what that counselor wanted?
- It's not important.
- Hey, when I said
we can't leave each other alone,
I meant information too,
and he's not yanking you
down there
first thing in the morning
for nothing.
It's not important because
what he wanted, I'm not doing.
I get it.
He wanted you to inform on
Gallo, and you don't trust me.
That's not true,
but I don't have to tell you
about every offer I get
that I don't take.
Yeah, that's fine,
but I need you to understand
what he's asking you to do,
because if you rat on Gallo,
I'm gonna be left here
by myself.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about
Mark Higgins.
He was my roommate
when I first got here.
He was being harassed
by some different asshole,
taking a beating
a couple times a week,
and that counselor, Julius,
convinced him to go on record.
Two weeks later,
they put him in a coma.
He never came out.
So you're telling me
that I can't trust Julius?
I'm saying Mark did,
and Mark's not here anymore.
♪ ♪
Harvey, where have you been?
Jessica needs--
Donna, I need you to get
Sean Cahill on the phone,
and I need it yesterday.
I know you're worried
about Mike,
but let the man do his job.
I'm not stopping him
from doing his job.
I'm telling him
to do it faster.
What do you want me
to do, Harvey?
I've left him
a dozen messages--
Then leave him a dozen more,
and while you're at it,
don't leave your desk
until he calls back.
- I can't do that.
- Why the hell not?
Because I'm making sure
that Louis
doesn't blow it
with another tenant today.
- Then get Rachel to do that.
- Harvey, Rachel has law school.
And besides that, this is
something that I want to do.
Donna, I don't give a shit
about Louis and his tenants.
Well, I do.
Because we all said
that we would give everything
we had to get this place
back to where it was,
and right now,
Jessica has a prospect
waiting for you
in the conference room.
So instead of coming down on me
and Sean for doing our jobs,
why don't you get over there
and do yours?
♪ ♪
The plaintiff ID'd
the defendant, Your Honor.
It's an open and shut case.
No, it isn't because
his reliability
as a witness can't be ignored.
What are you talking about?
His eyes work perfectly.
Yes, and so does his mouth,
because as the record shows,
he has a history
of making false statements
to extort settlements.
Don't you think
it's a little ironic,
you questioning someone's
character in an ethics class?
What's that supposed to mean?
I think the court knows
what it means.
And what I think is
if you're trying
to disparage me
to score some points,
then you should have the guts
to say what you mean.
So, Naomi, how is it ironic
coming from me?
Okay, everyone, why don't
we take a quick break?
It's ironic
because your fiancé
is currently serving
a two-year sentence for fraud,
and no matter what you say,
everyone here knows you knew.
All right,
that's enough for today.
But, Naomi,
if you're gonna impugn
another lawyer's character,
you should know
that in the eyes of a jury,
it doesn't say great things
about your own.
Rachel, can I speak to you
for a minute?
I'm sorry, professor, I have
another class in five minutes.
♪ ♪
They say coffee's for closers,
but it's not.
- Is that a fact?
- Yeah, which is why
I gave it up two years ago,
because that shit'll kill you.
So will playing chicken
with the SEC,
but you don't seem to have
a problem with that.
You know who I am.
I also know you have
an indictment on the horizon,
and you're looking
for new representation
because no lawyer
in his right mind
wants to touch you
with a ten-foot pole.
If that's how you talk
to prospective clients,
maybe I don't want to get
to know you better.
I think you do because
you got nowhere else to go.
The question is, what makes
you think I'd take you on?
Gee, I don't know.
Why don't we ask one of
the hundreds of associates
you have walking around here?
Oh, wait, you don't have any
associates walking around here.
I get it--you think
we're down and desperate.
No, I think you played chicken
with the ABA,
came up short,
and now you need a high-profile
client and a big, goddamn win
or you're gonna be on the street
in about ten minutes.
What I need is to
kick your ass out of here
right the hell now
because I'm not interested
in your kind of client.
All right, fun time's over.
I'll pay you a retainer
and triple your rate.
You can quintuple my rate.
My answer's never gonna change.
Listen to me.
We are a perfect fit.
I need this and you do too.
And it works out, my business is
your firm's the rest of my life.
♪ ♪
That's exactly
why I don't want it.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna enjoy my coffee.
I'd wish you luck
with your SEC troubles, William,
but I wouldn't mean it.
♪ ♪
Where is he?
He's not here.
What do you mean
he's not here?
I mean he's taking
his 4:15 constitutional.
You mean
he's in the bathroom.
I believe
that's the situation,
but I prefer to tell myself
he's out for a stroll.
Whoo!
I feel like a new man.
Like a 100-pound load
off my shoulders.
I think we all know
that's not where it came from.
Well, that was fun.
Come on, Louis.
We've got some
appointments to make.
No need.
I took care of it.
- What?
- What do you think I meant by
a load off my shoulders?
I signed the new tenant.
Without me?
Well, yes.
Listen, I found
this sweet old man
who runs a bunch of
friendly money managers
looking to expand,
and they're all, like,
1,000 years old.
They're not even
gonna need the bullpen,
and they start tomorrow,
and it's gonna be perfect.
No, Louis,
it's not going to be perfect.
What are you talking about?
We said we were gonna
do this together,
and I am a part of this firm
as much as you are,
and when you go ahead
and you do something like this
without me,
it really pisses me off.
Donna, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to prove to myself
that I could not screw this up.
Well, don't come running to me
when you do.
♪ ♪
Oh, please tell me
you're making
just plain old mashed potatoes.
I am getting so sick
of that Au gratin bullshit
they keep serving us.
Why don't you take it up
with the cook?
Well, what if I want to
take it up with you?
Well, I'd say
you're shit out of luck
because it is not my call.
Actually,
I feel hip deep in luck
finding you here
all by yourself.
You're not gonna do anything
to me here.
There's too many other people.
You know,
when I first got here,
I didn't have
a high school diploma.
Surprise, surprise.
Before you know it I was
a regular Poindexter
just like you.
Congratulations.
Your parents must be so proud.
They are.
I loved all my subjects,
but math was my favorite,
transitive property
in particular.
Gallo, we've been over this.
You're gonna get to Harvey
through me.
Thank you.
Got it.
That's true,
but that's just the beginning,
because if I can get
to Harvey through you,
that must mean I can get to you
through somebody else.
♪ ♪
You leave Kevin out of this.
A little late for that, Mike.
See, in here we use
the buddy system.
You left your buddy alone.
♪ ♪
What the hell did you do?
Why don't you find out
for yourself?
He's in the bathroom.
I'd hurry if I were you.
He's not gonna be conscious
much longer.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[coughing]
Kevin.
Hey, what happened?
I'd say you should see
the other guy, Mike,
but there were three of them.
Oh, come on, hey, get up.
I thought you said
you were gonna stay in the open.
[groans]
Everyone needs to go
to the bathroom,
and Gallo and his buddies were
waiting for me when I got here.
Come on, we got to get you
to the infirmary.
No, no!
We can't.
You need someone
to look at you.
We can't!
That's exactly what Gallo wants.
Because if we go
to the infirmary,
we're gonna have
to file a report.
Yeah, and then he won't have
to lay a finger on us
because someone else
will do it for him.
♪ ♪
What are we gonna do?
The only thing we can do.
Suck it up and take it
until Gallo gets someone else
in his sights.
♪ ♪
[laid-back music]
Dude, I don't give a shit
what those douches say.
Those shares aren't worth
the tampons they're printed on.
Uh, what floor?
Tell them to stick it
in their ass.
I'm on the phone, guy.
I know.
I understand that, but--
Pearson Specter Litt.
What business do you have
with our--
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Lick my balls.
What did you just say to me?
Hold on, Skidmarks.
[clears throat]
En El telefono, hombre.
Comprende?
All right, man, I got to jet.
We're settling into
our new digs today.
All right, later, Brosef Stalin.
[laughing]
[elevator dings]
Excuse me.
Uh, hi.
I couldn't help but overhear.
There must be some mistake.
We're leasing space
to the satellite division
of the Stevens Investment Group.
That's me, pal, Stu Buzzini.
I run the satellite division.
Well, that wasn't made clear
to me when I met your boss.
Old man river?
He's not gonna drag his ass
in here every day.
He's got one foot in the grave.
Well, then, did he share
with you the lease agreement?
Because it clearly outlined
a dress code.
You think I wear this to work?
What am I, an asshole?
Next time you see me
I'll be in a suit
three times more expensive
than yours.
- This is a Brioni.
- It's a Bri-shitty,
as far as I'm concerned.
Come on, buddy, give me some.
Come on, brah,
don't leave me hanging.
- Wha--I don't--
- Bssh. That's my girl.
I'm just kidding, Sally.
Hey, holler at me
if you need anything, okay?
I'm looking forward
to being douche-mates.
[chuckles]
Shit Stick, huh, you get
that girl's number last night?
That's right.
[laughing]
Ball Sack, how did you
track us down, man?
I thought we fired you.
[laughs]
Holy goddamn shit,
what have I done?
Come on, boys,
let's make some money!
- Donna, listen to me.
- I know.
Then you know that I--
Shit the bed like
you never have before?
- I am so--
- Banged the monkey?
Screwed the pooch?
- Donna, please--
- Flinked the flank?
What does flink
the flank mean?
It means I'm not finished
enjoying this.
When do you think
you'll be finished?
Because I need to know
what to do.
I don't know.
When does their lease expire?
Oh, my God, I cooked in
an extension option!
Louis, relax.
The important thing
to remember here
is that this is your fault
for not listening to me.
How does that help me?
It doesn't.
It helps me.
- Donna!
- Okay, listen to me.
If you really want my help,
I'm gonna give it to you.
What's gonna happen is,
sometime in the next 24 hours,
a minor incident
that would mean nothing
to anybody else but you
is gonna make you want
to undo this fiasco.
I want to undo it right now.
But I'm telling you not to
because in addition to
making things worse,
Jessica will kill you.
So just wait things out
and in another--
I'm sorry, when does
their lease expire again?
- 18 months.
- 18 months...
this whole thing
will be a distant memory.
Can you do that?
Can you let it go?
Mmm.
Yes, I think you can.
- Mmm?
- Mm-hmm.
You can do it.
Yes, I can.
Then go forth and conquer.
I'm gonna give him
about an hour and a half.
♪ ♪
Jessica, what can I do
for you?
What are you so happy about?
I just saw our new tenants.
A bunch of dickhead traders.
They're gonna drive Louis crazy.
Well, I just got
a very interesting phone call,
but I'm not smiling about it.
Nigerian prince leaving you
his inheritance?
Because I got news for you,
it's a scam.
Oh, I hope it's a scam because
I just heard you turned down
a client whose investment firm
is worth $2 billion.
Well, I don't give a shit
how much they're worth.
I'm not representing
William Sutter.
Oh, yes, you are,
or you're gonna give me
a hell of a reason why not.
You want the reason?
This guy makes Madoff
and Forstman look like saints,
and I'm not getting involved
with anther criminal.
Harvey, I don't think you
understand what's going on here.
We're filling up these offices
with subletters
to make it look like
we're still alive,
but if we don't land
a new client
and show the world
that we're back,
then we may as well let them
have the space for good.
Then let me land someone else.
Well,
then it better be someone huge,
and you better do it
in the next 48 hours
because that's when I set our
next appointment with Sutter,
and when we get there,
we're signing him as a client.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
You know who you have
to go to, right?
Donna, no way.
Not him.
Harvey, you heard Jessica.
We're in trouble,
and you know it,
and Nathan Burns
isn't a criminal.
He's just an asshole.
An asshole I told I'd never
get into business with.
Well, that's too bad
because I set up
a meeting with him
the second I saw Jessica
heading for your office.
♪ ♪
Mike, I can't talk right now.
I have an inmate coming in
in about five minutes.
Good, because this will take
about five seconds.
You need to get Gallo
transferred to another block,
and you need to do it right now.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, calm down
and tell me what happened.
I am calm.
He attacked my cellmate
while I was working.
Now, this is a huge prison.
You get him goddamn moved.
I don't have the authority
to do that.
That's the second time
this week you told me
you can't help me after
telling me you can help me.
- Mike, listen--
- And don't tell me
to make
a formal allegation again
because that is just going
to make this worse.
It doesn't have to.
Is that what
you told Mark Higgins?
Oh, that's out of line.
How dare you ask me about
discussions
I've had with another inmate.
From what I understand,
he can't have discussions
with anyone anymore.
And I don't want to hear
what happened to him.
I just want to figure out
how to get out of here alive.
Well, I can't help you do that
if you keep talking to me
like that.
♪ ♪
Listen to me, Julius,
I'm sorry,
but I cannot tell on Gallo.
So if you can't get him moved,
I need to quit my job,
because Kevin is
my only friend in here.
That's two hours a day
that he's exposed.
I'm not gonna leave him
alone again.
Mike,
I hate to keep telling you no,
but that's not
how it works in here.
How what works in here?
You can't just walk away
from a job,
and there's nothing
I can do about that.
♪ ♪
Harvey Specter,
as I live and breathe.
Good to see you, Nathan.
No, it's not.
I was wondering
how long it would take
after your lawyers left
before you came here
begging me to take you on.
Do I look like I'm begging?
To tell you the truth,
I didn't expect you
until next week.
You know,
desperation's a beautiful thing.
Okay, you got me.
The question is, do you
want to keep sticking it to me
or do you want to
take my one-time-only offer
to become my number one client?
Okay, Harvey,
I'm done sticking it to you,
but if you want my business,
you'll have to earn it.
What do you think these front
row Knicks tickets are for?
Great.
I'll give them to my stepson
because he's too stupid
to know the Knicks suck.
- What do you want, Nathan?
- Lockwood Energy.
They've been a pain
in my ass for ten years.
Now they're trying to bring
their business to my backyard.
And you want me to block them?
I want you to shove
so many restraining orders
up their ass
they can't even breathe,
and I want it done
by the time we sit down
for appetizers
tonight at Per Se.
Then the next time you see me,
they'll be a speck
in your rear view mirror.
But, Nathan, when I get there,
you better have a Scotch
waiting for me.
You can order one
for both of us
when you call
and make the reservations.
8:00 p.m. sharp.
Oh, and Harvey?
If you don't call yourself,
I'll know.
You really are a dick, Nathan.
I am,
but when I give my word,
the world knows
that it's rock solid.
So, be there on time,
get that shit done,
or don't bother
showing up at all.
♪ ♪
♪ Prune juice, prune juice
you are so sweet ♪
♪ I love you all the way
from my head down to my-- ♪
Goddamn it!
Hey, guy, what can you
do for me?
The name isn't Guy,
it's Louis,
and I had a two-gallon bottle of
prune juice in the refrigerator.
I want to know where it went.
No problem.
I had to toss that shit.
You threw away my prune juice?
Let me put it this way,
if my asshole had an asshole,
that's what it would smell like.
That's what it's supposed
to smell like.
Take it easy, bro,
it's just prune juice.
No, it isn't just prune juice.
It's the sanctity of my kitchen.
And on top of my prune juice,
you ate all of my bran bars.
You must spend a lot of time
on the shitter.
That's neither here nor there.
You, sir, are in violation
of subsection 3-C
of your lease,
which means if it happens again,
you're out on your ass.
What?
What kind of dildo
puts bran bars
and prune juice
in a lease agreement?
This dildo.
This dildo right here.
Are you nuts?
No.
I'm your worst nightmare,
because this quivering angry
dildo isn't going away
until it gets its satisfaction.
- What did you just say to me?
- I just said,
this dildo is gonna be in
your face slapping it around,
then up your ass marching you
right out the door
if it catches you in violation
of your lease ever again.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Hello?
Rachel, it's Professor Dunbar.
How can I help you, Professor?
I tried to talk to you
about this after class,
but I was wondering if you'd
be interested in helping me
with something that's
near and dear to my heart.
- What's that?
- The Innocence Project.
You want me to help you get
an innocent man off death row?
That's exactly what I want.
This wouldn't have
anything to do
with the incident after class
the other day, would it?
What makes you say that?
Because I can't do
both of these things
at the same time,
and you know it.
Okay, yes.
Yes, I thought you might need
a little relief,
but I wouldn't be
offering you this
if I didn't think
you'd earned it.
I appreciate that,
Professor, just...
I'm not one to back away
from a fight.
Rachel, I'm not asking you
to back away from a fight.
I'm asking you to pick one
that's more important.
♪ ♪
- Well?
- Well, what?
Did you grovel to Per Se
to get yourself a reservation?
I didn't grovel to Per Se.
I groveled to Nathan.
But I don't want to talk
about what I did.
I want to talk about
what you did,
because if you didn't
file those motions
then I might as well
cancel dinner.
I didn't just get them filed,
I got the city attorney
to put them
on the top of the pile.
Restraining order,
patent infringement suit,
tortious interference,
and environmental hazard report.
Lockwood isn't gonna
know what hit them.
Well, instead of patting
yourself on the back,
why don't you pick up the phone
and get me Sean Cahill?
Aw, she doesn't have
to get you Sean Cahill,
'cause he's standing
right in front of ya.
It's about time.
Why the hell haven't you
returned any of my phone calls?
Harvey,
I need you to sit down.
Sean, what took so long?
It took me so long to find out
that Frank Gallo's
not going anywhere
because he's got people
up in high places
who are protecting him.
Then tell me who they are.
I'll put them in the ground.
- Look, it's not that simple.
- It is to me.
Harvey, you don't understand.
I understand that unless
he's a government informant,
we can get a criminal put back
where he belongs.
You got to be kidding me.
Look, I can't reveal details
of a federal investigation.
You don't have to.
You just did.
Where are you going?
I'm telling Mike
what the hell's going on.
Stop.
Just listen to me.
No one can know
that this came from me.
No one's gonna know about it
at all...except Mike.
Harvey, if you go
to that prison now,
you'll never make it back
in time for your dinner
with Nathan.
Donna, I don't care
what you have to do.
Get him a message
that I'll be an hour late,
and make sure he says it's okay.
- Harvey--
- Take care of it.
I'm not leaving Mike alone
in there another minute
without knowing what's coming.
[suspenseful music]
Harvey.
Mike.
[door closes]
Please tell me you came here
with good news about Gallo.
I have news,
but it isn't good.
Oh, shit.
Mike, listen to me.
Cahill wants to help,
but his hands are tied.
What the hell does that mean?
Gallo's not here
because of good behavior.
He's here because he cut a deal.
You got to be kidding me.
He's a goddamn informant?
Yeah.
Oh, that's great.
So he's not going anywhere,
and neither am I unless
it's in a goddamn body bag!
Mike, I'm gonna
find another way.
I'd appreciate that, Harvey,
but what the hell am I supposed
to do in the meantime?
Hey, you didn't even
want me to try
and get him out
in the first place.
And I sure as hell
didn't ask you
to put him in here
in the first place.
And all the advice you gave me
to stay in a group did
was get the only friend
I have in here
nearly put in the hospital.
[tense music]
Look, there's only one
other thing I can think of,
but you'll have to play it
just right
or we're gonna
make things worse.
[scoffs]
Well, you might as well say it,
because from where I'm standing,
they are gonna get worse
whether you tell me or not.
♪ ♪
[lively music]
Louis, can I talk to you
for a second?
What, no brah?
No scrotum?
No dick nose?
No, man, just plain old Louis.
Well, I consider myself
a fair man.
What exactly do you have to say?
I want to say
I heard you before,
and I didn't treat you
or your office with any respect,
and I'm hoping we can
have a fresh start.
That's wonderful.
I'm touched.
Now take this
and get the hell out.
- What's that?
- It's an eviction notice.
I gave you a warning.
You screwed the pooch
and now you're out.
Are you kidding me?
You come at me, I apologize
to you, and then you do this?
Well,
in between those two things,
your traders were playing
touch football
in my beloved bullpen,
so I don't accept
your bullshit apology.
You won't get away with this.
I already did.
You're a son of a bitch.
Yeah, a son of a bitch
who's got the full weight
of the New York City Legal Code
on his side.
And you just learned
lesson number one.
Don't ever mess
with a Harvard goddamn lawyer.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Excuse me, sir?
Relax, I know where I'm going.
I'm sure you do, but I don't
think you're going to find
what you're looking for.
What did you just say to me?
I'm sorry, but you match
the description of a man
I was told would be
walking in here right about now.
And what exactly
is the description?
I'd rather not say,
but it fit you to a T.
So I'm fairly confident
you're the one
that was supposed to have dinner
with Nathan Burns.
- Let's have it.
- Have what?
The message
you're supposed to give me.
He wanted me to tell you
that being late to dinner
was a slap in the face,
and you could take your offer
and shove it up your ass.
♪ ♪
Goddamn it, Donna, I told you
to call Nathan's office
and tell him I'd be late.
Don't "goddamn it, Donna" me,
I did call them.
Well, he wasn't at
the restaurant,
so your message
didn't get through.
I didn't leave
a message, Harvey.
I spoke to his secretary
who I've known for 12 years,
and she said that
Nathan said it was okay.
Then either he lied
or she did,
and it wasn't him
because he may be an asshole,
but as he likes to put it,
his word is his bond.
Unless somebody
changed his mind.
What are you talking about?
The only person who has
the power to put pressure
on an asshole like Nathan Burns
is a bigger asshole,
and you said it yourself,
William Sutter will do anything
to get what he wants.
Donna, I need you to get
Bill Johnson at Goldman,
and I need you to do it
right now.
- I can't.
- Why the hell not?
Because he doesn't
work there anymore.
- Oh, shit.
- Harvey.
Donna, I need somebody
who can tell me
if Sutter's buying shares,
and I need it before
the market opens tomorrow.
Then it's a good thing Louis
just rented our offices
to a bunch of traders.
[tense music]
Oh, good,
Jessica, you're here.
I...I had a few contracts
I need to file.
I just need your signature.
You think I don't know
you've been
forging my signature
on shit like this
for the last five years?
I'm sorry...
No, you're not.
And you don't need to be.
You were just trying
to save me some time.
Now, why don't you tell me
why you're really here?
I...
I'm taking a practical ethics
course this semester.
Well, it's been a long time
since I read that textbook.
My problem's not
with the textbook.
Mike.
One of my classmates
stuck him in my face
in front of the entire class
to win an argument.
And the only thing you want to
stick in her face is your fist?
Something like that.
So the professor offered me
an Innocence Project case,
and I want to take it,
but if I do...
The other students will think
you're afraid of her.
Exactly.
Then you have to make
all of them afraid of you.
Then the only impression
they'll have of you
is that you're one badass woman.
Why do I get the feeling
that when you were in law school
you went through something
just like this?
Rachel, I don't know
if you've been paying attention,
but I go through something
like this every damn day.
I take it you're
the man in charge.
- What makes you think that?
- Because you're still here,
and the markets
closed six hours ago.
Maybe I'm just here
cheating on my girlfriend
with my secretary.
Like I said,
you're the man in charge.
I like you,
but you didn't come
all the way down to my office
just to kiss my ass,
so why don't you just get to it?
I need to know who just bought
5% of this company.
Well, that's gonna be
a problem
because whoever it was
doesn't have to file
with the SEC for three months.
You're right, I didn't come
down here to kiss your ass,
but I didn't come
for a refresher
on securities law either.
I'm here because a guy like you
can get me what I need.
And why should I help you,
when I went to your partner
on my hands and knees
and I'm still gonna lose
my lease
because I ate a couple
of goddamn bran bars?
You give me what I need,
as far as I'm concerned,
you can throw every bran bar
Louis has off the roof.
I got a guy that can
get you that information.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Now that I know
you got something to lose,
I need you to make
a little investment.
You serious about me
sticking it to your partner?
What do you think
I've been doing to him
for the last ten years?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Are you ready for round two?
I am.
In fact,
I think I already won,
because one of
the easiest things
to do in a debate
is to attack the debater.
What is this?
You went after me because of
something that my fiancé did,
but the truth is, we all have
skeletons in our closets.
The difference
between you and me
is that I don't care
to use them.
What do you want?
I think you know what I want.
Shall we get started?
I'd like to apologize
for saying what I said
to Rachel Zane.
I only did what I did
because she's my intellectual
and ethical superior.
I'm ashamed of myself,
and I forfeit this competition.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
How'd you get her to say that?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is,
everyone here knows
that I'm not afraid of her.
I take it that means you're
staying in the class then?
Nope.
That is my official
drop-out request.
I'm doing the Innocence Project.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here,
Harvey?
You didn't give me a chance
to show you all the motions
I filed to keep that
bastard out of your backyard.
Because I told you
if you were late for dinner
you could go screw yourself.
No, you didn't give me
a chance to show you
because you're afraid
of William Sutter,
when the person you should
be afraid of is me.
What the hell
are you talking about?
You think I don't know
he bought a piece of you
in the middle of the night,
and now he's pressuring
the board to kick you out?
Okay, fine.
He did, but I'm a whale,
and he's a shark,
and I have no other choice.
I got a little news
for you, Nathan.
I got a piece
of your company too,
which means you either hire me
and we fight
that bastard together,
or you go with him
and you take me on.
Either way, you're not walking
out of this thing without a war.
All I ever wanted was
to work together,
but I do not like being bullied.
No, you like to bully,
which is exactly why
I never wanted to represent you
in the first place.
You only came to me
because you needed me.
You didn't care.
You're right, Nathan,
I didn't,
but like you said,
your word is your bond.
This is a chance
for you to keep it,
and maybe now we can actually
start off on the right foot.
♪ ♪
Okay, Harvey.
I'm in.
Two years, five months,
12 days.
I'm not interested in hearing
how long it's been
since you got laid.
No, that's exactly
how long it's gonna be
until you walk out of here.
You trying to get me
to attack you right here?
Because that's
what's gonna happen.
I'm just trying to tell you
that you're eligible
for parole in six weeks.
Bullshit.
You don't believe me?
All right,
take a look for yourself.
It's all right there.
You can read, right?
Yeah, I can read,
but we're not all fake lawyers
like you,
so why don't you tell me
what it is I'm looking at?
The time you served
while awaiting trial
was never factored
into your sentence.
Your lawyer dropped the ball.
And why the hell
would he do that?
Because of an arcane statute
that nine out of ten lawyers
don't know about, but I do.
You think I don't know
this is your protector's idea
to get me off your back?
'Cause it's not gonna work.
No, Frank.
Harvey's idea was for me
to tell these guys
that the real reason you're here
is because you're an informant.
[tense music]
You tell that to one
living soul, I'll kill you.
I guess you have to decide
if you really want to spend
the next two years
trying to mess with me
or salvage
what's left of your life.
If you're really gonna pick
getting back at Harvey
over your own freedom,
you really are the sorriest
son of a bitch I've ever met.
♪ ♪
What the goddamn hell
is going on in here?
It's looking good, isn't it?
Okay, buddy, you just signed
your death warrant.
I gave you 30 days,
now you've got 30 minutes.
I don't think
that's happening, boss.
Not only are we staying,
but we're making
your beloved bullpen
the center of our operations,
because your big bro
amended our lease.
This is bullshit.
Why the hell would Harvey
do that?
Let's just say
I helped him out of a jam.
This isn't over,
because whatever Harvey did,
he doesn't know contracts
like I do.
And you don't know them
like I know them,
because this new lease
is tighter than your mom's ass.
That's it.
I am suing you for slander,
because my mom's ass
is miles from tight.
I'll take your word
for it, bro, and bring it on,
because you might be
a Harvard-educated lawyer,
but I'm a Yale-educated lawyer,
and the difference
between me and you
is I know the real money's
in trading.
Now get the hell
out of my bullpen.
♪ ♪
- Harvey.
- William.
I got something for you.
I assume it's an engagement
letter for me to sign.
It's the SEC form
you're gonna have to file
for buying 5%
of Nathan Burns's company.
- So you know.
- I don't just know.
I bought a seat at the table,
and I got Nathan
and the board on my side.
Bullshit.
None of you have the balls
to go up against me.
I'm not here to go up
against you, William.
I'm here to buy your shares back
at a tidy little profit
so you can use it to hire
whoever you want
to be your lawyer
because it sure as hell
isn't gonna be me.
Yeah, maybe instead
I'll make sure his company
gets in my pocket,
never hires you,
and your firm is out of business
by the end of the quarter.
Well,
that's never gonna happen,
because the only way
to win this thing
is to get down in the mud,
and if I was gonna be
your lawyer,
which I'm never gonna be,
I'd tell you that's
the last place you want to be
when you're staring down
the barrel of an indictment.
You know you're making
an enemy of me
for the rest of your life.
Take a number, buddy,
because one thing
I'm never gonna do
is get involved
with a shady piece of shit
like you.
♪ ♪
So you going to the movie?
I wasn't planning on it.
It's pitch black.
Packed in.
Gallo might try something.
I thought you said
you had some way
to get him off our backs.
Yeah, I don't know
if it worked yet or not.
Well, it doesn't matter,
because movie night is sacred.
What do you mean?
I mean it's one night
that every guy in here
looks forward to, you know,
doesn't want to mess up.
You try something in there,
you're gonna end up
like my old roommate,
Mark Higgins.
Well, what's playing?
"Crimson Tide."
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Well,
you heard what I said about
the sanctity
of movie night, right?
Besides, me,
I never joke about Denzel.
Uh-uh.
"King Kong ain't got shit on me!
We didn't land
on Plymouth Rock."
both: "Plymouth Rock
landed on us."
[both chuckle]
Shit.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
What's this?
That's your new job.
From now on you're doing
kitchen duty with him.
And if I catch you
doing the warden,
you're going to solitary.
♪ ♪
I didn't ask for kitchen duty.
Maybe not, but I think
I know who gave it to you.
♪ ♪
I heard you went
to see William Sutter.
Someone had to tell him
to drop dead in person.
I thought we agreed
we were gonna take him on.
That was before I made us
legal counsel
for the largest energy producer
on the East Coast.
You signed Nathan Burns?
I did.
Well, I hope you know
what you're doing, Harvey,
because we could have
had them both.
Jessica, I learned my lesson.
When you lie down with dogs,
you come up with fleas,
and I'm telling you,
we did the right thing.
Then put some music on,
because we're back on the map.
To being back on the map.
To drawing a new one.
- Should we get Louis?
- Aw, come on.
He takes one sip of this,
we'll have to hear that story
about the first time
he got laid.
We'd be lucky if
that's the story we get to hear.
Wow, you guys are drinking?
You haven't even
heard my news yet.
You figured out a way
to get Gallo transferred?
Even better.
I figured out a way
to get Mike out early.
You're kidding me.
You think I came all the way
down here to bullshit you?
Well, we all know there's
no such thing as a free lunch,
Sean, so what's the catch?
He has to inform on
one of his fellow inmates.
What makes you think he can
even get close to this guy?
Oh, I don't think
that's gonna be a problem.
It's his roommate.
Listen to me, Mike's never
gonna go for this.
So why don't you tell me what
the hell you're talking about?
Kevin Miller's a smoking gun
on another case.
We tried to get him to turn
on his family but he wouldn't.
Mike gets him to turn
or figures out
how to get what we need
out of him anyway, he's free.
When do you need an answer by?
Yesterday.
And the answer needs to be yes.
[dramatic music]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man