Previously on "Suits"...
I just heard you
turned down a client
whose investment firm
is worth $2 billion.
Well, I don't give a shit
how much they're worth.
I'm not representing
William Sutter.
I didn't kill anyone.
I've been saying it
for 12 years,
and I can prove it.
Do you want to take a chance
on each other or not?
I just got a visit
from Sean Cahill.
It turns out there's a way
he can get you out.
What's the catch?
He needs you to inform
on your cellmate.
- Tell me the truth.
- He said no.
But Sean, I'm telling you,
he'll come around.
Do you know how many
strings I pulled
to put this thing in motion?
You're gonna get me out
of here like you promised.
I never promised--
Six weeks, brother,
and if I find out
you're screwing me,
you better hole up in some
dark corner of this prison.
How would you feel
about renovating my summer house
in the Hamptons?
Are you sure?
I've never been as sure
of anything in my entire life.
The whole time, you were
always gonna bring him here.
Because this is the way
to get it done.
Then why didn't you tell me
that in the first place?
Because it would've ended up
with you wanting to use Rachel.
It ended there anyway.
Now get the hell out of my way.
Harvey!
I told Rachel everything.
I'm taking the deal.
[dark music]
All right,
let's talk specifically
about what you need.
What I need is a conviction.
Obviously, but what exactly
does that look like
from my side?
It looks like a smoking gun,
'cause I've been after Sutter
for three years now.
This guy's one slippery
son of a bitch.
Wait a second.
William Sutter?
Are you kidding me?
Harvey, what's going on?
He came to me a week ago
to take him on, and I said no.
Well,
it's a good thing you did.
- No, it isn't.
- What are you talking about?
When Kevin finds out I told
his father-in-law
to drop dead,
he's never gonna trust Mike.
If you're saying what I think
you're saying,
you're not taking this man
as your client.
Yes, I am, because if I don't,
we might as well
not even be doing this.
- Then let's not do it.
- Look where we are, Sean.
We're in a car,
sneaking Mike into prison.
You pulled every string
you have to make this happen.
You're gonna pull out now?
I am, 'cause I'm not
gonna put myself
in position to collude with you.
I won't put you
in that position.
I'm in that
position right now.
No, you're not.
He isn't even representing
anybody yet.
This conversation is
completely hypothetical.
I don't need legal advice
from the convict,
and I don't need
to lose my career
because you tanked
this guy's defense.
I'm not tanking anything.
I'm gonna kick ass for him
up and down the block,
and there's no law
against me rooting for Mike
while I'm doing that.
Okay, but you cross one line
that puts me in jeopardy,
I'm gonna pull the plug
on this whole thing.
Well, Mike better get
us what we need
before I have to do that.
♪ ♪
[phone vibrates]
Hello?
Rachel.
Professor Dunbar.
- What is it?
- I know how passionate
you were
about Leonard Bailey,
but I just heard back
from the Innocence Project,
and...I'm afraid his case
doesn't qualify.
What do you mean
it doesn't qualify?
We have three different grounds
for an appeal.
And, unfortunately,
none of them revolve
around the existence of
previously undiscovered DNA.
What does that have to do
with it?
The man was railroaded.
He deserves to have
his case retried.
It has everything
to do with it,
because in a case like this,
that's the primary determinant
for whether it qualifies or not.
I don't care whether
it qualifies or not.
I promised Leonard Bailey
that I'd fight for him.
Well,
you shouldn't have done that.
Professor, I know
that we're not supposed
to become emotionally
invested in our clients,
but if we don't have
any passion,
then what's the point of trying
to help them in the first place?
Rachel, I understand this is
a difficult thing to hear,
but there's nothing I can do.
Look, I give you my word.
We'll find you a new case.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[door buzzes]
- Mike, is that you?
- Yeah, yeah.
Go back to sleep.
I'll talk to you in the morning.
Oh.
[grumbles]
How are you?
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- What was it?
- Whatever it was,
they can't find a trace of it.
Officially, it's food poisoning.
Well, I finally got the chance
to meet your buddy Harvey.
- Harvey was here?
- Mm-hmm, in this very cell.
- You're kidding me.
- I shit you not.
You should've seen him.
Thought he was gonna attack
Gallo right then and there.
- What stopped him?
- Guards.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah.
I just need to get some sleep.
♪ ♪
Well, it's good
to have you back, buddy.
Once you get used to having
someone around you can trust,
it's hard to go back.
♪ ♪
♪ Suits 6x05 ♪
Trust
Original Air Date on August 10, 2016
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
[slow rock music]
Whatever it is you're doing,
I want you to drop it
and help me buy a house
in the Hamptons.
- Excuse me?
- I said I need a large,
expensive home in the Hamptons,
preferably on the water.
Louis, I don't mean to be
your business manager,
but why are you buying
a vacation home
when the firm's
just getting back on its feet?
Because I told Tara Messer
that I have a property
out there, and I hired her
to remodel it for me.
Okay, let me get
this straight.
You want to spend
a fortune buying a home
so that you can spend
another fortune remodeling it?
It's the only logical way
that I can spend time with her.
- Is it?
- Yes.
What other way
could there possibly be?
You could just ask her out.
- Well, I'm not gonna do that.
- Why not?
- Because I'm not.
- Louis.
Jesus Christ,
why are you trying
to sabotage my relationship?
You have no relationship.
That's what I'm trying
to tell you.
I have no relationship.
I'm all alone.
Ever since Sheila rejected me,
I never thought I would
find love again,
but there is something--
I don't know.
There's just something
about this woman.
I feel like this may be
my last shot.
I get that, Louis,
and if you ask her out,
she is going to see a kind,
intelligent man
that any woman
would be lucky to be
in a relationship with.
But if you do it this way,
and she finds out,
then you lose that shot,
because she's never
gonna trust you again.
Look at me, Donna.
A woman like that...
[solemn music]
Please.
I need her to get
to know me first.
All right, Louis.
I'll help you find a house.
♪ ♪
Looking at my pictures again?
- Sorry.
- What's going on?
Nothing.
I was just...
I was just thinking
about when I asked you
what you were in for.
We got interrupted.
You never told me.
Oh, well, just as well,
'cause I don't want to
talk about it.
- Okay, why not?
- Why not?
'Cause if I wanted
to talk about it,
I'd be talking about it.
Look, I understand that
we're not
supposed to talk
about that stuff,
but when you think you might've
been poisoned by somebody,
it makes you want to know
something about the guy
you're sharing a cell with.
You saying you don't
trust me, Mike?
Kevin, I'm serious.
I've told you pretty much
everything about me,
and besides the fact that you
don't want your kids to visit,
I don't know anything about you.
Look, Mike, there's a lot
of things that I'm ready
to tell you.
I'm just not ready
to tell you that.
Okay?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Mr. Specter, you don't
have an appointment.
It's okay, Julie.
Someone calls me
a piece of shit to my face,
I want to know
what the encore is.
You here to piss on my floor?
I'm here to tell you that
I'm taking your case after all.
Who says I didn't hire
someone else
the second you turned me down?
I do, because you didn't pick
my name out of a phone book.
You came to me
because you found out
that your guy's in prison
with my guy.
- So what if I did?
- Cut the shit, William.
Your son-in-law saved Mike
from a guy I put behind bars.
That means I owe you,
and you didn't tell me about it
because you knew
I'd find out
and come crawling back
on my own.
You're hardly crawling.
I didn't as a baby,
and I'm not gonna start now.
This is the best
you're gonna get.
So are we doing this thing
together or not?
Okay.
You got me, Harvey.
Now what?
Now I go see your son-in-law.
Why the hell would you
want to do that?
Because he's in prison,
and you're facing an indictment,
which makes him the biggest
vulnerability you have.
♪ ♪
You have a call
from Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept the charges?
Yes.
Harvey, we have a problem.
- What is it?
- I tried to talk to Kevin.
I got nothing.
Well, what do you want me
to do about it?
I don't know.
It would help if I had something
to talk about other than,
"Hey, what exactly
are you in here for?"
Okay, Mike, you want
something to talk about?
I'll get you something
to talk about.
♪ ♪
Well, if it isn't
my knight in beautiful armor.
How are you, Mr. Bailey?
Please, call me Leonard.
I'm afraid I have some
bad news, Leonard.
The Innocence Project looked
over the new evidence, and...
they decided not to
take your case.
What does that mean?
It means there's
nothing else I can do.
I knew you couldn't
do shit for me.
No, no, no.
You don't understand.
They almost never take cases
without new DNA evidence,
and yours had none.
I don't care about that.
You asked me to take
a chance on you,
and now you march in here
and tell me you're giving up?
No, no, Mr. Bailey--
You said you would
fight for me.
I did fight for you.
Well, then fight
goddamn harder!
♪ ♪
I'm sorry,
and I understand
how you feel,
but there's just nothing more
that I can do.
How do you know what I feel?
You don't know what it's like
to be kept away
from your loved ones.
- Actually, I do.
- How's that?
My fiancé's in prison.
♪ ♪
How long?
- Two years.
- Two years is nothing.
It doesn't feel
like nothing to me.
What if it was forever,
Rachel?
Would you give up on him
like you did me?
I didn't give up on you.
You said you found
compelling evidence.
I also said
that it wasn't enough.
That sounds like
giving up to me.
[phone slams]
♪ ♪
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
I'm here to give you
official notice.
I'm now
William Sutter's attorney.
Congratulations. I hope
you know what you're doing.
I do, because I'm also here
to notify you that
unless you bring an indictment
in the next 48 hours,
I'm gonna sue you and the SEC
for harassing my client.
What the hell are you
talking about?
You heard me.
You've been digging
into his accounts,
hounding his employees,
and questioning his investors.
He's under investigation
for insider trading.
That's how it works.
Well, if that's how it works,
then bring on an indictment.
Ah, I see what you're doing.
Mike can't get Kevin to talk
without me bringing an action.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Oh, well, it doesn't matter,
'cause I'm not
bringing an indictment
without knowing
that I can win at trial.
And you're never
gonna win at trial
if you don't shake the trees
and see what falls.
Damn it, Harvey,
I am not colluding on this,
and you're in here
trying to get me
to bring an indictment
against your own client.
Because when you bring
that indictment,
I'm gonna beat it,
and if you don't bring it
and continue
investigating my client,
I'm gonna sue you,
which is exactly
what I'd be doing no matter
who he was.
You know what, Harvey?
You want me to bring an action?
You got one.
[upbeat jazz music]
♪ ♪
Jesus Christ, there you are.
What's going on
with the house hunt?
I am on top of it, Louis.
Well, it doesn't look
like you're on top of it.
It looks like you're drinking
a goddamn cup of coffee.
Maybe that's because I was
on the Internet all night
trying to find houses
for you because I knew
that nothing would ever meet
your insane specifications.
- Is that true?
- Not one word.
Goddamn it, Donna,
this is important.
Right now there are hundreds of
men out there with beach houses,
and Tara could be meeting
any one of them.
Right now I wish I was
meeting any one of them.
Donna, I thought you
understood this isn't a joke.
I know it isn't, Louis,
and that's why I haven't sent
you anything I've seen so far,
because I haven't found
the right thing yet.
And what if I said I lost
confidence in your ability
to know what I'm looking
for in any given situation?
Then I would say
that that is exactly
why I've been avoiding you,
and if you had any
self-awareness at all,
you would stop bothering me
and instead trust me for once.
Well, we both know
that's never gonna happen.
Well, then, why don't you go
find your own house, Louis?
[dramatic music]
- Gin.
- Again?
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Don't play cards with a guy
with a photographic memory.
How many times I have to tell
you I'm still gonna beat you?
Deal.
Sorry to interrupt
your Go Fish.
There's a Harvey Specter
here to see you.
Saved by the bell.
Not you, Ross.
Miller.
♪ ♪
Mind if I ask why you're here
to see me instead of Mike?
Because I heard he's okay,
and I'm not just
Mike's attorney anymore.
I'm yours.
I don't need
your help with Gallo.
I'm not talking about Gallo.
William Sutter came to me
to represent him.
I turned him down until
I found out that his son-in-law
is the one who's been
watching Mike's back.
Well, I appreciate that,
but what does that
have to do with me?
I don't make it a habit
of representing people
I can't trust.
You saying you can't trust me?
I'm saying the SEC
thinks William's firm,
the one that you worked for,
is breaking the law.
So I need to know right now,
when they come at you,
what are you gonna say?
I'm gonna say
the same thing I did
when they came at me
the last time.
My father-in-law's innocent.
Is that it or can I go?
One more thing, Kevin.
An indictment's coming down
any second,
and once it does,
that makes you
every single inmate's
ticket out of here.
So if you ever have a doubt
about William's innocence,
keep it to your goddamn self.
♪ ♪
Kevin, talk to you
for a second?
Yeah, sure.
What's going on, George?
- It's about your roommate.
- What about him?
You got some nerve
playing cards here
while my life is wasting away.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about that motion
you were supposed
to file for me.
Then you better get your facts
straight, because I did file it.
Yeah, and it got
bounced right back.
- What? No, that's not possible.
- It is possible.
While you were taking your
little siesta in the infirmary,
I got an email that said
the damn thing
wasn't even filed right.
Oh, goddamn it.
Looks like you can't
keep your promises.
No, I can keep it.
This is just some procedural
mix-up, all right?
But I'm gonna need
to use your phone.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'm telling you that
I can have this thing
taken care of.
I just need to make
a phone call.
What's wrong
with the goddamn phones in here?
Nothing, but I already
used it today,
which means I can't use it
for another two days.
So unless you want to waste
that time playing cards with me,
which I guarantee you'll lose,
you'll give me your phone
right now.
I like you.
You got balls.
You know what?
So do I, which is why
I can take this out in front
of any guard in here
and know I'm not
getting in any trouble.
Don't forget that,
and get that shit handled.
♪ ♪
Harvey, I have
something for you.
- What is it?
- It's from Sean Cahill,
and I need you to take a look
at it right away.
Why? I know what
an indictment looks like.
It's not an indictment,
Harvey.
He's suspending William Sutter's
trading license.
Get Cahill on the phone.
Sir, I have Harvey Specter
on the line.
Oh, you've got
to be shitting me.
Harvey, what can I do for you?
You can explain to me what
the hell you're up to,
suspending my client's
trading license.
You wanted to get
the ball rolling.
This gets the ball rolling.
This isn't what I wanted.
And I don't take orders
from you.
And I'm not gonna be able
to stop this in court,
which means
Sutter's gonna fire me.
Then maybe you didn't
understand my initial position.
I don't give a shit
if you get fired or not.
You thought that you needed
to represent Sutter,
so you went ahead
and did what you needed to do.
I thought I didn't want
to bring an indictment
before I had enough to win,
so I did what I needed to do,
but what I need to do right now
is finish this
delicious ham sandwich,
which means the next time
that I talk to you,
I expect it to be in court.
[loud crunching]
♪ ♪
Hey, what's going on?
What do you mean,
what's going on?
I mean, we're playing cards,
and Harvey's here to see you,
and then next thing I know,
you're giving me
some death stare,
and you come out here.
Nothing's going on.
Well, what did Harvey want?
He's representing
my father-in-law,
which means now
he's also representing me.
That good enough for you?
All right, Kevin,
what's with the attitude?
I'm on your side.
Are you?
'Cause Harvey said I shouldn't
trust anyone in here,
and as far as I'm concerned,
that includes you.
What? Hey, that doesn't
make any sense.
You know what doesn't
make any sense?
One minute Gallo is your enemy,
and the next minute,
he's handing you his cell phone
like he's your best friend.
I'm trying to help him
get out of here,
which is good for both of us.
Is that what you were doing
last night outside of prison?
You were helping him get out?
Is that what was going on?
Kevin, come on.
I was worried
about you, cellmate.
I thought you were
in real trouble,
but they wouldn't
let me see you,
so I asked a friend of mine
who works in the infirmary
to check on you,
and ten minutes ago he told me
that he's pretty damn sure
you were gone
for at least three hours.
♪ ♪
Well, what do you have
to say about that?
I was gone because
I was in the hospital.
That's the first
I'm hearing about it.
Yeah, and why
would I tell you that?
Why wouldn't you?
Something's going on here,
and I can tell.
All right, Kevin.
You want to know what happened?
I went to the hospital because
Harvey paid the doctor because
he didn't trust that I would
make it through the night
in here, and I didn't tell you
because I didn't want
to put you in a position
where you'd have to lie for me.
You know what?
That sounds like a whole lot
of bullshit to me.
Yeah, you know what, Kevin?
I think it's pretty
goddamn funny
that you don't trust me
when you're the one
that won't even tell me
what you're in here for.
♪ ♪
No. No. No.
Shit, no.
Not now, Harvey.
I'm in the middle
of something important.
Whatever it is,
it's not as important as this.
What is this?
It's notice to suspend William
Sutter's trading license.
The question is,
what can be done about it?
- Nothing can be done about it.
- What do you mean,
nothing can be done about it?
You're supposed to be
the financial wizard.
I am, and I'm telling you
that this kind of thing
is at the SEC's discretion.
They have unlimited power
to suspend
trading licenses up to 90 days.
- Goddamn it.
- It's only 90 days.
90 days gets me fired.
Well, it's gonna
be okay, Harvey.
I mean, I know things
have been rough around here,
but business is picking up.
This isn't about
business, Louis.
It's about Mike.
[tense music]
What are you not
telling me, Harvey?
I'm not gonna tell you
the details,
because I'm not gonna
put you at risk,
but I have a chance
to get Mike out early,
and if I lose this motion,
it's over.
Well, then I'll figure out
a way to get it done.
Thank you, Louis.
♪ ♪
[cell phone buzzing]
This is Harvey Specter.
Harvey, it's me.
Mike, what the hell are you
doing with a private phone?
What the hell are you doing
representing Kevin?
You were the one having
trouble getting him to open up.
And you thought telling him
not to trust anyone in here
was the answer to that?
Look, I did that
to get him to trust me,
because if he trusts me,
he trusts you.
Yeah, well,
you didn't count on one thing.
He knows I wasn't in
the infirmary the whole night.
What?
How the hell does he know that?
Some guy he knows works there.
I told him some story about
you taking me to the hospital,
but he's not buying it.
Then you figure out a way
to make him buy it.
Fine, I'll think of something,
but that's not my only problem.
What now?
Gallo's filing came back.
It needs to be filed in person
and it needs to be filed
by his attorney of record.
You got to be shitting me.
You want me
to represent that animal?
If you don't,
then getting Kevin to talk
is gonna be
the least of my problems.
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Rachel, I need your help
with something.
What can I do?
I need you to draft
a parole application
for Frank Gallo.
I thought Mike was doing that.
There was a problem,
which is also why
I need you to draw up
an engagement letter
for me to be Gallo's attorney.
Done.
Hey, what is it?
I heard you get upset
with Louis earlier,
and now you're coming
to me about Gallo.
So...I just need to know
if you think
this whole Cahill thing's
really gonna work.
- Rachel--
- Harvey,
just tell me the truth.
Look, I don't know
if it's gonna work or not,
but I do know
I'm not gonna stop trying.
♪ ♪
Got to say, you don't look
so bad for a guy
who blacked out
in the yard the other day.
Yeah, they took
good care of me.
Well, I'm glad you're okay.
What's on your mind?
I need you to get a message
to the warden for me.
Sure.
I'll bring it to him
at our weekly brunch.
What would you like
for it to say?
- I'm serious.
- I don't care what you are.
You want to get a message
to the warden,
you go through
the proper channels
and get it to him yourself.
I can't go through
the proper channels,
because nobody can know
about it.
All right, Mike,
tell me what's going on.
I made a deal
to get out of here early.
What kind of deal?
The kind where
I inform on someone.
Someone?
[sighs]
Kevin Miller.
- Oh, Mike, come on.
- Julius, let me explain.
I don't need you to explain.
You are betraying your cellmate,
who you came to me to protect.
No, what I am doing
is putting away someone
who is out there doing
worse things than I ever did.
So I don't need your judgment.
I need your help.
I'm sorry, it's not my job to
help you do something like this.
No, it's your job to help me
prepare for life after prison.
Well, this is gonna make
life after prison
come a hell of a lot faster.
Well, fine,
you want to do this?
You go ahead and do it, but
I am not gonna be complicit.
You know what?
You talk a big goddamn game
about trusting you,
but what does that trust mean?
Now, I need to get
to the warden,
and I need to do it
without the guards finding out.
Can you help me or not?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Rachel, what are you
doing here so late?
Professor,
do you have a minute?
Of course.
Yeah, sit down.
I went to see Leonard Bailey
this morning
to tell him we were turning
our backs on him.
No one's turning their back
on him, Rachel.
There are just better cases.
No offense,
but that's bullshit.
- Excuse me?
- You read his file.
There's enough evidence in there
for him to get a new trial,
and instead we're gonna
let him rot on death row.
Rachel, I understand
how you feel,
but there are some things that--
I feel like I dropped
your class to take this case.
And I told you
I'd get you another one.
I don't want another one.
I want this one.
Rachel, I cannot provide you
with the resources
and the backing anymore.
Okay, so what if I were able
to provide my own resources
and--and to get the supervision
of a qualified lawyer?
What are you talking about?
I work at Pearson
Specter Litt, Professor.
They've been known to take
a pro Bono case
from time to time.
♪ ♪
Okay.
Okay, you win, Rachel,
but this is highly irregular.
I don't care.
That's not a good enough reason
to turn our backs
on Leonard Bailey.
♪ ♪
Well, don't ever question
my financial wizardry again.
Let's have it.
I was banging my head against
the wall, trying to figure out
a way to stop the suspension,
but then it dawned on me.
We don't need to stop it.
If we can turn Sutter's firm
into the subsidiary
of a separate holding company,
we can find someone else
to execute the trades for him.
- Beautiful.
- Yeah, but the only issue is,
we need to find traders
that are willing
to bankroll the son of a bitch,
given his reputation.
- Well, that's not gonna be
a problem.
- No, Harvey,
this is not nothing.
Nobody wants to work
with this guy.
- You're forgetting
our new friends across the hall.
- What?
What, are you kidding me?
You think that asshole's
gonna say yes to me?
- It's okay.
I know who he'll say yes to.
♪ ♪
- Hey, Harvey,
I know how tough it's been
not having Mike here,
and I just want to let you know
that I miss him too.
- I appreciate that, Louis,
but you didn't have to say it,
because actions speak louder
than words,
and you doing this says it all.
♪ ♪
Harvey, I've been looking
for you all day.
Well, here I am.
Then maybe you can tell me
why all of a sudden
we're representing
William Sutter.
- I changed my mind.
- You changed your mind?
You told me taking Sutter on
would be like selling your soul,
and now you're doing
a complete 180.
Jessica, I--
No, Harvey,
I'm not saying I don't like it.
I just want to know
what's going on.
Sutter's the one
Cahill's after.
Oh, you've got
to be kidding me.
I shit you not.
Oh, well, I get it.
You give him
a full-throttle defense,
gain his trust,
and hope to God Mike
cuts his legs out.
Exactly.
What?
Is he gonna give us
his investment business?
Not until after we win.
Which we're hoping we don't.
- Jessica, I have to do this.
- Harvey, relax.
I'm on board.
It pays the bills,
and we can leverage it
into more business anyway,
but we'd better
leverage it fast,
because losing this case
might be good for Mike,
but it's not gonna
be good for us,
and I don't know about you,
but I'd like to get back on top.
There's nothing I'd like more,
which is why I came in here.
What do you need?
I need you to get something
from those traders.
[dramatic music]
[door buzzes]
On your feet, Ross.
You're going to solitary.
What? Wait,
what are you talking about?
You heard me.
24 hours, let's go.
No, I'm not going anywhere
with you until you tell me
what's going on.
You'll go where I tell you to,
or you'll get acquainted
with this.
Listen to me.
I just want to know why--
Next question
makes it 48 hours.
You coming or not?
♪ ♪
What did you do?
Jessica--good, I caught you.
Rachel, what is it?
Do you remember
my Innocence Project case?
How could I not?
Badass Rachel.
Well, thank you.
So I took it, but now they're
saying that it doesn't qualify.
Let me guess.
You want us to take it on
as a pro Bono.
All I need is one hour
a week of supervision,
and if I need to appear
in court, you come with me.
I know that that's a lot
to ask, but--
Rachel, I wish I could tell
you I had an extra hour to give,
but I don't.
Jessica, please.
If you would
just come with me
and meet this man--
No, this is my point.
I just found out we have
less time than I thought we did
to get this firm
back on its feet,
and I can't afford to spend
one minute on anything else.
But, I mean, really--
Rachel, I'm sorry.
Now if you'll excuse me.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
Thank your counselor,
Mr. Rowe.
- I will.
- You must trust him a lot
to let him in on
your little arrangement.
I do.
He helped me, even though
he doesn't approve of this.
Sounds like you don't either.
- It's not up to me
to approve or not.
Is that what you
came down here to tell me?
No, I came down here
to tell you I've been doing this
a long time,
and I've seen a lot
of inmates come and go.
These kind of deals, they don't
always work out so well.
You saying you think I'll be
here for the whole two years?
I'm saying I hope it doesn't
turn out even worse than that.
♪ ♪
I thought the markets
were closed.
Did you ever see
"Wall Street"?
Money never sleeps.
What's this?
Have a look.
Let me get this straight.
I hire you,
and the first thing you do
is come to me for a favor?
I came to you for a favor
when you were my tenant.
Now, as your lawyer, I am coming
to you with an opportunity.
What are you talking about?
That's not
a charitable donation.
You do this,
you'll get paid for it.
- How much?
- Enough.
How do I know I'm not
leaving something on the table?
Because I never leave
anything on the table.
All right.
You know, I don't get it.
You're obviously
a big-time attorney,
and now you're subletting to me.
What the hell happened here?
- You don't know?
- Why would I?
- Google it.
- That bad?
We hired a lawyer.
Turns out he was a fraud.
It ruined our reputation.
Turned out to be a fraud,
or you knew he was a fraud?
Good night, Stu.
See you in the morning.
♪ ♪
[door buzzes, opens]
Warden, what are you--
what are you doing?
Did you know Mike Ross
left the prison grounds
the other night?
- What?
- Don't bullshit me.
Did you know his lawyer,
who I understand
is now also your lawyer,
paid someone to get him
out of here?
I don't know
anything about it.
I suppose if I asked you
who he paid,
you'd have the same answer.
I find out you're lying,
next time,
you are gonna be
the one in solitary,
and it won't be just one night.
♪ ♪
[door slams shut]
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- What?
- I'm just thinking about
when this asshole finds out
you're gonna blow his bullshit
suspension out of the water.
William, I am gonna
blow it out of the water,
but I'm gonna need you
to sign this first.
What the hell is
Stevens Investment Group?
It's the company you're
trading through from now on.
Bullshit.
They own me?
They don't own anything.
They control you on paper,
and unless you want to shut down
for the next 90 days,
this is what you have to do.
Well, bullshit.
What are you gonna do
if that guy indicts me,
cut a deal where I plead guilty,
and I get probation?
'Cause if this is
what you consider winning,
I might as well
find myself another lawyer.
Okay, gentlemen,
I'm ready to hear arguments,
but I have to tell you,
unless Congress passed
a new law last night,
this suspension stands.
That's okay, Your Honor.
My client's firm is now
the subsidiary
of a holding company
with a different
trading license.
- What?
- It's all right here.
In that case, I move
to have that
company's license suspended.
And that, right there,
is why I'd like to ask the court
to have Mr. Cahill removed
from any investigation
regarding my client
in the future.
Are you out of your mind?
We have an antagonistic
history, Your Honor.
Everyone knows it,
and this action
is nothing more than a stunt
designed to punish me
through my client.
This is ridiculous.
I've been investigating
William Sutter for 18 months.
And in the last 18 months,
he took no action,
and then yesterday,
when I informed him
I am Mr. Sutter's attorney,
within five hours
he suspends his license,
and now he's trying
to do it again.
That's what I call a win.
Mr. Cahill,
this doesn't look good.
I'm inclined
to take you off this case.
Your Honor,
Mr. Specter is right.
We have history,
but I've been involved
in this case
a lot longer than he has.
So if anyone has to be
thrown out for a conflict,
it is him, not me.
I'm not going anywhere,
Your Honor.
Then let Mr. Sutter waive
any claims
to conflict altogether,
unless, of course,
you want to set a precedent
that any time a defendant
doesn't like his prosecutor,
all he has to do
is hire a lawyer
he's gone up against before.
Mr. Sutter, would you like
to keep your attorney
or hire another one,
because I am not
taking Mr. Cahill off this case.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Harvey's my guy, Your Honor.
Then unless there's
some other issue,
the court has a full docket.
[gavel bangs]
♪ ♪
Guard tells you
you have a visitor,
doesn't say who it is,
you start thinking
maybe Angelina Jolie
opened your letters after all.
Sit down, Gallo.
You here to make
more false accusations?
I'm here to tell you that,
as of this minute,
I'm your new attorney.
Come again?
You need someone
to file that motion.
I'm that someone.
What if I don't want
your help?
Well, then you can rot in here
for the rest of your sentence.
It's actually
kind of funny, isn't it,
you fighting to get me out
when you fought so hard
to put me away.
Must kill you.
Makes me sick to my stomach,
but I'm gonna live with it,
because you're gonna give me
something in return.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
Until this thing goes through,
not only are you gonna
keep your hands off Mike,
you're gonna be his personal
protector in here.
- Bullshit.
- Not bullshit.
He so much as twists
an ankle in the yard,
I'll withdraw that motion.
Now, aren't you forgetting
a little something, champ?
I don't need you
to handle this thing for me.
Now that I know what's what,
I'll get my own attorney.
Yeah, you do that,
and I'll tell the courts
that you just admitted to me
that you tried to poison Mike.
You know how much time that's
gonna add to your sentence?
- I didn't do shit to him!
- Good for you.
Who do you think
they're gonna believe,
a former prosecutor like me
or an informant convict
like you?
Of course, if I'm your attorney,
I can't tell them any of that.
[chuckles]
You son of a bitch.
You set me up.
I sure as hell did.
So it's up to you.
You in or you out?
[dramatic music]
Can I talk to you a second?
What is it, Louis?
I can't find a house.
A house?
What house?
I don't know anything
about a house,
certainly not for a person
who doesn't have
any confidence in my ability
to know what he's looking for
in a given situation.
Donna, please, can't we just
pretend that I didn't say
what I said, like we usually do?
No, Louis, we can't,
because I need to know
that you have spent at least
one second contemplating
what your little
outburst was about.
I know what it was about.
Really?
What is that?
♪ ♪
I miss you, Donna.
I miss having you
as my secretary.
♪ ♪
I miss you too, Louis.
And don't get me wrong.
I'm not saying
Gretchen's not great.
Who would?
It's just--I'm just saying
she's not you.
- Who is?
- Nobody.
♪ ♪
Was this the kind of thing
you're looking for?
Oh, my God, it's perfect.
Is it still available?
- An offer went in this morning.
- We have to beat it.
No, Louis, we don't.
That offer was yours.
♪ ♪
Did they take it?
We find out tomorrow.
[laughs]
Donna--
No.
♪ ♪
[door buzzes]
[sighs]
I'm sorry about what happened
with the warden.
Yeah.
If you need anything--
I'll let you know.
Look, I didn't--
I didn't tell them
what you told me
about Harvey getting you out.
I need you to know that.
It's important to me.
Yeah, whatever you say, Kevin.
I know I haven't told you
why I'm in here, Mike...
But you don't understand.
From the second I got here,
I've had to watch
what I say, every single word,
and every morning I get up,
and I remind myself
not to say the wrong thing
to the wrong person,
and every night
I go to bed and think,
"Another day down
where I didn't."
Yeah, you think I don't know
what that's like?
I've been living a lie
every day for years.
Yeah, but you were
just protecting yourself.
You don't have a family.
Kevin, what did you do?
I got in a fight with my wife.
It was...
it was bad.
We said things to each other
we never said before.
I went out.
I got drunk.
I got into my car,
and I almost killed someone.
Next thing I knew,
I woke up in an ambulance,
looking up at a police officer.
♪ ♪
What?
I made one stupid,
stupid mistake.
♪ ♪
And it's gonna cost me
three years with my family,
and it's not just
the special things, man.
I'm missing a thousand chances
to hug my kids in the morning...
[choking up]
And kiss my wife good night,
all because I couldn't
control myself.
♪ ♪
What were you fighting
with your wife about?
What do you mean, you were
trying to protect your family?
Kevin.
[crying]
I--yeah, I can't.
I just can't.
♪ ♪
Okay.
I'll do it.
- Excuse me?
- Your pro Bono.
Bring me the file
tomorrow morning.
Jessica, I'm sorry.
Can I just ask why?
What does it matter?
It matters to me.
I've been out all day,
trying to drum up business,
and it hasn't been easy.
So from now on,
when people Google our name,
I'd rather they see,
"innocent man freed
by Pearson Specter"
than "Manhattan law firm
hires a fraud."
[stirring music]
Thank you.
Good night, Rachel.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here, Sean?
Oh, you know
what I'm doing here.
What were you thinking,
trying to get me
thrown off my own case?
He was coming at me.
I had to do something
to keep his trust.
Well, for your information,
if I get thrown off this case,
that deal that you don't know
about getting that certain
someone out early
doesn't exist anymore.
- You think I don't know that?
- No, I don't think you do,
because if I hadn't pulled
that shit out of my ass,
this whole thing
would've been for nothing.
What are you so pleased
with yourself about?
Nothing.
It's just...
you didn't want me
to take this case,
and now you're getting
pissed at me
because I'm too good a job
defending my client.
Now that you put it
that way...
It was a good fix, Sean.
♪ ♪
- It was a good move, Harvey.
- Want to get a drink?
Why don't we
just have one here?
This might be the last one that
we have together for a long time.
Why?
As of right now,
you have no action
pending against my client.
But as of tomorrow, I do,
'cause those indictments
are coming down in the morning.
[glasses clink]
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man