Harvard trivia,
the lightning round.
[Snaps] Go.
Pulitzer prizes. 46.
- Nobel peace prizes.
- Five.
What is the oldest book in
the Harvard library collection?
- The Bible.
- Wrong.
The gutenberg Bible.
Everyone knows
it's the gutenberg Bible.
Yes, but you didn't say it.
The rules dictate
you must be precise,
as the law is
a very precise endeavor.
- How many U.S. pr...
- Eight.
That's not fair, you didn't
even finish the question.
And yet it's right.
The question was gonna be
"how many U.S. presidents
attended Harvard?"
- You want names?
- No, we get it.
Final round. Ross ahead by one.
One question each.
Points are double.
Double 'cause he wants
to keep you in the game, Seth.
Bring it on, Ross.
I bleed crimson.
Oh, venomous banter.
This is adorable, I love it.
Ross, square pizza.
Where do you get it?
Are you kidding?
Any self-respecting
Harvard alumnus
would know the answer to that.
Late night studying
and you want square pizza,
where do you go?
Um...
You know,
I'm more of a burger guy.
I study better on protein.
[General laughter, boos]
I mean, that's just...
Pathetic.
It's Pinocchio's.
Mm, I answer mine, I win.
Yeah, I know.
How many current
U.S. supreme court justices
are from our Alma mater?
[Overlapping chatter]
Everybody knows that.
Five.
Hah! See, I told you
Keller was better.
[Cheers and applause]
You owe me 20.
- Awesome.
- Got anything to say, Ross?
Nope.
Just that the answer's wrong.
Scalia, Roberts,
Kennedy, Breyer, Kagan.
- Ginsberg.
- Ruth Bader Ginsberg
went to Columbia.
She graduated from Columbia,
after she attended Harvard
for two years.
The question was phrased
"how many justices were
from Harvard?"
Well, she was on
the Harvard law review.
And when she arrived
at Columbia as a transfer,
she was from Harvard.
The rules dictate
that you must be precise,
as the law is
a precise endeavor.
[Broken applause]
Told you Ross was hot.
[Cheers]
Congratulations.
This is what you get
for second place.
To the Victor belongs
the spoils.
A case.
Pro Bono, one of your very own.
Congratulations, enjoy.
Louis knows.
- Louis knows what?
- My dirty little secret.
- You're Canadian?
- Ha, ha, ha, ha.
No, he knows that
I didn't go to Harvard.
No, he doesn't.
How can you
be so sure about that?
Because you're walking
with me right now.
He did this whole
Harvard trivia thing,
and then he brought up
this pizza...
Doesn't mean he knows.
Look, I think we need to hack
into Harvard's system
or something.
You know, put my records in.
I can't,
I'm booked this weekend.
I'm breaking into fort knox.
I gotta return
some stolen doubloons.
Okay, hilarious. I'm serious.
Listen, nobody's
gonna check into your past
unless you give them reason to.
Louis is devious,
but he's not bold.
He won't think we did this.
Because he'd never
think to do it himself.
Doubloons?
The ridiculousness of
your suggestion
warranted the use of
a silly word.
Got it.
[Soft knocking]
Was that Quentin Sainz
I just saw leaving?
Mm-hmm. You know him?
I know of him.
Why was he holding your hands?
Kissing them?
What are you implying, Harvey?
I don't know, maybe
you two are going steady.
I was implying
that it looked like
he was grateful to you
for taking his case.
Good, 'cause that's
exactly what it was.
That's a bad move.
We may make money
billing out on their defense,
but when we lose...
Which we will... It's gonna
hurt us in the long run.
- How do you know we'll lose?
- Because it's my job to know.
And his company's ALS
wonder drug is killing people.
ALS is incurable.
And everyone
who is taking that drug
is going to die anyway.
Hm. That's your defense?
If he kills them a little
faster, it's a public service?
Our defense is
those allegations are untrue.
He has taken
this story all over town,
and not a single firm thinks
he has a case.
Which is why he came to me.
Because he wants someone
who believes in him.
And what is it exactly
that makes you believe in him?
Well, I got to know
his character pretty well
during the time
that we were married.
Quentin is
expecting you tomorrow.
[Ima Robot's Greenback Boogie]
♪ See the money wanna stay
for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feels ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Being busy, so I'm busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Yes, hey, hey,
I like to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
- You forgot this last night.
- I didn't forget that.
I have no intention of
taking this case.
Though, I did get you this.
- What is it?
- A wedding gift.
I'm sorry it's so late,
but it's hard to be on time
when I never
knew you were married.
Are you seeing anyone, Harvey?
Hm?
You don't wanna tell me,
and I don't really care.
Because you and I share
the same trait
of keeping our
personal lives personal.
You were married.
It happened when you were at
Harvard, didn't work out.
We were too dedicated
to our careers,
and that's all
I'm going to say about it.
Okay. You're right.
It's none of my business.
I'm still not taking this case.
Why is that?
Because sometimes I do things
that my clients don't like.
And if their ex-wives
are looking over my shoulders,
that's not really a problem.
But when their ex-wives
are also my managing partner,
that hamstrings me.
And if I'm gonna turn
this loser into a winner,
I can't be hamstrung.
I can't have that.
Do what you gotta do.
- You won't interfere?
- What did I just say?
Do you have any idea how hard
it is to develop a new drug
if you're not Pfizer,
or Amgen, or Merck?
This is important, Harvey.
If Quentin came to you looking
for someone to trust him,
why aren't you handling
this case yourself?
That's none of your concern.
Well, I'm not asking you
that as your colleague,
I'm asking you
as Quentin's attorney.
After Quentin and I separated,
he started seeing
one of his research consultants.
Lisa. They're still together.
But he never married her.
She doesn't want me
on the case.
Oh, terrific.
You're sticking me with
a losing case,
and a girlfriend
who isn't gonna like me
anymore than she likes you.
Well, I'm sure
it's not the first time
someone hasn't liked you,
Harvey.
[Retreating footsteps]
Who doesn't like me?
Picture the devil
without the charm.
Okay, so Karinski owned
this building for two years?
Yeah, then things got bad.
Three below, the heat went out
and I nearly froze to death.
Then a gas leak in my stove.
You could smell the damn thing,
but he said it was fine.
I called for a month,
then I had to replace it myself.
Why didn't you just move?
This is the apartment
that I grew up in.
It's the only place
I've ever known.
I don't have
any brothers or sisters.
My parents...
Not with me anymore.
I'm not leaving the
one connection I have to them.
You said you weren't sleeping.
Are you stressed out, or...?
- Bedbugs.
- No.
My place is literally
crawling with them.
Could you sleep knowing the
minute you turn out the light,
they're coming for you?
No, I couldn't.
Well, Karinski won't do
anything about it without proof,
and I can't get someone
from the city down
to verify they're there.
Don't worry. I can.
Two weeks. Next Thursday.
I-I-I-I don't think
that you heard me.
I need someone
down there today.
- Two weeks, next Thursday.
- Okay.
Uh, I'd like to speak
to your supervisor, please.
You can do that next Wednesday.
Okay, glenda, let me
tell you what I'm gonna do
between now
and next Wednesday...
I know exactly
what you're gonna do.
You're gonna do what
every lawyer threatens to do.
You're gonna
file a 409/3 grievance
claiming that I did
not fulfill my obligation
to promptly direct you
to my supervisor.
A grievance that will
be passed on to my supervisor
next Wednesday.
No, what I'm gonna do
is hire a private investigator
to look into
every aspect of your life
from the day you were born
until next Tuesday.
And then I'm gonna use
whatever it is they find
to make you wish
that your biggest problem
was keeping this job
that you seem to hate so much.
Yeah, I'm not like
every other lawyer, glenda.
What did you say your name was?
Specter.
Harvey Specter.
- You're a baseball fan?
- Oh, yeah.
Then I assume you know
Lou gehrig was a bad man.
They didn't call him
the iron horse for nothing.
Then he got ALS.
You know what it did to him?
His hands locked up,
then his legs,
his speech,
eventually his breathing.
Couldn't control 'em.
His mind knew what it wanted,
but his body...
He was trapped inside,
unable to do anything.
Even today, you get ALS,
within three to five years,
you die.
Or sooner, if someone takes
your drug and their liver fails.
Our drug makes people's
remaining years better,
and it doubles
their life expectancy.
Except for the people
who's livers are failing.
- You don't...
- Lisa.
[Whispers] It's okay.
I can see why Jessica likes you.
You cut through the bullshit.
That's something
I always loved about her.
She just does it with
a little less charm than I do.
Isn't she
a little taller than you?
- It's the heels.
- Let me tell you what it takes
to get a drug approved today.
We were $139 million
into development
before we ever hit the shelves.
We jumped through
every hoop they threw at us,
and we proved our drug
was safe for eight years.
So you're saying
these claims are baseless?
We're talking
about six terminal patients
with a wide array of
medical issues
and they're saying
my company's drug caused this?
They were drinking coffee
on the Titanic.
I don't think that put
Leonardo Dicaprio in the water.
Since Jessica vouched for you,
I'm gonna go ahead and
believe what you're telling me.
But since these other firms
determined you have exposure,
here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna pay them.
We're gonna pay them
a little bit of money
so you can keep saving lives,
because if we drag this out,
people won't think of your drug
as a way to save lives,
they'll think of it as
a death sentence.
The guy from
the housing department's
gonna be here in
about five minutes.
How did you manage that?
You know, they're
actually pretty receptive
when you explain
the situation to them.
That's what you have to do
to prevent the spread.
I had to get rid of most
of my things...
Clothes,
record collection, books.
I had a first edition
catcher in the rye,
you know what that was worth?
No.
The bugs can live dormant
for 18 months.
You just have
to throw everything out.
[Door opening]
- Frank!
- Karinski.
- You're here.
- Yes.
I live here.
Funny you should mention that,
'cause you haven't
paid rent in four months,
so I wasn't sure.
I haven't paid rent
because you haven't...
Frank has withheld rent
because the apartment
is not habitable.
New York housing code,
sub-chapter two, article four
section 27-20...
Hey, no rent, no apartment.
That's my code.
But if you
want something legal...
There's a court order.
You got three days to get out.
Or the sheriff's department will
empty the place for you.
Have a nice day.
You're late.
Look, it was
Louis' pro Bono, I...
Hey, that's my suit.
My extra suit from my office.
Yeah, it's Louis' fault.
I went to the client's place,
it was overrun with bedbugs,
so I went back to the office...
You tracked bedbugs
into my office?
- No.
- You walked in there naked?
No, Donna met me in
the downstairs men's room...
Okay, Donna's fired, and
you're buying me an extra suit.
By the way,
that's a three-piece suit.
Where's the vest?
Yeah, I've been meaning to
talk to you about that.
Vests? Really?
Says the guy
with the bike helmet.
Uh, safety first.
[Horn honking] Come on.
[Sighs]
Ah, the house that
Amylinx built.
Nice. Very nice.
Collin Church, Mr. Sainz
and Mr. Specter,
lately arrived to
our little legal dispute.
You say legal dispute,
I say shakedown.
Always a fine line between
the two, n'est pas?
Look, we can
sit here and posture
about the strengths
and weaknesses of our cases,
but frankly, that's gonna
bore the hell out of me.
Seriously?
- It could be much lower.
- It could be much higher.
Then let's pretend
it's just right.
My client's lives are
being cut short.
And according to
accepted calculations,
the current value of a life
is $7.9 million.
You're not even
offering pennies on that.
Those happen
to be e.P.A. Calculations
based on
a full life expectancy.
Adjusted for plaintiffs
who's expectancy
is just a fragment of this,
yields a value of $143,427.
Approximately.
What your child fails
to understand is that
for someone with only
three to five years to live,
each day is
worth infinitely more.
But the real crux
is the punitive damages.
Because if your client
wants to sell me the idea
that he didn't know about
these side effects years ago,
I'm not buying it.
Which is why
we want $250 million.
- What?
- Quentin.
No, man. This is outrageous.
Do you know what you're doing?
You're bankrupting this company
and taking away years of life
from real people
who are walking, talking,
and breathing easier
because of the drug we make.
I don't represent those people.
- My clients...
- Have tenuous claims at best.
And unless one of your six
is Rupert Murdoch,
you're out of your mind.
[Sighs]
Okay.
You printed that?
Well, not yet. But I will.
You realize that's libelous.
Maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
But after it runs,
you and I both know,
it won't much matter.
We're done here.
I don't take to extortion.
I'm not gonna be bullied by
an ambulance-chaser,
no matter how nice his suit.
It is nice, isn't it?
Italian. And it fits.
$250 million, Mr. Sainz.
I'll give you four days.
Church wants to play, we play.
[Thud]
I have housing court
in the morning.
It's housing court.
Your grandmother could win.
- [Sighs]
- Let's see just how real
his clients'
liver problems are.
And if they are real,
we suggest they're from
the disease itself,
or they took the wrong dose,
or they took a cocktail
of combined drugs.
Also, I wanna see
Quentin's company financials.
I already asked for them once.
I want you to call them
and follow-up.
I wanna know everything
Church could go after.
So we've gone from
settlement to scorched earth.
I didn't feel like writing
a $1/4 billion check.
- It's a negotiation.
- Exactly.
That's why I'm arming myself
for the next round.
By digging into Quentin?
I'm a boy scout.
I like to be prepared.
Hmm.
So you think
you'll look like a boy scout
by putting dying people
on the stand
and tearing them apart?
[Thuds] Mm.
You're gonna
look like an asshole.
For every one they claim
has a side effect,
we have 600 who don't.
And if I need to look like
an asshole to convince the jury
that hundreds are
more important than the one,
I'm not gonna lose
a minute's sleep over it.
Well, I have court
in the morning.
Oh, I'm... I'm not clear.
Was this a conversation with
my managing partner
or my client's ex-wife?
You need to
settle this case, Harvey.
Which I will do
if you stay out of it...
As you promised.
Make it go away.
- Rachel.
- Go away.
- I need to talk to you.
- Oh, oh.
Who's picking on you now, Mikey?
Mom and dad are fighting.
Harvey and Jessica.
What do you care?
Oh, I'm just rattled.
My first trial tomorrow
in housing court.
Housing court?
I could win at housing court.
You'll be fine.
- [Sighs]
- But not if you wear that suit.
Carvello versus
Karinski properties.
So how does this usually work?
Uh, well, usually
the trial starts,
and there's the judge,
and then... You know,
people say things.
You've never done
this before, have you?
Well,
I never drove a car before
the first time I drove one,
and I'm still here, aren't I?
[Sighs]
This is your first time?
I'm your first?
Don't worry, I promise
not to be gentle.
Frank. It's nice to see you.
One last time.
If it pleases the court...
It pleases the court
to decide who speaks and when.
I'll sit down.
We're talking about $4,000
in withheld rent pas...
Yes, your honor.
But we have receipts
for repairs, lost clothing,
as well as...
$4,000. Yes, your honor.
[Whispers]
She was talking to me.
Oh. [Chuckles]
Why hasn't he paid, counselor?
Uh, that one was for you.
Bedbugs, your honor.
I have receipts that show
my client's financial outlay
to rectify the problem
far exceeds the amount.
Housing department certified
the presence of bedbugs?
- Uh, yes, your honor.
- Abatement?
Excuse me.
I'll do it. There you go.
Your honor, this is
an eviction hearing.
The pertinent question is
not habitability,
but whether or not rent
has been paid.
Actually, city code states
that rent may be withheld
if the warranty of
habitability is breached.
Mm.
In that case, we request
to see the checks.
Mr. Ross' client
has placed in escrow.
- The... Uh...
- Checks, in escrow.
Pending the outcome of
a rent abatement hearing?
- That's not in the code.
- It is the accepted practice.
And therefore
binding in this courtroom.
Your client did put money
in escrow, I assume.
- I didn't have any money left...
- Your honor...
[Gavel pounds] Eviction upheld.
- But your honor, he...
- Did you see me bang the gavel?
That means step aside.
Next case.
You never forget your first.
You know what happens
to pitchers
when they get shelled
in rookie league, Mike?
You think they make it
to the bigs?
Or do they just end up
on some sad American legion
team of has-beens?
I get it, I lost. I'm sorry.
[Chuckles]
Well, you're sorry.
- In that case...
- No, I am sorry.
But right now I have
some research to do for Harvey,
so if you'll excuse me.
Remember when you stole
that client I had you bring in?
That was a good time
for you, wasn't it?
See, I gave you a nothing case
so that when you did win
it would still do
nothing for your career.
But I still
expected you to win.
So yeah, I guess...
Go back to your research.
Maybe that is your niche.
[Chuckles]
Maybe it is.
Most mornings,
I can make it out of the chair
and get across the floor.
[Giggles]
And I can hold my daughter.
How many were in the study?
412, over 2 years.
And we have videos of
all of them.
25% were given placebos,
the rest,
varying doses of Amylinx.
And more than half are
like that one,
showing significant
signs of improvement.
And you're telling me there
was nothing affecting the liver?
Yes.
If you're just coming to
question that, we'll move on.
You don't like it that Quentin
went to his ex-wife, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't want any garbage from
the past getting in the way.
I mean, what Quentin's done here
is nothing short of miraculous.
I think I may have found a way
to keep that miracle going.
I was going through
the plaintiff's medical files,
and then I found this.
This is good.
This is really good.
Jones versus Norco...
Washburn versus
Hawthorne incorporated...
Actually, seven cases
that Mr. Church solicited
lawsuits against
pharmaceutical companies.
In each case, he was able
to exact a settlement
because the company
knew that even if they won,
a protracted battle would
do more damage than settling.
You have evidence of that?
Plaintiff number two
in our case, Eleanor Baker.
She also happens to be
plaintiff number seven in
Jones versus Norco.
He's recycling plaintiffs.
That's very green of you.
Mr. Church?
Mr. Specter has his
documents, I have mine
showing that prior to
fda approval of his drug,
Quentin Sainz's company
was on the verge of bankruptcy.
Three months after
that drug hit the market,
sales rocketed to
$38 million a quarter,
which is clear financial motive
for falsifying clinical trials.
Now, your honor,
does that sound like
a groundless claim to you?
[Whisper] I told you
to go over those financials.
I asked him five times,
he never gave them to me.
- Your honor.
- Mr. Specter,
you can question his tactics
all you like at trial,
but he's right.
That right there is
financial motive for fraud
this case is moving forward.
[Gavel drops]
Thank you, your honor.
Jessica,
what're you doing here?
Get in.
I was just about to
get some coffee.
Heard about your
little setback in court.
Getting blind-sided
by my own client holding back
isn't a setback,
it's an embarrassment.
- What are you talking about?
- Did you ever think
it's time to consider that
he isn't the upstanding man
that you think he is?
[Sighs] When we were married...
When I took a client
Quentin knew was guilty,
he never shut up about it.
He went on, and on,
about right and wrong.
Sounds annoyingly
self-righteous.
It was.
But it's also how I know
he didn't do this.
For all his faults, Quentin has
never lied to me before.
And he's not lying about this.
So stop questioning his ethics
and start winning this case.
We had a deal that
you were gonna stay out of it.
You don't know
everything I know.
- All right.
- That's not staying out of it.
No, you're right.
I'm not staying out
of it anymore.
I'm sorry.
You looked into
his background this deeply?
The investigation
reveals what it reveals.
If he lied about this,
he could've lied about anything.
You think I didn't know
he started with Lisa
before we were separated?
This is old news, Harvey.
I moved on a long time ago.
Jessica, it's
a pattern of behavior.
Quentin came to me
because he knew
I thought he was a good man,
and I still do.
You obviously don't.
I'm taking the case.
What about Lisa?
If Lisa has a problem with it,
then Lisa can
take it up with me.
It's kind of ironic, isn't it?
You and I both
lost in court yesterday.
You lost... In housing court?
How does one
lose in housing court?
People win there
without lawyers.
Well, he had a lawyer,
Tanaka, and she...
- Vivien Tanaka?
- Yeah, what, you know her?
If your landlord's
using Vivien Tanaka,
this isn't about bedbugs.
Vivien Tanaka represents half
the high-rises in Manhattan.
This isn't a petty rent dispute.
Your guy's going condo.
Well, that's great.
Forcing Frank out
for conversion is harassment,
I can go after him for that.
No, you wanna take down Vivien,
you better go in there
with more than just one client.
You show the pattern,
the settlement goes up.
If they did this to him,
I guarantee
they've done this to others.
So I should find other
people in Frank's building?
Think bigger.
Bigger how?
Karinski owns five buildings
and they all used to be
rent-controlled,
but now they go for
a million and a half a unit.
Nice profit margin.
I went to look for
housing department complaints
in the year
prior to his remodel.
In each one of them,
tenants who couldn't
buy into the conversion
ended up with
some complaint...
Garbage, heat, air.
All of them, one by one,
Karinski drove them out.
You couldn't get their
names from housing complaints?
No, it gave me some names.
But I need to make this
bigger than just his building.
Look, I only get one hour
off a day for lunch,
and I never take it.
Do you really need me for this?
See these people
who are leaving the building?
Mm-hmm.
The entire building
looks like them.
I know I clean up okay, but...
Mm, you need me
to class you up a bit.
- Not class, but...
- Class.
All right, whatever
gets you through the door.
Come on, are you ready? Yeah.
Hi, there. My wife and I
are here to see
some of the new units.
Isn't that right, honey? Mmhmm.
So what do you think,
sweetheart?
Hm, it's fine.
But I like the place
on 52nd better.
52nd, that's
awful close to your mother.
No, no, no, we're
not talking about my mother.
Well, I... Look,
it doesn't matter to me,
I mean, I love
being near your mother.
I love your mother.
So why don't you tell us
something about
your little building?
Well, I think you'll find that
not only are
the amenities top quality,
so are the tenants.
That's good to hear.
Yeah, 'cause
we're not just looking at
buying square footage,
but really put down some roots.
Well, that is such
the right way to look at it.
- Mm.
- Is it?
Yes, and I
think you'll also find
that the people who've
bought here, they're like you.
They're young, ambitious...
Both: [Hushed whispers]
Is there a problem?
Any other questions
I can answer?
I'm sorry.
My wife here... My beautiful wife
is just... Gets a little
paranoid sometimes, you know?
You wouldn't believe
how long it took her
to just go out with me
in the first place.
[Giggles] Forever.
Are there any other tenants
who've been here for a while,
you know, who might be
able to show us
the ins and outs of the place,
the neighborhood?
Well, the building was
totally renovated two years ago,
so most of
our tenants are newer.
We only reopened in January.
- Mm.
But I think there are
some of
the old tenants who bought in.
You think that we
might be able to speak to them?
- Just to be sure.
- It would really make us
feel more comfortable.
[Chuckles]
Ow. [Chuckles]
She's feisty.
So in love, so in love.
Yes, we are.
You came to me
because you wanted someone
who knows you
always tell the truth.
Well, you don't.
What're you talking about?
Lisa.
I asked you back then
if anything had started
before we were separated.
You said it hadn't
and I believed you.
'Cause I didn't wanna hurt you.
You wanna know what hurts me?
I thought it was my ambition
that caused our divorce.
- I never said that.
- No.
But you let me believe it.
I shouldn't have started
with Lisa when I did,
but it happened long after
you and I both
know we weren't working.
Now I'm sorry.
Sorry I didn't have
the courage to tell you then.
- What about now?
- Now?
They're manipulating the facts.
And I'm not going to apologize
just because we happened
to hit it big when I
was about to lose everything.
I'm gonna defend you either way
because I took this case,
and that's what I do.
But if I'm gonna
stake my reputation on this,
then I need to know
if there are any other lies
that are gonna
come up and sandbag me.
And I need to know right now.
[Soulful music]
♪ ♪
Thanks.
I see I have
some catching up to do.
People are stupid when
they're young.
Do you wanna know why?
I wanna know why
they're stupid all
the other years of their lives.
Glenfiddich. Smooth.
That's nice.
You never got married.
Now we're
sharing our personal lives?
"Till death do us part."
I actually believed it.
Did he
falsify the clinical trials?
He says he wouldn't do that.
So why are we drinking?
He says he wouldn't do that...
Because he
needs the drug to work.
He's dying.
Quentin has ALS.
Miss Parker, how long
have you worked for Mr. Sainz?
Well, technically,
I'm an independent consultant.
But I've been a part of
Amylinx from the beginning.
Yes, I imagine you have been.
We're just trying
to establish your credentials
for testifying for him.
How long have you
known Quentin had ALS?
- From the beginning.
- And how long have you known
Quentin falsified trial results
to get the drug on the market,
to save his own life? What?
No, he wouldn't do that.
Come on, Lisa,
we're all on the same team here.
We're trying to figure out
how to protect the man you love.
Well, I thought
you believed in him.
You slept with Quentin
while he was married to me.
He said it never happened,
and I believed him.
But I have learned
that he can lie.
So do I believe in him now? No.
This is damage control.
We're just
trying to protect him.
Because they will find out,
and he will get caught,
and if you don't
tell us the real facts,
we can't mitigate
the damage from his lie.
But he didn't lie.
I swear.
He didn't.
But you did, didn't you?
- [Sighs]
- He was sick,
he needed the drug,
and you would've done anything
for fda approval.
Come on, Lisa,
help us help him.
You didn't
see what he was like.
He was... Barely Quentin then.
And then he got better.
And I've never
seen anything like it.
I was the one to see it.
See what, exactly?
6 months in,
1 person out of the 100
started showing
signs of liver damage.
And that would
jeopardize approval.
Yeah, and I couldn't
take that chance,
so I took the person
out of the study.
You never told Quentin?
No, he would've waited,
and we didn't have the time.
He didn't have the time.
And I love him.
So what else could I do?
Look, there is
an upside to all of this.
Upside?
To the fact that I
unknowingly defrauded the fda?
Well, the key word
is unknowingly.
Lisa's an outside contractor.
The company may be
liable for actual damages,
but we can shift the blame
for the fraud to Lisa.
There'd be a small payment,
but you might be able
to keep the drug on the market.
And throw Lisa under the bus?
She was throwing you
under the bus.
She was trying to save my life.
Would there
be criminal charges?
Possibly.
She should get her own lawyer.
It's a conflict for us.
Look, our goal is
to protect you.
Sh... I don't know.
There is an alternative.
You can join Church's lawsuit.
Jessica,
we're lawyers for the company.
We can't advise him to do that.
- Harvey, this is his life.
- That's not the point.
This is my case, my call.
Wait, wait, wait.
What would that mean?
Sainz pharmaceuticals
would go down,
but you'd share in
the settlement.
You could open a new company,
keep the drug alive under
a different corporate umbrella.
I'm not pretending
I'm one of them.
You are one of them.
Look, I can't do that.
It's not who I am.
Now isn't there another way?
You are one of them.
And they're one of you.
Mike, we got work to do,
where are you?
Oh, I'm looking at you
right now in conference room c.
I'm sorry,
can you please excuse me?
Aa meeting? Here in the office?
Funny. No, it's my lawsuit.
- Which suit is that?
- Against Johnny Karinski.
Between Frank's building
and the one Rachel and I
are about to buy into.
Oh, yeah. We're married.
It's a long story.
Look, you said
think bigger, right?
I tracked down
15 former tenants
who are willing to testify
to all manner of harassment
that forced them
out of their apartments.
You did this overnight?
Yeah, I couldn't sleep anyway.
Kept thinking I felt bedbugs.
But I can get these people
in front of a judge
to tell their story,
and there is no way
that Vivien Tanaka can spin
this to save Karinski's ass.
You should hear their stories.
It'd break your heart.
Uh, if you had a heart.
Emotion is fine,
but you better have some cold,
hard facts to back it up.
Because Vivien Tanaka
is no pushover.
But...
It's good work. Keep at it.
I'm gonna go do
what I gotta go do.
[Sighs] We need more.
[Whispers]
How're we gonna get more?
Mike?
Is this the building
we were in yesterday?
No rent, no apartment.
That's my code.
Uh, yeah. Before and after.
[Exhales]
We need to go carpet shopping.
I see you found my ad.
Trying to steal
my thunder, Harvey?
Business school 101,
you have a crisis,
you acknowledge the problem.
You wanna be Tylenol,
not Toyota.
A little late for you
to acknowledge this is a crisis.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you very much
for coming here today.
Quentin Sainz placed this ad
because your lawsuit
made it clear
that his drug had side effects
that he didn't know about.
We wanted to know how
widespread this problem was.
We had an
outpouring of response.
Not from people
struggling like yourselves,
but from people desperate
to keep the drug available.
You think we're lying.
You're here because
you think this company
has been hiding things
from you.
And you're right. They have.
But Quentin wants to come clean.
He wants to show you
exactly what it is
that he's been hiding.
I can't really open it.
I can't hold anything,
and I don't know how
much longer I can keep working.
It'll get better, it will.
You know it will.
I guess.
I bet my life on it.
It's not fair you
got ALS in the first place.
And it's definitely
not fair you had side effects
from the drug I created
and I didn't.
But now that I know they exist,
I wanna fix them.
So that people like you...
And maybe even you,
can have what I have right now.
But he can't.
He can't if he gives you
what you're asking.
We're not saying that
you don't deserve compensation.
Our commitment to you is this.
We are offering you partial
ownership in his company.
A company that is
trying to save lives.
Money isn't going
to help you live longer.
Taking the deal,
and letting Quentin
try and fix the problem could.
Like it or not...
You're all in the same boat.
Give Quentin the opportunity
to keep that boat from sinking.
They really took the offer.
Uh-huh, Church didn't like it.
But they didn't like Church.
They liked you. Hm.
And me.
[Chuckles] Who wouldn't?
Oh, your mother was
never a fan.
You wanna know the truth,
my father wasn't
much of a fan either.
Now that is a lie
and I know it.
Yeah. The real truth is,
they'd both take
you over Lisa in a minute.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
From now on...
Back to no more lies.
Well, if we're gonna do that...
You remember that time
that your jag got sideswiped
when it was
parked outside the house?
Yeah.
Yeah, it didn't
exactly go down that way.
I was mad. [Blusters]
- [Giggles]
- You were mad?
Oh, you brought a sack lunch.
We would've shared.
Amusing.
As was this,
your little lawsuit.
[Chuckles]
Take your sack of presents
and run, kid.
You're in way over your head.
Oh, I think he'll be just fine.
Hello, Vivien. Hello.
So the rookie
called in the veteran.
No, no, I'm just here to watch.
I love spectator sports.
You enjoy watching the Yankees
destroy a little league team?
David and goliath happens to be
one of my favorite stories.
Okay, I'll bite.
What's in the bag?
[Crinkling plastic]
- [Clears throat]
- Hey, hey, what're you doing?
Oh, do you recognize
this carpet?
Make him get that out of here.
This is your
own carpet, Mr. Karinski.
It's from
Frank Carvello's apartment.
Come on.
Feel the fibers, the texture,
it's almost alive.
You brought bedbugs in here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
That's vandalism, assault.
You know, I'm happy
that you put it that way,
because that's what we're gonna
be charging your client with.
What are you talking about?
He didn't just fail to
eradicate a bedbug infestation,
he actually created one.
Yeah, he pulled the carpet
from one of his old buildings...
Carpet that was already
infested...
And then he reinstalled it
in my client's apartment
to drive him out. That's crazy.
You might wanna warn
your client about perjury.
We've got sworn testimony
from the installer.
And a picture of
the same carpet
from one of his old buildings
before it was renovated.
By the way,
my wife and I really love
what you've
done with the place.
So it looks like
we're talking about, what?
Assault, violations of
rental codes, health codes,
and you know, just
basic codes of human decency.
And if a jury in
New York heard all that,
wow, imagine the damages.
Harvey...
Spectate, please.
Just get that carpet
out of here.
So, Vivien...
How am I doing for
my first time?
This still counts as
my first time, doesn't it?
Now let's talk about how much
this is going to cost you.
[Knocking] Yes?
Just thought
you'd like to know,
your case, the pro Bono...
I won.
How exciting for you.
But like I said,
it's just a pro Bono case,
it's not gonna help your career.
I did also manage
to sign 15 new clients
who are all suing
for the same harassment,
and they will be paying.
So you can multiply
this number...
Times 15.
That's not bad for
rookie league.
[Sighs] Come on.
Tell me that wasn't worth
missing your lunch hour for.
Mm, it makes me
proud to be your wife.
Yeah, wait,
what is that coming up?
Is that our third,
or our fourth anniversary?
It's our fifth.
Doesn't it mean anything to you?
Yeah. In fact, I think that
we should have
a date night to celebrate.
[Giggles] You're funny.
Hey.
I'm serious.
I can't date anyone
from the office.