- I wanna go legit.
- You can't.
Then I get Lola Jensen
to hack into the bar
and just put me in there
just like she did with Harvard.
Rule number one
of not getting caught,
you don't move
the goddamn body.
Harvey, I'm stuck.
I can't live my whole life
like this.
We're investment bankers.
Our job blows yours
out of the water.
Just admit it,
you want me to take the job,
but you're too afraid
to say it.
I want you to take the job.
You and your associate
conspired with Harold Gunderson
to file a lawsuit
against your own clients.
That is a bribe.
Quelling knows
about your bullshit lawsuit
with Harold Gunderson.
You need to call
Lola Jensen.
You said it yourself,
hacking into the bar
is twice the crime
I've been committing.
I am telling you
Quelling is on the trail,
and you quitting
isn't gonna change that.
You're letting Mike
walk out the door
without trying to stop him,
and anytime I ask you
about anything
all you say is,
"I can't talk about it."
Mike is gone, Harvey.
The jeopardy's gone too.
And now you wanna tell someone
who keeps finding a reason
to be pissed at you,
and it's not the third time,
and it's not the fifth time,
and it's not the last time.
You took money
from our client's competitors
to trump up
your bullshit suit.
The penalty
is being disbarred.
Being a lawyer
is what I am.
And if you take that away--
It's up to you.
I'll drop the suit.
I'm officially a member
of the New York bar.
You went to Lola?
I want to stay.
I'd bring in champagne,
but after
all we've been through,
I think scotch
seems more appropriate.
Does it?
Harvey, we've had
this conversation once.
If you want someone
who doesn't speak their mind,
I'm not that person.
I know.
And Mike staying
doesn't change my opinion.
Telling Scottie about him
is a mistake.
I know.
Then why are you
being so quiet?
Someone who keeps finding
a way to be pissed at me,
and it's not the third time
or the fifth time
or the last time.
- I wasn't gonna say that.
- Yeah, well, you did.
Because you forced it
out of me.
Donna, do you want me
and Scottie to succeed or not?
I want you to be happy.
- That's an evasive answer.
- No, it isn't.
Just isn't up to me
to decide what that means.
Now are we gonna drink
to Mike staying or what?
Give me that.
Not that one.
The bigger one.
Seriously?
[Glasses clink]
- Hey.
I'm so glad you're home.
I made dinner
because I want to celebrate.
I'm not taking the job.
What?
I went to see Harvey,
and, um...
I told him that I'm staying.
What about the fact
that it was eating you up?
Look, Rachel, I know
this isn't what you wanted.
What I wanted?
I didn't wanna give you
my opinion at all,
but you forced it out of me,
and then you told me that you
were gonna take the job.
Okay, Rachel--
No, and now
you come in here,
and you tell me
you're gonna stay a fraud.
- A lawyer.
- A fraud.
What happened
to accepting me for who I am?
to you taking the job?
It was a way out.
You said you were afraid
if you told me your opinion,
I'd hold it against you,
but now that I'm not doing
what you told me to,
you're holding it
against me.
I am.
Yeah, that's not fair.
I wanna know what changed
from when you told me you were
gonna take the job to now.
I went to see Quelling.
He once had
an offer on the table
that would change his life,
and he turned it down
because he wanted to do
what was right for his clients.
Cost him everything.
The only thing
it didn't cost him
was his ability
to practice law.
And I didn't want
to take it away from him
just like I don't wanna
take it away from me.
Mike.
You said that staying
is eating me up,
but the thought of going
is eating me up more.
I'm just--I'm not ready
to leave, Rachel.
Thanks.
Michael Ross.
Yes?
We'd like to ask you
a few questions.
Who's "we"?
The U.S. attorney's office.
What can I help you with?
We'd prefer to have
this conversation in private.
- Prefer?
- Insist.
Scottie.
I know we got in a fight,
but drinking before 10:00 a.m.,
is that really the answer?
It is on Mad Men.
Who's that guy
think he is anyway?
Mike's staying.
You must be happy.
I am.
Scottie, I'm gonna do better
about being open with you.
Good.
Are we good?
We're good.
Then let's go out tonight
and have some fun.
I'm in.
Scottie.
Yeah?
Let's go somewhere new.
Donna, I don't wanna hear it.
I didn't tell her
about Mike.
Harvey, Stephanie Liston
just called me.
Your friend
from the U.S. Attorney's office?
She said they just brought
Mike in for questioning.
Mr. Ross, Eric Woodall.
I'm the U.S. attorney--
For the Southern district
of New York.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Then you know
you're in a shitload of trouble.
You wanna come clean,
or should I lay it out for you?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You conspired
with Harold Gunderson,
to defraud
the United States government
by paying off witnesses
against Ava Hessington.
[Chuckles]
What?
You sound surprised.
I am
because it's bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
You're facing some major
prison time, my friend.
- I'm not your friend.
- You can be.
Pass.
I settled a lawsuit, okay?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Hey, I don't think you did.
Well, not on your own anyway.
Is there a question?
Come on,
you're a bright young man.
You see where I'm going.
I don't want the dealer.
I want the supplier.
Harvey Specter.
Roll over on him,
I'll cut a deal right now.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Suits 3x16 ♪
No Way Out
Original Air Date on April 10, 2014
♪ all right
♪ all that time
imagine this ♪
♪ the greenback boogie
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Harvey Specter.
I represent Mike Ross.
Sir, you can't
go back there.
Sir!
Well, hey there.
Are you charging him?
- Not at the moment.
- Then he's coming with me.
And you had no right
to bring him in.
I had every right
to bring him in,
but it doesn't matter
'cause he came in voluntarily.
And he's leaving
immediately.
We were just having
a friendly conversation
about the witnesses
who suddenly fell out
of the Ava Hessington case.
Seems your associate
was a little chummy
with the associate
at Bratton Gould.
Harvey Gunderson,
I think, is his name.
Harold Gunderson.
You're right.
You're Harvey.
I gotta keep this
all straight in my head
before I make my case.
Because once
we bring Harold in,
he'll point
the finger at Mike,
who will then
have no choice
but to bring it right home
to you, Harvey.
I promise I won't forget
your name again.
Open that door.
Good talking to you, Mike.
Hope it's the first of many.
Jessica,
I have some dire news.
I was just walking
by the conference room,
and I saw Max Pollard
sitting there all by himself.
Harvey was a no-show?
Don't worry,
I took care of everything,
but it's not like Harvey
to miss a meeting.
Thank you, Louis.
I'll look into it.
You see,
that's just it.
I think something
might be wrong with him.
You mean like he's a spy?
No, Jessica, listen.
Ever since my heart attack,
I've been worrying
about other people's health.
And I'd ask Donna,
but I don't wanna burden her
with the knowledge
of his mortality.
You don't think
Donna knows Harvey can die?
Look, Jessica, I know
Harvey appears to be lean
and relatively fit,
but coronary disease can strike
even the most handsome.
Louis, listen to me.
Harvey isn't sick.
He didn't have a heart attack.
And if he missed
that meeting,
I'm sure there's
a reasonable explanation.
I'm sure you're right.
I'm gonna go check
my blood pressure.
Oh, good idea.
Where the hell is Harvey?
Is he supposed to be
somewhere he's not?
Donna, no games.
He missed a meeting
with a longtime client,
so either you screwed up,
which you never do,
or there's an emergency
I'm not being told about.
Both.
Meaning?
I forgot
to cancel that meeting
because there's
an emergency.
What is it?
Mike Ross got called in
for questioning this morning.
Sorry about this, Harvey.
Could have been worse.
You thought they had me
for being a fraud?
Well, I didn't think
they had you
for overdue library books.
Why'd you go with them
in the first place?
Didn't your grandmother
ever teach you
not to get into cars
with strangers?
I was being cooperative.
Well, don't do that again.
Goddamn Quelling.
He didn't just
hand us to the bar.
He went
to the Justice Department.
I can't believe it.
I looked him in the eye.
He gave me his word.
Screw that guy.
I'm turning him into the bar.
Right now
he's not our problem.
Harold is.
No, I'm gonna talk to him.
Not a chance.
Harvey, they haven't
brought him in yet.
All I need
is five minutes to tell him--
To stick to your story?
That's exactly why they
haven't brought him in yet.
You talk to Harold,
they'll be watching,
we'll be done.
If we don't talk to him
before this Woodall guy
gets him in the room,
we're in deep shit.
Then we need to talk to him
without talking to him.
Allison Holt.
Harvey Specter.
Can't say I'm surprised
to see you.
So I assume that means you've
spoken to the U.S. Attorney.
I have.
Then I suggest
we make sure
we're on the same page.
Unlike you,
I don't automatically
protect someone who may have
jeopardized my firm.
What exactly did you say
when Woodall came to you?
He didn't come to me.
I went to him.
What?
A man named James Quelling
came at me,
questioning the settlement
between Harold Gunderson,
Mike Ross,
and your murder witnesses.
So you go straight
to the U.S. Attorney?
My integrity was questioned.
First step
isn't to go to the person
I'm accused of colluding with
to cover it up.
Answer me one thing--
does Harold Gunderson know
what's going on?
I don't know
what he knows,
and, frankly,
I don't care.
I fired Harold Gunderson
an hour ago.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Of course.
I just got
taken downtown.
What?
The U.S. Attorney's office
brought me in for questioning.
I thought it was about me,
but it wasn't.
[Exhales]
Thank God.
No, Rachel,
it's still bad.
They're looking
into the settlement
that I made with Harold
before Ava's trial.
That deal
wasn't exactly legitimate.
And they want me
to turn on Harvey.
I knew you should have
taken that job.
This has nothing
to do with that.
Doesn't it?
If you weren't working here,
they wouldn't be able
to use your relationship
with Harvey as leverage.
You think
I would turn my back on him
even if I wasn't
working here?
I don't think you'd ever
turn your back on Harvey.
That's the problem.
- What does that mean?
- Harvey wanted you to stay.
I wanted you to leave.
You chose to stay.
So your priorities,
they seem pretty clear to me.
- Rachel, come on.
- Hey, wait a minute
if they charge you
with something,
they're gonna go
through your records,
and they are going
to realize
that you're not
a member of the bar.
No, they won't.
What are you talking about?
I had Lola Jensen
hack into the bar
and put me
in their records.
And when were
you going to tell me?
I was going to tell you
everything last night,
but you didn't exactly seem
like you were in the mood.
Oh, I'm not
in the mood right now either.
I am gonna go outside
and get some air.
Why don't you just stay here
and figure out
if there's some other crime
you can commit
to get out of this one?
You should have called me
the minute this went down.
There wasn't time.
You had time
to see Allison Holt.
I was trying to get
out in front of it.
Allison Holt
isn't our problem.
Mike Ross is.
The U.S. Attorney
keeps poking around,
he's gonna find out
that his star witness
isn't even in the bar.
No, he won't.
If they look in the bar,
they'll find Mike Ross
listed as a member.
You had him
commit another felony?
You want me
to say that out loud?
No, I don't.
I'd rather get back
to the matter at hand.
We need to make sure
Harold Gunderson doesn't talk.
Then you need
to learn more
about the man
who's trying to make him talk,
because he's coming for you,
and you don't know who he is,
what he'll do,
or what he's got.
I know one thing--
if he had
any kind of proof,
someone here would have
already been arrested.
Arrested?
For what?
We're being investigated
for the settlement
between us and Bratton Gould
in the Hessington case.
Quelling didn't go away?
Quelling threatened
to go to the bar.
This is
the U.S. Attorney's office.
Well, that only matters
if the allegations have merit.
I never thought
I would have to ask this,
but do the allegations
have merit?
We're handling this,
Scottie.
I didn't ask
who was handling it.
I asked
if they have merit.
Scottie.
What, are you
gonna be charming?
Quote a TV show?
What happened to
"I'm going to do better"?
God damn it,
I'm trying.
Harvey, I don't think you
understand what trying means.
You know what, Scottie?
You keep on thinking
that there are things
being withheld from you, but--
But what?
It's just business?
- It is just business.
- Fine.
As a senior partner,
I want to know
if this firm outright
broke any laws.
- Harvey, I need to talk to you.
- Not now, Donna.
If you want me
to talk to Stephanie,
you have to tell me what you
want me to ask her right now.
[Sighs]
I guess it's
"not now, Scottie."
Mike. Mike.
I need to talk to you.
No, no, I can't
even be seen with you.
Go, now.
But you have to talk to me.
Allison Holt
just fired me out of the blue.
I'm freaking out, man.
Harold, listen to me.
You have to calm down,
all right?
Harold Gunderson,
you're not welcome here.
You know what, Louis?
We're kind of in the middle
of something right now, so--
Well, I don't give a shit.
Mike, do me a favor.
Do not let this unappreciative
ex-employee into our offices.
Harold, you have to go,
right now.
No, wait, Mike.
Please.
I got a call
from the U.S. Attorney's office
asking for me to come in.
Somehow,
they're onto what we did,
and I think we need to--
Harold, Harold, Harold.
Harold.
All I know
about that settlement
is that you stuck it to us
because you saw the chance
to get back at us
for firing you.
Mike, that's not true.
I don't want
to hear it, Harold.
What you did
was harsh and vindictive,
but it was completely legal
because you initiated it.
And nobody can prove
anything other than that
as long as we both
remember it.
- I lost my job, Mike.
- I'm sorry about that, Harold.
I wish there was something
I could do.
Now I have to go back inside.
Michael Ross,
Harold Gunderson,
you're under arrest
for conspiracy
to defraud
the United States government.
Hey.
Thanks for meeting with me.
Donna, you can thank me
all you want.
I don't know anything
about Eric Woodall.
Stephanie, come on.
You know everything that goes on
in that office.
You just don't want
to tell me.
What do you want
to know?
Well, how about we start with
why he's coming after Harvey?
Because he hates
dirty lawyers.
He thinks
they're the scum of the earth.
And Harvey got
on his radar?
And the reason
Woodall's not on your radar
is because the last case he won
took him four years.
So you're saying
he'll stop at nothing?
Not that I've ever seen.
Then we need
to know what he's got.
No way.
I called you
when they brought your guy in.
I could lose my job
for that as it is.
You have something else a lot
more important than your job,
thanks to me.
When are you gonna stop
holding that over my head?
In another 30 seconds if you
tell me what I need to know.
Okay.
He's got nothing.
But the thing is,
he wins with nothing.
You just said
he hates dirty lawyers,
and now you're saying
he'll break the law?
He may, he may not.
But he'll definitely
bend the shit out of it.
I want to know
what's going on.
I told you
Harvey and I are taking care
of a situation.
That's a bullshit answer,
and you know it.
I don't know how it went
with you and Edward Darby,
but you come into my office
with that attitude,
and it won't go well
for you with me.
My attitude comes
from the fact
that I worked
for Edward Darby.
I don't want to work
for another one.
You're way out of line.
Your name is not
on the door here.
No, but if this all comes down
because of something
you and Harvey did,
I'm tainted by it.
Then walk away, Scottie.
I'm not stopping you.
No, the noncompete
you had me sign is stopping me.
Is that
what's stopping you?
Jessica, I moved my life
back to New York.
I don't want
to move again.
So I'm asking you
one more time--
what is going on?
What's going on,
is you and Harvey
made an impulsive deal
for you to come here,
and clearly,
it's not working out,
or you'd be having
this conversation
with him and not me.
Well, look what
the cat dragged in.
I've been in here
for two hours.
You said I was under arrest,
but I still haven't
been processed.
I demand to call Harvey.
Sorry, we can't have that.
Then I guess you can't have
a guilty verdict against me
or anybody else,
because I know my rights.
Well, I'm afraid
your rights have run
smack into a little something
called the Patriot Act.
Whatever bullshit
you're trying to pull
only applies to terrorists.
Then it's a good thing
there are allegations
of terrorism against
those Hessington witnesses.
[Sighs]
You're not gonna
get away with this.
I'm not getting away
with anything.
I'm just being thorough by
looking into these allegations.
Try to be patient.
Maybe, uh,
think about the fact
that Harold Gunderson
is trying to be patient
right next door.
Pacing.
Right on schedule.
First sign that a man
is losing it.
It's called walking.
You can call it
what you want.
I know what I'm looking at.
Yeah.
So do I.
A guy who looked
into those terrorist allegations
and came up with nothing.
I'll admit the rumors
about those witnesses
were unsubstantiated.
But I'd be negligent
if I didn't look
into an American with ties
to such questionable characters.
And you never know
what a thorough background check
is gonna turn up.
Then go ahead.
Do your background check,
so I can get out of here,
because all this is doing
is making me bored.
Well, I can take care
of that for you.
Why don't I let you watch
a little TV?
Now, that's pacing.
Did you find out anything
useful on Eric Woodall?
I found out we need
to start going on offense.
How?
Donna's having Mike compile
every piece of communication
during that settlement
to prove
Harold contacted us first,
not the other way around.
- Is that true?
- You really want to know?
After that,
we're gonna read up
on every tactic Woodall used
in his last case.
Case?
Took him four years.
Dog with a bone.
That's why we're going
on offense.
Well, I found out
something too.
Scottie wants to leave.
What?
She asked out
of her noncompete.
And what did you say?
I said I had to discuss it
with my partner.
It would have been nice if she
discussed it with her partner.
She accused me
of some pretty shady shit.
And she's right.
What are you talking about?
I told you earlier,
I didn't want
to know about Mike and the bar,
and just now, you asked me
if I wanted to know
about Mike and Harold,
and again,
I didn't want to know.
And "I don't want to know" is
exactly what Edward Darby said.
We're not him.
Edward Darby didn't
commit those murders.
He just covered them up.
And it seems to me
we keep doing things,
and then we have to keep
covering them up.
We're not him.
Harvey.
What do you want me
to tell Scottie?
If she doesn't want
to be here,
let her go.
[Elevator dings]
What the hell
did you do?
You know what I did.
I handed you in
to the bar.
Mike Ross and I
had a deal.
Yeah, well, that deal
went away when he got brought in
for questioning
by the U.S. Attorney.
What?
That wasn't me.
I didn't go to them.
I don't give a shit
if you went to them or not.
This whole thing started
when you walked into my office
with a lawsuit
you were bribed to create.
And after that,
I made a deal with Mike.
And I held
to my end of the bargain.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
That deal went away
when they picked him up,
hauled him in,
and then tried to get him
to turn on me.
Well, you can still
stop this.
Yeah, well,
I'm not going to.
Well, then you better look
over your shoulder every day
for the rest
of your natural-born life.
- What did you say?
- You heard me.
Listen to me,
you son of a bitch.
You pulled out a gun
and threatened to shoot my guy,
and I don't give a shit
if you didn't mean to shoot it,
because it went off.
They're looking into me
because of you.
And I ever so much
as hear your name again,
I will find you, and I will
break every bone in your body.
You are nothing
but a badass on his high horse.
Well, Mr. badass,
I may have started them
looking into what you did,
but you were the one
who did it.
Quelling,
be on your way.
[Phones ringing]
- Rachel, have you seen Mike?
- No, Louis, I haven't.
Okay.
Is something wrong?
Yeah, something's wrong.
We got into a fight.
I haven't seen him since.
Well, I haven't seen him
since he was talking to Harold,
but I need him to give me--
He was talking to Harold?
Yeah, I don't know,
they were having
some idiotic fight outside.
Why?
No, it's nothing.
I have to go talk to Harvey.
Whoa, wait a second.
Harvey?
Does this have something to do
with why he missed his meeting
this morning?
I can't.
Rachel.
You need to tell me what
the hell's going on right now.
[Sighs]
Donna, I know you saw
what happened in the lobby.
I don't want
to hear about it.
Harvey, I can't find Mike.
What?
I've tried his email,
I've tried texting,
I've looked everywhere.
I'm telling you,
Mike is nowhere to be found.
- Louis, not now.
- Yes, now, Harvey.
I know where he is.
He's under arrest,
along with Harold Gunderson.
We need to get down there
right now.
Let me get this straight.
You two were
in a heated conversation
when we picked you up,
and that had nothing
to do with this.
It had everything
to do with it.
You mean you were
trying to cover your tracks.
No, we were having
a heated conversation
about what bullshit charges
these are.
Okay, I'm done
playing your games.
He was your only friend
at that firm, you got fired.
You got him another job,
and that's why you went to him
to set this whole thing up.
You've got
your information wrong.
He wasn't my friend.
I had the chance
to save his job...
But instead,
he threw me under the bus.
That is why I instituted
this lawsuit.
So you can take your bullshit
allegations somewhere else
because I am not
gonna roll on Harvey.
I'm not rolling on Mike.
And Harold is not
gonna roll on me.
You guys
are well rehearsed.
So I'll ask you again,
is that what you were doing
on the street today?
[Sighs]
Jesus Christ, you know,
you drive like my Nana--
he drives like my Nana,
and she's 102.
Relax, Louis.
Ray's on it.
Nobody's
getting us there faster.
I mean, I can't believe
this whole thing's been going on
and I've been
completely out of the loop.
Louis, I don't want
to rehash it.
Right now,
Mike's in custody.
We need to get him out.
Yeah, and you need to tell me
what the hell happened.
Are you asking
if we broke the law
when we made
that settlement with Harold?
That's exactly
what I'm asking.
We have exposure.
Well, then you better hope
that Ray drives
a little goddamn faster,
because you and I both know
what's going on in there.
Let me tell what
we're dealing with here.
Conspiring to bribe witnesses--
seven years.
You filed a sworn declaration
in support of your suit.
That's perjury--
another two years.
And to top it all off,
the money was
transferred overseas,
which would be--
well, you're a lawyer.
Fill in the blank.
- Wire fraud.
- Bingo.
Big winner.
And your prize is 20 more years.
And here's the thing.
I am gonna make sure
that it's not
a cushy white-collar prison.
[Car horn honking]
This is just ridiculous.
If Harold isn't broken by now,
I'll shit my pants.
If Harold's broken,
then when we get there,
Mike's gonna be
on his way to prison.
Someone needs to get in there
and hold his hand.
Not someone...
You.
Are you serious?
I'm the last person
in the world
that Harold Gunderson
wants to see right now.
Louis,
when we were associates,
who did you fear most?
That's easy.
My mother.
I meant in the firm.
Daniel Hardman.
So who would you most
want to come in
and take on Eric Woodall,
if you were in that room?
- Daniel Hardman.
- Exactly.
Look, Harold may not like you,
but he respects you,
and he's all alone.
Now, when we get there,
I need you to channel
your inner Hardman,
get him to trust you,
and then shut him
the hell up.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
You look concerned.
[Sighs]
Do you know why I never batted
an eye when I found out
Harvey had hired a kid
who didn't go to law school?
Because you're loyal to him.
Because I knew
what was inside him.
And I thought if he had
a protege--
He could have hired
a protege from Harvard.
But he wouldn't have been
forced to protect him.
And he wouldn't have become
the man he is today.
Well, now that protege is
in trouble.
[Sighs]
They have Mike
and Harold Gunderson in custody.
Then Harvey's
in trouble too.
No.
Mike would never
turn on Harvey.
You never know
what might happen to a person
once they get
in that room.
Not now, Scottie.
Donna, I'm just writing him
a note telling him
I wanted to talk.
[Scoffs]
"To talk."
I don't think you know how hard
he's trying.
I know he's trying.
I'm just not sure
that it's good enough.
You knew
who he was, Scottie.
- And I thought he would change.
- I think he has changed,
and if it's not enough
for you, then--
That's not the problem.
I think that he's changed
too much,
and I think it happened
before I got back.
He's a good man, Scottie,
but he's not perfect.
Sometimes you just have to take
what you get,
or walk away.
You know, they did
an experiment a few years back.
Took five mice,
put 'em in a cage,
fed them just enough to survive,
and you know what happened?
One by one,
they cornered the weakest mouse
and ate him alive.
You know what you're gonna be
when you get to prison, Mike?
The weakest mouse.
Bullshit.
They have done studies,
and I've read them,
and that's not what happens.
The only way a mouse
eats one of his own
is if he's been contaminated
by another species.
[Chuckles]
Yeah, you're right.
It's bullshit.
But you know who believed it
when I told it to him,
five minutes ago?
Harold.
[Knock at door]
[Door opens]
Looks like you're out of time.
Harold's ready to talk.
You want to tell me
something first?
Get to him
before he changes his mind.
- I demand to see my client.
- You can see him,
but I'm not letting him go,
'cause in five minutes,
I'm gonna come back to him
with a sledgehammer.
Not so fast.
I demand to see my client,
and my client isn't Mike Ross,
it's Harold Gunderson.
- And you are?
- Louis Litt, Pearson Specter.
You're telling me that a man
who works at the law firm
he's accused of colluding with
just happens to be his attorney?
That's exactly
what I'm saying.
- Bullshit.
- No.
What's bullshit is you thinking
it's up to you
who gets to represent
Harold Gunderson.
So if I walk in there
right now
and ask him who his attorney is,
he's gonna say it's you?
Doesn't matter
what he says.
It's 4:07, and if
you don't let me see my client,
anything he says after this
second will be inadmissible.
And I will rain down
fourth amendment claims on you
for the rest
of your goddamn life.
[Door opens]
If you wanted some me time,
all you had to do was ask.
You'd better have
some good news for me,
otherwise I'm gonna be having
plenty of me time.
Harvey, this Woodall guy
is serious.
- I'm serious too.
- Then why am I still in here?
Because we're waiting
for Louis.
Louis?
To do what?
Convince Harold not to talk.
Holy shit.
Louis is in with Harold?
Harold hates Louis!
It's our best shot.
So what do we do now?
We wait.
Louis, what are you
doing here?
First off, how you doing?
How do you think I'm doing?
I'm in the seventh circle
of hell.
Well, the cavalry
has arrived.
I don't need the cavalry.
I've decided to get out.
Okay, Harold,
you cannot sign a deal.
You'll never work
as a lawyer again.
What do you care?
You fired me as a lawyer.
Now all of a sudden
you're my best friend
when you need something from me?
Go to hell, Louis!
Okay, you know what?
You're right.
I'm not your friend.
Never was.
But the one thing
I've never done is lie to you.
Now, you have a chance
to walk out of here today,
as if none of this
has ever happened,
and all you have to do
is trust me.
You have no idea
who that man is.
No idea?
How do you think
I got in the room?
Okay, well, you know, Louis,
I am glad you got to take
a good look at it,
because if I don't
give them Mike,
I could be in here
for the rest of my life.
Lawyers don't get paid
to look out the window.
[Sighs]
I can't concentrate either.
I just wish
there was something we could do.
Rachel, if this thing
moves forward to trial,
I will do everything
in my power to win.
But there's two minutes left
in the game,
and our star players
are on the field.
So right now,
we just have to have faith.
Wwe?
We.
You're going to work here.
We're going to be family.
And the way to get to know your
family is by being with them
when their loved ones
are in trouble.
How long do we wait?
As long as it takes.
I want to talk to you
about my defense strategy.
This is
your defense strategy.
If this doesn't work,
you're gonna want to talk
to a different lawyer than me.
Harvey, I don't care
what Harold gives them on me,
I'm not giving them you.
- I want to tell you a story.
- I don't want to hear a story.
It's about the time I decided
to tell my dad about my mom.
You remember what I told you
about her?
- Harvey--
- I was 20,
out of the house,
and I told her
I would never tell him
as long as she never
brought anyone--
I came home to do laundry
one day, and I heard--
I heard,
and then I saw,
and I told him that night.
Because sometimes
it's better to tell.
She deserved that.
So do I.
This whole thing
was my idea.
I gave the go-ahead.
It's me Woodall wants.
- Well, he's not getting you!
- Yes, he is.
No, I don't care
what happens
in that room,
I'm not giving you up!
- Don't be a fool.
- Don't be an asshole!
Listen to me, God damn it,
I'm giving you permission--
I don't give a shit
what you're giving me!
I hired a fraud.
And then we crossed the line
with Clifford Danner,
then with Lola Jensen,
and then with these witnesses,
and to top it all off,
we suborned perjury
with Edward Darby.
If it comes to it, you point
the finger at me, you got that.
Let's just hope
it doesn't come to it.
It's over.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Hey, Mike.
How's it going?
Mr. Specter!
Eric.
Just because you stopped
Gunderson from testifying
doesn't mean
I'm dropping this case.
Then don't.
And I'll come after you
for malicious prosecution.
You have no basis for that.
You arrested my client,
he was here four hours,
and you have no log
with an outgoing call to me,
all on the basis
of a fabricated terrorism claim.
Now, if that's not malicious,
I don't know what is.
You say what you want.
You're a dirty lawyer,
and now you're on my radar.
If I'm a dirty lawyer,
then you're looking
in the mirror.
[Rock music]
♪
[Sighs]
I'm so sorry.
[Crying] I just thought
that
- Rachel.
- I would never--
Everything's
gonna be okay.
Hey, honey, I'm home.
Did you remember to pick up
the kids like I asked?
Yep.
The youngest one's turning
into a real pain in the ass.
- It's good to have you back.
- Good to be back.
What's on your mind,
Harvey?
You were right.
We are becoming Edward.
I know.
And we need to get back
to being us.
Did you let her know
about our decision yet?
I assumed you'd want
to take care of that yourself.
Hey.
You want a drink?
They do it
on Mad Men, right?
Jessica and I are gonna
let you out of your noncompete.
What about the buy-in?
We'll take care
of the buy-in.
Harvey, I, um--
Mike Ross never went
to law school.
I knew it,
and I hired him anyway.
Why are you telling me now?
Because you accused Jessica
of being Edward Darby.
It wasn't her.
It was me.
I still can't stay,
Harvey.
I know.
I just want to stop lying
to the people I love.
I'm sorry.
I told her.
I know.
- She won't tell anyone.
- I know.
She's leaving.
I know.
Harvey, you're a good man.
Am I?
I turned Quelling
into the bar.
I took my rage out on him.
He didn't deserve it.
Which is why I stopped it.
What are you talking about?
Do you seriously think
that Stephanie Liston
is the only person
who owes me a favor?
Well, that doesn't make me
a good man.
That makes you
a good man for me.
Harvey, sometimes we need
a little help.
[Soft rock music]
♪
Big day.
Horrible day.
It ended well.
Thank you.
You and Louis
really came through.
So did you.
Look, I know
what you're thinking.
- No, you don't.
- You don't want to go to jail.
Harvey...
I sat in that room today
and listened to you tell me
that ever since the day
we met,
you've had to cross one line
after another, and--
Mike-
No, just...
Let me finish.
First there was
Clifford Danner,
then the witnesses,
then suborning perjury,
not to mention the 17 things
we did to stop the merger
in the first place.
All of it,
since you hired me.
Look, that's not
what I said.
Yes, it is.
[Sighs] I wasn't blaming you
for those things.
It doesn't matter.
I'm tired of putting the people
I care about in jeopardy.
♪
I called Jonathan Sidwell
this afternoon.
I took the job.
We just got out.
Harvey...
You gave me permission
to point the finger at you.
♪
Give me permission to go.
You're a good man, Harvey.
Thanks.
Hey, when's your last day?
I don't know.
Why?
Well, I want to take you out
to dinner, you know?
I'm not gonna see you anymore.
I don't think you realize,
but I'm not exactly leaving.
Sidwell.
You're a client.
Which means technically,
you work for me now.
No, I don't.
"No, I don't, boss."
- Don't even try it.
- Or "sir."
Whichever feels
least comfortable.
You know,
since I'm working alone now,
I guess
that makes me Superman.
Or Aquaman, seeing
as you're in over your head.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man