Previously on
Suits...
I'm bonding
with your father here.
- Speaking of which--
- You're not taking it easy
on me, are you?
A little.
You mean something to me.
You've always meant something
to me
and you always will mean
something to me.
What do you need, Harvey?
Ava Hessington.
I am not losing to him.
You.
Your blood feud
or whatever it is
you have with that man
is what put the target
on my back in the first place.
I made this mess.
It's up to me to clear it up.
Harvey and Cameron made a deal
to take you down.
And part of that deal
was that I got to be the one
to tell you about it.
If he can't practice law
in the country,
he can't be a member
of our firm.
You set this whole thing up.
Jessica set
this whole thing up.
And, Edward,
we may be getting a divorce,
but I fully intend on keeping
ownership of the house.
Oh, come on, just because
I have to wake up early
doesn't mean you
should suffer.
Well, you know
what they say.
The couple
that wakes together...
Bakes together?
- Stays together.
- Yeah, that doesn't rhyme.
You're ridiculous.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
I know.
You're amazing.
You have no intention of
letting me go to work, do you?
There once was a girl
from Nantucket.
I love you.
Oh, that doesn't rhyme,
you know?
What are you,
the rhyming police now?
- You started it.
- And I'm gonna finish it.
I love you too.
You look happier
than you did last night.
I am.
What are you doing here?
I was thinking
I'd give you a ride.
You just gave me a ride
last night.
Yeah, this time
I thought I'd join you.
Harvey,
we put in 15-hour days
12 feet from each other.
You really want
to go to work together?
Who said anything
about work?
We have breakfast
at Nougatine
and an excursion to Hermes
that may or may not
involve a new handbag.
You've been needing
a new handbag.
You can never have
too many handbags.
You're a woman
after my own heart.
Well, in that case...
Harvey...
Why are you doing this?
Donna, we've all
been through a lot.
We deserve
a little celebration.
Well, in that case,
you have had it pretty rough.
We're gonna need to get you
more than one handbag.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
Jessica.
Louis, what can I do
for you?
Actually, I'm not here
about me.
I'm here about you.
How so?
Um...
I want to handle
the dissolution.
So this is about you.
No.
Jessica...
I got Ava out
when you wanted her out.
I proved that I will do
whatever it takes.
And what's more,
I know Darby's assets,
and I will get you everything
that you have coming.
I can get everything
I have coming.
Maybe, but after
what Stephen Huntley
and Edward Darby did, you want
to exact a pound of flesh.
You want to kill them both.
What's your point?
My point is, is that you go
into that room angry,
you're gonna have blinders on.
And they're gonna lead you
any way they want you to go.
I get in that room,
I'm cool as a cucumber,
and I will lead whatever way
you want to go.
We just got Edward Darby's
proposed formula
for splitting our assets.
- Son of a bitch.
- I know!
He thinks he can dictate terms
after what he's done?
We need to crush him.
See?
Blinders.
What?
Louis was just suggesting
that he run the negotiations.
Louis also suggested the firm
adopt a badger as a mascot.
The badger is a noble
and fearsome creature,
but that's not the point.
I can beat them.
And the Washington Generals
think they can beat
the Globetrotters,
but they're not even
in the same league.
My father played
for the Washington Generals.
- See?
- So what are you saying?
I'm not in your league?
I'm saying you and I
don't even play the same sport.
Harvey...enough.
And Louis has a point.
You seriously want
to consider this?
This is a joke.
Louis, will you give us
a moment?
Please?
I am not a joke.
You can't do that anymore.
You mean make fun of Louis?
It's one of life's
great pleasures.
When the two of you
were colleagues,
that's fair game,
but you're a name partner now,
and you have to show him
some respect.
I am showing him respect.
I'm being dismissive
to his face.
Harvey, remember Kopelman?
Combovers like that
are hard to forget.
When I first started here,
he and I would fight
like cats and dogs every day,
toe-to-toe.
Then one day
he went too far.
He crossed a line,
and I'd had enough,
and I went in,
and I ripped him up.
You know what I did the day
after Daniel and I
took over the firm?
I went to Kopelman, and I told
him how much I valued him.
Kopelman never voted
against you
the whole time I knew him.
Exactly.
And by the way,
Louis is right.
Jessica, it's one thing for me
to show Louis respect.
But you want to put me
on the sidelines for him?
No.
I'm gonna put him in
at quarterback,
then snap the ball to you.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ living in a beehive,
I don't mind ♪
♪ me and missy so early busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ Suits 3x09 ♪
Bad Faith
Original Air Date on September 10, 2013
♪ Y'all step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The Greenback Boogie
So let me get this straight.
You want to go after
their clients
so we get to count
those revenues.
Whoever has more revenue
is gonna determine
who gets what at the time
of closing.
Louis locks in
the settlement terms
while we tip the basis
for the settlement.
Exactly.
Some might say that's
negotiating in bad faith.
And I say Darby wasn't above
board when we got married.
Why should we be above board
when we're getting divorced?
And until the settlement
is done,
it's not stealing clients.
It's shifting
the attorney of record.
Wait a minute.
Did you think of this
all by yourself?
Why wouldn't I think of this
all by myself?
It was Jessica, wasn't it?
She thought of it
all by yourself.
The important thing right now
is to decide
which client to go after.
And to avoid my question
about whose idea it was.
- Exactly.
- Okay.
Well, if it's going to affect
the settlement calculations,
we're gonna need a big client
and we're gonna need a big one
who just took a loss.
Not necessarily.
You know who cries hardest
in the Miss America pageant?
- The runner-up.
- The winner...
Because she knows
she can't win again,
and winners always want
to win more.
Yeah.
That's not why they cry.
What's wrong with you?
Stay with me.
What we need is a huge company
that is still looking
to keep the crown.
Samsung.
- Get it going.
- Yeah.
Wait. Do you--
you actually watch
the Miss America pageant?
No, but I've celebrated
with the winner.
- Texas, Florida, New York?
- California.
Now, there's a question
you didn't want to avoid.
Exactly.
You wanted to see me?
- Yes, and it's important.
- What can I do for you?
Adjust the font
on the new business cards?
Order some pens?
I don't know.
If we don't have any pens,
what would you sign
the order with?
What do you want, Jessica?
I was just making
a little joke.
Oh, I thought I was
the only joke around here.
Louis, you are no joke.
And you're right.
You have been on the sidelines
far too long.
I want you to handle
the negotiations.
You won't be sorry.
You want a pound of flesh,
I'm gonna bring you
the whole carcass.
I believe you would,
but I'm going to ask you
to do something else.
- Anything you need.
- I need you to be fair.
- Fair?
- Yes, fair.
- That's one way to go.
- It's the way to go...
Because I need them to think
that we're moving on,
when, in fact,
we're going after their clients.
Oh, my God.
You and Harvey are letting me in
on one of your missions?
This is Litt-tastic.
Louis, calm down.
Calm down?
No!
This is just like
The Great Escape.
You're recruiting me
to go behind enemy lines.
I'm Steve McQueen.
- You know The Great Escape?
- Are you kidding?
Charles Bronson grew up
in my grandmother's shtetl.
Then you know Steve McQueen
was the cooler king.
Louis, I need you to be
my cooler king.
Yeah, I am cool.
So you're authorizing me
to sign on your behalf?
Yes, but under
no circumstances
are you to lock in the existing
client allocations.
Please, I'd die
before that happens.
Let's hope it doesn't come
to that.
- Is that coconut water?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I took some with me
this morning.
I hope you don't mind.
Why would I mind?
You needed the hydration.
You made me need
the hydration.
You're welcome.
- What?
- Nothing.
What?
Uh...
I just don't like
when you drink
from the bottles
in the refrigerator.
- But it's my bottle.
- The ones in my fridge aren't.
So you do mind
that I took it.
No, I mind that you drink
from the bottles in my fridge.
Okay.
And that you left your
coffee mug in the sink again.
I thought I was supposed
to put the mug in the sink.
Yes, on the right side.
The left side is for rinsing.
I can't rinse if there
are dishes piled on both sides.
I'll try and remember that.
You'd think a guy with your
memory wouldn't have to try.
- All right, let's hear it.
- Hear what?
- The list.
- What list?
Of things I do
that annoy you.
- I don't have a list.
- Everyone has a list.
- Do you have a list?
- This isn't about my list.
This is about your list.
No, it's about yours
because I just told you
everything that's on mine.
You're telling me
that the most meticulous woman
on the upper West Side
only has a list of two?
- That's not fair.
- No, what's not fair
is you making this
all about me.
I might not be perfect,
but neither are you.
So, excuse me, I have more
important things to do
than talk about where
I left my coffee cup.
- Fair?
- Fair.
- Yes, fair.
I didn't even like playing
nice in the sandbox.
Someone has better sand toys,
you take 'em.
Exactly.
And you don't ask
Bolshoi ballerinas
to dance the tango.
That would indeed
be blasphemy.
If Jessica wants compromise,
she should hire a mediator,
not a gladiator.
Except Jessica
doesn't want compromise.
She wants a stone-cold killer to
do one thing and one thing only.
And what is that?
Not to lock client allocations
till Harvey lands Samsung.
Then give me an order.
Your order is to not let
my inner gladiator
get past my outer negotiator.
That's not
gonna be easy, Louis.
You're like the Hulk--
once you get enraged,
there's no going back.
Though your description
of both my temperament
and physique is accurate,
the one thing that I have
on my side is that I have
no personal animus
against the other side.
Nesbitt.
Litt.
I see you're wearing
your checkered suit
with your crimson power tie.
You see correctly.
Looks like you came
to play hardball.
I didn't come
to play anything.
I came to win.
Well, I'm not here to win.
I'm here to make sure we
hammer out a fair agreement.
And to help you achieve that,
I see you've brought along
Tinker Bell.
You were so scared
of Tinker Bell,
you sent her to Barcelona,
for your cat trial.
During which time,
she worked closely,
with a different senior partner...
again and again.
Don't worry.
Dr. Banner's
not turning green today.
See, whatever you thought was
gonna happen to me here isn't.
So go ahead,
wind me up all you want,
'cause I ain't losing my cool.
Fine.
This is my initial proposal.
Those are letters
I wrote to Mikado.
Unopened.
You never read them to her?
- Not a single word.
- You son of a bitch.
You think you can rattle me?
I'm un-rattleable.
Really?
This portrait
that you sent her.
Get out!
- Louis--
- I said go.
Oh, yeah, you and I
are going to war.
Everything's
on the goddamn table!
Including the existing
client list allocations?
Did you hear what I just said?
I said everything!
You son of a bitch.
You knew
I'd come after Samsung.
I knew what suit
you'd be wearing.
I know Tiger Woods
wears red on Sundays.
It doesn't mean
I can beat him.
I'm not going to let you poach
our clients, Harvey.
You poaching our clients
is what led us
to this goddamn merger
in the first place.
That was fair game.
This is bad faith.
Bad faith?
I'm going after Samsung.
I'm not murdering anybody and
lying about it to my partners.
Don't you dare put me in
with them.
You put yourself in
Speaking of which,
what the hell you still doing
in bed with these people,
Scottie?
As you know, I don't always
have the best judgment
of who I get in bed with.
And as for why I'm still
in business with them--
Let me guess.
You beat me
on the dissolution negotiation,
you get your name on the door.
Yep.
Darby agreed to it
the second
that you pushed him out.
He only did that because
he knew when word got out
that his house was on fire,
he had to do something.
Well, he did.
He put me against you.
And as you just noted,
our house is on fire,
and I'm gonna fight tooth and
nail to put the damn thing out.
You can fight tooth and nail
all you like,
but it's never done a thing
for you against me before.
That's because I always
had something else
on my mind before,
but you've made it clear that
that's never going to happen.
So, if you think
you're gonna win this time,
you've got
another thing coming.
Say what you want, Scottie.
I'm going in there,
and you're not gonna stop me.
I'm afraid I already did.
Client list just got locked.
So you can go in there
and give it a shot,
but they're never gonna sign
with a guy
who just got played
on their front porch.
- Hey.
I got your message.
Thanks for meeting me.
It's not often I get invited
out to hear an apology.
I'm so sorry
I snapped at you.
I got defensive, and when I went
away to think about it,
I came up with why.
Why?
I feel like a guest
in your apartment.
And I think it's because
we spend all of our time
at your place and none
of the time at mine.
Yeah, but I told you,
when I'm at your place,
all I can picture is Tess
in a bedsheet.
I know.
And that's why we're here.
Come on, I want
to show you something.
Louis, we gave you one job,
and you blew it.
How the hell did you screw up
those negotiations?
Screw up? Come on.
What are you talking about?
I got us the corporate jet.
We keep
our first dividend checks,
and they pay
for our new letterhead.
So you know what?
You just put that in your pipe,
and you smoke it.
I don't give a shit
about the goddamn letterhead!
You don't think
I know that?
Nobody cares about
the goddamn letterhead, okay?
Nigel went after Mikado.
What the hell is Mikado?
Not "what," "who."
She's a cat.
He went after your cat?
He went after his cat.
He tortured his cat?
He deprived her
of my letters.
Louis, you lost your shit
during a negotiation
because someone didn't read
your letters to their cat?
Harvey, please.
I'm sorry I lost my head.
I don't even remember
signing the agreement.
Well, you did!
And, Louis,
you've been asking Jessica
to give you the ball
instead of me
ever since the day I met you.
Well, she gave it to you,
and you just went and scored
a touchdown for the other team.
Oh, my God.
Your grandmother's apartment.
I still own it.
You kept it
this entire time?
I couldn't rent it.
I couldn't sell it.
I...
Couldn't even come here.
That means the last time
you were here...
We were here.
So you want to move in here?
I want us to move in here.
- Mike--
- Rachel.
I've only ever been here twice,
and both times were with you.
The first time we stood here,
and we pictured
living together.
I'll never forget that.
- Neither will I.
- And the second time...
Was one of the hardest days
of my life,
but I got through it
because we were together.
That's one the sweetest things
I've ever heard.
You don't have to answer
right now, okay?
I just wanted to show you
what we could have.
Goddamn Louis.
Let it go.
Let it go?
You don't say "let it go"
unless you already
didn't let it go.
You gonna take it out on me
for taking it out on him?
At the moment,
we don't have the time.
Good, because
I've already got Mike
looking for ways
to revise the agreement.
The problem
isn't revising it.
The problem is
Louis already signed it.
You're saying
we need to find a loophole.
I am.
Well, if we can't steal
from their clients
and the revenues from new ones
don't count,
what the hell
are we supposed to do?
There's only one thing
to do--
look at the money
we're already owed.
- I don't follow you.
- We're on a cash basis.
We can't count the revenues
we haven't collected yet.
But if we can entice someone
to pay us sooner,
we can get that revenue in
under the window.
Bad faith--
I like it.
The question is,
who still owes us enough money
to make a difference?
Folsom Foods.
The second they pay
their settlement,
we get paid our fee.
You came to that
all on your own.
Yeah, about an hour ago.
Don't tell me I beat you to it.
Maybe. But you didn't have
Harvey slowing you down.
- That's a fair point.
- Okay, I'm right here.
Well, your idea is no good,
because it'll be
a cold day in hell
before Daniel Hardman lifts
a finger to help this firm,
and I'd rather lose
this negotiation
than to cut a deal
with that son of a bitch.
You don't have to.
Hardman was running point.
Folsom's not his client.
They're Robert Zane's.
- He's no fan of us either.
- Maybe not.
But we can handle
Robert Zane.
You caught on
to my plan there.
You mean the most obvious
plan in the world?
I mean the plan that
I thought of and that you didn't
and that I'm the perfect
person to implement.
You really think
you can handle Robert Zane?
I have a relationship
with him.
Yeah. You're sleeping
with his daughter.
I'm sure
he's your biggest fan.
Okay, it's not like that.
I had dinner at the man's house.
I had dinner
at the White House.
They're not gonna make me
Attorney General.
Okay, first of all,
bullshit.
Second of all,
do you have a better idea?
No, I don't.
But are you ready to use
your relationship with Rachel
to get her father to turn?
Doesn't matter,
because I'm not gonna do that.
I'm just gonna use it
to get him to hear me out
in the first place.
Good luck with that.
Hey, how'd you know that
White House thing was bullshit?
Mike. I was wondering when
I was gonna get you out here.
Ah, golf isn't really
my thing.
What is your thing?
- Sports.
- You're telling me
you're one of those guys
that doesn't think
golf is a sport?
Of course not.
I can tell you're an athlete
just by looking at you, sir.
With an attitude like that,
you must be here on business.
- Folsom Foods.
- Ah...
You're gonna stick that loss
in my face?
No, I'm here to make
that loss sting a little less.
You move up your payment
by one fiscal quarter,
we'll take a 10% haircut
on our fee.
- 10% is a little light.
- All right.
I'll cut right to it.
I can go as high as 20%.
Are you saying 20%?
Yes.
Then I'm saying no.
Sir, this...
This is a win for you.
No, this isn't shit
for me.
This is about Harvey Specter
and Jessica Pearson
and their divorce negotiations.
And you don't go
to the one you didn't marry
to stick it
to the one you did.
We could go
straight to your client.
By the time
they accepted the offer,
it'd be too late.
You just gave that away
when you went straight to 20%.
I went straight to 20%
out of respect.
Now you're repaying me
by being a--
What?
You don't have the balls
to say it.
I will.
A dick.
I'm being a dick.
The question is,
what are you gonna do about it?
I'm not gonna do
anything about it.
I just wonder
what your daughter's gonna think
when she finds out
you screwed over your own client
just to stick it
to the man she loves.
She loves Harvey Specter.
No.
But when you go after Harvey,
you go after me.
The Whooping Crane
of Manchuria.
- It's my calming animal.
- You've chosen well.
What can I do for you,
Katrina?
- I never heard back from you.
- About what?
About anything...
Especially what we're going
to do about negotiations.
There's no more negotiation.
I had one assignment,
and I blew it.
Louis, the opera isn't over
until the fat lady sings.
No, this is not the opera.
It's football.
Harvey said it.
They gave me the ball.
I scored a touchdown
for the other team,
it's the eighth inning,
and there's no more time
left on the clock.
I never thought
I'd hear you say that.
It's the fact.
There's nothing we can do.
I signed the agreement,
and Nigel's
never gonna reopen it.
Well, then I guess it's
a good thing I found a loophole.
What are you talking about?
We can't steal
their clients,
but we can still increase
our revenue.
No. New clients
don't count.
I'm not talking
about new clients.
I'm talking about new revenue
from clients we already have.
Well, that's operating
in complete bad faith.
Now, what clients
are you talking about.
First, I got you something.
Okay, Katrina,
you know what?
I really don't have time
for sentimental--
The trademark came through
ten minutes ago.
I...
Don't know what to say.
Say you forgive me
for letting you
lose control of Nigel.
I do.
Now, let's go get
some goddamn new revenue.
You.
How'd you get in here?
'Cause I know
how to get things done.
You didn't
the last time we met.
Last time you saw me
coming a mile away.
This time,
I'm blindsiding you.
- I didn't know we were at war.
- We're not.
It's just a training exercise.
These are my personal
bank statements.
You stole my money.
No, not stole...
Relocated.
- I could have you arrested.
- You could.
But then you'd be missing out
on all this...
Tax shelter in the Caymans,
carried interest classification
for your personal holdings,
blind irrevocable trust for up
to six of your unborn children.
- And this means...
- You'll never pay
a nickel in taxes
your entire life,
not to mention your money
will be too secure
for someone to do
what I just did.
How'd you do all this?
Well, you said you'd call us
for the paperwork.
This is how I do paperwork.
Oh, and one last thing--
that Ferrari
that your ex-wife took?
Yeah?
I got it back.
You're hired.
Don't you need to get
board approval?
To be my personal attorney?
No, for
Gianopolous Limited Holdings
to expand their relationship
with us.
- Are you crazy?
- How is that crazy?
I just showed you
what I'm capable of.
You showed me you could beat
a tribe of Visigoths.
You want me to give you control
of the Roman Empire?
I can handle
the Roman Empire.
Even if you could,
from Mr. Gianopolous's
perspective,
you're a nobody.
Please, can you at least find
a way to convince him?
I'm sorry.
If I bring your name
up to him,
he will laugh me
out of the room.
That's a check
from Folsom Foods.
It's the remainder
of what they owe us.
Holy shit.
That's all of it.
It's hard to believe that
you could get Zane to do this
without using
his daughter against him.
Maybe I'm
an excellent negotiator.
If you're
an excellent negotiator,
this wouldn't include
a 20% haircut.
It would be 10%,
like I would have gotten.
You? He wouldn't have
even talked to you.
Like you're not talking
to me right now?
What'd you say to Zane?
Let's just say we may have
gotten what we wanted, but...
My girlfriend's dad's gonna be
pissed at me for a little while.
Then you're a better
negotiator than I thought.
I never should have
given you my key.
And I never
should have forgotten
that you'll stop at nothing
to beat me.
No, you shouldn't have.
Harvey...
The man that I knew
may have fought to the death,
but he always operated
in good faith.
I told you, I am not bound
by good faith on this deal
after what your boss did.
It's not just Edward's firm.
What does that
have to do with it?
You shrunk the whole pie
for the sole purpose
of getting a bigger piece
for yourself,
and it screwed me,
along with Edward.
What do you want, Scottie?
I want you to exclude
the Folsom Foods payments
from the settlement
calculations.
And why would I do that?
Because I need you to.
I'm afraid that's not enough.
You, uh--
you came to me.
You needed help
with Ava Hessington
after you sent me back
to London.
You said that I mean
something to you,
that I'll--I'll always
mean something to you.
Was that bullshit or not?
It wasn't bullshit,
and if you're in trouble
personally--
I am in trouble personally.
You said so yourself.
Our house is on fire,
and it's my job to put it out.
If you crush me...
I'll have nothing.
That's not personal.
That's business.
Okay,
let's talk business.
You made a career out
of putting I.O.U.s in the bank.
Do the same thing right now.
Put an I.O.U. in with me.
And what's to stop you
from still trying
to screw me after that?
My word that I won't.
He asked you
to move in together?
- I know. It's...
- Quick?
I was going to say
that it's a-a big step,
because it's not
really that quick.
We've known each other
for a while.
Yes, but you only
just started dating.
So I guess that means
you're against it.
Rachel,
I'm not against it.
You told me that you love him,
and I couldn't be happier
for you.
But you got a lot
going on right now.
You don't even know where
you're gonna go to law school.
I'm just saying
maybe you don't want to rush
into this so quickly.
Rush into what?
Well, Mike asked me
to move in with him.
Move in with him?
Shit, what's he gonna
do to me then?
- What are you talking about?
- You didn't hear?
He came to me
on the golf course.
To ask for permission?
No, he didn't ask for shit.
I got to hand it to him.
The boy's got some balls.
- What?
- He kicked my ass.
Didn't even have the courtesy
to give me a--
- Robert!
- Oh, come on.
She's gonna be a lawyer.
Gonna hear a lot worse.
Dad, what are you talking
about--what happened?
He wanted an advance
on the Folsom settlement.
And he put the screws to me
to get it.
He put the screws
to you how?
Rachel.
This is a surprise.
What happened to--
Tess in a bedsheet?
It was replaced by the image
of you manipulating my dad.
Okay, I did not manipulate
your dad.
How exactly
would you describe it?
I didn't go there
to manipulate him, all right?
He--he was about to make
a decision
that was going to affect him,
us, and his client,
and I just pointed that out
to him.
And then when
that didn't work,
you pointed out
that I wouldn't approve.
He was bullying me.
So you used me
to bully him back.
I was talking to my mom
about moving in with you
when I found out about this.
Okay, Rachel...
I'm sorry, all right?
Let me call him right now.
I'll apologize to him--
Him?
He loved it!
He did?
Yeah, he thought
you had balls.
- So then what's the problem?
- Are you not listening to me?
I was thinking
about moving in with you,
and then I find out
that you go to my dad--
Wait, wait, wait.
Are--
are you saying
this changes everything?
- It's complicated.
- What's complicated about it?
Forget--I don't even want
to get into this
with you right now!
Rachel, if you don't want
to live with me,
why don't you just tell me
you don't want to live with me?
I didn't say that.
Well, do you?
You said I could have
some time, so...
I just need some time.
You excluded
the Folsom Foods payment
from the revenue totals
on this.
It's a draft document.
I haven't showed it to anyone.
I just wanted
to run it by you.
Well, what reason
could you possibly have
for wanting to do it at all?
Because Scottie
came to me and asked,
and I think
it's good business.
Well, your idea
of good business
is different from mine,
because we already took
less money from Folsom Foods,
and now you want us to take
less money from Darby.
Jessica,
if we screw him over,
he's gonna come back at us.
It might not be tomorrow.
It might not be six months
from now,
but he's gonna find a way.
- You mean she'll find a way.
- That's exactly what I mean.
And maybe she will.
But I've never known you
to run from a fight before.
My name was never
on the door before.
You said it yourself.
I have to think differently
now that I'm in this position.
I did say that.
And it's not just gonna
be one fight.
It's gonna be the Hatfields
and the McCoys all over again.
Are you sure this isn't really
about your history with her?
- What if it is?
- She could just be playing us.
She could, but...
I trust her.
Jessica,
it's time to turn the page.
Well, I don't want
to turn the page.
I want to close the book.
Tell her we'll exclude
the payment and honor our deal.
Louis, I know it didn't go
exactly as planned,
but you need to pick yourself up
and dust yourself off.
Exactly as planned?
I utterly failed.
I don't even deserve
this stupid mug.
"Litt Up"?
It should say "shit up."
You didn't fail.
You impressed him.
Yeah, that and $45 will get
my cat a Brazilian bikini wax.
You got a new cat?
Fostering.
Louis...enough.
You need to go to Harvey.
You mean tell him that I'm
even more of an embarrassment
than he says I am?
You're not an embarrassment.
You may need Harvey
to put the ball in the end zone,
but you had the idea,
you set it up,
and you drove the ball
down to the one-yard line.
No, I didn't have the idea.
You had the idea!
And you executed it.
But you're giving me credit.
If Harvey executes this,
he'll give you credit.
No, he won't.
He never does.
Louis, he might.
You want him to see
a different side of you,
give him a chance to show
a different side of him.
You know what?
It doesn't matter anyway.
Harvey doesn't need
my help anymore.
It's too late.
No, it isn't.
Haven't you heard?
Heard what?
Harvey,
I have some bad news.
- What is it?
- I think you should sit down.
Donna, unless someone died,
I don't need to sit down.
Just tell me.
Hessington Oil just fired us.
- Scottie betrayed me.
- You don't know that.
One plus one equals two,
Donna.
And I know
how to goddamn add.
I didn't count
the Folsom money,
and suddenly
our oil revenues are gone
and her piece of the pie
just skyrocketed.
Harvey, please,
don't do anything rash.
What the hell
are you saying?
- I'm saying call her.
- How would that go?
"Hey, Scottie,
thanks for dicking me over.
Could you please
take it back?"
You don't know
how it would go.
And you could find out
if you would drop your pride
and just give her
the benefit of the doubt.
You gave someone
the benefit of the doubt,
and look how that turned out.
You think just because
you bought me a handbag,
you can say that to me?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
But I just got played,
and I'm not about to call
Scottie and cry about it.
- So what are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna figure out
how to do to her
what she just did to me.
- Harvey.
- Not now, Louis.
Yes, now, Harvey.
I've got the answer.
- The answer to what?
- To shoving
the Hessington Oil firing
up Edward Darby's ass.
Harvey.
Harvey!
Tony Gianopolous.
He can triple the revenue
we lost with Hessington Oil.
And they're technically
not a new client.
So there's nothing
Scottie can do.
Well, what makes you think
he's gonna go for it?
Because I went there,
and they are primed to say yes.
They just won't...
They just won't
say yes to me.
Give him this.
They'll say yes to you.
Louis, this is brilliant.
And if you hadn't had the balls
to come to me,
we'd have nothing
right now.
Harvey, no.
I should have come
to you sooner,
but I didn't because I just--
Louis.
I've told you this before,
but it's always been when
I needed something from you.
And I don't need anything
from you right now,
because you just gave it to me.
So maybe you can hear it
when I say it--
I respect you.
You're an excellent attorney,
a valuable member
of this firm.
And a friend?
Don't push it.
Sorry.
Seriously, Harvey,
I just have to say, um...
It means so much
when you say all that.
Do you need a tissue
or something?
- Can I use your pocket square?
- Under no circumstances.
I'll be fine.
And you and Jessica
need to take that over
to Gianopolous right now.
Screw that.
I'm going over there with you.
He's not there.
What?
Where is he?
He went to see
Tony Gianopolous.
- By himself?
- No, with Louis.
With Louis?
What, is he mad at me?
Rachel's the only one
who's mad at you.
- She told you.
- She didn't have to.
What were you thinking,
pulling all that shit
with her dad?
I didn't think
it would come to that.
He didn't mind.
Why should she?
Anyone who understands women
in any way
would know that was
a bad idea from the start.
- Harvey liked it.
- Proving my point.
I asked her
to move in with me.
I know.
She told you?
Of course she did.
I can't intuit everything.
What am I, the Dalai Lama?
Donna, you should have seen
her face when I asked her.
She was so happy.
I'm sure she was.
It was very romantic.
How could she be so happy
and then just not want to do it?
Who says
she doesn't want to do it?
I told her to take her time,
but I-I didn't think
she'd need it.
Why wouldn't she need it?
Just because you made
some romantic gesture
doesn't mean that all reason
goes out the window.
I've had a pit in my stomach
since last night.
I...
I need to do something.
You need to look
in the mirror.
What?
I just jumped into
a relationship with a man
who, it turns out,
was pretending to be
something he wasn't.
Rachel already knows
that you're pretending to be
something you're not.
All you need to do
is just give her time
to figure it all out.
What if she says no?
Then she says no.
But pushing her isn't going
to stop that from happening.
If you're here to complain
about Hessington Oil,
I had nothing to do with it.
I'm just
the majority shareholder.
I don't get involved
in day-to-day stuff.
- We're not here to complain.
- We're here to bring a gift.
The question is,
what do you get a man
who can burn a $50,000 bond?
Something money can't buy.
- This isn't public.
- It will be in 48 hours.
And it's legal now.
How do you know that?
Because I structured it
that way.
I can do more of the same
for you, but he didn't tell you,
because I wasn't enough
of a name.
- You're not.
- But I am.
Well, you are, as a man
who shoots from the hip,
which I like, but--
You also need
a stabilizing influence.
- Not a football player.
- But a fan of the ballet.
- Muscle.
- And finesse.
And you guys think
that I'm not aware
that this is all
about your merger negotiations.
Oh, I was counting on you
being aware of it.
Because then
you'll also be aware
that we can be very flexible
in our billings.
As long as I pay
enough up front
to tip the scales
in your favor.
We'll structure
a schedule that results
in you getting a substantial
financial benefit.
Which is his specialty.
Go ahead.
Tell him.
He's a badass.
What do you say we celebrate
our new association
over dinner in Chicago
with Michael Jordan?
We can take my private jet.
Hey! Which will allow us
to pay for it
and for you to write it off.
Hey.
I know you're probably
busy...
I'm actually not.
Look, Rachel, I...
I know that dating me
is complicated--
- Mike--
- I just--
I just want you to know you can
take as much time as you need.
I love you.
I love you too.
I got into Stanford.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
I see you got
my little gut punch.
I came to you hat in hand,
and this is what you do--
stack the numbers?
- Hat in hand?
More like a wolf
in sheep's clothing.
- What are you talking about?
- Hessington Oil.
I had nothing
to do with that.
Something dropped
from the sky,
tilted everything
in your favor
right after I cut you a break?
I don't think so.
Harvey, I gave you my word,
and I honored it.
Bullshit.
You're just saying that
because I've got
the upper hand.
This is not
about the upper hand.
You're always
about the upper hand!
Harvey, stop.
I came to you
and asked for mercy.
Do you know how hard
that was for me?
And then for me to turn around
and use that to dupe you--
how could you think
I would do that?
Well, what would you
have thought?
I don't know,
but you could have called me.
- And say what?
- And asked me
to exclude the firing
from the calculations.
I'm not gonna do--
What?
You're not gonna do what?
Not gonna give me
the benefit of the doubt
and be vulnerable--
expose yourself?
I already did that
when I trusted you.
That was mercy, which is
from a position of strength.
Being vulnerable is
from a position of weakness.
Well,
I'm not gonna do that.
Well, then I guess
I'm not going to either.
Meaning what?
Meaning that I am not going
to dissolve this merger.
You already signed
the agreement.
Then sue me.
You're gonna totally
shaft me anyway.
What's my downside?
In the meantime,
you'll have a name partner
who can't practice in America,
whose reputation is shit,
and who's gonna tie up
all your profits in litigation
for the next five years.
You're willing
to do all that
and expect me to believe
you weren't behind
us getting fired
in the first place.
She's telling the truth,
Harvey.
- What?
- Scottie didn't get us fired.
Ava Hessington did.
That doesn't mean anything.
Scottie
could have arranged it.
Well, she didn't,
because Ava
didn't just fire us.
She's suing all of us...
for malpractice.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man