Harvey, I don't need
a perp walk
or a front page headline.
I just want the person
responsible.
Then hand me the deal
we just negotiated
and justice will be served.
You know what, if this were
anyone else but you,
I wouldn't even be giving
the courtesy of this meeting.
Becky, we're both benefiting
from this.
You've got nothing
on my client.
And I'm gonna help you get
the person responsible.
So let me just go do that?
You better make sure
Miss Stone signs this.
Otherwise, we don't have a deal.
How long
have we known each other?
Since you were
in the D.A.'s office.
Then you know
we'll have a deal.
Talk to ya.
How'd it go
with the Department of Justice?
Follow me, you'll find out.
I get to sit in?
With your head down
and your mouth shut.
This isn't a usual... Ah.
- What are you doing?
- Quick.
Act like you're telling me
something important.
I am telling you
And then after the injunction,
you know, both parties decided
to reassess...
my God.
That woman with Rachel,
I took the LSATs for her
a couple years ago.
If she saw me,
she could blow my cover.
Oh, really?
And how would that go?
"Excuse me, when I was cheating
for my LSATs,
that was the guy
who took the test for me"?
Come on.
It could go down like that.
You don't know.
People say things.
Miss Stone, correct me
if any of this is wrong,
but you and I both know
it's not.
Please address me
and not my client, Mr. Specter.
You mean your client
who purchased $10 million
in Lunardi Pharmaceuticals
and then a day later
word of their FDA approval
got out
and the stock shot up
to $30 million?
She purchased that stock
for your clients,
Burt Kimball and Dean Morello,
based on a tip sheet
handed out by your clients.
An allegation that tainted
their reputation,
yet the D.O.J. looked into it
and found nothing.
That doesn't mean
it didn't happen.
I'll turn your client over
in person, no handcuffs.
It'll be a country club prison.
And I'll make sure
she's processed
as gently as possible
as long as she admits
that she made this trade
of her own accord.
It's a crappy deal
wrapped in pretty paper.
Why aren't we dealing
with the Department of Justice?
Because the D.O.J. wanted
to put you behind bars
for seven years, and I got 'em
down to 11 months.
Look, it's a great deal.
You're gonna sign it, you're
gonna serve your year in prison,
and every night when you climb
into your bunk,
you're gonna thank
your lucky stars
that Harvey Specter
negotiated on your behalf.
Nobody's ever gonna believe me,
and I don't have the resources
to fight this thing forever.
So I'll sign the goddamn deal.
But I'm not thanking anybody.
Harvey, you came through.
My company's reputation
means everything to me.
Thank you.
So I trust we won't be hearing
from the Department of Justice
again?
Unless you plan
on inviting them
to the company's
Christmas party, Bert, no.
I told Morello
you could fix this for us.
Thank you, Harvey.
Reality's starting to sink in.
Gabby's a little wound up
right now.
Let's give her a minute.
I've got the pretty papers
in my office
for you to look over.
Keep an eye on her.
You here to make sure
I don't change my mind
about the deal? No.
Would you?
You know,
my father was a teacher.
He worked hard,
followed the rules.
Last year, the district
cut his pension
to save their budget.
I went to Wall Street
so I could make some money
before getting
into teaching myself.
I never thought
I'd have to worry
if they let
convicted felons teach.
Can I get you some water
or something?
Oh...
I'm just gonna get you
some water.
Hey. I got it.
Thanks.
So that girl
you were with earlier,
she a friend of yours?
Theresa, yeah.
She used to be a paralegal here.
We were pretty close.
She worked at Pearson, Hardman?
Mm-hmm.
And I just had the unique
pleasure of giving her
the summer intern tour
for prospective employees.
- Really?
- Yeah.
She's in her second year
of Harvard Law,
meeting with the partners
as we speak.
- Huh.
- I know.
We used to do everything
together.
And now, if she gets this job,
she will technically be my boss.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry, Rachel.
Do you need to talk about it?
No. Not now. Thanks.
Oh, no, no. No.
What?
She's gone.
Ima Robot's Greenback Boogie
♪ see the money wanna stay
for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive,
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and missus
busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Yes, hey, hey ♪
♪ Suits 1x06 ♪ Tricks of the Trade
Original Air Date on July 28, 2011
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
You left her alone
to get her a water?
What, she didn't want a latte?
I was trying to be helpful.
You were very helpful to her.
You didn't see her, Harvey.
She was scared.
She was a wreck.
Maybe that had to do
with the fact that she was about
to go to prison for 11 months.
I think she was having the
reaction of an innocent woman.
And what was telling you that?
Your years
of investigative experience?
You know, I just... I listened
to her, that's all.
Let me tell you something,
okay.
Just because a pretty girl
tells you a story
doesn't mean it's true.
If she'd gone to trial,
the burden of proof would be
on the prosecution,
yet her own lawyer
told her to take the deal.
Not to mention
that innocent people
don't run.
I think this fell out
of her purse.
I found it here.
Why are you
telling me this now?
Because you were mad
at me before.
So your answer to that
is to delay giving me
important information?
Well, when you put it
like that.
Okay, I got to smooth things
over with the D.O.J.
That phone is our only lead.
Try not to lose it
before I get back.
Okay?
Becky, there's been
a slight hiccup
on the Gabby Stone business.
I don't want to hear
about any hiccups.
Did she sign the deal or not?
Well, she was about to.
My associate left her alone
for a second,
and she took off.
Gabby Stone's in the wind?
"In the wind"? Really?
The woman
isn't a world-class felon.
She'll turn up.
Well, it better be soon,
or the deal's off the table
and I'm going
after your clients.
That's funny.
I don't think so.
The SEC decided
they had no case,
and their burden of proof
is lower.
If you had something
on my clients,
you would have charged them
already.
Harvey, I went out
on a limb for you.
You make me look bad on this,
I promise you,
you'll regret it.
Donna, where the hell's Mike?
♪ ♪
♪ You're so pompous ♪
♪ You can't keep up ♪
♪ ♪
Hey, anyone know a guy
named Bradley?
Ball!
The guy's who about to miss
the jumper.
Do you have a last name?
Brickstein.
Do I look
like I have time for jokes?
Reger.
Bradley.
Mr. Reger.
- Ohh.
- Come on, Reger.
Bradley Reger!
Sorry, can I help you?
I'm sure you've heard
about the investigation
regarding Gabby Stone.
Are you
with the Department of Justice?
I...
I have several questions
for you.
Did you help Gabby
when she was charged
with insider trading?
Of course I did.
She wasn't just a trader.
She was my friend.
I recommended a lawyer
and let her borrow some cash
after you guys
froze her account.
That was Henderson.
He's a stickler for procedure.
Tell me, when was the last time
you saw her?
Bradley, let me inform you
that withholding knowledge
of the whereabouts
of a known fugitive
is a federal offense.
Do you understand me?
Gabby came in here
20 minutes ago.
She asked to borrow my keycard
to Morello Assets offices,
and I gave it to her.
Well, the department
appreciates your honesty.
Oh, and, Mr. Reger, put
a little arc in your jump shot,
all right?
If poor shooting were a crime,
I'd be forced to arrest you
right here.
It's embarrassing.
Go get 'em.
Harvey, I know where she is.
What are you doing here?
I told you I'd get her.
And I would let you.
I just wanted to make sure
she didn't get away again.
The water was right
outside the room, okay?
And you said innocent people
don't run.
Do guilty people run back
to the scene of the crime?
You don't know
what she's doing.
She could be planning
on taking a baseball bat
to all these computers
for all we know.
Gabby, what are you doing?
That stock was on my tip sheet.
It was on mine.
If I could find that tip sheet,
I could prove my innocence.
Is this what guilty people do?
I know they're your clients,
but can you help me, please?
I'm sorry.
You can either come with us,
or we'll have the Department
of Justice bring you in.
So I meant to ask you,
how did your friend's interview
go yesterday?
Theresa?
She didn't get the internship.
So how do you feel about that?
To be honest, I'm relieved.
I mean, she would have been
a daily reminder
of what I couldn't do,
that I'll never score
high enough
on the LSATs
or get into law school.
You know,
that doesn't have to be true.
It is. I need to accept
that I will always be
a paralegal
because of this stupid test.
I had a hard time
sleeping last night.
You want to know why? No.
Because Gabby Stone
is innocent.
Oh, I slept like a baby.
I don't think you believe that.
You think she's innocent too.
You just don't want
to pursue it.
She's not our client.
No, Morello is our client.
And if someone else
in that office is responsible
and they do it again,
won't that put our client
in jeopardy?
Ahh. Ooh, yep.
I'm right, and you know it.
And now you have
the responsibility
to investigate.
Did you tell that guy
at the basketball court
that you were an attorney
for the Department of Justice?
Not explicitly.
I mean, people hear
what they want to hear.
I won't impersonate
a federal agent again.
Probably a good idea.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, Mike, can I give you
my roommate's cat
for the weekend?
Let's get it over with.
I have some actual work to do.
No, no, no,
it's not what you think.
It's just very annoying,
and I figured
if you were looking after it,
the cat's as good as gone,
right?
Gentlemen.
What's going on?
Some sort of shenanigans?
Uh, no, it's nothing.
It's just stuff
between associates.
I said, "What's going on?"
Seth's just giving me
a hard time
for losing Gabby Stone
yesterday.
Oh, but we know at this firm
that we don't dwell
on our colleagues' mistakes,
right?
I mean, just because one
of your fellow associates
is incompetent doesn't mean
you have to constantly remind
this moron
what a careless idiot
he really is, right?
You.
Harold, I called you
two nights ago,
and you didn't answer
your phone,
which is really funny,
because you're
a first-year associate,
who's lucky enough
to be working here
at Pearson/Hardroao, so, when
I need to get a hold of you,
you will be reachable
at all times.
I don't care
if you're in a coma,
hospital
that's been burning down,
your mother's about to jump
off the Brooklyn Bridge,
you will pick up your phone.
- Absolutely.
- Got it?
Yes.
Okay, thanks.
Can you leave my office, please?
Harvey, once this whole
Morello thing gets fixed,
remind me to be irritated
with you for not billing more
on the Swindon merger.
The fact is mergers
are boring, okay?
Plus, I'm busy. Also, mergers?
Boring.
How'd you get these?
Oh, you mean tickets to
the Royal Shakespeare Company's
production of King Lear?
This show was sold out
the minute these tickets
went on sale.
I live for King Lear.
- How did you know that?
- It's my job to know that.
But why?
Louis, your billables
are outstanding.
You've landed
three high-profile clients
in a month, and I want
to show you my appreciation.
And I'm very happy
that you're excited.
So should we get dinner
before or after the play?
Uh, um, I-I don't know.
Jessica, do you remember
when we went
to that Yankee game
and you caught that foul ball
and you ate all my nachos?
Did we go to the steakhouse
that night?
Oh, that was a good meal.
That was fun.
Have a good time.
You know what, Louis,
dinner after.
I'll have Norma
make a reservation.
Fantastic.
Dean, Gabby Stone's
still making noises
about these tip sheets.
She insists that she had
a different sheet
on the day she bought Lunardi.
She was lying.
I understand,
but, after she broke
into your offices last night,
the D.O.J. might be inclined
to start rattling cases again.
So, for the record,
you're telling me the truth,
right?
Harvey,
you work for me, remember?
Well, as your lawyer,
I need to be able
to tell the D.O.J.
we're all aboveboard.
- Of course.
- So you won't mind
if I look around for myself?
We've had a clean record
for 50 years.
Please, Harvey, look around.
Why is that on my desk?
'Cause the LSATs are a week
from Saturday.
Great. Go away. I'm busy.
There are only four tests
a year, which means,
if you miss this one,
you're gonna have to wait
another three months.
I can do math too,
Good Will Hunting.
When did I say I was ready
to retake the LSATs?
I thought that,
after our talk...
Nothing about our talk
said I'm interested
in bombing the test again.
You're not gonna bomb it again.
- How do you know?
- Because the first time
you took it, you were missing
one essential ingredient...
Me.
Not interested.
If I let you help me,
will you leave me alone?
Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- I'll see you later.
Get excited.
Whoo-hoo.
Hey, I forget, why are we
looking into Gabby Stone again?
Oh, right,
because I said she's innocent,
and now you agree with me.
No, I don't agree with you
that she's innocent,
but, if there's even
the slightest chance
that someone else is involved,
they're putting
the whole company at risk,
and I can't have that.
Okay, so you disagree
with what we agree about?
Oh, I'll agree with that.
I don't feel sorry
for Gabby Stone at all.
Because?
I found her.
I was her immediate supervisor.
I nurtured her.
Then she tries to cheat
and give us a bad name.
How commonplace would you say
cheating is here?
It's not. It's not the kind
of shop we run.
So when Miss Stone
made the trade
and the investment tripled
in value,
you weren't suspicious?
My job's not to worry
about the traders
that are making money.
My job's to worry
about the traders who aren't.
So how exactly
does the tip sheet system work?
Our technical analyst
predicts stocks
that are likely to have
larger-than-expected volatility.
These predictions are handed out
to our traders
on a daily basis in the form
of a tip sheet.
All these traders
get the same tip sheet?
Exactly.
They're printed on red paper,
so they can't be copied.
Every trader is responsible
for returning
their sheet
at the end of the day,
so they can be shredded.
So no records exist?
We keep electronic copies.
I'll need to see those copies
for the last year.
I thought you might.
I'm assuming you own a computer.
One more thing.
I'll need to see a list
of all the trades.
Morello Assets made
in the last year.
Well, I can't give you that.
Why not?
Tip sheets have expired.
But our current positions...
that's proprietary information.
And I can't release that
on just your say-so.
That's not a request.
We need to protect the company.
And we're covered
under attorney-client privilege.
And I'm telling you
I'm not giving you sh...
You think I don't know what
attorney-client privilege is?
You know, you corporate lawyers
look down your noses at us
because we didn't go
to Ivy League schools.
Just because I don't have
a fancy degree
doesn't mean you get
to come into my house
and order me around.
And you go whine to Morello
and I'll knock you on your ass
like the pussy you are.
Well, Sam, I'm sorry
that you feel that way,
but I've been working
for your boss Dean Morello
for a very long time,
and let me tell you something.
You try to stonewall me,
you'll be out on the street
in less than a week.
As for the other stuff,
do I think
that I'm smarter than you?
You're damn right I do.
But if you think that means
that I can't kick your ass
up and down this floor,
take a swing
and see what happens.
I didn't think so.
That was amazing.
It was like he was Mr. T
and you were Rocky,
but not like Rocky at the
beginning when he was all scared
of Mr. T, but at the end,
when he was all like,
"Ooh, give it your best shot."
You know?
"Adrian!" Yes!
That's funny, but you might
want to wipe that grin
off your face. What? Why?
Because without those trades,
we don't have sh...,
and your little girlfriend's
gonna rot in jail.
And by the way, you got to work
on your Stallone.
You need a lower register.
"Uhh."
That was
an incredible Stallone.
I've been doing that since I was
a kid, and you can't touch it.
- "Uhh."
- Don't do that
with food in your mouth.
No, I swallowed it.
"Uhh."
There's food in your mouth.
- "Adrian."
- That's disgusting.
Come on. You got this one.
It's "A".
No, it's "C".
Actually, it's "D".
It's definitely "D".
Final answer?
Yes, "D".
It's "A".
Rachel, you got to remember
they're asking why the argument
is most vulnerable.
I can make the case
that they're
all vulnerable arguments.
You could, but your
first instinct was "A".
You got to go with your gut.
Right.
So what if my gut can find
the exception
where "A" is wrong.
What am I supposed to do then?
- You ignore it.
- I can't.
That's easier said than done.
The test isn't trying
to trick you, Rachel.
But sometimes it is, Mike.
- Well, you got to let that go.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- 'Cause I don't want
to get any questions wrong.
Okay.
I think we found your problem.
You're so afraid of getting
fooled by a few trick questions
that you're letting it mess
you up with all the other ones.
Look, Rachel, you want
to get into Harvard,
you need a 170. Okay?
If you let a few
of these trick questions go,
you're gonna be fine.
But if you keep trying
to be perfect,
you're gonna overthink
this whole thing.
You're gonna end up with a 130.
Rachel.
Nobody gets
all the trick questions.
What about you?
First grade,
they gave me
an achievement test.
I scored in the 99th percentile,
so they kept giving me
achievement tests
all the way up
to the eighth grade level.
And I kept getting
in the 99th percentile
with every one of 'em.
You couldn't get the 100th?
There is no 100th.
Next question. Come on.
King Lear.
I happen to like King Lear.
And unlike some people I know,
Louie's references don't begin
and end with Top Gun.
Hey, I love Louis,
and I don't care
what you say,
I am not leaving my wingman.
See, that's funny,
because that's from Top Gun.
He's a wild card.
Flies by the seat of his pants.
Think I can't quote Top Gun.
Get the hell out of here.
Oh, that was good.
Hey, Mike.
Burt Kimball's coming
to see me.
I need you in the meeting.
Oh, the number two at Morello?
Bet he's coming to yell at you
after your big showdown there
yesterday.
If you need me,
I got your back.
Thinking about finally going
to law school?
Oh, no,
I'm helping Rachel study.
Pretty paralegal. Got it.
Okay. It's not like that.
It's exactly like that.
Oh, that reminds me.
How did you manage
to take the LSATs for a woman?
What do you mean?
We took the test the same day.
She signed my name on hers,
and I signed hers on mine.
Why? What's so funny?
I just pictured you in drag.
I could pull that off.
I've got soft features.
I want to apologize
for Samuel's behavior.
He's had a chip on his shoulder
ever since
the Department of Justice
investigated Miss Stone's
malfeasance.
He's very protective
of the firm.
That's a good man
to have in your corner.
Well, so are you.
In these folders, you'll find
every trade made by Morello
Assets in the last year.
Personally delivered by
Burt Kimball, I'm flattered.
Well, we just want to make sure
you've got everything you need,
Harvey.
We really appreciate
your diligence.
Now I better get back
to the office.
The Australian markets
are just opening up.
Good to see you.
Always a pleasure, Burt.
Harvey, this is great.
We can take
these tip sheets and put them...
what are you doing?
This guy's not that friendly
to his own mother.
He's hiding something,
and I'm pissed.
What are you talking about?
Those aren't the real trades.
Okay. So how do we get them?
Right. How do I get them?
Hmm.
Hello?
You figure out how to get
the most profitable trades yet,
Mike?
The Morello brokers hang out
at a bar
called the Closing Bell.
I'm on my way now. Good.
Just remember you're working.
I'll talk to you later.
♪ Something's got me
thinking about you ♪
♪ ♪
Can I get a beer?
Thanks.
♪ Something's got me
thinking about you ♪
Hey, hey, hey,
what's up, toolbox?
Oh, man. You know, you drink
that beer any slower,
I'm gonna have
to get you a nipple.
Do I know you?
Vince Landis, Morello asset.
Yeah, that's me.
Yeah. Russell Ginther.
The Ginth.
The Ginthesizer.
- What are you talking about?
- Come on, Gervich Investments.
Man, we got shithoused here
a couple weeks ago.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
You, me, Pepiol, Causwell,
Williamson.
That guy, dick.
You still owe me 20 bucks.
Yeah, right. Russell.
- Right, Russell.
- You still begging for scraps
over there at Gervich or what?
You wish.
Hey, I need a shot.
What is this?
No, drink mine, please.
Mm. Jaeger?
You're better than that, man.
Money!
God, you guys are a bunch
of pussies.
I guarantee you
my biggest trades kick the ass
out of your biggest trades.
I don't think so, brother.
Last month, I made $2 million
on Cahill Metal in one hour.
$2 million?
I made $4 million
off of Montroluxx
back in February.
That stock tripled over night.
What's up? $4 million?
Oh, that's adorable.
How about the $6 million
I just cleared
on Rypien Micro Devices.
Oh, yeah?
What do you think my boy here
made on Piper Web Systems?
What, this guy?
- Right here.
- Uh-huh.
Uh, I don't know.
A pack of chewing gum
and your sister's panties.
Oh, it's on.
Ohh!
Vince Landis! $7 million off
of Drogin Limited.
$8 million off of Epling RTX.
$9 million off
of RMA Integrated Products.
Well, gentlemen, greed is good.
So is his sister. Right?
Come on, man.
That's his sister.
That's not cool.
Dude, you just made,
like, the same joke.
Aahh!
Hey, Bradley's finally here.
Uh, all right, ladies.
Listen, I got to split.
It's been real.
I'll get drinks next time,
all right?
- Right.
- Make money, money, make money.
♪ ♪
Ah.
Harvey. I got the trades.
Good. We'll talk tomorrow.
What? No. I'm coming over now.
You're drunk. Do not come over.
All right. Cool.
I'll see you in a minute.
Hey.
Harvey, come on.
We got to save Gabby.
Gabrilini.
Oh.
Oh, you got a sweet place, dude.
Don't ever call me dude.
Do you think that maybe
I could take it off your hands,
like, when you go out of town?
Like a house-sitting-type
situation?
Remind me to have Donna
get you a spare key.
You have the trades?
Tada.
Good.
Hey, when can we...
I'm still upset that
I didn't get the internship.
It would have been so much fun
to work together,
don't you think?
Oh, absolutely.
Let me ask you something.
How did you turn it around
with the LSATs?
What do you mean?
Well, come on.
You took 'em,
didn't do so well,
and now you're at Harvard Law.
It's exactly what I want
to be doing.
So you can tell me.
What'd you do,
sleep with the grader?
What?
I paid someone
to take them for me.
What?
There's this guy.
I heard about him
from a friend of a friend's.
Paid him 1,000 bucks
and he took the LSATs for me.
He got me a 172.
You cheated on the LSATs?
When we were paralegals,
we were smarter
than half the associates.
Why should I be denied
my chance
because I can't pass
some stupid test?
I'm living my dream, Rache.
I'm not gonna apologize for it
to anyone.
Come on. Come on.
Hello?
Mikey, yo, it's Scott.
Scott? How are you, man?
I haven't talked to you
in forever.
Are you still taking LSATs
for other people?
I got a customer for you.
No, man.
I'm not in that business
anymore.
I'm sorry. Trust me.
You want to take
this meeting, dude.
This chick is smoking hot.
What's her name?
Rachel Zane.
You didn't give her my name,
did you?
No. Of course not.
I'm not taking
that meeting, man.
What do you want me
to sign now?
A confession
that I killed Kennedy?
I'm not gonna pretend
to be your best friend,
Miss Stone.
But my interests happen to be
aligned with yours right now,
so please sit down.
Your colleagues'
most profitable trades.
Why are you showing them to me?
Every single one of them
comes from stocks
that Morello Assets
didn't officially recommend.
This is either a hell
of a coincidence,
or these traders were all given
different tip sheets.
So you believe me when I said
my tip sheet had
Lunardi Pharmaceuticals on it.
Well, I'm getting there,
but you got flagged
by the D.O.J.
And no one else at Morello did,
so I want to know why.
What's different here?
None of these trades
are for more than $9 million.
That's Morello's
recommended amount.
And your Lunardi purchase
was for $10 million.
Maybe someone figured out
that any trade under $10 million
wouldn't draw D.O.J. attention.
Why'd you make a trade
for $1 million more
than the recommended amount?
Look at me.
I'm not exactly
fraternity material.
It's a cutthroat world,
and I wasn't performing well.
So I took a chance,
and I tried to hit it big.
I picked the wrong trade.
Gabby, if you knew
you were innocent,
then why didn't you fight this
harder?
After I saw how much money
the trade made,
I suspected something.
I went to Burt Kimball,
he reassured me that I made
a profitable trade
and did nothing wrong.
He even told me
I had a $300,000 bonus
coming at the end
of the quarter.
I should have gone to someone,
said something.
I made one mistake,
and I'm gonna regret it
for the rest of my life.
Scott. Yeah, it's Mike Ross.
This Rachel Zane,
tell her I'll take the meeting.
Just don't tell her my name.
Who's that on the phone?
It's nothing.
You thinking about Gabby?
I'm thinking about her lawyer.
- What?
- Knowing what she said,
why would that Zegan guy
agree to a deal
that puts his client behind bars
without even putting up a fight?
I can't stand
that kind of shoddy work.
It's like the bad version
of both of us.
He doesn't care about his client
and he's not about winning.
He's got even less style
than you.
I don't really see
how that's relevant.
Like at all. Hold on.
How did she get this lawyer?
Her friend Bradley.
The one who also works
at Morello?
Yeah.
I don't think Bradley's
as good a friend
as she thinks he is.
Here's what you're gonna do.
I looked into it.
You were right.
Put this together fast.
I care about Gabby.
You were right too.
You want me to go with you?
I'm sorry, but I got
to take care of this one myself.
Hot dogs, hamburgers.
- Thank you.
- Hot dogs, hamburgers.
Rachel?
What are you doing
all the way over here?
This guy has
the best soft pretzels in town.
Do you want to try it?
No, I'm good.
Hey, how are you feeling
about the LSATs?
I was really happy with all
the prep we did yesterday.
I'm really excited for you.
You're excited for me?
Why do you even care?
Hot dogs, hamburgers.
- I was just asking.
- Well, just stop asking.
Look, I came down here
because I just want
to be by myself
and I bump into you,
and the first thing
you want to talk about
is the LSATs.
Hey, sorry.
The truth is, I came down here
to clear my head too.
About what?
Gabby Stone.
The girl who did
the insider trading?
She actually suspected
that something was wrong
after the trade, but she didn't
do anything about it.
She didn't want
to jeopardize her career.
Now she's gonna be paying
for that mistake
for the rest of her life.
Anyway, I'm sorry
I ruined your alone time.
I'll see you back at the office.
Let me ask you something, Nick.
Does Burt Kimball drag his feet
paying you too?
Excuse me?
'Cause in my experience,
getting money
from that asshole is like
getting blood from a stone.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Yes, you do.
See, after I saw your client
sitting in jail,
I got to wondering.
How'd she find you?
- I'm gonna call security.
- Absolutely.
See, it turns out
that her friend Bradley
recommended you.
Bradley, who's been
at Morello Assets
for the past seven years.
So I checked.
You know what I found?
You represented Burt Kimball
in a civil suit 12 years ago.
It just so happens
you also represented.
Lunardi Pharmaceuticals in
their FDA approval proceedings.
That doesn't mean anything.
You've seen my relationship
with the D.O.J.
Want me to point them
in your direction?
Or do you want to admit to me
that Burt Kimball's
paying you off?
Harvey,
I don't understand.
I thought all this business
was done with.
It's almost sorted out, Dean.
I'm just here to let you know
that Burt's a crook.
What did you say?
Harvey.
He used a lawyer
to periodically provide him
with insider information.
Once he got this information,
he handed out one tip sheet
different from all the others,
so the trader, in this instance,
Gabrielle Stone,
would make a trade not knowing
that she was acting
on an illegal tip.
It was actually ingenious.
If the trade
was ever under suspicion,
even the trader couldn't point
to Burt.
We've heard more than enough,
thank you.
I don't think so.
Miss Stone made two mistakes.
One, she made a trade
for more than $9 million.
And the other was not going
to the D.O.J.
the second the stock shot up
through the roof.
You son of a bitch.
Harvey, this is a lot
to digest.
Well, I'll make it easy
for you, Dean.
He's a cancer.
You don't cut him loose, he's
gonna kill your whole company.
How dare you walk in here
and accuse me with these things?
I mean, you are my lawyer.
No, Burt, I'm the lawyer
for Morello Asset Management.
As far as the law is concerned,
Dean Morello's my client,
not you.
Dumb son of a bitch.
Burt, you're fired.
What?
Effective immediately.
You're gonna fire me?
Because of this?
I hope you're happy.
'Cause without me,
this hedge fund's nothing.
I'll be happy
when the Department of Justice
puts your ass in handcuffs.
Enjoy your freedom, Burt,
because they're coming for you.
And since you're a bigger trophy
than Gabrielle Stone,
you're gonna get a whole lot
more than 11 months.
Harvey, I want you to know
that I knew nothing
about any of this.
Dean, when I was 13 years old,
my little brother
was getting bullied by a kid
in the neighborhood.
One day, I confronted
the kid's father.
He told me he didn't know
anything about it.
You know what his problem was?
It was his goddamn job to know.
Thanks for getting me out.
We're just sorry
we couldn't get you your bonus.
It wasn't mine to begin with.
But without it, I don't know
how I'm gonna pay you.
Don't worry about it.
Dean Morello's
footing this bill.
You believed in me.
I can't tell you how grateful
I am to both of you.
Never doubted you for a second.
Oh, Gabby, I wanted
to give you something.
Left it on your desk.
Thank you.
All right, well,
I'm gonna find some water.
You don't come back soon,
we're sending out
a search party.
You never doubted her
for a second?
I didn't doubt her
for a second.
I doubted her for days.
Yeah, that's not what
you just led her to believe.
People hear
what they want to hear.
Oh, I meant to ask you,
that big guy
that you got in a fight with,
Mr. T,
was he in on this whole thing?
No, he was just a dick.
That was
the most brilliant portrayal
of King Lear I have ever seen.
"Come up between the dragon
and his wrath."
That was...
Thank you for tonight,
Jessica, really.
This was nice.
This is really, really nice.
You're welcome, Louis.
And, yes, this was...
this was really nice.
Listen, I just want you to know
how much I appreciate
everything that you do
for this firm.
I take a lot of pride
in my work.
I know, and you're very good
at what you do.
Okay, can you just please say
that once in front
of Harvey?
Louis, I know you and Harvey
have a rivalry.
And the truth
is that, right now,
Harvey is more valuable
to the firm.
But that doesn't always mean
that he is going to be on top.
Because another truth is
is that I can't always count
on Harvey to listen to me,
but I can count on you.
Yeah. Yes, you can.
So you keep doing
what you're doing, Louis,
and you're gonna be just fine.
And if he doesn't know it
already,
I promise
Harvey is going to understand
just how valuable
you are to me.
You know, next week
there's a revival of Cats.
No.
Nice touch.
Tickets to the Yankee game.
Found 'em on my desk.
Can't wait. You're welcome.
Nachos are on you this time.
Oh, those tickets
aren't for you and me.
They're for you and Louis.
Sunday the 20th.
Did I mention
that I'm busy that night?
I know you are.
You're busy going
to the Yankee game
with Louis.
Son, your ego's writing checks
that your body can't cash.
Oh, see, that's funny,
because now I'm quoting.
Top gun and...
get out of my office.
Very funny. Very funny.
Very funny.
Mike.
Hey, you got a second?
I just...
I just want to thank you.
Thank me for what?
For going out of your way
to help me with the LSATs.
It's nothing.
I'm sure you'd do
the same for me.
I put a lot of pressure
on myself.
I always have.
You're right.
I'm a perfectionist.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
My dad, he always wanted a son.
Never something
that they brought up.
It was just sort of there.
And I never felt
like I was good enough for him.
Which is why I don't like
to put myself in positions
where I might fail.
So I decided
to just push the LSATs,
give myself
a little more time to study.
That's good. That's great.
I think you made
the right choice.
Really? Why?
You were the one that's been
pushing me to take them
next week.
I just meant that I, you know,
support the decision you made.
Why are you suddenly changing
your tune?
Because if you're not ready,
you're not ready.
Listen, I got to go.
I'll see you tomorrow.
No, that's not why.
All that interest in Theresa
and then the other guy
didn't show up, but you did.
You were gonna take
the test for me.
What guy?
What are you talking about?
You know exactly
what I'm talking about.
You're the test genius, right?
- Um...
- Mike, I could pick up
the phone
and find out right now.
Yes, I took the test
for your friend Theresa.
That's the whole reason
you were trying to help me.
Because you thought
if you didn't,
you were gonna get caught.
That's not true.
How am I supposed
to believe that?
Honestly, how am I supposed
to believe anything you say
when the whole time
you were at Harvard
studying to be a lawyer,
you were actually cheating
for other people?
Yes, I was helping people
cheat, okay, but...
But what?
It's not the whole story.