You lose,
we don't merge.
You win,
you get what you want.
You lose,
you stay.
You extend
your noncompete,
and you get a chance to earn
your name on the door,
because it's not
going up there now.
There's no room
for both of us.
Unless we made room
for each other.
I put him on the list,
and I handed it in.
He didn't put you
on his list.
- I won't.
- You will.
Harvey will never
forgive me.
This is a letter
to the district attorney,
saying that you
are breaking the law.
You file your motion,
I'll file mine.
You weren't there.
- I didn't have to be.
- Jessica--
You don't work for Jessica.
You work for me.
You're fired.
No, he's not.
You could've just told me
that you didn't love me
instead of selling me out.
I didn't sell you out,
Scottie.
I just got fired.
Whatever she did,
you wouldn't have this merger
without her.
Would you have her work here
or in London?
You're going
to stay here,
be humble,
and learn
your goddamn place.
I never went
to Harvard.
What?
I'm a fraud.
[Rock music]
♪
Hey.
I got your message.
What's going on?
Partners meeting.
Essential personnel only.
In the middle
of the night?
You afraid
of the dark?
I wouldn't be if I had
my Cookie Monster with me.
Well, then go get him,
because we're finalizing
the terms of the merger.
We?
We.
So I'm a partner now?
Easy, Marcia Clark.
Jessica and I
discussed it.
You're responsible
for making this merger happen.
You deserve
to be here.
So Jessica and you
talked?
You forgave her?
She won.
I lost.
Nothing to forgive.
And me?
You did
what you had to do.
[Sighs]
You have no idea
how much I needed to hear that.
[Applause]
The merger is complete.
And we would like
to show everyone
that the new Darby Pearson
will be stronger,
better connected--
And most importantly,
based on a foundation that is--
Full of shit.
What the hell's
going on?
- I told her.
- Told her what?
That Mike Ross
is a fraud,
and I am not going
to let him get away with it.
How could you do this?
You did this
to yourself.
[Panting]
How long are you going
to keep staring at that offer?
Until one of us blinks.
Deron signed it.
You said it was great.
I'm not interested
in great.
I want it to know
who its daddy is.
What is it, Donna?
It's Sunday night.
Darby needs an answer.
London.
Send her to London.
Do you want
to talk about it?
Have Ray
meet me downstairs.
And where should I say
you're going?
Brooklyn.
[Rock music]
♪
I did not expect
the great Harvey Specter
to come all the way
to Brooklyn
just to deliver
a contract.
That's good,
'cause I came for the hot dogs.
I told you,
that was our final offer.
You did,
but the third quarter's
about to end,
and if you want Deron Williams
playing for you
in the fourth,
this is his number.
Even if you had
another offer,
which you don't,
he can't leave
in the middle of a game.
I was talking
about the fourth quarter
of game seven,
when you're looking
to lock up a championship,
because the question isn't
"do you want Deron or not?"
It's "do you want
a ring or not?"
You got nothing.
And I told you,
that's my final offer.
Then I guess I'll just have
to go bring Deron
his new Mavs jersey then.
There's no way
Mark Cuban pays that much.
Why don't you call him
and ask?
Oh, wait, you can't,
because he hates you.
Bullshit.
We may not
be blood brothers,
but he doesn't
hate me.
Oh, he does now.
Evidently, he found out
about that thing from last May.
How do you know that?
Because I was there
when I told him.
You have
until 10:00 a.m.
Then I'm calling Dallas.
And Mark may not
take your call,
but he'll sure as hell
take mine.
How do I know
you're not going to turn around
and get him
to pay more?
You don't.
But if you don't
match this,
you'll never find out.
[Rock music]
♪
Jessica.
Harvey.
I don't recall
giving you my key.
I don't recall authorizing you
to negotiate
behind Deron Williams' back.
His back
is just fine.
I'm standing
right behind it.
Then why is the contract
he signed in my hand?
How much
did you ask for?
Triple.
You out of your mind?
We have leverage.
And what is that?
- It's complicated.
- Simplify it for me.
- I bluffed him.
- That's not leverage.
It is
if he believes it.
And if it fails,
he fires us
and takes ten other players
with him.
Then it better not fail.
You asked the man
for triple.
If I had what I said I had,
that's what I'd get.
I don't ask for triple,
he knows I'm bluffing.
Then don't bluff
in the first place.
I'm afraid
that's what I do.
You know
what I think?
I think you want it
to fail.
I think
you're stuck
with a merger
you don't want
and a noncompete
you can't stand,
and you're trying
to get me to fire you.
I could bust
that noncompete wide open.
But you gave me
your word.
Which is
why I'm staying.
Jessica, I've always
operated this way.
It's what you hired me for,
it's what you pay me for,
and it used to be
what you valued me for.
I'm not going
to fire you.
Neither is Deron Williams.
Nets just caved.
So unless you're looking
to cook me breakfast tomorrow,
I'd say we're done.
[Rock music]
[Knock at door]
♪
I told you
I needed time.
I know,
but it's been two days,
and I can't
take it anymore.
I had to see you.
I don't want any comments
about how messy the place is.
Okay.
And what would clean
look like?
Don't even think
about it.
I can't not think
about it, all right?
It's all I've been able
to think about for two days.
Mike, why are you here?
Because that's not going
to happen.
Now or ever?
[Scoffs] You lied to me
about everything.
Rachel--
Do you remember
when I told you I needed time?
That's what
I needed it for--
to process this bomb
that you dropped on me.
I had a nightmare.
You asked why I'm here.
That's why.
I--
you exposed me
to the entire firm.
- I would never do that.
- I know.
And I woke up,
and I realized
that the real nightmare
wouldn't even be that.
The real nightmare
would be--
would be if you didn't want
to be with me.
Do you really
mean that?
I meant it
the first time I ever saw you.
Rachel, I know that I'm not
who you want me to be,
but--but you know
what happened in that room.
You know
what we both felt.
I--
I don't want
to lose that.
I just keep wishing
you never told me.
But then it never
would have happened.
And it did.
And I'm--
I'm really glad
that it did.
I am too.
But what happens
if you get caught?
Because what you had
may have been a nightmare, Mike,
but you can't tell me
you're not afraid
of being exposed.
Of course I am.
But there's nothing
that I can do about it.
Well, maybe there is.
What are you saying?
Quit.
Go in tomorrow,
and just quit.
♪ See the money wanna stay,
for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie,
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know,
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see,
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive
of your mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so very
busy busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
3x01
The Arrangement
♪ The Greenback Boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
for www.addic7ed.com
[Alternative music]
♪
[Knocking on door]
I need to talk to you.
You want to talk
about how things played out,
but the place to do that
is somewhere more private.
You didn't just come through
on the merger.
You bluffed Hardman,
turned Monica Eton,
and put us over the top
on Folsom Foods.
Now that's a lot
of coming through in the clutch.
And I wouldn't have saved
your ass
if I didn't think
you deserved to be here.
I don't know
what to say.
Well, the usual response is
"thank you."
The usual road
to getting here
doesn't involve
stabbing someone in the back.
Doesn't it?
When I was 16,
I came home,
my mother sat me down,
and said my parents
were separating.
Trial basis.
But the good news was
she was going to get me a car
to help with my sister.
All my friends talked about
how lucky I was to have it.
I hated that car.
Every time I got in it, I--
it just reminded me.
Why are you telling me this?
Because five years later,
that same car got me to Harvard,
which led me here.
So you can think
of this office
as a reminder
of what you did to Harvey
or as a symbol
of what you can accomplish
at the firm.
Now, do you still
have something to say?
No.
No, I don't.
They ever get back together?
No.
No, they didn't.
Ah, God!
Damn it!
Louis, what happened?
Oh.
I'll tell you what happened.
This stupid merger.
It's bad enough
my vote is worth
1/3 of what it was
last week.
Now our uni-balls, gone.
Our... What?
Pens, Donna.
The new quartermaster,
Barbara L. Tottingham, will not
buy us any more uni-balls.
There's not one single uni-ball
in this entire firm.
- Please stop saying uni-ball.
- No, I will not.
Stuck
with these stupid plastic things
that keep breaking.
So buy your own pen.
Bu
okay.
There are two things
in this firm
that I hold very sacred--
my uni-balls
and my raspberry Bran bars.
And if I have to go
and buy 'em myself,
well, then,
this Barbara L. Tottingham
has a message for me,
loud and clear,
and that's "Louis Litt,
go screw yourself."
Louis, the ink on your face.
You've got just, like--
you've got, like,
a little bit right there.
Where, here?
No, I think you've gotta
give it, like, a good--
Okay, fine.
Gone?
Thank you, Donna.
You're a true friend.
I got your back.
Hey, do you remember
when you used to do
those rotator cuff exercises?
Oh, yeah,
what are you kidding? Of course.
Every day for, like, 18 months.
Why do you ask?
No reason.
Edward.
Jessica,
how lovely to see you.
I wanted to thank you.
- Ah. You saw the sign.
- Mm-hmm.
You didn't have
to do that.
Our agreement stipulates
Darby Pearson,
not Pearson Darby.
Our agreement also stipulates
a 51/49 percentage structure.
And this is your way
of showing me
that you think of it
as 50/50.
- Merely a gesture.
- Ah.
Heck of a gesture.
How would you propose
to a woman?
A woman?
I think we both know that--
Yes, we do.
[Laughs]
Anyway...
It is shaping up
to be a lovely day.
Oh, I wish
I could say that same.
I assume you know
about the latest goings-on
with Hessington Oil.
I wouldn't be much
of a partner if I didn't.
Now they've decide to take on
Ava Hessington personally.
- Who is they?
- The U.S. government.
I've decided to let Harvey
handle it.
- Why?
- Why not?
It's not a good time.
He's still digesting
the merger.
- Meaning?
- He's acting out.
Well, he may be
acting out,
but I understand he just got
his client triple the money.
By taking a huge risk
he didn't have to.
This case,
he may have to.
So that's why Harvey.
And this case is more
important to me than just money.
And why is that?
Because it is.
What if I said no?
[Laughs]
I'm afraid that's not an option.
So I guess
that sign
really doesn't mean 50/50
after all.
I did say
it was merely a gesture.
Hmm.
You keep showing up
to surprise me,
people are gonna
get the wrong idea.
People are going to think
what they're going to think.
I'm here to bury the hatchet.
And what prompted that?
Darby found out what you did
with Deron Williams.
Don't tell me.
He was impressed.
He was pissed.
Thinks you're trying
to get fired.
And you told him
how smart he was.
I told him
you said it wasn't true
and that I believed you,
and then I fought to give you
a chance to prove it.
Ava Hessington.
I got you on it.
What does that matter
to me?
Harvey,
I know you and I
have had our problems,
but this is a chance
for us to move past it.
Let's take it.
You really do
wanna make up.
I never wanted to be at odds
in the first place.
Neither did I.
Are we good?
Don't you wanna tell me
I better win this goddamn case?
I didn't think
I had to.
Never stopped you
from saying it before.
Well, I'm learning
to let go.
Oh, Harvey,
there is one more thing.
You better win
this goddamn case.
I know
it's not my place,
but you really suck
at quitting.
I can explain.
No need.
It was just a suggestion.
Rachel, I tried to do it,
but--
But then Jessica
gave you this office to stay?
Actually,
she gave me this office
before I could even
bring it up.
Well, aren't you
just the luckiest person
in the world?
Rachel--
You came to me,
you were petrified
of being exposed,
and I gave you a way out.
And now, 12 hours later,
you're in a brand-new office
with a diploma on the wall
that, for all I know,
came from Kinko's.
What do you want me to do?
Everyone hangs one.
No, Mike,
everyone doesn't just hang one.
So that's
what this is really about.
You're damn right
it is.
I've been trying to earn one
for as long as I can remember.
And you have one and everything
that goes with it,
and you didn't do
a single thing to deserve it.
You have no idea
what I have or haven't done
to get where I am.
And that's
the whole problem.
I have no idea
who you are.
Harvey, I'm just in the middle
of a little afternoon crossword.
Are you a puzzler?
Don't you have work
to do?
My dear fellow,
if I have to do work,
then I'm not doing my job.
What can I do
for you?
Jessica told me
that you agreed to let me
be lead on Ava Hessington.
I wanted to thank you.
- You're welcome.
- There's just one problem.
You didn't agree to anything.
You demanded it.
And you let Jessica
play good cop
because you didn't wanna
undermine the chain of command.
That's quite
the conspiracy theory.
Well,
here's the good news.
My plate's a little full
right now.
And since you didn't want me
on this case in the first place,
why don't you let
somebody else handle it?
Good luck.
I hear it's a tough one.
What do you want?
I want out.
I win this,
you tear up my noncompete,
and you fire me.
You hate this merger
that much.
I had an agreement
with Jessica,
and I honored it.
Then she accused me
of trying to get fired.
Then she lied to me
by claiming
that she fought for me
to be on this case.
She really does wanna
make up with you, you know.
Funny way
of showing it.
Ironic.
Her belief that you wanted
to be fired
led you to wanting
to be fired.
Do we have
a deal or not?
[Inhales]
It appears we do.
Oh, hey.
Uh, go ahead.
No, that's all right.
You were here first.
Why are you being
so polite?
Come on, you have
one stupid copy.
You could've finished it
already.
[Sighs]
Louis, I--
A letter of resignation?
Why?
It's complicated.
Well, simplify it for me,
Mike.
Harvey.
He's the one
who hired me.
Now he wants nothing
to do with me.
What are you talking about?
He just gave you a new office.
No, Jessica gave me
a new office.
If it was up to Harvey,
I wouldn't even have a cubicle.
What happened?
All that matters is that,
uh, I can't fix it.
You know, when we were
in the bullpen,
Harvey was like Superman.
And then, one day,
Hardman decided to just
knock him down a peg.
Gave him
this bullshit assignment,
undoable workload,
unwinnable case.
And I took it
as a chance
to break down his walls
and offer my help.
And I just thought,
this just might be
the chance
that we could become--
- Friends.
- Yeah.
And he looked at me--
how dare I?
I get it.
He's alone.
He always has been.
He always will be.
Always was.
Harvey is
not Superman anymore.
He's Batman.
And Batman needs Robin.
And I just need
to remind him of that.
What's the one thing
that Harvey values
over everything else?
- Winning.
- Yeah.
You help him win,
he'll remember
why he needs you.
I have to figure out
what cases he's working on.
The I.T. Department
has access to every computer
in the entire firm,
syncs up every night.
So all I have to do is get
access to Harvey's hard drive.
That place is a fortress.
Both: Benjamin.
[Clears throat]
It's you.
Aw, that's sweet.
You remember me.
Oh, yes.
I remember everyone
who's ever bamboozled me
into giving them
a top-of-the-line laptop.
Their names
are Michael Ross.
I didn't bamboozle you,
Benjamin.
I won it
fair and square.
And I've been tracking
every Internet move you've made
for the past ten months,
waiting for the slipup.
Bet you thought you had me
at teenybikini.com.
No.
No, no.
Because I cross-referenced that
with your workplace
harassment case, and I knew.
But don't think I'm not aware
that you went home for dinner
and used your personal computer
to go back there.
Okay,
that's not actionable,
but hacking
my personal computer is.
Good luck proving that.
Now, what do you want?
- I want access to a hard drive.
- No way.
Not only that,
I want you to give me
whatever I want
whenever I want it
for the rest
of your life.
And why would I
do that?
Oh, right.
Because I just recorded you
admitting to violating the law.
- The XJS-5000.
- Mm-hmm.
- You--you set me up.
- Yep.
You knew that I would
track your home computer.
And after
you've been convicted,
you'll be lucky to be hired
as a network administrator...
At a high school...
In Jersey.
How long are you gonna
keep at this?
Until I find out
what I just got myself into.
I mean, look at this stack
of papers.
It's 1/5 of the files
we have on Ava Hessington.
- You need a shortcut.
- Well, I'm not going to Mike.
I'm not talking
about him.
Ava Hessington
started in the London office.
It's too late.
No, it's not.
You gotta be
kidding me.
How did you get
through security?
Charm and this smile.
You bought a ticket,
didn't you?
Trinidad-Tobago.
First-class?
You're not even going.
I prefer to not travel
in style.
I'd prefer to be alone
right now.
Scottie,
I need your help.
I'm sorry,
I have a plane to catch.
A plane, by the way,
that you put me on.
After I saved your job,
which you accepted.
So now we're both working
for the same firm.
Oh, I guess now I'm just
one of the many partners
who gets to work with you
and yet wants nothing to do
with you.
Scottie.
Please!
You once helped me
without me asking.
Well, now I'm asking.
Then tell me something.
Something what?
Just...
Something.
I remember the first time
I ever saw you.
Con Law.
You threw me some line, and I
gave you shit about your hair.
No, it was two weeks
before that
outside Langdell.
You were wearing a blue dress.
The wind was blowing.
When I saw your face,
it stopped me dead in my tracks.
That's not enough.
Well, I'm not finished.
The next time I saw you
was Con Law.
You answered the first question
that Dyson asked,
and I knew that that face
that blew me away
was your second best asset.
Look, you mean
something to me.
You've always meant
something to me,
and you always will mean
something to me.
You are such a dick.
What do you need, Harvey?
Ava Hessington.
[Chuckles]
[Clears throat]
Well, this is gonna
take a while.
So you're gonna
buy me a drink,
and I'm gonna take that ticket
to Trinidad-Tobago.
Okay, Norma,
it's been 24 hours.
If you can't get me Barbara lL.
Tottingham on the phone,
well, then guess what,
you don't get--
Oh.
It's you!
Well, you tell Norma if I don't
have a package of uni-balls
on my desk by noon,
she can kiss her trip
to Dollywood good-bye.
Now, why don't you
get the hell out of here,
so I can fix myself
a raspberry Bran bar in peace?
What are you looking at?
Looking for this?
It's the last one.
Not today.
You're Barbara L. Tottingham.
I hardly made it difficult
to figure out.
Barbara L. Tottingham.
B.L.T.
Which is a sandwich.
And what does one put
on a B.L.T.?
Mayonnaise,
invented by the French.
Which points directly
to another French sandwich.
Of course, the monte cristo,
as in the Count of Monte Cristo.
How did I not see that?
It was staring me
right in the face.
Indeed it was.
The count returned
from the dead,
as I am now returned
from the banishment
to which you sentenced me...
As quartermaster.
I would ask you
how you did it,
but I know you wouldn't tell me,
because I wouldn't tell you.
What I will tell you is
that during my time
in the wilderness--
- It was three days.
- And nights.
I endeavored to discover
what perquisites
you value most in this firm--
your beloved Bran bars.
You're never going
to have them.
I can buy them myself.
Even if you were willing
to buy them yourself--
which we both know
you aren't--
you'll never eat them
on Pearson Darby grounds.
You didn't.
I did.
They're banned.
Wait a second.
You're telling me that
Barbara L. Tottingham is Nigel?
No.
Stay with me.
B.L.T., mayonnaise,
monte cristo sandwich.
Oh, my God,
I'm so hungry.
- Donna.
- What?
What do you want from me, Louis?
I'm busy.
So you can't have your pens
or your Bran bars, big deal.
Donna, listen.
When I was in ninth grade,
there was this wrestler
Randy Cusumano.
And one day after school
in the locker room,
he pinned me down, and he taped
my butt cheeks together.
Wait a second, is this the
story from The Breakfast Club?
I'm not familiar
with that song.
Never mind.
Look, I swore
that I would get him back
no matter what it took.
What did it take?
Ah, you don't really
wanna know.
Thank you.
The point is
if I'm Nigel and Nigel's me,
he's not gonna stop
at Bran bars and pens.
I gotta take care of Nigel
once and for all.
You need to get rid of him
as quartermaster.
Miss Hessington,
first of all, I want you
to familiarize yourself
with this man.
U.S. attorney
Richard Jensen.
He's one of the best
there is,
and he's
who we'll be going up against.
Well, that's all
well and good, Mr. Specter,
but I have one question.
Why should I hire you?
Because you trust
Edward Darby.
I'm afraid that only gets you
in the room.
This civil servant
seems to have
a personal vendetta against me,
and I don't even know why.
Well, I do.
He needs a head
on a platter.
Why mine?
You've been skirting
environmental laws for a decade.
He's got a chance to nail you,
and he's gonna take it.
This isn't
an environmental allegation.
No, it's a bribery charge,
it's got teeth,
and it's coming your way.
Don't sugarcoat it,
Mr. Specter.
Give it to me straight.
Okay, I will.
Because when he digs
a little deeper,
he's gonna find evidence
of the spill your company
covered up in 2008,
the whistle-blower
you bought off in 2010,
and the environmental impact
study you doctored in 2006.
So it's not gonna be hard
to convince a jury
that you're guilty of bribing
a foreign government
to get your pipeline.
And what are you going to do
to stop him?
Bury evidence,
contact witnesses,
or sleep with your rival
pitcher's girlfriend
the night
before the big game?
The heart wants
what the heart wants.
I got it.
I looked into you.
You looked into me.
I actually prefer it
that way.
And why is that?
Because you know
what I'll do to win.
Saves me the trouble
of explaining it to you.
And I won't have
to explain to you
what I did to win
that pipeline.
You bribed them.
Guilty as charged.
And I don't care
what Richard Jensen says.
Every company with a pipeline
over there
did the same thing.
- Is that your defense?
- It's the truth.
It would be nice
if we only found oil
under Texas ranchers
or North Sea fishermen.
But in the real world,
we find it in nasty places
under nasty people.
And any executive worth a damn
does what's needed
or goes out of business.
- Good. We're done.
- Excuse me?
I just needed to know
what I was dealing with
before I make
my next move.
- And what is that?
- I'll let you know.
I haven't officially
hired you yet.
Yes, you have.
How long
you been waiting here?
Since I found out
what you need.
What I need is for you
to leave me alone.
No, what you need is
information on Ava Hessington.
In 2008, her company tried
to destroy evidence--
Of an oil spill?
Okay, well,
in 2010, they--
They bought off
a whistle-blower.
And if the next thing
you're gonna tell me
is about an environmental
impact study in 2006,
don't.
You think
you're not replaceable?
I got all that
from an associate
I picked at random.
I've been doing this
before I met you,
and I'll be doing it long after
I've forgotten all about you.
You had enough?
No.
No, you know what, I haven't,
because you haven't.
Excuse me?
You haven't said whatever
you have to say to rip me
to shreds enough so that
you can start to forgive me.
So go ahead.
Whatever it takes,
I can take it.
Go!
Harvey, I'm sorry,
all right?
But I need you
to listen to me now.
Listen to you?
You know when I would've
listened to you?
That night.
- Jessica threatened me.
- I don't care.
Anyone comes at you
with any threat at all,
you come to me.
I don't give a shit
if it's the Queen on England.
You come to me.
You tell me!
You tell me everything!
That's what
goddamn loyalty is.
[Sighs]
[Knocking on door]
Okay, you're right.
You don't know
who I am
or what I've done
to deserve anything.
So here's what's gonna happen.
I am gonna tell you.
I am gonna tell you
everything,
and when we're done,
either we're gonna be finished,
or we're gonna go back there
and we're gonna do exactly
what we should've done
the other night.
Okay.
Okay, one more time.
I'm gonna show you.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- You sure?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
So I was here.
Mmhmm.
Yeah? And I was running
down here.
And the cops,
they were back here.
So I am running--
let's see, where is it?
Oh, yeah,
it was down here.
And I run into here,
and then Donna,
she was right here.
- Okay.
- So she let me in...
Here.
And then Harvey,
he was right down--
No!
[Laughing]
What?
Harvey is not getting
anywhere near there.
Oh, no one is ever
getting anywhere near there.
Oh, you think
you're that good, do you?
It's one
of my many gifts.
Being that good
or thinking you're that good?
Do you want a replay?
'Cause I will go right now.
- Like you could.
- I could!
Soon... ish.
Do you have, like,
an energy drink or something?
- Oh.
- Come on! We were up all night.
You kept me up
all night.
You kept me up all night.
I can't tell you
how it feels
that you know.
Mm, well, who knew
that honesty
was the best policy?
Oh, wait.
Everyone knew that.
[Laughter]
[Murmurs indistinctly]
- [Laughing]
- What?
[Muffled chatter,
laughter]
Can I help you?
Louis Litt.
Oh, I know
who you are.
Freshly minted
senior partner,
expert in matters
of corporate finance,
and the man responsible
for the superb training
of the associates.
[Chuckles]
You've looked into me.
Mmhmm.
I've looked into you.
Tarte au chocolat
from Cafe Pouchkine.
The best patisserie
in Paris.
A steeping cup
of da Hong pao.
The most expensive tea
in the world.
Two of my favorite things.
What better to enjoy
after signing this order...
Making me quartermaster?
Pity you don't have
a Montblanc pen
for me to sign it with.
With cobalt ink.
We already have
a quartermaster.
Sir, I know...
That this is
Nigel's position
and him losing it
would not be easy for him.
But let me
just assure you,
I'm not just prepared
for this position...
I was born for it.
I have PhDs
in chemical engineering
and petroleum exploration.
I've made it to the top
in a field dominated by men,
and I'm facing
a prison sentence
for an allegation
which any man in my position
would be fined for.
Every similar case
has been settled with a fine,
not prison.
That's what we're proposing.
Well, there's just
one problem.
I'm not charging you
because you're a woman.
I'm charging you
because you're the one I caught.
Ava, can you give us
a minute?
[Door closes]
Okay, she's gonna
write you a check.
Let's talk about how much.
I'm sorry, Harvey.
Not this time.
Is that what I said to you
on Hazelton?
That was
a long time ago.
We're not at the D.A.'s office
anymore.
I didn't realize our bond
had an expiration date.
It doesn't, but...
you want to deal on this,
I need jail time.
You're running for office?
What if I am?
You need a scalp.
I can think of four people
off the top of my head
that make her look like
Mother Teresa.
Harvey, I can't afford
to horse trade on this.
You've done it before.
And I'll do it again,
but... not today.
Richard, you are singling out
this woman, and it's wrong.
That's not my problem.
What if I told you
I need this one?
Then I'd have to tell you...
I'm sorry.
Not gonna forget this.
Harvey, look.
If our bond can't survive
me telling you no,
then...
It didn't mean much
to begin with.
- Hey, Rach.
- No time, code two!
Richard Gere's
in the lobby?
- Leaving now, let's go.
- Relax.
We have trained for this.
Okay.
[Laughter]
Wait!
Congratulations.
Your writing implements
and nourishment of choice.
Mm.
Yeah, I'd say I'm sorry,
but I'm not.
- Please don't do this.
- [Chuckling]
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
You're not gonna trick me into
letting you stay quartermaster
just so you can take away
what's most dear to me
little by little.
Then I'm afraid I'm gonna have
to take it away all at once.
What are you
talking about?
I took you for a bylaws man.
It seems I was wrong.
At Darby International,
one cannot be in charge
of both the animate
and the inanimate
at the same time.
Your beloved associates
are mine.
You set me up.
What better way
to catch a rat
than with
quartermaster cheese?
What are you gonna do,
beg Darby to undo
what you just begged him to do?
Hold on.
Nigel, the associates
are my life.
So please don't do this.
When I was
at preparatory school,
like you,
I was bullied again and again.
It was painful,
but I always saw them coming.
But with you,
I didn't.
So it wasn't a stab in the back,
it was a stab in the heart.
And I just gave you
the opportunity to take it back,
and you passed.
So no, quartermaster Litt,
I won't forgive you.
Nice office.
Thanks.
Do you mind
if I ask you a favor?
Yeah, anything.
I have
a ton of old files
that I need organized
and shipped to storage,
and I was wondering if you
could maybe do that for me.
I
Because I figured if you were
suddenly doing things for people
that they don't need you to do,
didn't ask you to do,
and don't want you to do,
then maybe I'd get in on that.
I put that on Harvey's desk
for him, not you.
Maybe.
But I know
what you don't seem to get.
Harvey didn't value you
for your help on cases.
He valued you for your loyalty,
which he told you last night.
Yeah, I know that.
And I'm trying
to get it back,
and this is
the only way I know how.
By sending Rachel
to distract me
and sneaking
into his office?
Oh, by the way, you think
I don't know about you two?
Took me one look.
Donna, come on.
You wanna know how
to get Harvey's loyalty back?
Get in a time machine and undo
what you did with Jessica.
Oh, shoot,
you can't do that.
You know what, I figured
you'd bring this file back.
There's also one
in your bottom drawer.
You might wanna grab that too.
And just in case of that,
I put seven other copies
in his office.
'Cause whether
he forgives me or not,
he's still gonna need it.
Some random associate
gave him all that information
on Ava Hessington?
No way.
It was Scottie.
Yeah, I found the ticket
to Trinidad-Tobago.
It's not a giant leap.
The only problem is
Scottie's not here.
She's in London.
And Harvey--
he is still gonna need this.
This file doesn't lead
to Harvey forgiving you.
Donna...
Please could you just separate
our relationship
from yours and his
for just, like, one second?
Are you kidding me?
Do you think I'm mad
just because of him?
You did this
to me too.
And whether you appreciate it
or not,
I've had your back
since the day that you got here.
Yes. Yes, you have.
But what about last year?
When I had your back,
you ignored me,
and it almost cost him
his license.
The difference is
I did what I did for him,
not for me.
And I didn't get
a brand-new office for it.
I got fired.
Yum.
Oh, what do you want, Michael?
Please.
I'm just trying to eat
my egg McMuffin
while I'm still off-line,
okay?
I thought
you were never off-line.
Five minutes a day.
Listen, Benjamin,
I don't wanna hold what's
on this dictaphone over you
for the rest
of your life.
Why not?
I don't need
any more enemies.
I'd rather have a friend,
but...
I do need a favor.
And if I don't
give it to you,
then what do you do
with the dictaphone?
It's the only copy
there is.
Go on, erase it.
Then I'll ask you
my favor.
How do I know
that this is the only copy?
Because I'm giving you
my word.
[Beep]
What do you need?
I need you to build me
a time machine.
And a bite
of the sandwich.
Come on.
That's not sanitary, Michael.
Come on,
just a little.
You can have
the rest.
- How did it go with Richard?
- It didn't.
- He didn't budge.
- Why not?
Says he's running for office,
but it doesn't make sense.
Yeah, it does.
Son of bitch!
He looks me in the eye,
and he feeds me
a bullshit sandwich.
He's obviously not
the same man he used to be.
Yeah, well, I am.
Wait a second.
Let me guess. Mike?
Just because you use it
doesn't mean you have
to forgive him.
You're right.
I don't.
Harvey.
What are you doing here?
Hessington Oil's
number one competitor
also happens to be your biggest
campaign contributor?
Which has nothing to do
with the fact
that your client
broke the law.
You don't want a deal.
What you want
is a long, drawn-out trial
that puts our stock
in the toilet.
You think I wasn't
gonna find that out?
I mean,
I gotta hand it to you.
You set it up perfectly
to shield yourself
from prosecution.
To shield myself
from breaking the law.
Richard Jensen:
Prosecuting the competition.
It's a hell
of a campaign slogan.
Harvey,
your client did this.
I'm not going
after an innocent person.
And you know
that if I win this election,
I will do good things.
You know what, you sound
just like Cameron Dennis.
You remember?
Always a reason,
always out for the greater good.
But in the end,
it's all about him.
Look, I've never claimed
to be out for the greater good.
So cut me a deal
and find yourself another donor.
Harvey, it's too late.
Please.
I need this.
Well, that's not
my problem.
Send Carolyn my love.
You wanted to see me?
I know why you care so much
about Ava Hessington.
Well, it's no secret.
Her father
was my first client.
I think he was
a little bit more than that.
It was a different time.
Does she know?
She knows
that I care about her.
I'm sorry, was there
something else you wanted?
Just to let you know
that if I could figure that out,
Harvey can figure that out.
And why would that
be a problem?
Because it's one thing
for Harvey to know
that this case
is important to you,
another to know
how important.
Are you telling me
you don't trust him?
I told you
he's having a difficult time
digesting this merger.
I don't want him using this
as leverage to leave.
At the end of the day,
I don't believe
Harvey really wants to leave.
Harvey...
What a coincidence.
Cameron.
You grew the mustache back.
I'll let you in
on a little secret.
It wasn't a success
the first time.
What are you doing here?
Ah, Richard told me
that you mentioned me
at your last meeting.
It's funny,
'cause he called me
after your first meeting,
wanted my advice.
So I guess
you're here to tell me
he's not gonna give me
a deal.
I'm here to tell you he's
recusing himself from the case.
He didn't want the appearance
of a conflict
to damage the workings
of justice.
So he appointed
a special prosecutor.
Lucky for me,
I've always been special.
No, you've always been
a corrupt prick.
It just took me a while
to realize it.
And it took me a while
to realize
that you don't have a speck
of loyalty in your entire body.
Loyalty is a two-way street,
and you ran me off the road.
So what
are you gonna do?
You gonna let Jessica fight your
fight like you did last time,
or you gonna run away
like you did when you left
the D.A.'s office?
Neither one, Cameron.
But thank you.
For what?
For reminding me
that I don't run from a fight.
What was so important
that I had
to come down here
right away?
Don't tell me
you want a bigger office.
You told me
that I can think of this office
as a reminder
of what I did to Harvey
or as a symbol
of what I can do at this firm.
But the thing is
I don't wanna be here
if I'm not solid
with Harvey.
Well,
that's between you and Harvey.
It's between you and me.
You put yourself between us
when you blackmailed me.
Well, the word
you're looking for is extortion,
not blackmail,
and I'm not going to comment
on that accusation.
But as for your choices,
you made those
all by yourself.
So don't come crying
to me.
[Clears throat]
This is a copy of the letter you
wrote to the district attorney
when you threatened
to expose me.
Expose you?
For what?
I never wrote
a letter like that.
I'm not recording you.
I don't need
to record you.
This letter was printed
from your hard drive,
which has your computer's
digital signature.
What do you want?
I wanna know,
if you had the chance,
would you have traded
that car
to get your parents
back together?
[Scoffs]
That's a stupid
goddamn question,
and you know it.
I never had that chance,
so what does it matter?
Because I do.
What do I want?
I wanna give
this office back.
I didn't earn it,
I don't want it,
and if there's a chance
it'll help Harvey forgive me,
I'm gonna take it.
Oh, and, uh,
if you ever do
send that letter,
you're in the same boat
as me.
Harvey,
you're looking determined.
- I am.
- What can I do for you?
Look, I know
we had an arrangement,
but I came here
to change it.
Change it?
But you might not even win.
I've just heard about
this new special prosecutor.
Relax, the case
was always gonna be hard.
It just got
a little harder.
Because you made it
that way.
That's my problem.
And now you're using
that increased difficulty
to renegotiate our deal.
That's your problem.
We both know
how important Ava is to you.
What do you want?
I don't wanna run
from a fight.
Meaning?
I win,
you don't fire me,
you back me
for managing partner.
You want
to take down Jessica.
Yes, I do.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Resync for WEB-DL by lost0ne
for www.addic7ed.com