Palmer figured out that
we're doing this with Seidel.
And unless we drop the lawsuit,
he's gonna come after us
for collusion.
If I pull out of that hearing,
Palmer can't touch us.
I'm not doing anything
until you tell Nathan
exactly what's going on.
There's nothing to tell.
You said
you're doing this case
as a way
to get into the Bar.
And I just withdrew
my application.
I knew Mike was a fraud
before he was arrested.
I leveraged it
to get my name on the wall.
I thought I knew
what kind of man you were.
How dare you say that to me
when the first time
we slept together,
you were with another man.
I don't want to spend
the rest of my life
with a man who gave up
on his dreams,
and I know that you don't want
to be that man either.
We have proof
of over a dozen instances
of you committing
corporate espionage.
What do you want?
You're gonna settle
with those miners.
You're gonna forget
you ever heard of us.
And you're gonna honor
your original agreement
with Craig Seidel.
I don't just want you
to set that hearing.
I want you to bulldoze anyone
who stands in my way.
[instrumental music]
[groans]
What time is it?
Don't worry.
You're not late for work.
Here.
Thanks.
I could use this.
I got in pretty late
last night.
Does that have anything
to do with the flowers
I just found in the kitchen?
Can't a guy just buy you
flowers 'cause he loves you?
He can.
But he didn't.
You're right.
I bought them
to say thank you
for doing whatever it took
to make sure
I got my shot
at getting into the Bar.
Wait, does that mean that...
Yeah. We did it.
My hearing's tomorrow.
Seidel's on our side.
I can't believe it.
This could really happen.
I know.
What is it?
I promised Oliver
that I would tell Nathan
about the whole thing.
- Mike, you can't do that.
- I know I can't.
But I gotta get a couple days
off for the hearing,
which means I gotta tell him
something.
♪ ♪
Louis, what are you
doing here?
I hope you don't mind
I stopped by.
I had to see you.
I couldn't sleep at all
last night.
- Neither could I.
- Tara, please.
I know we had a fight,
but you told me
you wanted to get to know me.
And I swear, what I told you
was the worst thing
I've ever done.
Louis, the thing I'm having
trouble dealing with
has nothing to do
with that person at your firm.
It has to do with
how you treated me last night.
- Tara, please.
- Let me finish.
You shared
something horrible with me,
gave me no time to process it,
and while I was taking it in,
you not only attacked
my integrity,
you made me feel
ashamed of myself.
You're right.
I lashed out,
and I shouldn't have.
But I only did it because I was
afraid of you rejecting me.
And I will...
Tara, I'll die
if you reject me.
That's the thing, Louis.
You had a reason for reacting
the way you did.
But I'm not sure
I want to be with a man
who thinks there's ever
a reason to treat me that way.
- Tara...
- I'm sorry, Louis.
They're waiting for me
in the conference room.
I told you I'll call,
and I will call.
[lightly tense music]
♪ ♪
- Nathan.
- Mike. What's up?
Nothing.
I just wanted to give you this.
This is a check for $50,000.
I know.
We settled.
I gave the miners their checks
last night.
Mike, this is the most money
we've ever made on a case.
For once, we're not gonna
have to worry about making rent.
[laughs]
Yeah. Right.
That's not a joke.
Wait, you're telling me
that $50,000
can really make that big
a difference to the clinic?
I'm telling you
that I know in corporate law,
money doesn't matter unless
it's in the millions, but...
here, $50,000 makes
all the difference in the world.
Well, in that case, Nathan,
I've been working here
seven days a week
since I started,
and I've got some
personal stuff that I need to--
Stop right there. Look.
You just bought me 30 days rent.
The least I can do
is give you a few days back.
Great.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Okay, let's hear it.
- Hear what?
The joke you spent all morning
coming up with.
What joke?
I was just gonna ask you
where the law library was,
but then I realized
you've never set foot in there.
Shouldn't you be at the clinic
saving whales?
First of all,
that's Greenpeace.
And second of all,
I took the day off
so I could prepare for the
Character and Fitness Committee.
Oh, that means
you're taking
whatever that hitch
is gonna be seriously.
- You know I am.
- That's what I like to hear.
Because I don't want
somebody working here
who doesn't listen to my advice.
Harvey, I still don't think
you understand.
When this thing is over,
I am not coming back here.
- Mike--
- I told you, I want to do good.
- Then do good here.
- And I also told you
that the only reason
I agreed to this whole thing
in the first place was because
I couldn't stand
to watch
someone like Oliver fail
and not be able to help him.
And people like Oliver
don't work in places like this.
They work in places like that.
And people like you
shouldn't be working anywhere.
What are you doing here,
Anita?
I'm here because
the U.S. Attorney's Office
requested that they be notified
if Mike Ross
ever applied to the Bar.
What does the U.S. Attorney's
Office have to do with Mike?
Nothing.
Except I happen to work there.
And as of one week ago,
I'm also the newest member
of the Character and Fitness
Committee.
Bullshit.
There's a whole process
to get on that committee.
There's no way you just happened
to be in the pipeline.
You're right.
I wasn't.
But when a member takes leave,
he has the right
to appoint his replacement.
And Walter Samson appointed me.
You think
I'm not gonna find out
whatever bullshit you did
to get this guy to drop out?
Be my guest, because if Mike
is going before that hearing,
that means
you did something too.
What do you want?
I want to tell you you might
as well cancel this hearing,
save us all a lot of time.
Because the vote
has to be unanimous.
And you are never getting
my vote.
[dramatic music]
♪ Suits 6x16 ♪
Character and Fitness
Original Air Date on March 1, 2017
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Rachel, whatever you're doing,
you need to put it down
and start looking
for every single instance
where a person was
admitted to the Bar
and the vote wasn't unanimous.
Mike, what's going on?
Anita Gibbs got herself
onto the board.
Then what we should be doing
is finding a way
to get her kicked off.
Harvey's working on it.
But in the meantime,
I need to know
the ins and outs
of this committee,
because while she's on it,
she's gonna use
every dirty trick in the book
to end this thing
before it gets started.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go hole myself up
in the library
and start preparing answers
to every dirty question
I can think of.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Louis, are you okay?
I'm fine, Donna.
What can I do for you?
I know you know Benjamin and I
have been working on a business.
But I'm not sure
that you know
that we brought on
Stu as an investor.
- I didn't, Donna; That's great.
- It is.
But there's a problem,
and I need your help with it.
Anything.
Benjamin applied for a patent,
and it turns out
that our technology
overlaps with someone else's.
- How much overlap?
- 32.5%.
That's over the threshold.
Unless Benjamin
can get you below 30--
He can't.
But Stu says we can negotiate
with whoever
holds the patent,
get them to give us
an exclusion,
and we'll still be able to move
forward with The Donna.
Donna, this is exactly
what I need.
What do you mean?
Tara and I got
into a huge fight.
She's deciding right now
if we're gonna stay together.
This is exactly
what I needed
to take my mind off it.
Louis, I don't mean
to sound insensitive,
but this is
incredibly important to me.
I know you, and if this is
gonna make you go in there
and blow this thing up,
I can't have that.
Donna, listen to me.
I may be losing
the closest woman in my life,
but you are
the second closest.
I swear that I won't do anything
to harm your company.
Thank you.
[paper slaps down]
Knock 'em dead.
♪ ♪
- When were you gonna tell me?
- Tell you what?
That the prosecutor
that put Mike in prison
just got herself put
on that panel.
- What?
- That's right.
And I want to know why I heard
about it from her and not you.
I'll tell you why.
Because I didn't know.
But now that I do,
this thing is done.
- The hell it is.
- Are you crazy?
Anita Gibbs is a goddamn
Assistant U.S. Attorney.
She gets one whiff of this,
and we are both disbarred.
Which is why we're gonna
make sure that doesn't happen
by getting her
kicked off that panel.
And how exactly
are we gonna do that?
We're gonna start
by you telling me
everything there is to know
about Walter Samson.
Well, then we might as well
give up right now,
because Walter Samson
is as clean as they come.
- No one is that clean.
- Well, this guy is.
And I didn't sign on--
Listen to me.
You said you were
in on this.
And I'm telling you right now,
you still are.
Because we moved
heaven and earth
to get you out of hot water,
and I got no problem
putting you right back in.
Fine.
But you better be careful.
Because if
you're looking at Gibbs,
she's going to be looking at us.
And you coming to my lobby
in the middle of the day
is going to get us all caught.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Gentlemen, thank you
for meeting with me
on such short notice.
Our pleasure.
I assume you looked through
the documents I sent over
and found them to your liking?
On the contrary, we found them
most disturbing.
In particular,
the fact that you used
our fundamental principles
and worked up from there.
What?
We've never even seen
your fundamental principles
prior to applying
for that patent.
Can you prove that?
Of course we can't...
prove that.
It's not possible
to prove a negative.
Words spoken by every hack
who's ever copied
someone else's technology
and claimed it as their own.
What's going on here?
I came to you to negotiate
an exclusion in good faith.
And we're prepared
to offer you--
We don't care
what you're prepared to offer.
And we didn't bring you here
to give you an exclusion.
We brought you here
to send a message.
This is a $90 million lawsuit
against your client
if they go to market.
Gentlemen, please,
I am not saying
we got here first.
But it's a 2.5% overlap,
and we are open to a 15%
revenue sharing arrangement.
And we're not open to shit,
because we were here first.
Listen to me.
I am trying to keep my cool.
We don't care
if you keep your cool or not.
Because we've got you,
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
So you can take your offer
and shove it in a drawer
along with that sorry excuse
for a digital secretary,
because neither one of them is
ever gonna see the light of day.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Oliver.
What are you doing?
Is it still on?
- Is what still on?
- Your deal.
To get into the Bar.
Oliver, listen to me.
Because when I asked Nathan
where you were,
he said you were taking a couple
days for personal reasons.
And all of a sudden,
I got this pit in my stomach
that wouldn't go away.
So I decided to ask you if
there's a reason I got that pit
or if I'm just an asshole
for doubting you.
You're not an asshole,
Oliver.
God damn it, Mike!
You told me
you didn't have to tell Nathan
because there was
nothing to tell.
And when I told you that,
there wasn't.
But then my deal
got put back on the table.
Which means you could have
told him this morning.
But you didn't,
so now I have to.
Oliver, hey, wait!
Please, hear me out!
I'm not gonna
hear you out, Mike.
I was sitting here for an hour,
hoping I was wrong about you.
You weren't wrong about me.
I care about people.
I want to help the clinic.
And the reason I didn't tell
Nathan what I did
is because I'm just waiting
until I can help him even more.
Help how?
By being a shady lawyer?
By being someone who wouldn't
have lost Sofia Price her home.
I cannot believe
you just said that to me.
I said it because it's true,
and you know it.
Look, I am gonna
tell Nathan everything
as soon as my hearing is over.
You have my word.
Why should I believe
the word of a liar?
Because of what I did
for those miners and the clinic.
And if that's not enough,
how about what I did for you?
You didn't do shit for me.
But fine, I won't tell Nathan.
Just so long as
when this thing's over,
you go back
to your corrupt corporate world.
Because I don't care
what you tell yourself.
You're never
gonna belong in mine.
[tense music]
Harvey, what are
you still doing here?
The hearing's across town
in ten minutes.
I'm not going to the hearing,
Donna, and neither are you.
- Why not?
- Because if you and I can't do
what we need to, then whatever
Mike does at that hearing
isn't gonna matter.
Give it to me.
We need to figure out what
Walter Samson's weak spot is.
Tell me how, and I'm all in.
Start by contacting
every person we know
and asking them what they know
about this asshole.
Because Gibbs
has something on him
and if I can't find out
what it is,
then I can't get her
off that committee.
Where are you going?
To see someone
who doesn't know Samson at all.
Before we get started,
I'd like to point out
these interviews are normally
for us to quickly approve
standard applicants to the Bar.
However, Mr. Ross
is no standard applicant.
Therefore, we will convene
for as long as it takes
before ruling
on his application.
Now...
Mr. Chairman, if I may.
Last winter,
Mr. Ross pled guilty
to defrauding
the citizens of New York.
Therefore, I propose we reject
his application right now
because Mr. Ross is a felon
and the New York Bar
does not accept felons.
Mr. Chairman, with all due
respect to the new board member,
you do.
Not only does the Bar
accept felons, but years ago,
this very committee
admitted Neal Wiesner,
a man who spent years in prison
for attempted murder.
Now, Ms. Gibbs may think
my crime is worse
than attempted murder,
but I don't think
it's worth throwing away
140 years of precedent
by not even allowing me
to make my case.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Come on, let's go.
- What the hell are you doing?
- What does it look like
I'm doing? I'm watching my money
go down the toilet.
Well, it looks to me
like I paid you to do a job,
and you're sitting here
doing this.
Okay, I'll let you in
on a little secret.
It only takes 15 minutes
to hack someone.
If you can't find something
in the next 45,
it means
there's nothing to find.
Bullshit. There's always
something to find.
I'm telling you,
there isn't.
He doesn't drink, smoke,
gamble, cheat, nothing.
Listen to me. I paid you
good money to do a job,
and if you don't put
some more effort into this,
I'm gonna spread the word
that you aren't worth shit.
And this time it won't
be coming from Louis Litt.
It'll be coming from me.
Then keep your damn money.
When I tell you
there's nothing to find,
there's nothing to find.
I guess what I'm saying is
not only do I admit what I did,
but...I regret it
with every fiber of my being.
And I'd like to apologize
to my clients,
my former colleagues,
and finally to the fraternity
of men and woman that
I've wanted to be a member of
since I was a child.
Well, that was
a moving statement.
I just have one question.
If you regret
what you did so much,
why weren't you willing
to serve your full sentence?
Well, I wasn't unwilling.
I was offered a deal
to help convict a known
criminal, and I took it.
You were offered a deal
to get out early,
and you took it.
I protected an innocent man--
What you did
was insinuate yourself
into your roommate's life,
gain his trust,
and pretend to be his friend.
True or false?
[scoffs]
You're taking it out of context.
The context is
you portrayed yourself
as one thing
when, really, you were another,
which is what you did
the entire time
you pretended to be an attorney
and what I believe you are doing
to this body right now.
Mr. Chairmen, if she's going
to impugn his character
while he's speaking,
then he's entitled
to let someone else
speak for him.
This isn't
a trial.
We don't allow
character witnesses here.
Actually, you do.
Article 4, 16A.
Applicants are allowed
a witness as a rebuttal
for an accusation leveled
by a committee member.
That article hasn't been cited
in 30 years.
Maybe that's because no
applicant has ever had to stand
before the person
who put them away.
You make a point.
We'll pick this up
first thing in the morning
with your witness.
Thank you.
Rachel, that was exactly
what I needed.
If you hadn't done that--
I know.
But right now I'm more
concerned with the fact
that she's turning them
against you.
Which means even after
Harvey kicks her off,
Seidel's job is gonna be
that much harder.
And we only have one shot
at having someone speak for me.
Mike, come on.
We gotta get back to the office
and start going through
everyone it could be.
We'll make a list
of pros and cons.
Rachel...
I know who it is.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Julius.
Mike.
What are you doing here?
I was hoping
we could talk.
Uh, look, I'm sorry, man.
This is not a good time.
I just put the baby down
and the wife and I--
Please, it won't take long.
I got this hearing tomorrow
for the Character portion
of the Bar,
and I wanted to ask
if you'd speak for me.
You mind if I ask, why me?
Because you're the only one
I know who's qualified
to tell the board
that I was a different man
when I got out
than when I went in.
No offense, Mike...
but the truth is,
I'm not sure you are.
What do you mean?
I mean you said
this hearing is tomorrow.
But you're just now
coming to me,
which means
something's going on.
What's going on is the woman
who put me away
managed to get herself
on the committee,
and now she's slamming
the door in my face.
- And why would she do that?
- Julius--
Mike, how did you even
get a hearing?
What are you talking about?
I applied, like everyone else.
No, you're not
like everyone else.
You didn't go to law school.
It doesn't matter.
There's an exception
called "reading the law."
See, right there, Mike,
that sounds like the bullshit
artist I met in prison.
So you tell me right now.
Did you pull some shit
to make this happen?
Damn, Mike, if you can't
be straight with me,
this conversation
ends right here.
Yes, I did.
Ah, finally.
Some truth in the night.
Julius, I work at a law
clinic, but not as a lawyer.
An opportunity presented itself
for me to become one
and I turned it down,
but then I had to sit there
and watch a woman
get put on the street
because I couldn't help her.
And I knew I'd have to
watch that happen
over and over and over.
So when that opportunity
presented itself
for the second time,
I took it.
Because I knew
it would never come along again.
- You don't know that, Mike.
- I do know that.
So you can say no
if you want to,
but don't say
I haven't changed.
Because the Mike you met
that night in prison
never would have told you
the truth just now.
Julius, please.
I need this.
[paper rustles]
This is the address.
It's tomorrow at 9:00.
I don't have anyone else.
[dramatic music]
[elevator dings]
Mike, hey.
Harvey, tell me
you got some good news.
I do.
I took care of Seidel.
He's still gonna back you.
I'm not talking about Seidel.
I'm talking about getting Gibbs
off that committee.
It's not that simple.
What's not that simple
about it?
I haven't found
anything on him yet.
Harvey, I am struggling
to get someone on my side,
and every second
that she is on that committee
she is turning people
against me.
I need your help.
Mike, I told you
I'd get it done.
I'll get it done.
Anything?
No.
It's the same as when
you called an hour ago.
If he killed someone
and hid the body,
nobody knows where it is.
Then why don't you tell me
who's next on the list.
Harvey, I have been at this
all day,
and you said
we don't have much time.
Why don't you just
bluff the guy
into giving you
whatever you need?
Because we've only got
one shot at this.
The more information I have,
the better chance
a bluff is gonna work.
Harvey, what's going on?
It isn't like you to stay in
and make phone calls
instead of confronting someone
face-to-face.
What if I can't do it
and Mike doesn't
get into the Bar?
How can you say that?
You are the best poker player
I have ever seen.
You can do it.
I don't think you understand,
Donna.
A bluff only works
if he's dirty.
What if the guy
really is clean?
Harvey, Gibbs got him
off the committee.
He's not clean.
Now, enough is enough.
Go do what you do.
[edgy music]
♪ ♪
Louis, you mind telling me
what this is?
Where'd you get that?
That is a lawsuit
against Donna's new business.
I know what it is.
Well, why haven't you told her
about it yet?
Because she's gonna think
that I blew it
because I was upset about Tara.
Louis, did you go full-blown
you on some poor bastard
and ruin Donna's chance
at success?
Gretchen, I went there
in good faith
to get a settlement,
and I was ambushed.
I swear.
Then you need to fix it.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Because I cannot
stop thinking about Tara.
We got into a huge fight
and I was...
such an asshole.
So I went to apologize.
She said she wasn't sure
she could stay with me,
and I haven't heard
from her since.
So now instead of not knowing
how to fix things
with one woman in my life,
I don't know how
to fix things with the other.
Louis, I was married
a long time.
And I'll tell you,
Carl and I had some doozies.
Tell you the truth,
I wasn't always sure
we were gonna pull through.
But we always did,
because we loved each other.
What if she doesn't love me
anymore?
It doesn't turn off
like that, Louis.
And from where I'm standing,
you're worth loving.
Now, do you think
you can fix this thing
or do you need me
to get us some help?
I don't need any help.
I'm gonna blow those guys
out of the water.
- Walter Samson?
- Yes?
I saw you out there.
First time playing?
[chuckles] Sorry.
Do I know you?
The question is,
how do you know Anita Gibbs?
Because you gave her your seat
on the Character
and Fitness Committee,
and the woman
who prosecuted Mike Ross
has no business being there.
- Who's Mike Ross?
- I get it.
We're going that way, huh?
He's the reason
Gibbs strong-armed you
into giving up that seat.
I gave up that seat
because I wanted to spend
more time with my family.
Bullshit.
She found out whatever dirty
little secret you're hiding.
If you don't come clean
with me,
I'm gonna find out what it is
and I'm gonna squeeze harder.
I don't know who you are,
but it must be nice
living in a world where everyone
has a weak spot
and is unethical,
but in this case,
I took a leave of absence
and I replaced myself
with a worthy attorney.
So you can look for
a pressure point all you want.
But I'm sorry to inform you,
you're not gonna find one.
You want to know who I am?
My name is Harvey Specter.
And you can say you never
heard of Mike Ross,
but I know you heard of me.
So maybe she didn't
blackmail you.
Maybe she promised
to do something for you.
Either way,
I'm gonna find out what it is
and you're gonna wish
you told me right now.
You think
you're showing strength.
But intimidation
is only weakness.
And for your information,
I never met Anita Gibbs
until the day I appointed her
as my replacement.
[lightly tense music]
♪ ♪
When I first met Mike Ross,
I thought he was like
every other criminal
I work with:
an entitled fraud who spent
his life cutting corners.
But I'm here to tell you,
he went into prison one man,
and he walked out another.
And in
my professional opinion,
he has the integrity to serve
his community as a lawyer.
While I don't doubt
your sincerity, Mr. Rowe,
just because he was able
to fool you
doesn't mean he's going to be
able to fool this board.
It's Dr. Rowe.
And I'm glad you were the one
who responded to my statement.
- And why is that?
- Because you tried to paint
a false picture of his release,
and I'm here
to set the record straight.
The record is straight.
And you're not qualified to talk
about the deal that he made.
- No, we're gonna hear this.
- Thank you.
It's true Mr. Ross entered
into an early release agreement.
But it's also true that he
stayed in longer than he had to
to keep his cellmate safe.
And while he was there,
he risked his own life
to prevent a violent man
from falsely obtaining parole.
And for all we know,
he did that
for self-serving reasons.
And for all I know, that's
what you're doing right now.
You're out of line.
I'm not the one
under examination here.
Neither am I.
I'm a prison psychologist.
And in my experience,
self-serving men
do not risk their lives
to help people.
I don't call defrauding
your fellow man helping people.
And I certainly don't call it
having integrity.
With all due respect, ma'am,
I'm done wasting my breath
on you
because the purpose of
this hearing was to determine
if Mike Ross had reformed.
But you don't seem to be
interested in that
because you've already
made your mind up.
- Maybe I have.
- Then maybe you shouldn't be
on this committee.
Because as I said,
in my professional opinion,
the world could use
a lawyer like Mike Ross.
And if you're looking
for my personal opinion,
he has more integrity
in his little finger
than you have
in your whole body.
[edgy music]
♪ ♪
Harvey,
where have you been?
I've been trying
to level the playing field.
That's the thing;
we just did.
You should have seen Julius
up there.
I mean,
if those members vote no
after hearing what
he had to say--
Doesn't matter
what he had to say.
You haven't found a way
to get Gibbs off that committee.
No.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, Mike.
You don't have to be sorry,
Harvey.
She warned us that
she'd never let me into the Bar.
We just didn't listen.
Listen to me.
This vote isn't
until tomorrow morning.
There's still time for us
to think of something.
You keep trying, Harvey.
I got something else
I need to take care of.
♪ ♪
What's going on?
Gretchen said you wanted
to talk to me about the patent.
What are you guys doing here?
I went back to them, Donna.
And the reason I asked
Stu and Benjamin to be here
was so that you'd know
I didn't shit the bed.
Are you telling me
you couldn't get them
to back off the lawsuit?
He's telling you we won't
be able to patent
The Donna at all.
- What?
- Donna.
They weren't authorized
to let us partner with them.
That's what I sent you
over there to take care of.
I know, and then they said
they would fight us
to the ends of the earth.
So I pulled out every trick
in the book.
And I got them
to make you an offer.
An offer sounds like
a buyout.
That's because
it is a buyout.
With a special provision
that allows us
to produce The Donna
for in-house use.
That's not good enough.
Donna, we're talking about
a lot of money.
I don't care
about the money, Stu.
I care that Louis didn't
fight for me.
I did fight for you,
Donna, I swear.
They got us dead to rights.
There's nothing more I can do.
Bullshit. Louis Litt
does not roll over for anybody.
He didn't roll over, Donna.
I went over it with Benjamin,
and we can't get
the overlap under 30%.
I also ran it by my own attorney
and he was shocked
at what Louis was able
to get us.
So you're telling me
you want to take it?
We do.
But The Donna wouldn't even
exist without you,
and we're partners,
so if you don't want to,
then we won't.
[lightly edgy music]
♪ ♪
I'm gonna need
to think about it.
♪ ♪
- What's that?
- Liberty Rail.
I tried to give it to you
once before.
You wouldn't take it.
You said it should come
without strings.
Well, here it is.
No strings.
It's still got strings,
and you know it.
You want me to
let Mike in the Bar.
I do, but I'm giving you this
whether you do that or not.
Why would you do that?
Because I'm hoping
if I showed you I could change,
maybe you'd believe
he could too.
You for him.
What?
Tomorrow morning,
I'm going to ask Mike
if anyone knew he was a fraud
while he was at Pearson Specter.
He admits you knew,
I'll let him in the Bar.
I do that,
they'll kick me out.
That's what
"you for him" means.
You said
you'd do it for him once.
This is your chance to put
your money where your mouth is.
He won't go for it.
He wants to be a lawyer
so bad he can taste it.
You can make him go for it.
Just remember,
you didn't like being
too late last time.
You're not too late this time.
Good. You're both here.
Thanks for staying.
Of course we stayed.
Your message said it was urgent.
What's going on?
Is there a problem
with the settlement?
No. I gave Oliver my word
that I'd tell you the truth,
so...I'm here
to tell you the truth.
- Truth about what?
- I made a deal.
A quid pro quo that
we would handle the miners' case
in exchange for the chance
to be admitted to the Bar.
Are you goddamn kidding me?
I asked you point blank
if something was going on,
and you lied to my face?
Nathan, I'm sorry.
But I didn't want to tell you
until there was
something to tell.
You weren't going to tell me
until you got away with it.
No, I wasn't.
But as it turns out,
I'm not gonna get away with it,
and I'm telling you anyway.
- You're fired.
- Nathan, please--
I don't give a shit what's
about to come out of your mouth.
Clean out your office.
Never show your face
around here again.
Wait. Don't do it.
Did you hear what he said?
He lied.
Not once, not twice--
I don't care,
because we need him.
- We don't need him--
- Sophia needed him,
and she got me,
and look what happened.
Yeah, Nathan, that was some
shady shit he pulled,
but you gotta be blind
if you can't see
that he actually cares.
And I don't remember us
beating down a place
like Velocity Data
before he got here.
So if it's all the same to you,
I'd like him to stay.
Well, it's not all the same
to me, Oliver.
It's up to me.
Not to the person that kept it
from me as much as Mike did.
He didn't keep it from you,
Nathan.
He said that if I didn't
tell you, he would.
So here I am.
And I know I don't have a leg
to stand on, but...
I'd like to stay.
[edgy music]
Monday morning,
you better start
putting your money
where your mouth is
and find us
another $50,000 case.
♪ ♪
- Louis, do you have a minute?
- Sure, Harvey.
I don't know how much you know
about what's going on
with Mike's hearing.
Enough to know
that look on your face
means it's not going well.
It's not.
And I may have a way
to change it,
but I wanted to run it
by my partner first,
because it may mean
that I need a little time off.
What do you mean,
"a little time off"?
I mean Gibbs
offered me a deal.
Mike goes on record admitting
I knew he was a fraud,
she'll vote
to let him in the Bar.
Are you insane?
You do that, it won't be
a little time off.
You'll get disbarred.
And by then,
he'll be a lawyer.
And we can argue that he said
that just to appease Gibbs.
Bullshit. You do this, two
out of three names on that wall
will be gone, and I won't be
able to keep this firm going.
And if you can't,
we'll have done it for Mike.
Zane will hire you.
I don't want to go to Zane's.
I want to do
what we said we were gonna do
and rebuild this place together.
Louis, I owe him.
Well, what about
what you owe me?
You said we were partners.
We are partners.
Which is why
I came to you with this.
No, you didn't come
to ask my permission.
You came to tell me
that you were gonna do this.
And what if I did?
Then you're not
just an asshole.
You're an idiot,
because there's no way
Mike Ross ever agrees
to trading you for him.
- Well, I'll make him agree.
- No, you won't.
Mike.
Harvey, whatever deal
she's offering you,
I'm not gonna take it.
You don't even know
what it is.
I don't care what it is.
I'm not getting into the Bar if
it means getting you kicked out.
Mike, she wants me.
She always has.
No, Harvey.
She wants both of us.
And she's not going to stop
until she gets both of us.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
And if you don't get that,
then she's got you
right where she wants you.
So you're just gonna
sit there tomorrow
and let her
take everything away from you?
She's not
taking anything away.
She's keeping things
exactly the way they are.
You mean working
for that clinic.
Harvey, I'm lucky to still
have a job at that clinic.
So tomorrow morning,
I'm gonna go in there
with my head held high.
But what I'm not gonna do
is let her strip you
of everything that you are.
♪ ♪
Harvey, he's right.
Let it go.
♪ ♪
Whatever it is,
Donna...
Harvey, I know you're
in a rough place right now,
but whatever's gonna happen
with Mike is gonna happen.
You've done everything you can.
And I'm tired of putting
my wants on hold.
What is it?
You know about my product
with Benjamin.
I do.
Well, it turns out
we have a 32.5% overlap
on our software
with another company's.
They refused to budge,
and Louis said
he pulled out every trick
in the book to get us this.
- Can you get it under 30%?
- No.
Then take the money.
I don't want the money.
- Donna--
- I want something more.
And I've never said that
out loud,
but I can't pretend
that's not true anymore.
What do you mean "more"?
I don't know.
[edgy music]
I guess I'm gonna have to
figure that out.
♪ ♪
Good night, Harvey.
I'll see you
tomorrow at the hearing.
♪ ♪
Mr. Ross, we are prepared
to hear your final statement.
Before we do,
I have one last question.
Mr. Ross, you say
you're a changed man
and you care about the truth.
But I want to know if you're
capable of telling the truth.
So I'm going to ask you
a question
and I suggest that you consider
your answer very carefully,
because as far as I'm concerned,
your answer will determine
whether or not
you become a lawyer.
During your time
at Pearson Specter Litt,
did anyone there
have knowledge of the fact
that you were a fraud?
[tense music]
Mr. Ross.
Did anyone else know?
I knew.
And if you're looking
for a scalp,
you can have mine.
But I was under the impression
that this hearing
was not about my old firm,
but whether or not
Mr. Ross should be a lawyer.
I say he should.
It doesn't matter
what you say.
He's already had someone
testify for him.
I'm not here to talk
about him.
I'm here to talk
about someone else.
Someone else
has nothing to do with this--
I'd like to hear this.
15 years ago,
a young woman was arrested
for illegally obtaining
prescription drugs.
Turns out she had chronic pain
and didn't want
to drop out of med school,
possibly never to return.
So she stole
a couple of prescription pads
from the hospital
where she was interning--
a crime with a mandatory
sentence of seven years.
But instead of throwing the book
at her,
the prosecuting attorney
showed mercy,
had the charges knocked down
to a misdemeanor,
recommended probation,
and sealed the records.
That's a touching story,
but I don't see
what a random attorney has to do
with these proceedings.
She's not talking
about a random attorney.
She's talking about me.
But just because
I showed compassion once
doesn't mean he deserves it now.
Maybe he doesn't.
But that young woman
is now an ER doctor.
She saves lives.
And the world's a better place
because you saved hers.
Thank you, Ms. Pearson.
Mr. Ross?
♪ ♪
I don't think
I can add anything to that.
I've made my case.
I leave the choice to you.
Then this hearing
has concluded.
We will deliberate and let you
know our decision by day's end.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
So what do we do now?
They said they would let us
know by the end of the day.
So we wait.
Well, it is the end
of the day, which means...
It doesn't mean anything,
Louis.
Whatever's going on in there,
Seidel's gonna fight like hell.
It's not gonna
make a difference.
She's never gonna
change her mind.
- I think she will.
- What do you mean?
I mean that story
wasn't any old story,
and that woman
wasn't really a woman.
It was a man
named Joseph O'Neal.
And it was
Walter Samson's godson.
- So she did call in a favor.
- Yeah, she did.
Then we need to get her
kicked off that board.
No, Harvey. We don't.
Because I didn't fly
all the way down here
to strong-arm that woman.
And I know the story
of the wind and the sun.
What the hell
are you talking about?
She's talking
about Aesop's fable.
Which basically says
that if you want to get a man
to take off his coat,
you don't blow it off.
You make him feel warm, and
he'll take it off on his own.
That's not a strategy;
it's a prayer.
Louis, I already admitted
that I knew about Mike,
and I reminded her
of her own compassion.
That's the best
we're going to do.
You know they could
disbar you for that.
In New York, they might.
In Chicago,
nobody's gonna care.
Thank you, Jessica.
Don't thank me.
Thank Harvey.
[phone vibrates]
He's the one that called me.
It's Seidel.
Hello.
I'll tell him.
Thanks for calling.
♪ ♪
You're in.
[triumphant music]
- [gasps] Oh, my God.
- [laughing]
It happened.
♪ ♪
I'm gonna go get us
some champagne.
- Thank you so much.
- [laughs]
Thank you for flying in.
I wouldn't miss this
for the world.
♪ ♪
Hey.
You said you had to go to
the bathroom a half hour ago,
but you never came back
for your champagne.
I know.
Louis, what's wrong?
You never asked me
how it went with Tara,
telling her about Mike.
I'm so sorry.
I just got caught up
with the hearing.
The thing is, I...
I told her.
We got into a huge fight.
And she said
she needed to think about
whether or not
she could forgive me.
- And?
- She just called
when Harvey was
giving us the news about Mike.
Left a 15-second voicemail.
I'm afraid to listen to it.
Louis...
She's either gonna tell me
that she never wants
to see me again
or she wants to make up.
Do you want me to listen
for you?
No. But I'd like it if
you stay with me while I do.
Of course.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
[sobbing]
What's that?
I wanted to give you
a present.
Your first year's salary
in advance.
Welcome back.
Harvey, I'm running out
of ways to tell you I don't want
to be a corporate lawyer.
Before you answer,
you might want to take
a look at this check.
- You're trying to bribe me.
- I'm trying to close you.
- I told you--
- Yeah, I get it.
You want to do good.
Well,
you really want to do good?
Donate half of this
to the clinic.
You'll fund the place
for a year.
Oh, so that's what you think
I'm all about.
Just giving money.
No.
But I think you're about more
than just working at that place.
And you know it.
What are you talking about?
I'm offering you a deal.
One for you, one for me.
You can save the spotted owls,
stop global warming,
and help as many damsels
in distress as you like.
And the good news is,
you'll be doing it from here.
What makes you think
I'd take you up on that?
Because here's the thing,
Mike.
You wanna be here,
and you know it.
- That's not true--
- Uh-uh.
I saw the look on your face
when you strong-armed Palmer
and you took on Seidel and
every other talented attorney
you've beaten over the years.
And I told you this once before.
This is the major leagues.
You don't get
this feeling anywhere else.
And I'm offering you
the best of both.
[light instrumentals]
♪ ♪
Why are you giving me
a peace sign?
- Double it.
- What?
I don't wanna just fund
the clinic for a year.
I wanna fund it for two.
And while we're at it,
I want some left over
for a little something nice
for me and the wife-to-be.
- That's all it's gonna take?
- Oh, not even close.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
Any case I want to bring
the clinic on to, I can.
Done.
Anyone I want to bring over
from the clinic, I can.
Louis doesn't get a say,
you don't get a say,
no Harvard rule.
Done.
And there's one more thing,
and you're not gonna like it.
You are not getting
my office.
Oh, yes, I am.
And I will tell you why.
- Why?
- 'Cause she's gone, Harvey.
And she's not coming back.
It's time for you
to take the reins.
[bluesy rock music]
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man