.
- There's no violation
with us seeing each other.
- This isn't something that I am
trying to get away with.
It's something
I'm feeling inside.
- My son was up for parole
next month.
He wouldn't have gotten
into a fight.
- There's got to be
at least 20 complaints
of prisoners being denied
their release date.
- And every one of them
involves injuries
and some kind of vague
disciplinary action.
- If our firm is in any way
associated with that case,
we lose a huge client.
- I'm not working on it.
- Then you're gonna put that
in writing.
You have nothing to do
with this case.
- My job requires
a reputation for discretion.
- He'll never tell a soul,
and your business
will stay intact.
- You lived a lie for years.
You can't keep a secret
about working one goddamn case?
- We have a job
we'd like to offer you.
- I don't do business
with people I don't trust.
- You can help these people.
- I want $50,000.
- Oliver, it's me. I'm in.
- What about your promise
to Harvey?
- You let me worry about Harvey.
- Hey.
Wait, you're leaving?
Why didn't you wake me?
- 'Cause you still have an hour
before your alarm goes off.
- It's 6:30.
Where are you going?
There's no way you have
something this early for Harvey.
- I got something
at the clinic with Oliver.
He needs my help with a case.
- Wait.
I was hoping we could
have dinner tonight.
- I probably have to meet
with Oliver tonight, too.
- Well, then why don't you
ask Harvey for some time off
to take care
of what you're working on?
- He's already letting me
go back and forth.
I don't wanna take advantage.
- Mike, I'm just worried
about you
burning the candle at both ends.
- Yeah.
We talked about it last night.
It's not gonna last forever.
I promise.
- Okay.
- Go back to bed.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
Oliver, I can't be here all day.
So let's get down to it.
What do you got?
- I've got us a meeting
in Brooklyn with Marc Stevens.
- Who's Marc Stevens?
- He is plaintiff number 18
in our class.
We're meeting him at nine.
- Great.
That'll give us time
to come up with our cover story.
- Mike, I know you're
not technically allowed
to work on this, but no one
here is gonna rat you out.
- It's not a technicality.
Oliver, we've been over this.
Me working on this case
means the whole thing
could get tossed out.
- I get it.
There's only two people
in the loop, me and you.
- Exactly.
So if Nathan asks...
- Nathan asks what?
- Nathan.
- I was just telling Oliver
that if you get sick
of seeing me around here,
then he's gonna have
to tell you too bad,
'cause I am not gonna let
the Brooklyn Housing Project
keep bullying its tenants.
- You can't handle
the BHP on your own?
- I can, but it's nice
having Mike give me some backup.
- Good.
Tell you the truth,
after you made me sign
that conflict of interest waiver
on Oliver's prison case,
I didn't think you'd be
around here that much at all.
- Is there anything left for me?
- No, you slept in late so you
missed me making you breakfast.
- I see, but for the record,
heating up Pop-Tarts
isn't making me breakfast.
- Well, how 'bout
I make it up to you
and not take you out to lunch?
- I appreciate
the non-invitation,
but I can't today.
- Come on, why not?
- I have an appointment.
- Since when do you see
patients at lunch?
- It isn't with
a patient, Harvey.
It's actually with my lawyer.
- What do you mean, your lawyer?
- It's nothing.
It's a nuisance suit
from an ex-business partner.
- Well, who's handling it
for you?
- I hope you're not
about to suggest
that you handle it for me.
- I'm not, but I can get you
to the next best person.
- And does this person
have a name?
- Louis Litt.
- The one you punched
in the face?
- Paula, he's the best man
for the job.
I'm telling you,
Louis is a pit bull.
- And who says
I want a pit bull?
- Listen to me,
if whatever this thing is,
it's reached the level
of a lawsuit,
you're gonna need
a lawyer like Louis
whether you like it or not.
- Well, I appreciate
your concern, Harvey,
but I prefer
to handle this myself.
But if you still want to help,
why don't you buy me
a new box of Pop-Tarts?
Any flavor will do,
as long as it's strawberry.
- It was total bullshit.
- Are you saying you didn't
get in a fight at all?
- No, I got in a fight,
but it was only to stay alive.
- Just tell us what happened.
We're on your side.
- Look, I was two months
from getting out, okay?
I was gonna keep my head down
every single day until I walked.
Next thing I know,
some big-ass son of a bitch
is on top of me, and I'm
the one that gets extra time?
- What was his name?
- I don't know, man.
I have no idea.
- Look, Marc, I don't know
if you're afraid of payback
or something, but we need to
know everything if we're gonna...
- I'm not afraid
of no payback, okay?
I don't know who he was.
And if I knew, I would tell you.
Look, that place
took two years of my life.
Two extra years on top of
the two for stealing a few TVs.
If you're going after them,
then I want in on this.
- Then you're in,
but I was in prison
an even shorter time than you,
and I still knew
all the guys' names
on my cellblock.
So either he was new to yours
or you were new to his.
Either way,
I need to know what happened.
- That's easy. I had dinner in
a different block that night.
- Why did you do that?
- 'Cause they told me to.
- Who told you to?
- The guards.
Look, they would post it
on the wall whenever
they felt like it to keep us
from getting too comfortable.
- Which means
you don't know the guard
who decided to move you,
and you don't know the name
of the guy
you got in a fight with.
- I'm telling you guys, man,
I'm not lying.
- I don't think you are.
I think they set it up that way.
- ♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
.
- Louis.
- Hold on, man.
- What are you doing?
- Playing desktop cornhole.
It's supposed to calm my nerves.
- Okay, I hate to interrupt,
but I need to ask a favor.
- Anything.
What do you need?
- You know I was seeing
a psychiatrist last year, right?
- Harvey, if this has
to do with your well-being,
I'm all ears, but as you know,
I'm not a licensed practitioner
of mental health services...
- Louis, that's not it.
Look, my psychiatrist
is being sued.
She has her own attorney,
but I don't trust him,
and I want you to handle it.
- I don't understand.
If you don't trust him,
why aren't you taking it?
- I told you,
she's my therapist.
- Yeah, was.
That doesn't stop you from
helping her with a legal issue.
- All right, you want the truth?
I'm seeing her.
- You're dating your therapist?
- Look, I don't need
a lecture from you, Louis.
- This isn't a lecture, Harvey.
If you're dating your therapist
and someone finds out about it,
she could lose her license.
- No, she can't.
We didn't start dating until
after the official
waiting period was over.
- I want your word on that,
because if someone ever asks...
- You have my word.
I wouldn't lie about that.
- Okay, I'll go talk to her.
But wait a second, Harvey,
does Donna have any idea
about the two of you?
- No, she doesn't,
and for right now I'd like
to keep it that way.
- Six years for stealing
a few TVs, that's not right.
- No, it's not.
- What's our next move?
- We gotta figure out
who decided
a guy two months from parole
should eat
in a different cellblock.
- How the hell
are we gonna do that?
- I don't know, Oliver,
but right now you're gonna
have to work on that yourself.
- What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
- If I don't show
my face at work,
Harvey is gonna get suspicious.
- Mike, are you sure what
we're doing is worth it?
- Oliver, you're the one
that pushed me
to stick with this
in the first place.
You heard that guy,
they doubled his sentence.
Chris Reyes is dead.
Yeah, it's worth it.
- You must be Harvey Specter.
- Thanks for meeting me, Rick.
I know dominating the energy
sector is a full-time job.
- Get to the point,
Mr. Specter.
I didn't interrupt my day
just so you could kiss my ass.
- Then let me tell you
why you did.
Lockwood Energy is about
to release a solar panel
that looks a hell of a lot
like the one
you've been developing
for years.
- How did you know that?
- Because I didn't
spend all morning
brushing up
on my ass-kissing techniques.
- Then you also know that
Lockwood's green division
has only existed
for three months.
They stole that technology.
- Which is why
you should sign with me
so I can go get it back.
- I already have a law firm.
Why shouldn't
I let them handle this?
- Because you don't want
the guy who's gonna sue Lockwood
after they've stolen
your girlfriend.
You want the guy who's gonna
put them in the ground
before they get the chance.
- You're pretty
sure of yourself.
- You want someone
handling this who isn't?
Look, why don't you take
the week to think it over.
Of course,
while you're doing that,
Lockwood's gonna be rushing
your product to market,
and when they do, your
board's gonna be wondering
why you didn't hire me
when you had the chance.
- All right, Mr. Specter,
you win.
You've got three days.
Let's see if you're as good
as you think you are.
- You must be Paula Agard.
- I'm sorry,
but do we know each other?
- Not yet, but it is
a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Louis Litt, and I understand
you are looking for a lawyer.
- I have a lawyer,
and his name's Peter Shumpert.
- Ah, Peter will not
be joining you today.
- Excuse me?
- I mean, I'm sure
he's a nice guy,
but he's not a litigator.
- Well, I don't see what that
has to do with this.
- When an attorney
lets a client meet
with another attorney, trust me,
you need better representation.
- I already know what
an excellent attorney
you are, Mr. Litt.
Harvey said as much when
he offered your services.
- And why'd you turn him down?
- Because...
there are things
about this situation
that I'd rather
not share with Harvey.
- I can understand that
completely,
and whatever they are,
if I were your attorney,
there is no way in hell that
he would hear them from me.
That I can assure you.
- Okay.
Okay, Louis.
You can represent me.
- Good. So let's start by
you giving me the history.
- Well, that's just it.
We weren't solely
business partners.
We were living together,
we had a practice together.
- What happened?
- He broke it off,
and he broke my heart.
I gave him everything in
the partnership that he wanted
just to be rid of it and of him.
- And then?
- Some of our group patients
didn't respond well
to his treatment,
so they started
coming to see me privately.
- Privately or secretly?
- If what you're asking
is if I knew it was a violation
of our agreement,
then yes, I did.
But these people were hurting.
- And you couldn't in good
conscience turn them away.
- No, I couldn't.
- Paula, you have my word,
this stays between you and me.
- Thank you.
[phone buzzes]
- Oliver, tell me
you found something.
- Nothing.
They've got a system
that randomly assigns changes
from time to time.
- Well, what are you
calling me for?
- Because there
might not be a link
between our cases
and the guards,
but I did find one
between the fights.
- I'm listening.
- Out of the 20 cases
we have so far,
the fights have been
with a total
of only four inmates,
and I got the perfect one,
JaMarcus Collins.
He's in the middle of
a ten-year sentence
on cellblock C,
one over from Chris Reyes
and Marc Stevens.
- Well, then we gotta pay
Mr. Collins a visit.
- I've already set it up.
I'll pick you up in an hour.
- Great.
I will see you at the Brooklyn
Housing Authority then. Okay.
- Whatever you're doing,
put it on hold.
I've got a good cop/bad cop
situation and I need you.
- Wait, right now?
- No, three months
from Thursday.
Come on, let's go.
- Harvey, I can't.
- What do you mean you can't?
- I ha... I have a meeting
with Oliver at
the Brooklyn Housing Authority.
I can't leave him hanging.
- Oliver?
You just did a pro bono.
That's not our deal.
- I know that, Harvey, but I
put this in motion weeks ago.
I didn't know you were gonna
give me another pro bono.
- Fine, I'll handle it myself.
Look, whatever you're
doing with Oliver,
wrap it the hell up.
I didn't bring you back to not
be here when I need you.
.
- Dr. Lipschitz, it's Louis.
Um, look, there's
no two ways to say this.
I was way out of line
the other night,
and I know you care about me,
and not just because
you have an obligation to.
So if it's not too much trouble,
I would like to resume
our sessions, please.
Please call me back.
Thanks.
- Louis, I need to talk
to you about Harvey.
- What about him?
- I just want to make sure
that you and he
are on good terms.
- Yeah, Donna,
we're on good terms.
- Are you sure?
'Cause we all pulled together
to get back on solid footing,
and I saw the two of you
huddled up in here earlier,
and I'd hate to think
that things are going
in the wrong direction.
- No, not going in
the wrong direction, Donna.
There is no need to worry.
- Well, I do worry, Louis.
Because I know what kind of
mental state you're still in,
and I know that the slightest
thing can touch you off,
and I know that...
- Look, Donna,
for your information,
we are on such good terms
that Harvey...
- That Harvey what?
- Nothing.
- Louis, what's going on?
- Okay, look, Donna,
I'm only gonna
tell you this once.
Harvey asked me to handle
a matter for him.
It's personal.
He trusts me with it.
Now, if you trust me at all,
you'll take my word for the fact
that Harvey and I
are on good terms.
- Okay.
I trust you.
- Harvey Specter.
We didn't have
a proper introduction
the last time we met.
Holly Cromwell.
- What do you want,
Ms. Cromwell?
- So much for formalities.
- I got a lot on my plate.
I don't have time
for formalities.
- If you brought me on,
maybe you would.
- Excuse me?
- Headhunting isn't cutting it
for me, Mr. Specter.
I want back in the game,
and since you're the reason
I'm out of the game,
you should hire me as
a full-time in-house consultant.
- So you want me to give you
a handout out of guilt?
- I don't want a handout.
But you made me a promise you
wouldn't ruin my reputation.
- What do you want me to say?
What you do is dangerous.
- I want you to say you make
promises you can't keep.
And by the way,
you wouldn't have sent
that Rachel woman back to me
if you didn't know
what I do is worth it.
- Okay, first of all,
I never sent anyone back to you.
And second, whatever job
you think you're suited for
doesn't exist in my firm.
- It does at Baker Simms
and Walker Stein.
- Yeah, well, I'm not looking
to make a spot on the payroll
for someone whose only
skill set is crossing lines.
- You mean when you cross them
so well yourself.
- Like I said, Ms. Cromwell,
I got a lot on my plate.
- Give me a Macallan, neat.
- The way Lockwood
stock shot up,
why not make it a double?
- I'm sorry,
I don't recognize you.
Do you work in Business Affairs?
- No, I work in suing your ass
for trying to pass off
Galvadyne's solar panels
as your own.
- I don't know who you are,
and I don't know
what you're talking about.
We developed
that technology in-house.
- Oh, bullshit.
That technology
takes years to develop,
and your entire division's
only been in existence
since last Tuesday.
- What can I say?
When you invest
in the right talent,
you can move mountains,
and last I checked,
being smarter than your
competition wasn't illegal.
- Well, if you're half as smart
as you say you are,
you'd give us
our product back now,
or we'll take your company
from you later.
- If you're here
without the FBI,
it means you're just
a shakedown artist
without a shred of evidence
to back up your claims.
- No, it means I'm giving you
the chance to make it right.
Because once I prove
you stole our technology,
the only thing
you'll be celebrating
is a felony fraud conviction.
- Thanks for meeting us,
Mr. Collins.
I'm Oliver Grady,
and this is my associate.
- Your associate got a name?
- My name's not as important
as the questions I have.
Like why did you incite
a brawl in the cafeteria
during lunch on November 4th
of last year?
- What is this?
I thought you were here
to talk about reviving
my shot at parole.
- We can absolutely
talk about that,
after you tell us why
you conspired with this prison
to get your fellow inmates'
sentences extended.
- This is bullshit.
Guard!
- Listen, you don't have
to talk to us.
But this thing comes out,
instead of getting out
in five years,
you're gonna spend the rest
of your life in here.
- All right,
what do you wanna know?
- Let's start with who's
telling you to pick fights
with guys who are
about to get out.
- Nobody ever told me
to pick a fight with anybody.
All I know is new guy
comes into the block,
I'm supposed to teach him
a lesson.
- Well, how do you know that
if nobody ever told you?
- It happened, like,
two years go.
I got in a fight with a guy,
they dragged me away.
Thought they were gonna
throw me in Solitary.
Instead, they threw him
in Solitary.
I get back to my cell,
brand-new PlayStation in there.
- And let me guess,
you never thought to ask why.
- I knew why, and I'm not giving
up my goddamn PlayStation.
- You willing to testify
to that in court?
- You really gonna
get me out of here early?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Guard!
- Hey, how'd it go?
- Well, if you're wondering
if I convinced Paula
to take me on,
the answer is yes.
I am her lawyer now.
We have a settlement
meeting tomorrow,
and this is the last we will
speak about it ever again.
- Louis...
- No, Harvey.
Paula is my client now,
and I don't wanna have to worry
about you sticking
your nose in a case
that you think you can
handle better than me.
- I don't think...
- Because if you could
handle it better than me,
you would, but you can't,
because you're too involved,
and you know it.
- You're right.
She's in good hands.
I'll stay out of your way.
- Ah, no. Not good enough.
I want your word, because
I will drop it right now.
- Okay, Louis, you have my word.
- Harvey. Everything okay
with you and Louis?
- Yeah. Why?
- 'Cause he said he was
handling a matter for you,
but he wouldn't tell me
what it was,
and five minutes ago
I saw the two of you
having an intense discussion.
- Everything's okay,
and it wasn't
an intense discussion.
It was a strategic meeting,
so you don't need
to get involved.
- I wasn't trying
I was coming to tell you
that Rick Dunn's
been waiting in your office
for 15 minutes.
- 15 minutes? Why didn't
you come and get me right away?
- Because I only just noticed
him when I walked by,
and I'm not your
secretary anymore.
I'm COO of this firm,
so instead of criticizing me
for working late, why don't
you go see what he wants?
- Rick, I could have
come to your office
if I'd known
you wanted to see me.
- Well, when someone's
avoiding me, I come to them.
- No one's avoiding anyone.
I was gonna give you
a call later.
- And if you had good news,
you'd have done it already.
So what the hell happened?
- What do you think happened?
They denied everything
and said they developed
that technology on their own.
- Well, I don't give a shit
what they said.
You said you could
get me results.
- And I will, but I didn't say
it would take just one meeting.
- Well, let me tell you what
happened after that one meeting.
They just announced
they're moving up their launch
by a month.
- Rick, listen to me.
They're not moving anything up.
It's a bluff,
and I give you my word,
they'll never go to market
with your product.
- Now you listen to me.
You said you wouldn't have
anything after one meeting.
Well, you sure as hell
better have it after two.
Because if you don't, I'm gonna
tell everyone in the city
that the only thing
Harvey Specter is good at
is making promises
he can't keep.
[tense music]
.
- Shit.
There's no paper trail
proving any inmates were
rewarded for picking fights.
- Okay. Just because
Collins didn't talk
doesn't mean
the other three won't.
- Yes, it does, and you know it.
And none of them
are close to parole,
which means we don't even
have that to offer.
- Okay, then let's go back
through the guards again.
- I told you, that's a dead end.
Brunswick has a system
of randomly assigning changes.
- Then let's start looking
outside of Brunswick.
- Holy shit.
You're right.
They own eight other prisons,
and if they're
doing this in one...
- Then they're doing it
at the other seven.
- And maybe one of them
isn't as good
at covering their tracks.
- Bingo.
All right, let's do it.
'Cause I'm supposed to be
at dinner right now with Rachel,
not going through files
with you.
- Take your pick.
Wabash, Dalton,
Lambert and Blackwell...
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Lambert?
Lambert Correctional Institute
is owned by Reform Corp?
- Yeah, why?
You know someone there?
- No.
No, I know somebody
who used to be there.
- He the kinda guy
who'd know something?
- He's the kinda guy
that would know everything.
- Rachel, have you seen Mike?
He's not in his office.
- Uh, he left earlier
this morning for the clinic,
so he must still be there.
- Again? I told him
to wrap that case up.
- Harvey, he's working hard
to live up to your deal
and still come through
for his other clients.
- Well, right now I need him,
and I'm getting a little tired
of looking into his office
and finding it empty.
- Maybe there's something
I can do to help you.
- No, it's fine.
Just let him know
I'm looking for him.
Actually, now that you mention
it, there is one thing.
I heard you went back
to Holly Cromwell.
- Yes, Mike and I did.
Is there a problem?
- No, there's no problem.
I just want to know
if she came through.
- Well, she stuck it to us
on the fee a little,
but other than that,
yeah, she came through.
- Was it worth it?
- Let me put it this way, the
article they wrote about Mike,
it never would have
existed without her.
- Wow.
If it isn't Mike Ross.
I take it you're not here
selling Girl Scout cookies,
but if you are,
I'll take two boxes
of go fu... yourself.
- Just sit down, Gallo.
I don't want to be here
any more than you do,
but I need your help.
- Last time I helped you,
I got five years for my trouble.
- Well, maybe we can
do something about that.
- What the hell is this?
- That is a lawsuit
against your former prison,
for starting fights with inmates
so that they could
extend their sentences,
and I want you
to be an expert witness.
- You gotta be shitting me.
- Frank...
- Save your breath.
There's not a chance
in hell I'm doing this.
- What if I told you I could
make it worth your while?
- It doesn't matter
because I don't know
what the hell
you're talking about anyway.
- Bullshit.
You expect me to believe
that you own
all the guards in here,
but you didn't know
about a conspiracy
at your last prison?
- Sounds like you know
a whole hell of a lot.
What do you need me for?
- I need somebody
to tell me everything, and
in exchange I am willing to...
- I'll tell you
what you're willing to do.
What you promised to do
in the first place.
You're gonna get me out of here.
- You know I can't do that.
- Bullshit. That Cahill guy
owes you big time.
March those pretty
little feet in there
and say what has to be said,
or you won't know
anything about anything.
While you're at it,
next time you're here
bring me a goddamn cookie.
- Hope you had time to look over
the settlement offer I sent.
- To be Frank, Mr. Litt,
this number's so low,
we won't even be countering.
We're not negotiating
against ourselves.
- Oh, no, you want me
to negotiate against myself.
Let me tell you something,
that number should be zero.
But Dr. Agard
is willing to pay something
in order to put
this matter behind her.
- But she's not willing to face
me and own up to what she did.
- All she did, Dr. Manning,
was care for your patients.
- Which means she violated
their partnership agreement.
- And according
to the Hippocratic Oath,
patient care supersedes
any legal agreement.
- She didn't care
about those patients.
She just wanted
to steal my business.
- Really? Then why
did they contact her?
- You have no proof of that.
- Yes, I do.
I have phone records.
My client had
an ethical obligation
to care for those patients.
- And what about
her ethical obligation
not to sleep with a patient?
- What'd you just say?
- I know that she's been running
around with Harvey Specter,
and it's no surprise that it's
his partner defending her.
- Dr. Agard's personal life
has no bearing on this case.
- Oh, it'll have
plenty of bearing
when the ethics board learn
that she started dating
one of her patients
before the mandatory
waiting period elapsed.
- That's a bald-faced lie,
and now you're twisting facts
in order to blackmail my client.
- Blackmail is
a serious accusation.
My client never asked
for anything
in exchange for his silence.
- Well, he sure as shit
implied it.
- This meeting's over,
Mr. Litt.
Why don't you take
the evening to cool down?
Think of a real number.
- The great Harvey Specter
came all the way
below 14th Street to see me.
I'm honored.
- What can I say?
When I have good news, I like
to deliver it face-to-face.
- Does that mean
you're ready to hire me?
- Not yet, but if you
take care of something for me,
I just might be.
- Lockwood's launching
a solar panel?
Since when are they in
the renewable energy business?
- Since they stole
the technology from Galvadyne.
- No way.
They didn't steal it.
- How can you know that?
- Because there's only
six people capable
of that kind of work, and if
one of them did it, I'd know.
- Well, they got it somehow,
and I need to know
how they did it.
- That's not a hell of
a lot to go on.
- If I had more to go on,
I wouldn't need you.
- In other words, you want me
to do the impossible to audition
for a job you told me
yesterday didn't even exist?
- Then consider it
a magic trick.
You make this
information appear,
all of a sudden,
so does that job.
- Then start picking out
an office,
because the next time
you hear from me,
I'm moving in.
- Where the hell have
you been all morning?
[door shuts]
- I went to see Sean Cahill
at the S.E.C.
- I hate to break it to you,
Mike, but the S.E.C.
doesn't have jurisdiction
over private prisons.
- I know that. I was trying
to cut Frank Gallo a deal.
- Whoa.
He said he'll testify?
- Not unless he gets parole,
and Cahill said no.
Which means we need to go
through Gallo's files,
see if we can find another way
to get him released.
- Mike, Mike, hold up a second.
Gallo's files said
he got an extra five years
for assault with a deadly weapon
while he was at Danbury.
- So?
- So that's pretty damn close
to when you got outta there.
Mike.
Is this the guy
who tried to kill you?
- Oliver...
- Jesus, Mike!
We can't put a guy like that
out on the street.
- I'm not trying
to get him out now.
All right, I'm gonna
get him out two years early,
which is still
five years from now.
And in the meantime
if I don't do that,
how many guys are gonna end up
just like Chris Reyes?
- Right now I'm worried about
you ending up like Chris Reyes.
- If Gallo is gonna
come after me,
it doesn't matter if it's
in five years or seven.
We only have so long
before me working on this
becomes too risky, which
means this is the only way.
- Okay.
But I've seen you do things
no other lawyer could.
You're sure as shit
smart enough to convince
this guy to take
something besides parole.
- You don't know Frank Gallo.
- What I know
is what you taught me.
Everybody has
something they want.
Which means all you have
to do is find out
whatever else Gallo wants
and give it to him.
- Louis, hello.
How did it go?
- Listen to me,
if I'm gonna be your attorney,
I need you to tell me
the goddamn truth.
- I'm not sure I like your tone.
I told you the truth.
- Did you?
Because I need to know
if you started seeing Harvey
while he was still your patient.
- What? No.
Who told you that?
- Your ex, and he's threatening
to go to the board with it.
If there is
one shred of proof...
- There isn't any proof,
because it didn't happen.
And if you don't care
to believe that,
then you can turn around
and walk right out.
Because I don't care to be
represented by a man
who questions my integrity.
- Okay, I am sorry.
I just don't like
being blindsided.
- Well, I'm glad
your shock is behind you,
but mine isn't.
What do you mean
he's going to the board?
- I mean he is blackmailing you
with the threat
of going to the board.
- What?
That would ruin my career.
- I know, which is why
you need to tell me
what really happened
between you and Jacob now.
- Louis, I don't feel
comfortable doing that.
- I'm sorry, Paula,
but you're gonna have to,
because the only defense
against what he is trying to do
is the truth.
- When I told you
he broke my heart,
I was telling the truth.
But what I didn't tell you
was that after that
he changed his mind.
.
- Donna, I need you
to draw up some paperwork
for a new employee.
- I'll get to it
first thing in the morning.
Wait a second,
why are we bringing on
Holly Cromwell as a consultant?
- Because she kicks ass,
and I don't want to have
to track her down every time
I need her help with something.
- Harvey, I think this
is a mistake.
- Well, it's my call.
- No, actually it isn't.
- Excuse me?
- I told you, I'm not
your secretary anymore.
I'm COO, and you
made me that for a reason.
I know people, and I'm
telling you it's reckless
to hire someone
who betrayed her employer
the first chance she got.
- Donna, I gave her
my word I'd do this
if she came through,
she's gonna come through,
and I already broke
my word to her once.
- Well, then maybe you
shouldn't promise a job
at a law firm to someone
who isn't a lawyer.
- Are you kidding me?
You're not a lawyer,
I just promoted you,
and that worked out pretty
damn well if you ask me.
- And you only did that after I
proved my loyalty to this firm.
- And she's gonna start
proving her loyalty now.
Need I remind you that...
- That you're in charge?
No, you don't.
And if you try to give me your,
"This isn't something
we vote on" bullshit,
I will find out where Louis is,
and I will bring him
down here right now
with a copy of the bylaws,
because I am betting it is
something we vote on.
- Okay, Donna, you win.
You don't wanna hire her,
we won't.
But you wanna be the one
to make that call,
you're gonna be the one
to tell her to her face.
- Hey.
You hungry? There's some
leftover Thai in the kitchen.
- Great, I'm starving.
Haven't eaten all day.
- Mike, about that,
I know I said that maybe
you should ask Harvey
for a little time off
to help with the clinic,
but I'm wondering if maybe
you should take
a little time off
from the clinic to help Harvey.
- Rachel...
- He was looking for you today,
and it was clear
it wasn't the first time.
And you said yourself,
he was nice enough
to make this deal
in the first place,
so maybe it's time
to remember that.
- I do remember that.
It's not like we work
on every case together.
He knows that.
- And I know that, too.
But he brought you back
for a reason,
and that's so that
when he does need you,
you'll be there.
- You're right.
I'm just... I'm working
on this Brooklyn Housing thing,
and there's a deadline.
But as soon as it is over,
I will take a break
from the clinic.
Promise.
- Okay.
- Now, did you get
the spring rolls that I like?
- Yes.
No.
Maybe?
- You ate them all, didn't you?
- Well, they were calling
out my name.
- Every time!
- You know that.
It's the sauce!
- Louis, we've never discussed
the specifics of a case before.
Why do you think this one is
so important all of a sudden?
- I don't know.
She kept telling me
all these horrible things
about this guy, but...
- But what, Louis?
- She also told me that all he
wanted to do was get her back.
She felt sorry for him.
I guess I felt sorry
for him, too.
- Sorry for him or for yourself?
- What are you talking about?
- Louis, I hate to draw
comparisons for you,
but is there a chance
you're putting yourself
in this man's shoes
because it's so similar
to what happened
between you and Tara?
- I didn't cheat on her.
- But you behaved poorly.
It ended the relationship,
and you wanted her back.
- And I told you
that I do not want
to talk about getting closure
with Tara anymore.
- I know that, Louis,
but it is my duty
to keep bringing it up to you.
Otherwise, why are we
seeing each other?
- Okay, then, Doc,
honestly,
I don't think that's it.
- Then you shouldn't
have any trouble
doing what you know
you have to do.
- Holly, right?
- Yes.
- I'm Donna Paulsen.
Thanks for meeting me so early.
- No problem. We can go over
the deal points informally,
but I will need my lawyer
to take a look at the contract
before I sign.
- Actually, I have a few
questions for you first.
- What kind of questions?
- The kind that determine
if you're
Pearson Specter Litt material.
- I'm not here
for my contract, am I?
I'm here because you have
a problem with me.
- I do have a problem with you.
- I see what this is.
I should have known.
I have an MBA from Wharton,
I graduated with honors,
and you think
all I am is a high-priced...
- No, I don't give a shit what
you think about sex and men.
My problem is that you're
in the betrayal business.
You betray the men
that you prey on,
and then the only time
we had an interaction with you,
you turned on your employer.
- Well, why don't you bring
that up with your employer?
Because he's the one
who got me in that position.
It was the first and last time
I ever did anything like that,
and I lost my livelihood
because of it.
- I didn't know that.
- Discretion and integrity were
the foundations of my business.
Your boss knocked them down,
and I don't appreciate you
questioning whether or not they
were there in the first place.
- What's this?
- That is what I thought I'd be
delivering to my new employer.
- This is exactly
what Harvey needed.
How the hell did you get this?
- What I do is an art.
I find out what people want,
what they're afraid of,
what makes them tick,
and I use it.
And they never know
the big picture,
so when they give me what I
need, they think it's nothing.
- And then when you put
all the pieces together,
it adds up to exactly what
your clients are looking for.
- That's everything
I promised I'd get Harvey,
and it took me less than a day.
I kept my word.
- Where's my cookie?
- Brought you something
better than a cookie.
You were a prisoner
under Reform Corp, too,
which means you are now
a member of the class.
We win this, you're not
Brooks Hatlen bagging groceries
at the Food-Way
when you get out.
You're gonna be Andy Dufresne
sitting on a beach in Mexico
with a bank account
full of cash.
- I already make
a nice living in here.
- You do, but I was thinking
maybe some of that money
might go to your daughter.
- What'd you just say to me?
- I did some digging, Frank.
I know you don't talk to her.
And she is not doing great,
and this much money
could really change her life.
- If you're playing
with me on this thing...
- I'm not playing you, Frank.
And I'm not trying
to bully you with this.
I'm trying to help you.
- We had an arrangement.
- Brokered directly
by the prison?
- Not at first,
but I saw the pattern.
Break some skulls, get a reward.
So I went to the source
to get things codified.
- And did you?
- Yeah.
Found out what was what.
It was good at first,
then I realized
it was like working for the mob.
Great work while you can get it,
but you can never quit.
So I tried to put an end
to the whole thing.
That night the guards
killed the cameras,
and five of my so-called
friends did a number on me.
- Wait a second.
Are you saying this the deal
that got you to Danbury?
You already informed on
this guy?
- No, what are you, nuts?
No one cares how prisoners
are treated.
I informed on real guys
about real crimes.
That's how I got out.
- Are you willing to go on
the record with this?
Tell me your source?
- It's not gonna be
that easy, Mikey.
I'm gonna need an advance
on that settlement.
.
- Please, sit down.
- Glad to see you've come back
with a real number, Mr. Litt.
- The only number I'm back with
is the one that
I'm gonna do on your client.
- What the hell? You said
he was ready to cut a check.
- Oh, well, what she should
have told you, Jacob,
is when you threaten
someone with blackmail,
you better goddamn be ready
to defend yourself.
- And you better watch how
you talk to my client.
- You client is a lying,
cheating piece of shit,
whose only motive for suing
his ex is to get revenge.
- She broke our agreement.
- No, you broke your agreement
when you had an affair
for two months
and you thought you were
gonna leave her.
- That has nothing
to do with this suit.
- It's got everything
You see, you messed up.
You changed your mind
and you wouldn't
take no for an answer
when she ended it,
and that's why you've been
stalking her for the last year.
- I haven't been stalking her.
- Bang. Signed affidavits
one and two.
Unlike your
bullshit accusations,
I have actual proof
from the agency
that you hired to follow her,
to the guy at the news stand
who says you stand there half
the day watching her building.
- Jacob, is this true?
- It is true.
He knows it's true.
And that is a Class D
felony, Doctor.
I should have you arrested,
or maybe I'll just
go to the board,
have your license removed.
- We were going
to have a life together.
I planned everything out.
Where we were going to live,
how many kids we'd have,
where we'd go
on our anniversary.
And then I make a mistake,
and the next thing I know,
my whole life was gone.
- We'll be dropping the suit.
- You looking for Oliver?
- Nathan, hey.
Uh, yeah, just had some things
that I wanted to run by him.
- On the Brooklyn Housing case
or on your prison lawsuit?
- Look, Nathan, I had to...
- Mike, come on, relax.
I'm not angry.
Though I do wish I had a picture
of your face right now.
- What tipped you off?
- Come on, are you kidding me?
I mean, the second you signed
that agreement,
I knew you'd go back on it.
- So then why didn't
you say anything?
- Because this time
you're screwing over
Harvey Specter and not me.
Look, you're either
gonna win this thing
and we're gonna get
all the credit,
or you're gonna get caught
with your hand
in the cookie jar,
and we'll drop the case.
I have no downside.
- Does Oliver know?
- Yeah, yeah, I pretended
to be pissed at him
and sent him home.
Look, Mike,
why don't you take the night
and think about how much
respect you just gained for me,
then come back
and kill it in the morning.
- Thanks, Nathan.
- You're welcome, Mike.
- Donna, before you
go home tonight,
I need you to cut me
a check for Holly.
- What do you mean? I'm gonna
put her on the payroll.
- She doesn't want
to work here anymore.
Said she'd rather do
one-off jobs if at all.
Here's the amount.
- I don't understand.
I was good with having her.
- Well, whatever you said made
her not good with having us.
- Harvey, we're
a tight-knit group.
We don't betray each other
and we don't keep secrets
from each other.
I had to find out
where she stood.
And if the cost of that
was her not coming here,
then I don't regret it.
- I understand, Donna.
I'm not coming down on you.
I just need the check.
- Harvey, is there something
that you're not telling me
about this woman?
'Cause it seems like you've
been different lately,
and... I don't know.
- It's nothing about this woman.
I just thought she'd be
a good addition.
These things happen.
- It's funny.
I love my new position,
but I miss this.
- I miss it, too.
- You want me to pour us
a couple drinks?
- Maybe tomorrow night.
I have something I have
to deal with right now.
- Okay.
I'll cut you that check.
- You were right, Doc.
I hadn't really dealt with Tara.
But one thing is clear.
The situation was my doing.
Which means...
I need to keep
working on myself,
because...
I don't wanna mess things up
with the next Tara.
- Louis, typically I refrain
from saying things like this
to my patients, but...
I am proud of you.
- Good night, Doc.
- Good night, Louis.
- Time for one more appointment?
- Hello.
What are you doing here?
- I wanted to take you out
and celebrate.
Louis told me what happened.
- I just got off
the phone with him.
He did an amazing job.
And you did an amazing job
recommending him.
- Why didn't you tell me
about Jacob?
- I asked Louis
not to tell you that.
- Louis didn't tell me.
- Well, then how do you...
- Because I do,
and all I could think of
was I wish you trusted
me enough to know
that I wouldn't go nuts on
this guy for what he did to you.
- Is that why you think
I didn't tell you?
- Well, you know my history
with infidelity.
What else could it be?
- Harvey, the man cheated on me.
I trusted him,
and he cheated on me,
and I was afraid
of how you'd see me.
- Why would him cheating on you
make me see you differently?
- Because some people
think that a woman
who can be cheated on
can't be...
loveable.
- How can you know me
and think that?
- Well, it's not about you.
It's about me.
- And if this guy
did this to you,
then he's an idiot,
and all he did
is lose out on something great.
Not loveable?
- Psychiatrists don't
know everything, you know.
- I'm starting to realize that.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- You really are burning
the candle at both ends.
- Hey.
Is this for me?
- Mm-hmm. Since you were
too busy to come to dinner,
I thought, why can't
dinner come to you?
- I don't understand.
What do you mean, come to me?
- I brought it to the clinic,
Mike, but you weren't there.
- I just... I must have
not been back yet.
- Back from where?
Was it the nursing home
in Brooklyn
or was it
the Department of Buildings?
Because Oliver, he couldn't
seem to decide which.
- Rachel, I didn't...
- Mike, if you can't tell me
what's going on,
I'm gonna start to wonder
what else you've been
keeping from me.
- I wasn't lying about
working a case with Oliver.
I just didn't tell you
which one.
- The prison one.
- Yeah.
- You signed an agreement.
This is a fireable offense.
- Harvey isn't gonna
fire me for...
- Okay, but maybe he should.
- How can you say that?
- Because you're taking
advantage of his trust,
not to mention mine.
- Rachel, these prisoners are
being exploited for money.
- And you trying
to do the right thing
doesn't change the fact
that you gave your word.
- Rachel...
- Look...
We've been through enough
for you to know
that I'm still gonna
love you in the morning,
but you have to ask yourself:
What is your word worth?
'Cause with the way
things are going,
it's not gonna be worth
very much.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net