Previously on "Suits"
I'm offering you a deal...
One for you, one for me.
- You are not getting my office.
- Oh, yes, I am
'cause she's gone, Harvey.
It's time for you
to take the reins.
I'm here to ask you out.
As of this morning,
I'm the head of my firm,
and, when I thought
of sharing that with someone,
I thought of you.
One dinner.
I figured out what I want,
and I want to be
a partner at this firm.
All I'm asking is
for a seat at the table.
I'll have Louis about it.
You're afraid to take
responsibility for this firm,
and you won't admit it
to yourself!
You told me that you're
now head of the firm.
I am... i just haven't
told Louis yet.
I think this may have
been a mistake.
You don't think
I've had fantasies
that one day you'd take me
in your arms and kiss me?
Those fantasies weren't
of a man who's still too afraid
to take control of a firm
that bears his name.
I'm not giving up
my associates!
That's enough.
Donna asked for a seat
at the table,
and I gave her one.
You don't make her Goddamn
senior partner.
If Jessica were here,
she'd tell you to do
the same exact thing.
Jessica isn't here,
but I am.
I think I know
what you may need.
If you're telling me that
I need to talk to Tara...
You were gonna get married.
That can't all end
over a voicemail.
I know we haven't spoken.
I just really need
to see you tonight.
♪♪
♪♪ Smooth music...
Oh, wow,
the sunrise is beautiful
from up here.
To be honest, I can't remember
the last time
- I saw the sun rise.
- Really?
It takes something
pretty special
to get me up before 7:00 A.M.
As I recall,
I was pretty special last night.
There... you surprised me again.
You know, the truth is
I'm a little surprised
- by all this myself.
- What do you mean?
Well, I mean, you disappear
for nearly a year,
and then, one day, you suddenly
show up in a '57 Chevy...
- '72 Ferrari, yeah.
- But,
And you sweep me off my feet.
And I liked it.
That's good 'cause
I wasn't sure you would.
Of course you weren't.
You don't really know me yet.
Till yesterday, we'd spent
about 50 hours together,
and we'd spent most of them
talking about you.
I know, and that's what I love
about our relationship.
- Harvey...
- Paula...
Before you say
what I think you're gonna say,
let me say
you may know me better than anyone.
And now I'd like
to get to know you too.
I'd like that.
♪♪
I guess what I'm trying
to say is I acted irrationally,
but please, Tara, if you could
just give me another chance...
I promise you that I will
never let you down again.
You know you can't
say that, Louis.
Wait, I'm sorry, what?
This is my role play.
I can say whatever
the hell I want.
And we've talked about you
making bold proclamations
about your own behavior.
What does that
have to do with this?
You just promised to never
let Tara down again.
That is unrealistic.
What happens when you inevitably
break that promise?
I'll apologize and promise
I'll never do it again.
And you don't see a problem
with that pattern?
What I see, Dr. lipschitz,
is we're 46 minutes
into this session, and I haven't
gotten closure yet.
Louis, we spent seven years
on the fact that your mother
made you wear
Esther's hand-me-ups.
You're not getting closure
in 50 minutes.
Well, then what the hell
am I paying you for?
Okay, Louis.
What's really going on here?
It's not about Tara.
It's... it's about the baby.
♪♪
I'm just worried
I'll never be a father.
♪♪
I think... that's a good place
for us to pick up next week.
- What the fu...?
- Louis, calm down.
No, I just told you
my deepest fear
is that my clock is running out,
and all you care about
is your precious time?
Has it ever occurred to you
that you don't have a clock
and can have children
whenever you want?
Well, that sounds like
a load of crap coming from a guy
who's looking at his clock.
What about your idol,
Tony Randall?
♪♪
Oh, my God.
Tony Randall fathered
his first child at 77.
Doc, this is fantastic.
So you're good till next week.
What, are you nuts?
I'm teetering.
Clear up tomorrow,
all afternoon.
♪♪
I was at work.
It was the kids'
daycare calling.
Shannon never showed up.
And then what happened?
Then the police called.
My world ended.
And one month later,
I got a letter
from the insurance company
saying Shannon lied
on her application.
About what?
They're claiming
she was a smoker.
- Was she?
- No, she quit five years ago,
and she was totally
up-front about it.
So then why would they think
she lied on her application?
Because of this.
It's a picture of Shannon
at her cousin's wedding.
They sent it to me
along with her denied claim.
Please tell me this picture
is over five years old.
It was taken eight months ago.
They must've gone
into her Facebook page.
Shit.
It was one cigarette,
and I gave her hell for it.
It doesn't matter
if it was one or a hundred,
it's enough for them to claim
her policy is null and void.
My wife died
in a car accident, Mr. Ross.
She was a healthy
39-year-old woman.
She died rushing from her job
to pick up our children.
What the hell does any of this
have to do with smoking?
It shouldn't have
anything to do with it,
but this company is not
in the business
of helping people.
It's in the business
of making money.
So if they can find any reason
not to honor a claim,
they'll take it.
Without that insurance money,
we're gonna lose our home.
Please... my children
have lost enough.
♪♪
I'll find a way.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ me and missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ all right ♪
♪ all step back, I'm 'bout to dance ♪
*SUITS*
Season 07 Episode 02
Title: "The Statue"
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
Hey, I didn't know anybody
was moving in here.
It looks great.
Well, as it turns out,
we're getting ourselves
a new partner, and they needed
a new office, so.
- New partner?
- That's fantastic.
Shows we're back on our feet.
What firm are they from?
- This one.
- I don't understand.
That's 'cause it hasn't
been announced yet,
but you're looking at
the newest senior partner
at Pearson specter litt.
Wow.
Congratulations, Donna.
- You must be thrilled.
- I am.
And I know what
you're thinking...
How can a secretary
be made a partner?
- But...
- I wasn't thinking that, Donna.
I know how hard you work and
how much you mean to this firm
- and everyone in it.
- Thanks, Katrina.
You're welcome.
I'll let you get back to work.
♪♪
All I'm saying is
I think you're rushing it.
And I'm saying that,
when you overthrow a dictator,
you don't leave their statue
up in the square.
You tear it the hell down.
You don't think that
this sends a message
that you have
something to prove?
Harvey, do you remember
Arthur Reeves?
You mean the guy
who played superman?
That was George Reeves.
Arthur Reeves founded this firm.
And when Gordon, Schimdt, and
Van Dyke ran him out of town,
they didn't just tear
his name off the wall.
They called his biggest client
and told them
to pack up their shit
and find another firm.
- What's your point?
- My point is they wanted
the world to know there was
a new sheriff in town,
and the message that sends
isn't that you have
something to prove...
It's that you're in charge.
And you're staying that way.
♪♪
Hope you don't mind I took
the Liberty of hanging that.
Let me guess...
It's your last official act
as my secretary.
I told you once before
I wouldn't leave you
- high and dry.
- Thanks, Donna.
You're welcome, Harvey.
And speaking of not being
your secretary anymore...
This is a press release
announcing your partnership.
It's more than just
a press release.
It's a... statement to the world.
I'll take a look at it later.
Do you mean, like,
later this afternoon
or later, like,
after you go see Dr. Agard?
- What?
- Harvey, the last time
I stopped being your secretary,
you started having
panic attacks,
and I'm not saying
that's gonna happen again,
but you just got a look
on your face,
and I wanna make sure
you're okay with all of this.
I'm okay with it, Donna.
I'll get you what you need
to issue that release,
but, right now,
I gotta make a statement of my own.
♪♪
What can I do for you,
Mr. Ross?
Well, you can start by writing
a check to Harry kirst.
- You don't waste time, do you?
- No, I don't.
So why don't you cut my client
a check for $300,000,
and I'll withdraw this lawsuit
I haven't filed yet.
Mr. Ross, I'm afraid
there's been
a little misunderstanding here.
We're not looking to settle.
Then why the hell did you
set this meeting?
'Cause it's policy to meet
with our clients and try
to resolve their issues.
Okay, well, my client's issue
is you're not honoring his claim
so he can't support
his children.
Yes, and I'm very sorry
about that,
but my hands are tied.
I get it.
Your policy is to give people
the runaround so they get
demoralized and drop their case.
No, Mr. Ross, our policy is
to follow the letter
of our contracts, and,
if we let one person who lied
on their application
get away with it,
we wouldn't have
a business anymore.
Look at me.
I'm not some personal injury
lawyer, all right?
I work at Pearson specter litt.
I'm not gonna get worn down.
So I suggest you just
cut me a check.
Save yourself the trouble
of me wiping the floor
with you in court.
As I said, my hands are tied,
but it won't be me
you'll be going up
against in court.
It'll be our outside counsel,
Mr. Ackerman.
And, from what I've seen,
nobody wipes the floor
with Mr. Ackerman.
♪♪
Nice office.
Mine's better.
Isn't that the same line
you used when you thought
your Ferrari was better
than my cobra?
It was better.
And a good line never gets old.
- Tell that to your hairline.
- Tell that to your waistline.
Good to see you, Harvey.
What brings you down?
I'm here to finish
a conversation
we started years ago.
Well, I know you're not
coming over here,
so you must be talking about
me working over there.
What if I am?
I'd say "which one of
my clients are you after?"
Because we both know
you can't have Pfizer.
Yes, I can.
Are you telling me
you're ready to drop
Jessica's oldest client
just to get me?
That's what I'm telling you.
Ah.
Why now?
Because Jessica's gone,
so now I can.
- Then make me name partner.
- What?
This isn't about Jessica's
gone so now you can...
This is about Jessica's gone,
so now you wanna tell the world
that you're not her.
And that's not about hiring me.
That's about getting my client.
Alex, this is a win/win.
I don't poach.
You come over.
We have fun.
But I'm not gonna just
- give you the run of the place.
- Then I'm not coming.
Because my name is going up
on this wall within a year.
And Pfizer's not leaving me.
- Alex...
- You always say you're
the better poker player.
Well, not today, because I'm
all in, and you got nothing.
So either add my name
to your letterhead
or take your chips and go home.
♪♪
Your honor, they can dress
this up all they want,
but the fact is the deceased
entered into a contract
in bad faith by claiming
she was no longer a smoker.
The only fact here is that
they're manufacturing
a reason to weasel out
of a legitimate claim.
Are you gonna tell the court
that we manufactured
this picture of your client
smoking eight months ago?
I'm well aware
of the photo that you sent
a grieving husband,
but an image of a woman
not inhaling a cigarette
doesn't prove anything.
- She lied on her application.
- Which had nothing
to do with how she died.
And manner of death
isn't at issue here.
The contract is.
He's got a point.
Your honor, they're claiming
that my client entered
into a policy in bad faith.
Well, what kind of faith is it
when a company pores through
a woman's social media history
just to stick it
to her grieving husband
and three children?
Better faith than a man
that pretended to be an attorney
for the better part
of three years.
What are you talking about?
Your honor, this is Mr. Ross'
Harvard diploma.
The only problem is Mr. Ross
never actually went to Harvard.
The only place he did graduate
from was danbury federal prison
where he spent time
for impersonating a lawyer.
All right, that is
inadmissible and irrelevant.
You're claiming bad faith.
Your whole life is bad faith.
I think a jury should have
a chance to hear that.
- Your honor, this...
- Your motion to dismiss
is denied, Mr. Ackerman, but,
Mr. Ross, I am inclined to agree
that your history is relevant
to this case, which means,
if he wants to bring it up
at trial, I'm not stopping him.
So that's how you're gonna
play it?
- Excuse me?
- You're not gonna give me
your real settlement offer
right now?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Bullshit... I knew there was
a reason that woman
didn't give me an offer before.
Now I know it's because
you wanted me to see that.
Now that you mention it,
I did take the Liberty
of whipping up a little
standard boilerplate.
No admission of guilt,
you settle for pennies
on the dollar, and that's
take it or leave it.
Well, then let me
tell you right now...
We're leaving it.
You're required to present
this to your client.
Well, I'm also required
to give them my legal opinion,
which is that you stand to lose
a lot more than that.
Maybe you missed what
just went on back there.
What went on back there
is the judge ruled in my favor,
and you didn't get
your case dismissed.
He also showed his hand.
Now, how do you think
12 jurors are gonna rule
when it's plain as day
that the guy hearing the case
doesn't even trust you?
♪♪
- Good, you're here.
- Of course we are.
When the managing partner
calls a meeting,
the rest of the partners
show up.
So what'd you want
to talk about?
I wanna talk about bringing on
Pfizer as a client.
Harvey, I'm sure
you already know this...
That would mean dropping
Jim Reynolds.
I think that's the point,
and I think
it's a great idea, Harvey.
Pfizer's ten times the size
of Jim Reynolds,
and Jessica's always
been stubborn about him.
Good, because, in order
to do that, we need to make
Alex Williams a name partner.
- What?
- Who do you think's
bringing Pfizer over here
in the first place?
So then give him a corner
office with a killer view
because I'm not gonna do
something like that
- for someone I barely know.
- Harvey-
- well, I've known him
for 15 years,
- and I'm vouching for him.
- I don't care if you
came out of the womb with him.
You don't just slap
somebody's name on the wall
to get a client.
I'm not just slapping
his name up, Louis.
I'm making a move.
- Harvey...
- Hey, that's enough.
I asked you last night
if you had any problems
with me calling the shots,
and you said you didn't.
Now, are you on board
with this or not?
♪♪
Okay, Harvey, I'm on board.
Ah, there you are.
I need your help.
And you can have it
after I've enjoyed
my ham sandwich in peace.
Nope, sorry, that ham's
gonna have to wait.
Harvey is about to make
some stranger name partner.
What?
Louis, you must've
misunderstood something.
Gretchen, I heard him
clear as a frickin' bell.
He wants one of the guy's
clients, name partnership
is the price, and I think
it's a huge mistake.
- Well, did you tell him that?
- Yes, of course,
but he couldn't hear me.
And I told him last night that
I would back his decisions.
Which means you want me
to find out as much dirt
as I can on the sucker
so you can convince Harvey
not to hire him.
Exactly, so let's move
this little piggy to the market
- and go...
- not gonna happen, Louis.
Gretchen, did you not hear
what I just said?
I heard you.
Have you never heard the saying
"there's more than one way
to skin a cat"?
- You mean "stuff a cat."
- Why would I mean
- "stuff a cat"?
- Because they are
glorious creatures, and only
a barbarian would skin one.
Louis, your brain
is not right.
My point is, if Harvey wants
this man's client,
there has to be another way
to get them.
Holy shit.
You're right.
If I can get Pfizer,
Harvey doesn't even have to bring
this clown to the firm at all.
Strap in, Gretchen, because
we're about to get
elbow-deep into stuffing
the shit out of this cat.
And I'm out.
♪♪
I don't understand.
I mean, I get that
the offer is horrible,
but if the judge is letting
this thing go to trial,
- he must think I have a case.
- You do have a case, Harry.
But the lawyer on the other side
of this thing has made it clear
that he is willing
to pull out all of the stops,
no matter how low.
They already used the photo
of Shannon.
What else do they have?
- Me.
- What are you talking about?
Look, I am a fully-licensed
member of the bar now,
but, before I was,
I... I was practicing law
without a license,
and I got caught.
And you didn't think
I should know that?
I didn't think that
it would be relevant.
It sure as hell
seems relevant.
They are just trying to
prejudice the jury against me...
they're going to be prejudiced
against you... I'd be.
I'm telling you that
I can still win this.
- Still win?
- They're gonna make it seem like
Shannon lied on purpose,
and then I went out
and hired a liar to cover it up.
♪♪
If you want someone else
to handle this,
I...
Completely understand.
The only problem with that is
I went to 15 firms
before I came to you,
and none of them would take
my case because of that photo.
You were my last hope,
Mr. Ross,
and now you're telling me
we're gonna lose.
No, Harry.
I am promising you that I will
not cost you this case.
Good, Donna, you're here.
I'm gonna need someone to draw
up a contract for Alex, and...
Harvey, I don't think
we should drop Jim Reynolds.
- What?
- I understand what
you're doing, but I think that
maybe you're rushing into it.
I'm not rushing, Donna.
I'm being decisive.
Then you need to tell Jessica
before you do it.
Tell Jessica?
I'm doing this to show people
that this is my firm now.
Asking mommy's permission
isn't part of the plan.
Well, is it also
part of the plan
that you signal to the rest
of our long-term clients
that you'll just throw them over
for the next big thing?
Where the hell
is this coming from?
What do you mean
"where is this coming from?"
You made me a partner.
I'm saying my piece.
That's what the meeting
was for.
Well, maybe you didn't notice,
but you and Louis were having
- a private meeting.
- Well, you know what, Donna?
You had the balls to ask
for a seat at the table.
So the next time
you have something to say,
have the balls to say it
at the Goddamn meeting.
- Hey.
How'd it go in court?
Not great.
No, don't tell me the judge
agreed to dismiss the case.
No.
The lawyer on the other side
somehow got a copy
of my fake diploma.
Mike, that's bullshit.
Your history has nothing
to do with this case.
I know that, but he got
the judge on his side,
and he's gonna try and do
the same thing with the jury,
and my own client
barely trusts me.
Okay, what are you gonna do?
I was wondering if you would
take over the case for me.
If that's what you want,
then I would be honored to.
♪♪
Alex, I'm glad you called.
We're still working out
the paperwork...
if you're still working
on the paperwork,
how come I just found out you're
trying to poach my client?
- What?
- Don't bullshit me.
Kevin Bauer told me that PSL
called to set an appointment,
and it sure as hell wasn't
to tell my own client
that I'm going to be
name partner at your firm.
God damn it.
You're telling me you
had nothing to do with this?
That's exactly
what I'm telling you.
Then get your shit together
and either
make this thing happen or not
'cause I went out on a limb
for you once before.
I'm not about to let
the same thing happen again.
♪♪
Did you set a meeting
with Pfizer?
Harvey, you don't understand.
What I understand
is you were on board
with bringing Alex over,
and then you tried
to poach his client.
It's not like that.
I knew what you really wanted
was Pfizer, so I tried
- to make it happen.
- No, Louis, what I really
wanted was to bring over
my friend who I've known
- for the last 15 years.
- Yeah?
Well, what about what
this friend thinks?
We already had
that discussion,
and then you went
behind my back.
Maybe because it was stupid
of you to offer your friend
- name partner in the first place.
- Excuse me?
What kind of genius negotiator
gives away the house
- from the start?
- Louis-
- no, you want Pfizer?
You go get Pfizer.
But don't you bring in
some Johnny-come-lately
and water down the name
- of this firm.
- You don't give a shit about
watering down this firm.
You're scared of watering down
your place in it.
I'm not afraid
of a third-rate lawyer.
Bullshit, you're afraid
and you're jealous.
And this entire firm knows it.
Now there's no need
to be jealous
because he's not coming here.
- Yes, he is.
- Well, then why don't you
try reading the by-laws?
Because in order to make
someone name partner,
you need my vote or Jessica's
vote, and if you think
she is going to ditch her
oldest client to bring in
someone she doesn't even know,
you're out of your Goddamn mind.
♪♪
- Harvey, do you have a minute?
- That's about all I have.
Okay, I was wondering
if it would be okay
if I took over
Mike's pro bono case.
- What?
- Something came up.
He asked me if I could do it.
I... i wanted to get
- your permission first.
- No.
- Why not?
- Because I made a deal
with Mike, not you.
Now, you wanna tell me
what's really going on here?
Because Mike's not giving away
his first case
unless he's in a coma.
The lawyer on the other side
outed Mike as a fraud.
- Meaning?
- He brought out Mike's
Harvard diploma,
and he prejudiced the judge.
So Mike thinks if he hands
the case over to you,
he takes that weapon
out of their hands.
- Yes.
- Well, now it's a definite no.
Why does that make it
a definite no?
- Because I said so.
- Harvey, can you at least
- talk to Mike?
- No, I can't.
- Why not?
- Because I got a plane
to catch.
♪♪
You wanted to talk to me?
What gave it away?
The nine texts
- or the 16 messages?
- I was on a plane.
Yeah, well, I'm in your old
office wondering why you even
gave it to me if you're not
gonna let me make
simple personnel decisions.
Mike, if you let this asshole
bully you, you're gonna be
backing down
for the rest of your life.
I'm not backing down.
I am buying time
so that I can stop this bullshit
from ever happening again.
You don't need time.
I have a way.
Stop apologizing
and start intimidating.
Well, that's a hell
of a slogan, Harvey,
but what does it actually mean?
It means you go out,
you find a reporter,
and you take control
of the narrative.
Instead of a lying fraud,
you're a hero
fighting for redemption.
I don't have time to change
my image.
Look, if I lose this case,
the only article that's gonna
get written is that I never
should have been able to
practice law in the first place.
Yeah, well, if you can't
figure out a way to win
without Rachel's help,
then maybe I shouldn't have
brought you back
in the first place
because I've had about enough
of having every employee
I have question
every decision I make.
♪♪
I thought we were gonna meet
at the restaurant.
I got down here early.
Manhattan doesn't have
views like this.
Thanks for making the time
to see me, Jessica.
I will always make time
to see you, Harvey.
Especially after you've flown
all the way out here
- to put the screws to me.
- Louis called you, didn't he?
About an hour
after your plane took off.
Then you've already heard
his side of the story...
and I don't need
to hear yours.
- Jessica...
- Harvey, I understand
wanting to make a statement,
but, you rush into this,
the only statement you're making
is that you're not ready.
I can't believe this.
My first act as managing
partner, and you're cutting
my legs out from under me.
I'm not cutting anything out.
I'm trying to help you.
You can't give out name partner
like it's Halloween candy.
That doesn't sound like help.
That sounds like I'm a child...
- then to figure out...
- Harvey, you do this, what's gonna happen
the next time you wanna
bring someone over?
I'll tell you what happens...
You're going to get rolled
because you haven't
thought this through.
You know what I think?
I think this has nothing
to do with my decision.
You're pissed I'm dumping
your client for a better one.
No, Harvey, that's something
you'd be pissed about because
you've never been able
to look at the big picture.
Well, how's this
for big picture?
- I think you want it both ways.
- And what the hell is that
- supposed to mean?
- It means you want to live here
and keep your name on my wall
because you're not ready
to let go of my firm.
Well, if that's how you really
feel, then take my name
off your Goddamn wall,
and then you can do
whatever the hell you want.
♪♪
Hey, I hope you don't think
I forgot about our dinner.
Yeah, I don't, but I'm afraid
I have to reschedule.
Sure, any time is good for me.
Thanks for being
understanding.
And, for the record,
I was really looking forward
to getting to know
each other better.
So was I.
But the truth is I guess
I'm glad we're rescheduling.
I didn't want to end up
focusing on myself
like I did the last time.
Why, is something going on?
It's not a big deal.
Harvey, you can talk
to me about it.
- But you said before...
- I know what I said before,
- but this is different.
- How?
Because you heard me,
and you respected my wishes,
which means instead of me
listening to you
as your therapist, you know,
I'll be listening to you
- as your...
- Not therapist.
- Yes.
- Look at that,
even when we cancel, I feel like
I'm getting to know you better.
Me too.
So are you gonna tell me
what's going on?
You know what?
Now that I just talked to you,
I feel like I can
- work it through myself.
- Good.
Good night, Harvey.
♪♪
- Hey.
- You busy?
- You know I am, which means
you wouldn't be here
if it wasn't important.
You're right.
I talked to Harvey.
- You changed his mind?
- No, no.
He told me if I run from this,
I'll be running forever.
Look, I hate to say it,
but he might have a point.
- He does.
- So then why are you here?
'Cause he got me thinking.
The woman I first met over there
said they couldn't let people
like Harry and his wife get away
with lying on their application
because they wouldn't have
- a business anymore.
- Right, but they didn't
- lie on their application.
- No, they didn't.
But a company that
thinks like that...
Might have a policy of trying
to not pay their claims at all.
Exactly.
So if we can prove that that's
the company's real policy,
- we got 'em.
- But, right, Mike, we can
get all the subpoenas
in the world, but they're never
going to hand over
a smoking gun like that.
No, they won't.
But I think you know someone
who can get it for us
without issuing
any subpoena at all.
♪♪
Ms. cromwell, remember me?
Yes, unfortunately.
If you'll excuse me.
We have a job
we'd like to offer you.
- Not interested.
- You haven't even heard
- what it is.
- I don't need to know
what it is... I don't do business
with people I don't trust.
- You're a corporate spy.
- Not anymore...
'cause the last mystery man
she brought me said word
wouldn't get out about
our little arrangement.
Well, it did, so now I'm trying
to make it as a legitimate
headhunter, which pays
about 10% of what I made before,
so, if you'll excuse me,
I'm meeting with
an actual client
in a few minutes.
Ms. cromwell, please.
A mother of three was killed
in a car accident,
and she was 39 years old.
Now her husband can't
support his children because
acumen insurance is trying
to scam him
- out of their claim.
- What am I supposed to do
- about that?
- This can't be the first time
- they've done this.
- And we're betting that
there isn't a major corporation
in this city
- that you don't have access to.
- Please.
- You can help these people.
- I don't give a shit
about helping people.
I give a shit about helping me,
- which is why I want $50,000.
- What?
I just told you...
You cost me millions.
- So if you want my help...
- Okay, never mind.
Mike, I knew this was
a bad idea.
- We'll pay it.
- Mike.
Rachel, if she can
get us something we can use,
it's worth it.
It'll come out
- of the settlement offer.
- Uhuh, I want it up front.
And how do we know that you
won't take the money and say
- that you couldn't find anything?
- You don't,
but, given the fact that
you're still here,
it doesn't look like
you have much of a choice.
♪♪
So how are you, Louis?
Wanna know how I'm doing?
I'll tell you how I'm doing.
I tried focusing on
my professional life
instead of my personal one, and
it's been a Goddamn disaster.
I take it your thoughts
of Tara have been getting
- in the way of work.
- What?
No, I'm over her...
She's yesterday's news.
Your words make me
think otherwise.
Well, how about you listen
to these words:
Harvey's making his friend
name partner.
He's accused me of being
jealous, and I don't know
- what to do.
- Are you jealous?
Of course I'm Goddamn jealous!
Louis, it's natural for you
to feel that way.
You've worked hard to get
where you are,
and a new person threatens
your position in the firm.
That's not...
That's just not it.
The one silver lining
of Jessica leaving
was that I thought that Harvey
would finally turn to me,
not only as his partner,
but as his friend.
That's not happening now
because I'm being replaced.
And you're scared
of losing your friend.
What do I do?
I can't tell you that, Louis,
but I can tell you
it was your behavior
that drove Tara away,
and, if you keep
letting your emotions
dictate your behavior,
you won't need to worry
about being replaced.
You'll drive Harvey away
all by yourself.
♪♪
I'm not sure I've ever
seen you here this late.
New office, new hours.
I guess so.
Katrina, whatever's
on your mind,
I recommend you just say it.
As you know, I'm on track
to be a senior partner here.
In fact, it's one of the main
reasons I agreed to come back.
I know.
I'm not saying Donna
doesn't deserve a promotion...
I know what she does
as much as anyone.
I'm just saying making partner
means something,
and I'm concerned that being one
here won't mean what it used to.
♪♪
What would you have me do?
I don't know. I just thought,
if I was thinking it,
it occurred to me
that others might be too,
and... I thought
you should know that.
Katrina, being a partner here
will mean as much
as it always has.
I'll make sure of it.
♪♪
I hope you came here
to tell me you got everything
- straightened out.
- I came here to tell you
- that the deal's off the table.
- What?
Name partner means something,
and I can't just give it away
to make a statement.
I never should've offered it
- to you in the first place.
- God damn it, Harvey.
This is the second time
you've done this.
And I'm sorry, Alex, but this
is a take it or leave it offer.
You can let me know
in the morning.
I'll take it.
I wasn't really gonna make
name partner in a year.
Maybe not ever.
I know.
How?
Because if they were really
gonna do it in a year,
you would've leveraged them
to move it up the second
- I left your office.
- So why didn't you
- call me on that before?
- I don't know.
Maybe it's because I felt
like I owe you,
or maybe because I wanted
to prove to the world
that I'm not Jessica.
Or maybe it's because
I wanted to work together.
I'll see you Monday, Harvey.
See you Monday.
♪♪
- I'll get that.
- Keep your money, Mr. Ross.
You're gonna need it.
I think, after you see this,
you're gonna wanna save
every nickel you have.
Thanks.
Now, correct me if I'm wrong,
but I believe that's a memo
between acumen senior management
and their sales force
outlining their policy
of doing whatever it takes
to avoid paying claims.
Well, this thing
can be interpreted
a dozen different ways.
It doesn't prove a thing.
But it proves that
we're not just talking
about my client anymore.
You're looking at
a class action.
And if there's one thing that
a jury hates more
than a fake lawyer,
it's an insurance company
that rips off widowers
and children.
- What do you want?
- 50 million.
- With an admission of guilt.
- No way, they won't
- go for admission.
- Okay, then here's what you're
gonna do instead.
A reporter's gonna call you.
And when he does, you're gonna
tell him the story of how you
thought you were gonna
wipe the floor
with this fraudulent attorney,
but instead you ended up praying
that you never
go up against him again.
You knew they wouldn't
go for admission.
- You set me up.
- Well, now that you mention it,
I did.
And that's take it or leave it.
Then I guess I'll take it.
And leave out the part where you
traded admission of guilt
- in exchange for self-promotion.
- Don't you dare say that to me.
I'm not doing this for myself.
I'm doing it so that
pieces of shit like you
never try to use my history
against my clients again.
♪♪
Louis, before you
say anything...
Harvey,
before you say anything,
I just wanna say I'm sorry.
You were right.
I was jealous
of Alex coming over here,
but not because I'm afraid
- of another lawyer.
- I don't understand.
See, Harvey, I know you like
to make fun of me,
and... I know I might not
mean as much to you
as you mean to me,
but you're my friend,
and, because I don't have many,
that friendship
is important to me.
You don't have to worry
about that, Louis.
But I don't want my behavior
to drive a wedge between us,
which means... I accept
Alex as name partner.
- About that, Louis...
- I mean, it's just gonna
have to be like when lebron
James joined the Miami heat
when he and D-Wade
worked it out with Chris Bosh.
I thought you didn't know
anything about sports.
I stayed up all night
trying to come up with
the right analogy.
And, if I'm not mistaken,
they went on to win
back-to-back super bowls.
That they did.
Louis, for what it's worth,
Alex is still coming,
- but not as name partner.
- Really?
Yeah, you were right.
We can't water down
the firm like that.
♪♪
You've never knocked before.
And you've never had
a door before.
I know, and it's
a good thing I do because...
you can't be a partner, Donna.
What?
You can't do that.
I have to.
I made a mistake.
Bullshit, I...
I paid you $500,000.
You haven't signed
the partnership agreement yet,
so I can refund your money,
and...
I don't want a refund.
I want what we agreed to.
I can't do that.
You are not a lawyer, and
being partner at a law firm...
It means something,
inside the firm and out,
which is why I wrote up
a new release for you.
This says
"director of personnel."
Everybody knows
you're great with people,
so it'll play out there,
but, between you and me...
No, Harvey, I didn't ask
for partner just so I could
keep being a superwoman
behind closed doors,
but, to the rest of the world,
be a glorified office manager.
Partner is off the table,
Donna.
Then keep my buy-in
and make me COO.
I can't do that...
That's the same as a partner.
No, it isn't.
Skadden and Zane
and Bratton gould all have COOs,
and none of them are lawyers.
How do you know that?
'Cause I never thought
you'd make me partner
in the first place.
- Okay, it's a deal.
- And I keep my vote.
- Donna...
- Within these walls,
I have a seat at the table.
Take it or leave it.
I'll take it.
♪♪
Thanks, Harvey.
You're gonna make
a hell of a COO.
♪♪
And?
How'd it go?
Out of the park.
Got everything we wanted.
What do you say we go out
and celebrate tonight?
Well, we're celebrating,
but we're not going out.
What do you mean?
A reporter from "The Times" is
gonna be here in five minutes.
- Okay.
- We are doing an interview.
The redemption
of a fraudulent lawyer.
Well, that is the best news
I've heard since finding out
- you got into the bar.
- Thank you.
But I think you should
do it without me.
Rachel, I... I couldn't have
done any of this without you.
And that may be true,
but this is your story,
and you should be
the one to tell it.
♪♪
Go... I'll see you at home.
- Mike?
- Yeah.
- David gruen.
- Good to meet you.
Where do you want to do this?
I was thinking maybe
your new office.
Uh, yeah, we could
end up there.
But I was thinking maybe we'd
start out where I started out.
- Where's that?
- In the bullpen.
♪♪
What is it now, Harvey?
You want to put the Janitor
in charge of bankruptcy?
Or the guard downstairs could be
head of litigation.
- Are you finished?
- Depends on what you say next.
I'm sorry I said
those things about you,
and I want you to know
I didn't mean any of them.
I'm sorry too, Harvey.
Jessica, you don't
need to apologize.
Yes, I do.
You were just tearing
the statue down.
Just like you saw me do
all those years ago,
and I didn't like it
because the statue was me.
Well, if it's the same to you,
I'd like the statue to stay.
Sounds good to me.
- There's one more thing.
- There always is.
I'm still bringing Alex over,
only not as a name partner,
but Pfizer's still insisting
we drop Jim Reynolds.
And you want to know
if I'm okay with it?
No, I'm letting him go.
I'm just calling you to tell you
before I tell him,
like I should've done
in the first place.
I was wrong when I said
you weren't ready, Harvey.
No, you weren't,
but you are now.
Good night, closer.
Good night, Jessica.
And take your feet
off my desk.
Not a chance.
♪♪ Upbeat music...
Synchronized by srjanapala
♪♪
www.tvsubtitles.net