Previously on "Suits"...
Rachel,
it's Professor Dunbar.
I was wondering if you'd
be interested in helping me
with the Innocence Project.
You want me to help you get
an innocent man off death row?
What do you want, Harvey?
Help me protect Mike Ross.
He's in there
with a guy I put away,
and the guy is no joke.
What am I supposed to do?
You're supposed to move
the guy to another prison.
You want me one-on-one?
You got it.
I'm gonna use this,
and they're gonna hold you.
- No!
- What's going on here?
[tense music]
Why'd you come back
with a guard?
I didn't do it
to get you to forgive me.
I never should have let him
in here in the first place.
The time you served
while awaiting trial
was never factored
into your sentence.
You're eligible for
parole in six weeks.
You think I don't know
this is your protector's idea
to get me off your back?
Nah, Frank.
Harvey's idea was for me
to tell these guys
that you're an informant.
I figured out a way
to get Mike out early.
What's the catch?
He has to inform
on his roommate.
Mike gets him to turn,
he's free.
When do you need an answer by?
Yesterday.
And the answer needs to be yes.
♪ ♪
Harvey, wait a second.
Where are you going?
Where do you think I'm going?
I'm gonna see Mike.
And I know what
you're going to say,
but Mike went to prison
so we wouldn't have to,
and now he's in danger
from a guy I put away.
So you'll forgive me if
I don't stand around and wait
for you to drop the hammer.
You think I like the idea
of him rotting in that place?
But if you want
this thing to work,
you can't go running up there
in the middle of the night.
You heard Cahill.
He needs an answer yesterday.
What he needs is results.
And if Mike's lawyer
pulls him out of his cell
in the middle of the night,
then his roommate
is going to sense
there's something wrong
before this thing
even gets started.
Fine, but I'm going up there
first thing in the morning,
and nothing you say
is going to stop me.
♪ ♪
Can't sleep?
Not really.
Well, as long as you're up,
might want to think about
putting up some
pictures of your own.
That way, you won't have
to keep staring at mine.
How old are they?
Maddy is seven.
Nate just turned five.
They look really sweet.
Yeah...they're great.
How often do you
get to see 'em?
- I don't.
- What do you mean you don't?
Bad divorce or something?
Nah, nah,
nothing like that.
We've been married
for ten years.
I just--I just don't
let 'em come here.
What?
Why not?
They shouldn't see
their father as a criminal.
Kevin, come on, man.
I know it's hard on them.
It tears me up every
single day that I'm here.
But they're kids.
They're resilient.
Yeah, I wouldn't be so sure.
Well, Mike,
you don't have kids.
So you don't know.
No.
I don't.
But I do know what it's like
to be a kid missing his dad.
Please don't tell me your
old man abandoned the family.
Both of my parents died
in a car accident when I was 11.
Hit by a drunk driver.
Jesus, that's...
I'm sorry, Mike.
[somber music]
Yeah, it was a long time ago.
Kevin, I understand
the instinct to protect
your children, but what are
you protecting them from?
What do you mean?
I mean we've been
roommates for a while now.
Don't you think it's time you
told me what you're in here for?
[door buzzes]
Hey, Ross.
Your lawyer's here.
- Now?
- I'm just the messenger.
You want out of this box or not?
♪ ♪
Mr. Bailey, my name
is Rachel Zane.
I am a law student at Columbia,
and I'm here to talk
to you about your case.
Student?
Yes, we work alongside
the Innocence Project
to determine if you have
the criteria for an appeal.
Do you know how long
I've been sittin' on death row?
12 years.
I read your file.
And for the last ten of 'em,
I've been writing letters
and begging any lawyer
to listen to my story.
And they finally get around
to getting back to me,
and they don't even
have the courtesy
of sendin' me a real lawyer?
Mr. Bailey, trust me,
I will fight for you.
You're a student.
You can't do shit for me.
Well, you know what?
You killed two people.
In cold blood.
You know it, and I know it,
and that's why you're in there,
so thank you
for making the decision
to not take your case
an easy one.
You don't know me.
All you know is what you
read in some damn file.
I didn't kill anyone.
I've been saying it for 12 years
and I can prove it.
You're right.
I don't know you.
And you don't know me either.
So do you want to take
a chance on each other or not?
I need help, Ms. Zane.
♪ ♪
So let me help you.
[door opens]
Harvey, what are
you doing here?
There's something I need
to talk to you about.
Sit down.
What is it?
I just got a visit
from Sean Cahill.
About Gallo?
I thought you said
he can't get him transferred.
He can't, but it turns out
there's a way
he can get you out.
What do you mean "out"?
I mean out, as in
you walk out that front door
and you never look back.
- What's the catch?
- Mike--
Harvey, you're not here
telling me that I can get out
with that look on your face
if there isn't something else.
He needs you to inform
on your cellmate.
What?
If whatever you get
leads to a conviction
on his father-in-law,
he'll commute your sentence
and you get to walk.
[dramatic music]
- What'd the guy do?
- Who cares what he did?
I care,
because if it was so bad,
why didn't Kevin turn on him
in the first place?
Mike, what does it matter?
He can get you out.
This is my only
friend in here.
I'm not gonna betray him.
Friend?
Listen to me, God damn it.
There's someone in here
trying to kill you
and I'm giving you a way out.
I'm taking care of Gallo.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means that I did
what you told me to do.
I threatened to tell people
that he was an informant,
but what I also did was found
out a way to get him parole.
Parole?
Are you crazy?
He's not gonna get parole.
Who's gonna say he deserves it?
You know what, Harvey?
Instead of coming here
and telling me
to betray my cellmate because
Gallo will never get parole,
maybe you should be helping
me get it for him.
I'm never helping that
piece of shit do anything,
and this isn't about Gallo
and you know it.
No, it's about you telling me
to turn on the one guy in here
that I trust based on
some plan that Cahill has
that we don't even
know will work.
No, Mike.
It's about giving you
a chance to get your life back
while it still looks the same.
Now, are you going
to take it or not?
♪ ♪
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 6x04 ♪
Turn
Original Air Date on August 3, 2016
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Son of a bitch, it's
the prune juice all over again.
What the?
Hey, douche stick.
Are you responsible
for my mugs being here?
I didn't--I don't--we didn't
have anything else to use.
I don't give a shit!
Take those things
and put 'em back where--
Well, if it isn't Louis Shit.
What's happening, boss?
You bastard.
You took my mugs,
and you didn't even have
the balls to do it yourself.
I have no idea what
you're talking about,
but if something
of yours is in here,
it had nothing to do with me.
Really?
Why don't you ask
the stuttering ass clown?
We needed them for our...
[whispering]
Urine tests.
What'd you say?
You peed on my catch phrase?
I don't know what's funnier--
you got a catch phrase
or that we peed on it.
I want those mugs sterilized
and I want 'em destroyed.
They're your mugs,
you do what you want,
but I'm not touching 'em
with a ten-foot pole.
You know how much
asparagus Luterman eats?
[chuckling]
Later, Chief.
[rock music]
♪ ♪
How'd it go this morning?
I was petrified.
Death row.
How could you not be?
It's not just that.
When I got there, it hit me
that if I do this, I have
a man's life in my hands.
Rachel, you can handle it.
I know I can.
Then why do I get the feeling
that something is bothering you?
Because when I got
back from there,
I was so angry about what
happened to that poor man
that I sat down, I started
working on this case, and I--
I haven't moved since.
I don't understand.
Why is that bad?
Because it's the first time
since Mike left that I haven't
thought about him every second.
[poignant music]
Listen to me.
That's a good thing.
It doesn't feel
like a good thing.
Rachel, you can't live
your life on pins and needles.
It's not healthy for you.
It's not healthy for Mike.
It's not healthy for anyone.
And forgetting about him
is healthy?
Isn't that why
you took this case?
To give yourself
something to focus on?
Yes, but I just--
Then don't fight it.
If working to free
an innocent man helps you
to forget about Mike
for a while,
he would be the first person
to tell you to do it.
And trust me,
if you really
lose yourself in this,
I have a feeling it's gonna seem
like a lot less than two years
before he gets out.
♪ ♪
Where's Harvey?
Harvey's not here.
Well, get his ass in here
because he made some
goddamn side deal
with those traders
and I want them out.
Louis, I am telling you,
now is not the time.
And I am telling you
that I cannot look at
their smug, stupid faces
for one more day.
Maybe you don't
have to look at them.
What are you talking about?
Louis, did I ever tell you
about my first apartment
in the city?
No.
I was sharing a 400
square-foot studio
and it was a disaster
until we finally decided
that we had to separate
our spaces for privacy.
Well, this isn't
"The Brady Bunch," Donna.
We can't put a masking tape line
down the center of the office.
I'm not talking about
masking tape, Louis.
I am talking about
hiring an architect
to reconfigure the offices.
[laughing]
You're right!
We can even do a remodel, which
is what I've been wanting to do
for the last five years.
And the best part is,
you don't have to deal with
those asshole traders
ever again.
Donna, you're a genius.
I know.
Get me the names of
six architects before lunch.
Louis, you have
your own secretary.
Thanks for nothing.
[upbeat music]
Why do I even?
Nice of you to show up.
Been peeling these
potatoes by myself.
Sorry, I...got caught up.
Speaking of which,
how'd it go with your lawyer?
You gettin' out of here?
What?
I'm just kidding.
So what's going on?
Nothing.
It's not important.
Your lawyer shows up
without you knowing about it
and it's not important?
Come on, do I look like
I was born yesterday?
I just said
it is not important.
And I'm sorry
I left you hanging,
but you wouldn't even
have this job without me.
I wouldn't even need this job
if it weren't for you.
So what's your problem?
I'm sorry, Kevin, I'm...
[tense music]
I'm just not having a good day.
Hey, it's okay.
Don't sweat it.
All right?
I mean, it's none of
my business anyway.
♪ ♪
No, actually,
it is your business.
He came here to tell me that he
tried to get Gallo transferred,
but...it's not gonna happen.
Well, as long as
we stick together,
we can deal with Gallo
anyway, right?
Yeah, that's--
that's what I told Harvey.
Right.
Next time you talk to him,
tell him I said
thanks for trying.
♪ ♪
How'd it go?
He said he had
to think about it.
What?
Why?
'Cause he's an idiot,
that's why.
So what're you gonna do?
I'm gonna figure out
how to buy us some time.
Well, you better do it fast
because Cahill's in your office
and he wants an answer.
Sean.
What'd he say?
Said he wants to see
the details in writing.
I'm not in the mood, Harvey.
And I'm not messing around.
Please tell me
you're kidding me.
Oh, come on, this is bullshit.
You know my word is good.
Yeah, and I told him that,
and then find out
commuting his sentence
really means cutting it in half.
He's not risking anything.
No one's gonna find out.
I'm sure that's exactly
what Frank Gallo thought.
So either put it in writing
or we don't have a deal.
He didn't go for it, did he?
What are you talking about?
Mike being at risk
has nothing to do
with putting anything
in writing.
And you told me
he wouldn't go for it,
so Harvey...
tell me the truth.
All right, he said no.
But Sean, I'm telling you,
he'll come around.
He just needs a couple of days.
Do you know how many
strings I pulled
to put this thing in motion?
if this case
wasn't huge for you.
So instead of yelling at me
for saying that it's gonna
take a couple days,
why don't you just
give me a couple of days?
Okay, Harvey.
The deal's still on the table.
But if I find a way to move
forward without his help,
there is no deal and
he does the whole two years.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[rousing music]
Jessica.
Harvey.
What's going on with Mike?
I gave him Cahill's offer.
And he's thinking about it?
I'm working on it.
Well, in the meantime,
while you were out,
I got a call from Nathan Byrnes.
He thinks someone's trying
to take over his company.
Why the hell would
he think of that?
Because word on the street is,
someone's selling off
a block of his stock.
That doesn't make sense.
We bought Sutter's shares
from him.
Those goddamn traders.
No way.
They wouldn't do that
without telling me.
They bought it in good faith.
Well, they're dumping it
in bad faith.
- I'll take care of it--
- No.
You have your hands
full with Mike.
I can handle this.
Jessica, it was my idea
to involve them.
I should be the one
to take care of it.
I don't care whose idea
it was, Harvey.
You take care of Mike.
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
Hello?
You have a call from
Danbury Federal Prison.
Do you accept the charges?
Yes, of course.
[line clicks]
Mike, is everything okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, everything's fine.
I was just thinking about you.
I was thinking about you too.
You were?
Yes, in fact,
I was just in the middle
of a heated discussion with you
about the best way to handle
a death row appeal.
I don't understand.
I took on
an Innocence Project case,
just to have something to take
my mind off of our troubles.
But I...I didn't want to
take my mind off of you.
So I figured I would just
imagine we were working
on it together.
I don't know what to say.
Say you're in.
I mean, that depends on
what strategy we landed on.
Mike, seriously,
is there something wrong?
No, I just wanted to make
sure you were doing okay.
And that...
that we were still good.
Now that I have something to
take my mind off our situation
and connect me to you
at the same time,
yeah, we're better than good.
[solemn music]
All right, can you do me a
favor and transfer me to Donna?
Of course.
Can I ask why?
I only get one phone call,
and I'm pretty sure
she had something to do
with the idea of you
imagining us working together,
so I just want to thank her.
Okay.
I love you.
I love you too.
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Donna, I have Mike
on the phone.
Put him through.
Hello?
Donna.
If Harvey's there,
do me a favor--
keep your voice down,
and don't tell him it's me.
Mike, what's going on?
I'm not taking the deal,
Donna.
Are you crazy?
It's not that simple.
What's not simple about it?
Harvey said that if you--
I don't care
what Harvey said.
Because what he didn't say
is that if I do what he wants
and someone finds out,
then I may never get back
to Rachel at all.
Harvey would never
let them find out--
Donna, look, I called you
so that I didn't want to have
this argument with him.
Now, I don't have much time.
Are you gonna do this for me
or not?
I'll tell him.
Then I also need you to
tell him something else for me.
If he comes here to try
to change my mind,
I'm not gonna see him.
[dial tone droning]
♪ ♪
You mind telling me
who the hell said
you can dump Nathan Byrnes'
stock without talking to us?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Who's Nathan Byrnes?
CEO of Exodyne.
Oh, that Nathan Byrnes.
In that case, I said
I could sell that stock
because I own it.
Just like I own this one
and this one and this one.
Hey, look at that,
my Neubacher Capital position's
going through the roof.
That's not the deal you made
with Harvey and you know it.
Welcome to the big,
bad world of Wall Street.
Now, do you want something
or can I get back to work?
Oh, I want something.
You're going to unwind that sale
and buy those shares back.
At a premium?
Not gonna happen.
I'm your landlord.
And the fact
you had to lease to me
means you don't have
much of an operation.
You listen to me,
you little pissant.
You don't know who
you're messing with.
Then why don't I find out?
Over dinner?
You've got to be kidding me.
You want me to have
dinner with you
in exchange for
backing off that trade?
I think of it as you get
to have dinner with me
and I choose to back off that
trade 'cause I am a standup guy.
Well, let me let you in on
a little something there, Stu.
I don't share dinner staring
down the barrel of a shotgun.
So why don't you unwind that
trade and then ask me out?
And then we'll see
if you're as charming
as you like to think you are.
You know what?
I am charming.
But I'm not an idiot.
And I'm not unwinding my trade
without getting
something in return.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Harvey, I need to talk
to you about something
and you're not going to like it.
About what?
That was Mike
on the phone before.
Why didn't you get me?
He's not taking the deal,
Harvey.
The hell he isn't.
[tense music]
Where are you going?
To that prison.
Harvey, the reason
he called me and not you
is because he knew you wouldn't
take no for an answer.
And I'm not going to.
Which is why he said
if you show up there,
he's not gonna leave his cell.
Then get me Rachel.
No, no, Harvey,
you cannot tell her.
Like hell I can't.
She's the only one
who can convince him.
If you tell her that
Mike's not taking a deal
that can get him out,
it'll tear her apart.
And if I don't tell her,
he's gonna be in there
for two more years.
Is that what she wants?
That's between them.
That's why I want to tell her.
She'll make it between them.
- Harvey.
- [scoffs]
God damn it, he plays checkers
with this guy
and thinks he owes him his life.
No, that's not fair
and you know it,
because Mike's loyalty is
the reason you're not in prison.
♪ ♪
That's what's killing me,
Donna, don't you understand?
He's in there instead of me
with a guy I put away,
and I can't just sit here
doing nothing
when he has a chance to get out.
Which is why you have to
think of something else.
Because if you tell
Rachel about this,
the life that's waiting
for Mike when he gets out...
it isn't going to be there.
♪ ♪
Harvey. I'm surprised
to see you here so soon.
I didn't think
you'd turn him this fast.
I need more time.
I don't think you understand.
I'm being pressured to move
to another investigation.
You've got 24 hours to change
his mind or this thing is done.
Then I need you to
do something for me.
I am doing something for you.
I'm getting Mike out of prison.
Well, you need to do
something else for me
or that's never gonna happen.
What are you talking about?
I need you to get
into a room with him
because he won't listen
to what I have to say.
What exactly do you
want me to tell him
that you haven't already?
Sean, Mike's a bleeding heart.
You need to make the case
directly to him.
He needs to see the victims of
whatever the hell this guy did.
That's a swell idea, Harvey,
but if I go into that prison
and someone sees me,
not only are we dead
in the water,
but Mike's life
isn't worth shit.
You think I don't know that?
What the hell do you think
I'm doing here?
What are you talking about?
I have a plan.
But you're not gonna like it.
Why not?
Because I need you
to pull another string,
and I need you to do it
before Frank Gallo tries
something else with Mike.
[dramatic music]
[crowd chatter]
All right, fake lawyer.
Let's see what you got.
You're gonna let me
look into it for you?
Look into it?
Shit.
You're gonna get me out of here
like you promised.
I never promised.
I said there was
an excellent chance
that you could get--
Six weeks, brother.
I'll be counting the days.
I'll file the motion
first thing in the morning.
There you go.
That's what I'm talking about.
And if I find out you're
screwing me on any level,
you better hole up in some
dark corner of this prison,
pray to God
I don't find your ass.
♪ ♪
What was that all about?
Looks like he took me up
on my offer after all.
♪ ♪
God damn it, Gretchen,
where the hell is she?
Where the hell is who?
That architect
you were supposed to call.
She's not supposed to be here
for another half hour.
And if I want
someone's business,
I show up a half-hour
early at the latest.
And what exactly are
you looking to have me do
about your little conundrum?
I want you to give her a call
and tell her if she doesn't have
the goddamn common courtesy
to show up early, then she might
as well not show up at all.
- Mr. Litt.
- I--
Y-yes?
I'm Tara Messer.
I'm here to discuss
your remodel needs.
My needs?
Well, I'm sorry, Ms.
Was-Going-to-Be-Our-Architect.
We no longer need your service.
Gretchen, calm down.
You are overreacting
like a crazy woman.
You're hired.
I am?
Oh, yeah.
You're right for the job.
I can feel it.
Oh, you can feel something,
all right.
Then why don't we start
with what you're looking for
in the space?
Oh.
Space.
Right, the space.
Exactly.
What I'm looking for are clear
yet unobtrusive boundaries
between our offices
and the tenants'.
But it needs to be
elegant and organic
or we might as well
not do it at all.
I understand.
Like the perfect aria
leading seamlessly
to its inevitable cadenza.
You're an opera lover?
Second only to the ballet.
Then I suggest we start
with a marriage.
I mean a tour.
♪ ♪
Excuse me, Professor Dunbar.
Do you have a moment?
This is the faculty lounge,
Ms. Zane.
You're not supposed
to be in here.
I understand that,
and I'm sorry.
It's just this is important
and you weren't in your office.
What can I do for you?
I met with
Leonard Bailey yesterday.
He's the inmate on death--
I know who he is.
Is there a problem?
Yes, there is.
He's rotting on death row for
a crime that he didn't commit.
So you met with him
for ten minutes
and you're ready to release him?
No, what I'm saying is--
You're a second-year
law student, Rachel.
I asked you to be a part of this
because you're one of
my brightest students,
but I also asked
you in particular
because I didn't think
you'd be so naive.
Excuse me?
Your job wasn't to
talk to Mr. Bailey once
and, after being moved
by his tale of woe,
tell me to jump him
to the top of the pile.
It was to assess his case
and present evidence.
And that's exactly
what I'm doing here.
I just left two boxes
of textbook prosecutorial
misconduct with your secretary.
You found all of that
since yesterday?
Yes, because while I may only
be a second-year law student,
I have been
a practicing paralegal
for the past eight years.
Looks like I have
some reading to do.
[tense music]
I'm sorry for
interrupting your day.
Good afternoon, Ms. Zane.
Good afternoon, Professor.
♪ ♪
And then we use
the glass motif
you already have
to partition their space
from yours starting at
that wall over there.
And no one ever knows
they're two separate entities.
And if we use
the frosted glass,
you'll never even have to
lay eyes on them.
Well, there's
just one more thing.
You want to know
if I can design another
bullpen area for your side.
After all, it's the heart
and soul of the space.
You get that?
It's my job to get that.
I don't understand.
To me, architecture isn't
just about design.
It's--it's about connecting with
my clients on an intimate level.
Well, you're very good at it.
And you know, it's too bad you
already sublet to someone else.
We're looking to
expand ourselves.
This space would
have been perfect.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
In fact, it's so perfect,
I would have made you
an offer on the spot.
Anyway, I'll have some plans
drawn up as soon as I can.
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
We need to get rid
of those traders.
Excuse me?
I don't care what kind of deal
you and Harvey cut with them.
We need to get rid of them
and we need to do it now.
Well, Louis,
I'm not going to do that
because whoever
we replace them with,
this conversation is just
going to happen again.
Because we both know
that you're out of your mind.
It's not gonna happen again
because in this particular case,
I am not out of my mind.
Why do you want me to do this?
Because I'm in love
with an architect.
Let me get this straight.
You want me to further
antagonize people
that I'm already fighting with
because you don't have the balls
to ask a woman out on a date?
That's one way
of looking at it.
No, there's another way.
The answer is no.
Okay, fine.
I'll just stick to
the original plan
of having her completely
redesign our space,
and I'll just make sure
it takes long enough
for her to fall madly
in love with me,
and it shouldn't take more
than two or three years.
Louis, I want you to
look at me when I say this.
If you hire this woman
to do anything relating
to this firm's space,
I will personally throw you
off the roof this building.
Is that clear?
So you'll think about it?
Get out.
[scoffs]
Yo.
Ahnold.
Come on.
Let's see what you got.
[grunts]
I didn't know you played.
Played?
Shit.
I set the P.S. 092
single-game scoring record.
P.S. 092 is an elementary
school, my friend.
Yeah, sixth grade.
I dominated.
Heard you had to file that
motion for Gallo's parole.
- I did.
- Already?
It was an 18-page
sentencing amendment.
I could do that in my sleep.
I should get you to
do some work for me.
Why?
You need some?
No, but if I did,
I'd probably get myself a lawyer
who didn't sleep in a prison.
[chuckles]
[clears throat]
You all right?
I don't--I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
- [coughs]
- What is it, your stomach?
Oh, my God,
something's not right.
Take a deep breath.
Put your head down.
Oh, God, I can't--
that's not gonna do anything.
I think...
[echoing]
Oh, my God, I think somebody
did something to me.
Hey, can I get
some help over here?
Guard!
Mike, talk to me.
It's Gallo.
Yeah, he must've put
something in my--
Somebody do something!
Guard!
Call Harvey.
Mike.
Mike!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
Where is he?
If I knew who you were
talking about, maybe I could--
Mike Ross.
I need to see him right now.
And who are you?
Harvey Specter.
I'm his attorney.
♪ ♪
Mr. Ross is in the infirmary,
but you can't see him in there.
Then get me the warden.
♪ ♪
I don't appreciate being
pushed around, Mr. Specter.
I don't care.
I want everyone to know
what happened here today.
They saw what happened.
Yeah, there's a difference
between seeing and knowing.
You Kevin Miller?
Who are you?
Harvey Specter.
I'm Mike Ross's lawyer.
Look, I already
told the warden
I didn't see anyone
touch his food.
Did you see Frank Gallo
with him?
♪ ♪
Did you or didn't you?
Are you trying to
get me killed, man?
Did he touch his food or not?
Yeah, he did,
last night at dinner.
But Mike offered
to get Gallo parole
and Gallo took him up on it,
so why would he poison him?
Because he didn't really
take Mike up on that offer.
He just did it
to get close to him.
Or he did it to give Mike
a taste of what happens
if he doesn't come through.
Either way, you stay the hell
away from that son of a bitch.
All right, that's enough.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
Hey, counselor!
I heard your boy had a little
tummy ache out in the yard.
You piece of shit.
You goddamn poisoned him.
Guards, get him out of here.
I didn't do shit.
Why don't you come over here
and say that to my face?
- You think I won't?
- God damn it.
I said get him back to his cell!
Hey, this wasn't part
of the deal.
We talked about you
seeing his roommate,
not rushing Frank Gallo.
Yeah, well, my guy's lying
unconscious in the infirmary.
So sue me.
♪ ♪
How did you know Gallo
would take the bait?
Because he's an animal, and
animals always take the bait.
Well, I'll give you credit for
knowing how it would go down.
I don't need credit.
I need to know
where Mike Ross is.
Where I was instructed
to put him.
Let me tell you something,
Mr. Specter,
I don't know you.
So in case you're thinking
of trying anything,
that kid has a monitor
on his leg,
and if it goes dark
for even one second,
I'm gonna make sure that you
end up in a cell here with him.
It's not gonna go dark,
and he'll be back here
when I said he would.
Then after that,
I'm gonna make sure
he gets out of here.
For good.
♪ ♪
How you feeling?
What's going on?
Where am I?
You're in the back of my car.
You were drugged.
By Gallo.
By me.
What?
Cahill got the warden
and the prison doctor
to put something in your food.
They're the only ones
who know what's going on.
What the hell are
you talking about?
We needed to change your mind
about taking this deal,
and we couldn't do it
as long as you're in there.
Jesus Christ.
So you drugged me?
We needed a cover for why
you're not in your cell,
and this was
the only way to do it.
Are you insane?
You broke me out of prison?
I didn't break
you out of anywhere.
Cahill sanctioned it.
And if anyone's insane,
it's you, 'cause you're the one
turning down a chance
to get out of that place.
But we don't have time
to talk about that right now.
Cahill's waiting for us.
You got me out to see Cahill?
I said he's waiting.
I didn't say that's where
I'm taking you.
Well, then where the hell
are you taking me?
[window motor whirrs]
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
You think me spending
a couple of hours with Rachel
is gonna change my mind?
If it doesn't, there's
something wrong with you.
So, you gonna yell at me?
Or you gonna take the only
chance you're gonna get
to be alone with
the woman you love
for the next two years?
Please tell me that
you did not tell her
about Cahill's offer.
Oh, I wanted to.
But you have Donna to thank
for the fact that I didn't.
♪ ♪
What am I supposed to tell
Rachel about why I'm here?
If it were me,
I'd tell her the truth.
Now, since you don't
want to do that,
you're lucky I came up
with something else.
♪ ♪
Wait till it hits 30
and then sell.
Well, look who it is.
You change your mind
about my offer?
[laughs softly]
I'm not there just yet.
But I did come to apologize.
I didn't mean to be
so combative before.
You're a proud woman.
I understand. Bygones.
You know, your operation
here is kind of impressive.
Mind if I look at one?
You can take a look at
anything of mine you want.
[chuckles]
Huh.
Now, what does
that line right there mean?
What the hell, that's my
Neubacher Capital position.
Well, it seems to be
falling very quickly.
Is that a good thing?
You did this.
I'm not sure what you mean.
All I did this afternoon
was call my friend
at Jacobson Kearney
and have them issue
a press release
about their client's
merger negotiations.
I mean, how was I supposed
to know that it would make
your Neubacher position
fall through the floor?
You used the information
I gave you yesterday
about my holdings,
that's how.
That's inside information,
and I can prove it.
No, it could have been,
if your attorney hadn't filed
your position with the SEC
ten days earlier than he had to.
I'm not gonna forget this.
Good, because my
operation's been around
a hell of a lot
longer than yours,
and we can be friends
or we can be enemies.
But you mess with me again
and I'll not only kick you
out of these offices,
I'll put you in the ground.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Rachel.
[both gasping]
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
How?
Harvey.
Oh.
I don't understand.
I know you know
about Frank Gallo.
But what you don't know
is that they put me in solitary
confinement for 36 hours.
- Oh, my God.
- It's okay.
I was safe.
Then Harvey made them
watch the video,
which showed that I was
only defending myself.
Turns out they were
more than happy to trade
six hours and an ankle bracelet
to avoid a lawsuit.
♪ ♪
We only have six hours?
Yeah, and I don't want to
waste any of it.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
Mr. Litt,
what are you--
Oh, please, call me Louis.
What can I do for you, Louis?
Tara, I'm afraid
I have some bad news.
We're not gonna be
moving forward
with the renovations after all.
I'm sorry to hear that.
No, it has nothing
to do with you.
And of course I will pay you
out of my own pocket
for any of the work
you've already done.
That won't be necessary.
Please, Tara, I insist.
In that case,
I might as well at least
show you what I had in mind.
As you can see,
these are just rough drawings.
Not to me.
Here's the frosted glass wall
curving in an elegant "S"
that separates the space.
It's beautiful.
That's not even
the best part.
Because I know how important
the new bullpen is to you,
I modeled it after the
Kimmel Center in Philadelphia,
and I enclosed
the entire space--
In mahogany.
[sighs]
It would have been exquisite.
But some things
weren't meant to be.
♪ ♪
Yeah.
How would you feel about
renovating my summer house
in the Hamptons?
I appreciate the thought,
Louis, but I don't do
residential work.
It's not residential.
I use it as a home office.
But it would be so small.
Oh, no, I want
the entire house to be
a satellite division
of the firm.
Are you sure?
I've never been as sure
of anything in my entire life.
♪ ♪
Then I look forward to
working with you, Louis.
♪ ♪
Sean, what can I do for you?
- Where the hell are they?
- What?
I've been sitting in my office
for two hours waiting for them.
Where the hell are they?
I don't know.
Maybe they're caught in traffic.
Listen to me,
I can contact the prison
and find out exactly
where they are.
But I do that,
it starts a tornado of shit
with your boss in the eye
of the storm.
So you're gonna tell me right
now what the hell they're up to.
He's waiting for Mike
outside of his apartment.
Waiting for him to do what?
- He's with Rachel.
- You got to be kidding me.
I didn't pull in every
favor I have so Mike Ross
could have some conjugal visit.
No, you pulled in
every favor you had
so that Harvey could convince
Mike to do what you wanted
and this is gonna
make that happen.
By getting him laid?
By reminding him of
what he's missing out on
if he doesn't take your deal.
That wasn't the plan.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go down there and do
what we said we were gonna do.
I'm gonna show Mike
the innocent people
that lost everything
because of that bastard.
Sean, please,
if you do that,
Rachel will find out
about everything
and that can't happen.
Why not?
Because Mike chose prison
over her once,
and if he does it again,
she'll never forgive him.
Mike's problem.
Not mine.
No, that's Harvey's problem.
He promised Mike
he wouldn't tell her,
and Harvey's a man of his word.
If he were a man of his word,
he would be here right now.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna do what
should've been done
in the first place.
I'm gonna tell Mike's fiancée
that he has a chance to get out
but he doesn't want to take it.
[dramatic music]
You want to tell me
what that was all about?
♪ ♪
Harvey and Cahill
got Mike out of prison
to convince him
to take the deal,
and Harvey brought Mike
to Rachel instead of to Sean.
He broke Mike out of prison?
Is he crazy?
It sounded crazy
to me at first too,
but Harvey's living with the
guilt of putting Mike in there
and Cahill was willing to do it,
so can you blame him?
No.
I can't.
♪ ♪
But I want to know how
this whole thing shakes out.
And I want to know tonight.
♪ ♪
- Shh.
- What time is it?
We still have time.
Oh, my God.
I fell asleep.
You did.
Why didn't you wake me?
Because you looked
so peaceful.
Rachel, I don't want us
to waste--
We're not wasting anything.
Mike, I don't know how well
you sleep in there,
so to be able
to give you this...
[solemn music]
Thank you.
♪ ♪
Can I cook you something?
I'll make you anything you want.
No, I just want us to lie here
and stare at each other.
Not say anything.
♪ ♪
Oh, God.
You're so beautiful.
♪ ♪
I thought you wanted us
to be quiet.
Well, couldn't help it.
You know, you always tell me
how beautiful I am.
You never give me a chance
to tell you how handsome
I think you are.
I thought you loved me
for my mind.
I do.
But that doesn't mean
that I don't also think
you're handsome.
♪ ♪
Mike, what's going on?
There's something
I need to tell you.
Does it have something to do
with why you're really here?
Because I didn't believe
what you told me earlier.
Why didn't you say something?
Because you're here,
so I didn't care.
♪ ♪
What's that?
I'm unwinding my position
with Nathan Byrnes' company.
Well, I appreciate that.
But I don't need to take home
the paper trail.
It's not a paper trail.
It's an engagement letter.
Turns out my attorney was filing
my positions before he had to,
so I let him go.
You want me to
take you as a client.
If you'll have me.
On one condition.
I hear you've been having fun
with Louis Litt.
But it stops now.
Done.
[elevator bell rings]
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
I should have known a guy
who would hire a fraud like that
would pull a stunt like this.
This stunt is gonna get you
exactly what you want.
No, Harvey.
I'm gonna get what I want
by telling that kid's
fiancée the truth
and letting her do
the work for me.
Listen to me, Sean.
She doesn't know because
he doesn't want her to know.
I don't give a shit
what he wants.
Then trust me, this is the
only way to get what you want.
Trust you?
You lied to my face.
I made a judgment call.
Then look me in the eye
and tell me you didn't
make that call before
you asked me to get him out.
I knew it.
The whole time you were
always gonna bring him here.
Because this is
the way to get it done.
Then why didn't you tell me
that in the first place?
Because it would have ended up
with you wanting to use Rachel.
It ended there anyway.
Now get the hell out of my way.
Don't make me stop you, Sean.
Are you threatening
a federal prosecutor, Harvey?
You're goddamn right I am.
Well, you better think
about this move
more than you thought
about the last one.
'Cause it's not gonna
end well for you.
Far as I'm concerned,
it's the same move.
I made a promise
and I'm not gonna break it.
♪ ♪
Harvey!
Whatever you're fighting about,
you can stop.
I told Rachel everything.
I'm taking the deal.
Then let's get in the car
and get moving.
[rousing rock music]
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man