Previously on "Suits"...
You made a fool out of Dad
for the last time.
- Harvey--
- Stop it.
You get the hell
out of my father's house.
I am walking out of here
with that thing in my hands,
or I am putting your firm
in the ground.
- Take the painting.
- You told me that painting
was the one happy memory
you had of your mother.
Every application
I filled out today
asked if I was
a convicted felon.
None of these places are gonna
hire me after I check that box.
A legal clinic isn't the only
way to get back.
Are you offering me
a teaching job?
- I am.
- You think this is funny?
Cracks me up that our teacher
was in prison last week.
All you care about
is proving to me
that you should be
managing partner,
when everyone in the world knows
that you shouldn't.
So, if you think I'm gonna let
you be managing partner,
you're out of your
goddamn mind!
One of the students told his
parents that you were in prison.
I tried to explain the situation
to them, but...
I'm sorry, Mike.
They're all leaving,
Donna--
first Jessica and now Mike.
They're family.
You always talk like
we're your only family.
You need to go make things right
with your mother.
[R&B music]
♪ ♪
[cup clatters]
Mike, what are
you doing here?
I thought school started
at 7:00.
It does.
I just don't work there anymore.
What?
What happened?
One of the students told their
parents I was a criminal.
They went
to the archdiocese, and...
you know, Father Walker
had no choice.
Why didn't you tell me this
last night?
'Cause I didn't want to step
on your moment.
You were so happy
about Louis' offer.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna take the day
to enjoy my life as a free man.
And then tomorrow...
I'm gonna start all over again.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hey.
Ray's downstairs
waiting for you.
I didn't call him.
I did.
He's got your black suit
and an overnight bag,
and he's taking you
to the train station.
Donna...
You need to go to your
father's funeral, Harvey.
I can't.
There's too much going on here.
Listen to me--you just
suffered a huge loss,
and you're acting like
it's business as usual.
I'm acting like I've got
a job to do.
Harvey, if you don't
grieve him--
I will grieve my father
in my own way.
No, you won't.
You'll bottle it up,
and you'll try to move on, but--
She's gonna be there, Donna.
I know she is.
But this funeral
isn't about her.
And it's not about you.
It's about your dad...
the man you love more than
anyone in the entire world.
And if you don't
say good-bye to him,
you're gonna regret that
for the rest of your life.
[sighs]
[dramatic rock music]
♪ ♪
[knock at door]
Donna, what are you doing here?
The question is,
what are you still doing here?
I made you an 8:00 reservation
to Boston,
which means you should be
halfway there by now.
I missed my flight.
Harvey, you never
miss your flight.
And the last time
you said you did,
you were lying
to me then, too.
- Donna...
- Please tell me
you didn't change your mind
about seeing her.
I didn't.
Then what's the problem?
I haven't seen the woman
in seven years.
The last time I did--
I know what happened
the last time you did.
Listen to me.
Every day you go out
in the world,
and you find a way to win.
It's who you are.
It's what you do.
Donna, this isn't
about winning.
Yes, it is.
But it's not just one person
in this case, it's two,
and right now
you're both losing.
What if I can't do it?
Then don't get on that plane.
But that bag
sitting over there
tells me that you're ready
to forgive her.
And if you are, then that's
all you need to do.
♪ Suits 6x12 ♪
The Painting
Original Air Date on February 1, 2017
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
[knock at door]
- Nathan.
- You remember me.
I remember everyone.
What are you doing here?
I'm here because I may not
have been there
when you dropped off
your résumé,
but I still run that clinic.
I'm here to offer you a job.
- I don't understand.
- Hector Suarez.
I'm assuming you remember him,
too, right?
- What about him?
- Well, after you left,
I picked up your file.
Don't tell me--you kept him
in the country.
No, Mike. You did.
I thought, "Maybe this guy
will become a lawyer someday."
And then I read about you
in the paper last year
and found out you never did.
So you knew that I faked
being a lawyer twice,
and you're still here
to offer me a job?
I wouldn't be,
except for this.
You told the truth.
As far as I'm concerned,
that means
you're worth
taking a chance on.
Wow, you really are
a do-gooder.
I'm not here to do good
for you.
I'm here to do good
for my clinic,
because I'm hiring
a partner-level attorney
from one of the top firms
in the city
for the price of the kid
who gets me my coffee.
You have a kid
who gets you coffee?
No, we can't afford that.
But if we could, I'd pay him
what I'm gonna pay you.
So are you in or not?
When do I start?
I don't think I've ever seen
you in a suit before.
Harvey, you made it.
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
[sighs, chuckles]
Harvey, listen, um--
You don't have to say it.
I know.
She's here.
It's not just that.
She asked if she could say
a few words about Dad.
And what,
you're gonna let her?
- Harvey--
- She is not saying
a single word
as long as I'm here.
Yes, she is,
and if you make a scene
in front of my kids
on the day that we put
our dad into the ground,
I swear to God, I will beat
the shit out of you,
because she's my mother, and
I'm gonna let her say her piece.
Hey.
Harvey...
It's good to see you.
Wish I could say
the same thing, Lily, but...
I'd be lying if I did.
Well, I'm sorry
you feel that way.
And whether you believe it
or not, I loved your father.
And I am sad to see him go.
Yeah, well,
I don't believe it,
and I didn't come here
to see you.
I came here to honor my father,
so get up there,
say what you're gonna say,
and let's get this over with.
[sobs]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Harvey.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to talk to you.
I can't believe it.
This is wonderful.
I thought maybe you wanted
to get dinner tonight.
There is nothing
I would rather do
than get dinner with you,
but I can't tonight.
I wish
you would have called.
I would have,
but, uh...
You didn't have
my phone number.
No, I didn't.
How about tomorrow night?
I wasn't really planning
on being here two nights.
My firm is in a...
vulnerable spot right now.
Harvey, it's the kids'
art show.
It's once a year.
I can't cancel it.
You know what?
This is silly.
You flew
all the way up here.
No.
We can do it
tomorrow night.
Don't tell me.
You took the job.
Actually, until this morning,
I didn't think
there was a chance in hell
I was getting this job.
Sounds to me like you had
a friend at the front desk
who put your résumé
at the top of the pile.
Sounds to me like I owe
that person a beer.
Just so we're clear--
I'm that guy.
I get the picture.
- Welcome to the clinic, Mike.
- Thanks, Oliver.
- I see you met Oliver here.
- I did.
We got along right away.
Good, good.
Well, you're off
to a good start.
I guess the only thing left
is for you to show me
where my desk is.
Right. It's, uh, right inside
that office right there.
I didn't think
I was getting an office.
Look, just because
I'm paying you dick
doesn't mean I'm not gonna
give you the tools for the job.
What exactly is my job?
'Cause as far as I can tell,
I'm the only one here
with an office.
Everybody listen up.
You have a new supervisor
starting today.
His name is Mike Ross.
Mike is from
Pearson Specter Litt,
and he knows more about law
than all of you combined.
So, if Mike tells you to do
something, you do it.
I don't mean to question
the new world order,
but what is his title?
Great question, Marissa.
Um...
senior individual
in charge of you?
Any more queries?
I didn't think so.
All right, back to work.
Let's go.
You really weren't kidding
when you said you were
doing this for you.
No, I wasn't.
I've been trying to get somebody
in this position
for this money
for the last ten years,
and now that I have...
I'm gonna take
full advantage of it.
Then why don't you go back
to wherever your office is
and stay there for the rest
of the year?
'Cause I'll be busy
kicking ass out here.
That's what I like to hear.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hey, who do you have to know
around here to get a good table?
Jesus Christ.
Do my eyes deceive me,
or do you look
just like my big brother,
only older, fatter,
and douchier?
I appreciate you noticing.
I put in a lot of effort.
Seriously, Harvey,
why are you here?
I thought it was time
to, uh, make my peace with Mom.
Harvey, that's great.
But, uh, a lot has been said
over the years.
You can't just show up
on Mom's door.
Actually, I already did.
What? When?
I went over to the college.
She's having an art opening
tonight for her students,
so we're gonna have dinner
here tomorrow night.
Well, then
I will get you a table.
And what you're going to do
is cancel whatever fancy
bullshit hotel you booked,
and you're going to stay
the night with us.
Marcus, come on, I'm at the
Ambassador Suite at the Ritz.
Don't think of saying no
because I'm going to tell Katie
and the kids that you're here.
You guys offer
room service?
If by "room service,"
you mean string cheese
and Triscuits,
oh, yeah,
we've got room service.
All right,
well, then count me in.
Marissa, right?
Mike.
I know. The new boss.
- [chuckles]
- What?
It's nothing--
it's just where I come from,
the, uh--the bosses
don't bike to work.
I guess this is
no Pearson Specter Litt.
No, it's not, which is
actually why I came here.
I'm glad, because there are
a lot of people here
who could really use your help,
but I'm not one of them.
Aren't you still
a law student?
A law student
who's won every case I've had
since I've been here.
Great, so I guess that means
you have everything
under control
on the Price case, then?
You just got here.
How did you--
I'm a fast reader.
Marissa, I'm not trying
to throw my weight around here
on the first day,
but according to her file,
Miss Price missed
her court date,
which means I need to know
what your plan is.
My plan is
to have Miss Price
explain that she is
a single mother
living in an apartment
with a broken window
and no heat for months, and
they're trying to kick her out.
And if all you're gonna do
is tell the judge
that it's not fair,
you're gonna lose.
You need legal foundation.
I have legal foundation.
Berger v. Chozick--
tenants are permitted to seek
injunctive relief
if vital repair requests
have gone unanswered.
Then I hope you have backup,
'cause the attorneys
representing the other side
have kicked out
300 tenants
in the past six years,
which means
they are not messing around.
I'm not either,
which is why I have
Miss Price coming in
at 3:00 tomorrow.
So is there anything else
I can help you with?
Or maybe
you can spend some time
on some of the other people's
cases around here.
♪ ♪
Louis, I need your help.
- Of course. What is it?
- Teddy Doyle just called.
He has an emergency.
So you mean Harvey
needs my help.
- Louis--
- Donna, give me
one good reason
why I should help him.
You're not helping
Harvey, Louis.
You're helping the firm.
Teddy is a client of all of us.
No, Harvey made it clear
that there is no us.
Louis, Harvey's going
through something right now.
His outburst
wasn't about you.
You can believe
whatever you want,
but Harvey lashed out at me,
and now he's not even man enough
to come to me to ask me
for help himself?
Why should I even lift a finger
to help him?
Because he went to go make
things right with his mother.
And he did it because of how he
felt after he lashed out at you.
Otherwise, he'd be taking care
of Teddy himself.
So you want
to help him or not?
What do you need me to do?
Mike?
What's going on?
Rachel. I thought you weren't
getting home till 8:00.
- It's 8:30.
- I guess I lost track of time.
I have just been buried
in this paperwork.
Yeah, I can see that.
Are we being audited?
I got a job.
And I would have called you
right away,
but I've been swamped from the
minute I walked into the clinic.
You got a job
at a legal clinic?
Mike, that's amazing.
Yeah, it is.
- Um...
- Yes, they know about me.
In fact, it's the reason
I got hired.
Let me guess--they were
smart enough to appreciate
they can get someone
with your experience
for ten cents on the dollar.
You got it.
$35,000 a year
to be exact.
Mm!
Which means...
we should probably start
packing up the place now,
'cause we definitely cannot
afford to live here anymore.
I would live
in a shoebox with you
if it meant you were happy.
Aw, I think you meant that you
would live in a shoebox
as long as the Thai place
still delivered.
- And the sushi place.
- Of course.
- Want one?
- You kidding me?
After reading "Pinkalicious"
for the seventh time,
I need a six-pack.
[chuckles]
[bottle cap clatters]
[sighs]
[sighs] It was nice
putting them to bed.
Oh, yeah,
let's hear you say that
after doing it
365 days a year.
I thought Katie put them
to bed most nights.
Yeah.
I was saying it for her.
[chuckles]
Thanks for making me
stay over, Marcus.
♪ ♪
Well, maybe after
tomorrow night,
you can do it more often.
♪ ♪
Maybe.
Thank you all for coming.
I'm Lily.
I was married to Gordon
for almost 30 years.
We didn't make it the whole 30,
and for a long time,
I considered myself a failure
because of that.
But Gordon didn't.
A few years
after our divorce,
I wanted to apologize
for things not working out.
He just smiled and said,
"Lily, what the hell
are you talking about?
"We achieved something together
that neither one of us
could have done on our own."
Our sons...
Harvey and Marcus.
When Gordon was on the road,
he would call home...
[chuckles] Six times a day
to check on them.
Did they eat enough dinner?
Had they done homework?
How many points
did Marcus score?
Did Harvey get his tux
for the prom?
Gordon was proud
of a lot of things in his life,
but none of it compared
to how proud he was of them.
[somber music]
They were his everything.
♪ ♪
No matter where he is...
[sniffles]
I know he is watching
over them right now.
♪ ♪
- What are you doing here?
- Doing my job.
- This is my case, not yours.
- No, Marissa.
It's our case.
We're on the same side.
And if you'd just listen to me,
you might learn something.
- Like what?
- Like the ways
experienced attorneys
can trick you.
I'm not gonna
get tricked, so...
if you don't mind,
I'd like to meet with my client.
I've already met with her.
You met her without me?
When did you do this?
Half hour ago.
You said 3:00,
so I called her in at 2:30
because I knew you wouldn't
give me the chance to meet her,
just like I know
the other side
is gonna approach her
when you're not there.
- They can't do that.
- Why? Because it's unfair?
- Because it's illegal.
- Only if she pursues them,
which she'll never do
because they're gonna find out
whatever her weak spots are,
and then they're gonna offer her
exactly the amount
she needs to get by,
and then
she's gonna take it.
If she does that,
she'll end up homeless.
Which is why we need to be
prepared for it to happen.
Now, do you want to work on this
thing together or not?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
that she was gonna speak
before you got here.
I just didn't have it in me
to have it out with you.
It's okay, Marcus.
She got to you, didn't she?
I'm sad about Dad.
And, yeah, she pulled
on that string,
but one speech
doesn't make up for everything.
Maybe it doesn't.
But you have
to start somewhere.
Yeah.
Well...
I'm gonna head back home.
Oh, come on, Harvey,
come to the house for the wake.
I got a few things
I got to take care of at work.
Oh, come on, Harvey, you're
not leaving because of work.
♪ ♪
It's time to let things go.
I complained about the heat
not working a million times.
Landlord always says
he's gonna fix it,
and then nothing happens.
We couldn't afford to move,
so I was just making do,
but then my little guy--
he got asthma.
The doctor said that we need
to keep all of the windows shut,
keep out the pollution,
but the window
in the living room--
it's been broken
for seven months.
My son is only
three years old.
The sound of him wheezing
at night...
not knowing if he's gonna
wake up in the morning...
So I thought, "Since that
slumlord only cares about money,
"I'm not gonna pay rent
until he fixes the window
and turns on the heat."
I'm so sorry, Sofia.
That sounds terrible.
It is.
And no one should have
to live like that.
But by violating your lease,
he has grounds to evict you,
which is why you have
to give him a check
for the money you owe him
while this case moves forward.
I-I can't do that.
You don't have
the money anymore.
I had to buy blankets,
space heaters.
There were a couple of nights
that AJ's breathing was so bad,
we had to go to a motel
down the street.
Don't worry, Sofia.
Not only are we gonna get
your window fixed,
but I promise you, you'll get
to keep your home, too.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
♪ ♪
Are you crazy?
What are you talking about?
You just told her you were
gonna fix her problem.
Because I'm going
to fix her problem.
That's not the point.
Even if you think
you can make everything better,
you don't guarantee that
to a client.
You know what?
Maybe you don't care
about these people, but I do.
Oh, God.
And I'm willing to fight
to make sure
they stay in their home, and
I'm not afraid to tell her that.
This is not about caring.
There's a real world out there,
and like I told you,
there's an experienced lawyer
on the other side
looking to exploit
our mistakes.
If you over-promise
and under-deliver,
you're just making them
that much more vulnerable
to a shitty offer.
Is that what they taught you
in Corporate Lowballing 101?
Excuse me?
You don't give a shit
about these people,
and Nathan
and everyone else here
might be buying your bullshit,
but I know
why you're really here.
I get it.
You checked up on me.
I didn't need
to check up on you.
I've heard your story
a thousand times.
You couldn't hack it
at your corporate law firm,
so you're slumming it here
until you can figure out
a way to jump
back into your cushy,
stick-it-to-the-working-man job.
[sighs]
I see that I'm right.
So keep your wisdom
to yourself,
because I'm actually here
to help people,
not just remind them what
a cruel world it is out there.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[telephone ringing]
- Harvey Specter's office.
- Donna, it's me.
Harvey. Hey.
Are you almost here?
Because your 6:00
is in the conference room.
I'm not back
in New York yet.
You were right, Donna.
About what?
If I'd missed his funeral,
I never would be able
to forgive myself.
[sighs]
Good luck making up
with your mom.
How did you know?
Because you've never missed
a flight
in your entire life.
And the only reason
you'd stay longer
is if things were going better
than you thought they would.
Thanks, Donna.
I don't need
your thanks, Harvey.
I'm just really happy
you're there.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
I know
what you're thinking.
How could she not know?
- I checked the box.
- You did.
But I was the one who brought
the application to Nathan,
and he told me
not to tell anyone.
Why not?
Because he didn't want them
to judge you.
I would have thought
everyone knew anyway.
Why would you think that?
Because it was all over
"The Journal."
People here don't read
We read
"The Huffington Post."
[chuckles]
So what Marissa thinks
is what they all think?
I don't know,
but for what it's worth,
I wouldn't have said anything
whether Nathan told me
to or not.
It's not my story to tell.
Thank you, Oliver.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
You made
your strawberry pie.
It was his favorite.
Maybe you forgot
it was mine, too.
I didn't forget.
It was a nice speech.
Thank you, Harvey.
Harvey...
when my parents died,
I felt like I was completely
alone in the world.
I don't want you
to feel that way.
I want you to know
that whether you want me
in your life or not,
you still have a mother
that loves you
and will always
be there for you.
I know that.
Harvey, I'm--
I'm sorry for your loss.
Are you kidding me?
You brought him here?
Harvey--
I said, you have the nerve
to bring him here?
- He's my partner.
- Is that what you call
every guy you slept with
while you were with Dad?
Don't speak to me like that.
Bobby and I are still together.
- You think I give a shit?
- You should...
because it shows what kind
of man I am.
You're a piece of shit.
You have no right being here
the day we put my father
in the ground.
Harvey, please.
We were just about--
Yeah, I don't care
what we were about to do.
You spit in Dad's face
by bringing him here.
I-it's okay.
Lily, I'll go.
I don't care
whether you stay or not.
No, well, I do,
and he is staying,
because you may not
want to hear this,
but your father accepted him
a long time ago.
You know what? You want
to take his place, Bobby,
why don't you go right ahead?
Maybe one day you'll even walk
in on her with another guy,
and you'll know exactly
what my father felt.
The only difference will be
at least then...
I won't be asked to keep
the goddamn secret.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
So, what's good here?
Actually, everything's
good here.
You eat here a lot?
Of course I do.
[chuckles]
This...
This feels strange,
doesn't it?
Yeah, a little bit.
So, where do we start?
I guess we start
with me telling you
that I'm ready
to forgive you.
[sighs]
Why now?
Someone very special to me
convinced me that I needed to.
Whoever it is...
I'm glad she did.
That's good.
I want you to know...
that I forgive you, too.
Forgive me?
For what?
For the last time I saw you
and for you being gone
all those years.
I had my reasons
to be gone.
Yes, you did,
when you were younger,
but you're not
a child anymore,
and you haven't been
for a long time.
I can't believe you.
You're turning this
around on me?
I'm not turning it
around, Harvey.
You have no idea what it's like
to have a child
who acts
like you don't even exist.
You don't know what it's like
to have a mother
who asks you to lie
to his own father for her.
Harvey, I never
should have done that,
and I have been trying
to tell you
I am sorry about it
for 20 years,
but until yesterday,
you made it clear to me
that you had no interest
in whether I lived or died.
- Because I didn't.
- Well, can't you understand
how that could devastate
a person?
I can understand
how this was just a mistake,
because you are the same
selfish, self-centered,
disloyal woman
you always were.
And you are the same
self-absorbed,
childish man
you always were.
Well, whose fault is that?
Oh. There you go. Leave.
That's what you do best.
What'd you just say to me?
I said take a look
in the mirror, Harvey,
because I may have neglected
my family in the past,
but you've been doing it
for as long as I can remember.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
So what am I supposed to tell
the kids in the morning?
You tell them I've got
business back in New York.
You want me to lie for you?
Marcus,
she had the nerve
to say that I owed her
an apology.
[knock at door]
If that's her, you tell her
I've got nothing more to say.
You know what, Harvey?
You can tell her yourself,
because I'm doing being
in the middle of you two.
Bobby.
Where is he?
- Hey, now's not the time.
- You son of a bitch.
You think you can just walk
into our lives
and--and rip open
old wounds?
Your lives?
You better get the hell
out of my face before I do
something that you'll regret.
You already did something
I regret
by talking to your mother
the way you did.
That woman gave up the right
to be called my mother
when she got together with you
behind my father's back.
Well, maybe you don't consider
her to be your mother,
but she's my wife,
and if anyone else spoke to her
the way you did, they'd be
on the floor right now.
You want to take
a swing at me?
- Harvey, Harvey--
- No, no, no.
Let him get it
out of his system,
'cause I know I want
to get it out of mine.
I didn't come here
to fight, Harvey.
I came here to tell you
I've never seen your mother
more excited
than when she was heading out
to have dinner with you.
She was finally gonna get
to reconnect with her son.
And then you pulled the rug out
from underneath her.
You took that excitement away.
So, when you leave this time,
just stay gone,
because the truth is,
this family works better
without you.
♪ ♪
Rachel, I need you
to help me with something,
and I need it quickly.
What is it?
Teddy Doyle needs to access
the proceeds from the sale
of his company
that were put in trust
to avoid taxes,
and he needs to do it
without triggering those taxes.
Louis, are you kidding?
This isn't Dubai.
He's not gonna be able
to do that.
I know that, but I need him
to be able to anyway.
Give me the file.
I'll figure something out.
Thanks.
I'm proud of you, Louis.
For what?
Teddy Doyle is
Harvey's client.
And I heard about your thing.
So this must mean
that you forgave him.
I did.
Bring that to me as soon
as you have something.
♪ ♪
Hey, Mike, I got a question
about the Haberman case.
He lost his job.
They're taking his car.
I'm trying--
You need
a reaffirmation agreement.
Can I help you in a minute?
Yeah.
Great.
Hey, everyone, can you listen
up for a sec?
Marissa...
this won't take long.
When Nathan introduced me,
he told you
that I used to work
at Pearson Specter Litt.
What he didn't tell you is
why I don't work there anymore.
And the reason isn't
that I couldn't hack it
as a corporate lawyer.
It's because I wasn't
a lawyer at all.
♪ ♪
Here, read that.
That is my story.
That's what I did.
Every word of these articles
is true.
I never should have been
at Pearson Specter.
But not being a lawyer
isn't the only reason
I didn't belong there.
You see, the whole reason
that I wanted to be a lawyer
in the first place
was so that I could help
the kind of people
that come into this clinic
every single day.
Now, I thought
you all knew this,
but it's clear to me now
that you don't.
Nathan wanted to protect me,
but...
I'd rather have you respect me.
If any of you have
any questions at all,
please come talk to me
about it.
If not, let's get back to work.
♪ ♪
Mike.
You didn't have to do that.
Yeah, I did.
♪ ♪
Hey.
You're still here.
My flight isn't
for another two hours.
I wasn't gonna let that asshole
drive me away.
Listen, Harvey, about what
Bobby said last night--
You don't need to make excuses
for him, Marcus.
Oh, I'm not making excuses.
I'm telling you
he had every right
to say what he said to you.
I don't believe this.
You're on his side now?
The only side I'm on
is my family's--
the family that you've never
been a part of.
- Marcus, come on.
- Do you know what it's like
to tell a five-year-old
why Grandma
and Uncle Harvey can't be
in the same room together?
Because that's the position
you put me in year after year.
There's a whole life
going on here
that you're not even
a part of.
You think I don't know
what I've missed?
I'm not just talking
about birthdays, Harvey.
I got sick again,
couple years ago.
What?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why would I?
So that we could have this
at the same time?
- Marcus--
- No, listen to me.
You know who helped out when
Katie was taking me to chemo?
Mom made dinner every night.
Bobby took my kids
to school every day,
which means...
while they might be
monsters to you,
to my kids,
they're Grandma and Grandpa.
And you might not like that shit
coming from Bobby,
but it's the truth, Harvey...
whether you want
to hear it or not.
♪ ♪
Do you have a minute?
Of course.
I'm sorry
that I misjudged you.
It's okay.
Like I said,
we're on the same team.
We are, and I also
should not have promised Sofia
that we would win.
But I told you
that I wouldn't stop looking
for a way to keep her
in her home,
and I think I found one.
Marissa, it doesn't matter
what kind
of legal basis you've got.
If she can't pay her rent
in the meantime--
That's what I'm talking
about--Troy v. Suffolk.
As long as we can prove that she
tried to tell the landlord
about the heat--
Yeah, but we can't prove it.
She doesn't have it in writing.
We can if we use
the phone records.
Phone records aren't proof
of a complaint.
No, but the only people
who call their landlord
three times a week
for two months
are people who have a problem
that needs fixing.
Then we enter
the motel receipts
and the receipts
for the space heaters
as substitution for rent paid.
And not only
can he not evict her,
she doesn't have to pay
back rent.
We just need
to convince the court
to accept these phone records.
The problem is we can't
convince the court of anything.
I'm not a lawyer yet,
and I was hoping you
could do it, but then...
It's okay.
I've got just the person.
[footsteps approaching]
Harvey.
Can I come in?
Depends on why you're here.
I'm here to apologize
for the way I acted last night.
Is this 'cause Bobby
came to see you?
No, it's because
Marcus got sick,
and you took care of him, and
he couldn't even tell me that.
- Harvey--
- I'm so angry.
I don't want to be
angry anymore,
but I don't know how to stop.
Then let me say
how sorry I am
for all the pain
that I have caused you.
You don't need to tell me
how sorry you are.
Yes, I do.
Harvey, we both
may have played a part
in the last 20 years,
but I was an adult,
and I put you
in that position.
And not a day goes by
that I don't understand
why you hate me.
I was your mother.
[voice breaking]
I was supposed to protect you...
not scar you.
Harvey...
I am so sorry.
[sighs]
I don't hate you, Mom.
I hate what you did,
and I probably always will,
but I don't hate you.
I'll take that.
♪ ♪
What is it?
It's nothing.
It's...
it's just, I had your
painting on my wall
for the longest time,
and I just realized...
how much I missed it.
I love you, Harvey.
♪ ♪
I love you, too, Mom.
Your Honor, my client is
a single mother
with two small children.
And my dog is
a Labrador retriever.
But the only thing
that's relevant here
is that his client hasn't paid
her rent in three months.
And the reason she hasn't paid
it is because she's had no heat
and a broken window
all winter,
despite repeated requests
for repairs.
There's absolutely
no documentation
of any such request.
That's not true.
My client called her landlord
20 times over the course
of two months,
as you can see
from her phone records.
That's not proof
of anything.
It's proof your client
spoke to mine
for an average
of two minutes per call,
and it wasn't to talk
about the weather.
Your Honor,
Mr. Grady gave me
a copy of this nonsense
20 minutes ago,
and he specifically agreed
it wasn't relevant.
That--that is a lie.
Really?
Because I have a phone record
of a two-minute call
that I made to you
ten minutes ago.
You may have called me,
but we didn't talk about that.
That's right.
Just because I called you
doesn't mean I can prove
what we talked about.
Your Honor,
she called 20 times.
Yeah, probably to say
why her rent was late,
because she never paid it.
But we won't know that
because we don't have it
in writing,
which is what
the court requires.
Your Honor, I need...
I'd like to request time
to confer with my supervisor.
His supervisor?
He's a lawyer.
- You have to help him.
- I can't.
I just need a minute
to--to gather my thoughts.
What is this,
preschool circle time?
Your Honor, the woman
didn't pay her rent.
The deadline is now.
We are requesting
permission to evict
if we don't have a check
by 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
- Your Honor, please.
- She's gonna lose her home.
Time's up, counselor.
Permission granted.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Harvey, what are you
doing here?
When did you get back?
Ten minutes ago.
How'd it go?
It went well.
I'm glad.
As a matter of fact,
I need your help with something.
Anything.
But there's something
you have to do first.
- Mr. Ross.
- Miss Price.
I wanted to talk to you.
Do you have a minute?
Not really.
They're coming tomorrow.
I've been packing, and--
They're not coming.
$3,600?
Should be enough to cover your
rent for the last three months.
- I don't understand.
- The clinic has a fund
to help
with this kind of thing.
We do it all the time.
But this is from you.
It's just quicker to do it
from my account--
you know, red tape
and all that.
- I don't know what to say.
- Say you'll take that
to your landlord
first thing in the morning.
And if they do anything
but give you a written receipt,
you call me right away.
I will. Thank you.
[both chuckle]
- You're back.
- I am.
And I heard you took care
of my client.
Thanks, Louis.
You're welcome,
but we're partners,
and they're all our clients.
They are.
Louis, I didn't mean it
when I said
you weren't ready to be
managing partner.
Yes, you did.
Maybe I did,
but the truth is,
I'm not ready either.
What do you say we both act
as interim managing partners?
I'd be honored.
It seems to me,
the first order of business is,
what are we gonna do about
the name of the firm?
I don't know
about you, but...
I think we should keep it
exactly the same.
Me too.
I mean, you never know
when she's gonna want
to come back, right?
No, Louis.
You never know.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
What are you two
still doing here?
We've still got 12 hours.
We're not going to stop trying
to keep Sofia in her apartment.
Good for you.
But you don't
have to do it tonight.
Turns out she got
a little grace period.
How did she get that?
It's amazing
what you can do
when you care
about your clients.
Then I guess
first thing tomorrow,
we should plan our next move.
I guess we should.
[soul music]
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man