♪ ♪
Ross.
Triple double,
courtesy of
America's favorite burger chain.
Louis won
the class-action suit?
♪ 10,000 men of Harvard
want victory today ♪
♪ For they know that
o'er old Eli ♪
♪ Fair Harvard holds sway ♪
♪ So we'll conquer
all old Eli's men ♪
My favorite part.
You don't know the lyrics,
do you?
I don't even know the lyrics,
Louis.
Now are we practicing law
down here,
or auditioning a chorus line?
It's called esprit de corps.
And I just got a $100 million
jury award overturned.
I don't have to overturn
awards like that
because I've never lost one
in the first place.
So what is this, a new cologne
or just a hint of jealousy?
I'm surprised you, uh,
don't recognize
your wife's perfume.
I know, you're not married.
It's still funny.
You do realize
we're celebrating
making fat people
even fatter, right?
If you wanted to do good,
you should've been
a fake doctor.
Business cards.
Yup.
My mistake is now official.
Come with me.
And learn the goddamn lyrics
to the Harvard song, will ya?
Oakhurst Capital has agreed to
a $200 million licensing deal.
We are at the goal line.
How are we on brand protection?
The contract is airtight.
The only issue here
is to get the Joyful Toy Company
to close.
I'll go over it with Joy
one-on-one.
Protocol in a meeting is
to put your phone on silent.
- Uh...
- And if it does ring,
you answer it.
Oh. Yeah.
Not in here.
I... okay.
Don't feel the need
to rush back when you're done.
Who is this?
Dude, it's Trevor.
Don't hang up.
I only get one call.
I'm in jail.
I... I tried to hop this bus
at Port Authority.
I was drunk.
It's all messed up.
Look, I know we haven't talked
since we fought,
but I didn't know
who else to call.
Hey.
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry.
Okay.
- I'm gonna pay you back.
- Yeah, you better.
Your bail cost me
everything I have in the bank.
The thing is,
I don't have the money.
What are you talking about?
You're clearing
$10,000 a month selling weed.
It went out
as fast as it came in.
Came in?
I quit.
I'm not dealing anymore.
- Bullshit.
- I'm serious.
After we fought, I don't know.
Things just
started to fall apart.
Jenny broke up with me.
I didn't know.
Well, I just realized
I needed to make a change.
Even sold my bong.
What have you done
with my friend?
Yeah. You should talk.
Look at you. You look like
Gordon Gekko's little brother.
Okay.
What, are you
working on Wall Street, man?
Why'd you call me, Trevor?
You're the one person
I knew would show up.
You want to ask me
for anything... else?
Look, all I care about
right now
is keeping my record clean.
You don't happen to know
any good lawyers, do ya?
No. I don't.
Ima Robot's Greenback Boogie
♪ See the money wanna stay
for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feels ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ Living in a beehive,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Being busy, so I'm busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Yes, hey, hey,
I like to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I don't have to be a hero ♪
Why the rush now?
You've already wasted
ten minutes of my life.
Please tell me
you didn't wait ten minutes
just to scold me.
I've been waiting for you
to bring the paperwork down
so I can close
a nine-figure licensing deal.
If your phone rings
while I'm talking to Ray,
I'm throwing it out of the car
while it's attached
to your hand.
Eddie Hope
and the Mannish Boys.
1959, three guesses.
Guesses?
♪ Won't Be a Fool No More ♪
You insult me, Harvey.
Don't worry, we won't be late.
"Eddie Hope and The Mannish Boys'"
Won't Be a Fool No More
♪ ♪
Okay, what was the name
of the record label?
Marlin records.
Who covered it
in the late '60s?
Ahh! I want to say
The Stones, but...
You need some guesses?
Oh! Oh, my God.
Just like
a private car service, huh?
Thinking
you don't have to yield?
What? Yield?
You ran a red light!
That light was yellow!
No, sir, it was not!
Are you calling me a liar?
- Back off.
- Mind your business, okay?
- No, I'm minding my business.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Anyone throws a punch,
or I'm gonna introduce you
to Mr. Taser.
Trade insurance,
I'll take reports,
one at a time.
Yeah, as much as
I'd like to help you out,
I'm late for a meeting.
No, no, no.
You're not going anywhere.
I need a statement
from you too.
Here's mine.
I need you to babysit
the client till I get there.
And don't mention the deal.
If she asks any questions,
just nod your head
and look pretty.
Ms. McAfee, I'm Mike Ross.
I work with Harvey.
Oh, you're the protege that
he's been gushing about.
He was gushing?
Well, he mentioned
that you existed.
For Harvey, that's gushing.
Uh, he's running
a few minutes late today.
Um, car trouble.
I was just about to have tea
with the girls.
Would you care to join me?
I'd love to.
Good.
And for heaven's sakes,
call me Joy.
Okay, Joy.
These...
Are the girls.
Susie, Sarah,
Stacy, Sinclair,
and Sabrina.
Susie, where are your manners?
Shake hands
with this nice young man.
Mm...
Just kidding,
I know they're dolls.
Oh.
They're named
after my daughters.
I started the company
because of them, really.
You know,
dolls didn't used to be
these cheap, plastic bimbos
from China that we have today.
Your mother made them for you
by hand.
I wanted my girls to have
that same experience.
And here we are,
30 years later.
Every parent's worst nightmare.
What do you mean?
These little angels,
they sell for $90 a pop.
I wasn't born with a butler,
you know.
I gotta say, this is amazing,
taking on a project
like a licensing deal.
Why is that amazing?
Well, my grandmother
could never pull this off.
She's been retired
for ten years.
How is that treating her?
She lives near my apartment.
I get to see her
once a week, so...
- That's very sweet of you.
- No.
No, it's not.
You know, whenever I needed her,
she was there.
You know, no matter what.
She'd give me a hug,
she'd tell me everything
is gonna be all right.
And...
Even if it wasn't.
And now that she needs me,
I am always at work.
And I'm...
I'm so sorry.
Yeah?
Never answer your phone
in front of a client.
- But it's you.
- What's happening?
Well, actually we're
in the middle of a tea party.
I knew you were
the doll-playing type.
Put Joy on.
Ms. McAfee,
it's Harvey.
Oh.
Joy, I'm sorry,
I have to reschedule.
No need to apologize.
I like this one.
I'll send him back after tea.
Tell me you didn't ask
our client for a doggy bag.
What can I say? Stacy insisted.
Just got off with
Joy McAfee's general counsel.
It seems she had an epiphany.
She wants less on her plate,
not more.
I thought you
were going to close her.
We need that doll money.
I'm on top of it.
Harvey took five months
to structure that deal.
Please don't make me set fire
to your desk.
I...
All you had to do
was have tea with the dolls.
Donna, schedule another
tea party with Joy
as soon as possible.
And text me
the names of her girls.
Oh, what a shock.
You can't keep girls' names
straight in your head.
Just yours, Debbie.
See, that's funny
because your name is Donna.
Harvey Specter.
I got your order right here.
I didn't order a pizza.
You've been served.
Cab driver who hit Ray
named me as a witness
in a civil suit.
I need to pay Travis Bickle
a visit.
Harvey,
if you let me go talk to Joy,
I know I can fix this... No.
You don't send a puppy
to clean up its own mess.
Optimally,
you don't even have a puppy.
Ross, rumor has it you talked
a client out of $200 million.
The deal's not off the table,
all right?
It's just a speed bump.
Dude, I think we just
found him a new nickname.
Speed Bump!
I feel like
I'm back in high school.
They called you Speed Bump
in high school?
Kidding.
But if you need any boxes
to pack up your office, just...
Ow.
Hmm, wait a minute, uh...
There.
I think that belongs to you.
It wouldn't hurt so much
if you had thicker skin.
What do you want?
I wanna pay you back
for posting bail.
Trevor, you've owed me
40 bucks since fifth grade.
I wrote it off, okay?
Look, I want a clean slate,
okay?
So you don't want to see me,
I'll mail you a check.
Okay.
Yeah, let's hang out
tomorrow night.
Nothing crazy, though,
all right?
I have to be up early.
We can crochet panty hose
if that's what it takes
to be cool.
I think we can do
a little better than that.
Why don't we, uh...
Why don't we say Rex's, 7:30.
First six rounds are on me.
If you're serious
about paying me back,
the first 100 rounds
are on you.
All right.
So it's the tough guy.
This is a matter for insurance,
not a frivolous lawsuit.
You know, for your information,
I suffered emotional pain.
Emotional pain?
Rub this
on your emotional pain.
You condescending son of a...
Look at me,
I am gonna warn you once.
Do not pursue this matter.
You know, I have been held up
at gunpoint three times.
So do you think a fancy suit
and a $500 haircut,
that's gonna scare me?
You take my driver to court,
I'm gonna represent him myself.
And when you lose,
you'll be covering my fee,
which is gonna be
a hell of a lot of haircuts.
Hmm, so you weren't
a one-way fare.
Ray's worked for me
eight years.
Then you don't have to worry
about being a witness,
because as his employer,
you're liable for his actions.
You know, I think you've seen
way too many reruns
of Ally McBeal.
Hmm. You know, I emigrated
here after September 11th,
and they shut the doors
on everybody.
I couldn't pay for a lawyer,
so I had to take them to court.
I sued for my citizenship,
so I have
a very special appreciation
for the law.
I appreciate
a good single malt.
I don't pretend I can make one.
I wiped the floor
with the U.S. government,
counselor.
I'm gonna do the same with you.
- Ray.
- Donna.
What are you doin' here?
I don't have you scheduled.
Uh, I need to see Harvey.
Oh, come on.
You know the rules.
No one sets foot in there
without a warrant,
a papal edict, or my say-so.
I just got named
in a multimillion-dollar
lawsuit.
The accident wasn't my fault.
Can I get in to see Harvey,
please?
Okay, say no more.
I will get you in.
You are so beautiful
when you're forceful.
I know you meant that
as a compliment,
but I don't appreciate
limitations
being placed on my beauty.
Harvey,
I'm already losing money
with my car in the shop.
A trial means I can't work.
And how do you think
my name is gonna play
in front of a New York jury?
Rahim Benghazi.
I may as well buy
a one-way ticket to Guantanamo.
- Not gonna happen.
- If I lose,
I won't even be able
to afford a livery license,
let alone my insurance.
That's why I'm gonna be
defending both of us.
Ray, this goes against
every fiber of my being.
I'm taking your case pro bono.
I don't know what to say.
Absolutely nothing, I've got
a reputation to maintain.
Besides,
it's not gonna take long, okay?
I'm gonna get it dismissed.
Donna, call the court.
We need priority status
on the docket.
Yeah, I already tried.
You drew Judge Palermo.
You know what you have to do,
don't you?
Yeah. The other thing
that goes against
every fiber of my being.
Louis, has anyone told you
you're an exquisite soprano?
What do you want, Harvey?
You're right.
Why prolong my suffering?
I need you to get me in
to see Judge Palermo.
You need my help, and you're
not gonna pull rank on me?
Your case has nothing to do
with firm business, does it?
What's it gonna take?
A mani-pedi? Tickets to Celine?
I'll see what I can do.
And your pound of flesh?
I need my back scratched,
I'll let you know.
Louis, unless that's
a metaphor, the deal's off.
Huh.
Joy, when I told you
that my grandmother
didn't have much time,
I... I didn't realize that
she's 15 years older than you.
Now, how would you know
how old I am?
That is
a very closely guarded secret.
I did some research.
Very resourceful.
I did it to assure myself
that you can handle
a heavier workload.
I appreciate that,
but I'm not worried
about my health.
Is it the money?
Because I can guarantee,
200 million up front
is just 1/10 of what you
stand to make on this deal.
Michael,
my dolls eat better
than most people.
I've got plenty of money.
This deal meant staying on
for five more years
and doubling my workload.
I am going to take
my grandchildren on a cruise
to Tahiti. Tahiti?
You know,
the licensing agreement
includes a theme park.
You could...
you could take them there.
It's not about the deal.
I have had this same view
for 25 years.
I need a change of scenery.
I am gonna speak to Harvey,
and I'm gonna tell him
that I want to sell
the whole business.
So...
I just spoke to Judge Palermo.
And because he thinks
I'm a good guy,
and I told him I'd owe him one,
your case is gonna be
moved up way ahead.
Back scratch.
I don't have a firstborn,
you know,
so what exactly
do you want for that?
No, you're not getting
one of my ties.
No.
Your shoulder? What...
your lapel...
Donna?
Oh, God.
Norma is going to Istanbul
for two weeks,
and you know
that I'm not good with temps.
Oh, my God.
Ask me for something else.
Harvey, this is non-negotiable.
You owe me now.
Donna is one thing
that I can't give you.
- Why not?
- For one thing,
she'd never agree to it.
You're her boss.
You just tell her to do stuff.
I don't tell her
to do anything.
She just does.
All right, fine. You know what?
That's just... Not a problem.
I will call Judge Palermo,
and I'll tell him
I was mistaken,
and then your hearing
will be in,
I don't know, maybe six months?
I tell you what.
If you can convince her
yourself,
you have my blessing.
She's gonna love me so much,
you're gonna fight
to get her back.
Hi, Donna.
Harvey and I were just,
uh, talking about you.
And... No.
You don't even know
what I was gonna say.
Yes, I do.
And how is that possible?
I read lips,
I know body language,
and I talk to Norma.
I'm not some token
you win at a fair, Louis.
You're not... I know you're not.
You're not a token.
I'm a human being, and I...
Yes, you are.
I'm sorry, I just...
you know what,
that just made me feel really...
Cheap. I...
No, I'm just trying to tell
you that you're really good
at what you do, Donna.
So I'm gonna ask you...
It's like my soul hurts now.
No, Donna, listen, even if
your soul hurts a little bit...
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's gonna be fine. Don't cry.
Please don't cry, Donna.
Oh, sh...
I think I owe you one for that.
That was fun.
Wait a second, the...
the time that you cried,
and then I let your parents
stay in my condo...
Yup.
"Philadelphia Grand Jury's"
Ready to Roll
♪ ♪
♪ You, I just want you
to know ♪
So you don't want
to talk about it?
What is there to talk about?
I did exactly what my boss
told me not to do,
and it blew up in my face.
Dude, I told you,
I'm taking care of this.
In my last few hours
of employment,
please, I should pay.
All right, put the wallet away.
Oh.
Wait... give... dude,
this is epic.
This is the scam
we always talked about.
God, I bet you're
gettin' laid left and right.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You lose appreciation
after a while.
Come on. Yeah,
why'd you put
a phone number on there?
It's a real firm.
Oh, yeah?
Huh.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just calling
the employee directory.
It's part of the scam, man.
- They'll check your story.
- Stop it.
- What?
- Trevor, stop.
Hang up the phone. Oh, no.
Trevor,
hang up the phone, stop!
- What?
- All right? I'm working there.
Oh, yeah. What, as a lawyer?
Are you...
dude.
It's a long story, okay?
But you can't tell anyone.
Ever. Okay?
That is awesome!
Man, I... I always said
that if you quit smoking pot,
you could do it.
- Yeah.
Yeah, oh, that's right.
Yeah, you did.
Right before you
passed me the bowl.
Oh...
What?
Naw, I just...
I wish you trusted me enough
to tell me.
I mean, all I did was set you up
on a drug bust.
Oh, God, that was too soon.
I'm sorry.
Hi, ladies. How are you?
Um, I want to let you know,
if you... either of you
ever get arrested for anything,
you call this guy.
He's the best attorney
in the city.
Well,
what would we get arrested for?
- Um...
- I don't know.
I don't know. What are you
thinking about doing?
♪ I'm not like
some other brothers ♪
♪ I'm not like some
other brothers ♪
♪ But I'm ready to roll ♪
Uh, as your attorney,
I would definitely advise you
to do that.
Uh, four more. Yeah.
I must warn you
that representing yourself
at trial is not the...
What's he doing here?
You think you can schedule
a meeting without me knowing it?
Oh, no.
I'm privy to all communication
between you and the court.
Well, if your driving
matched your legal knowledge,
we wouldn't be here.
Your Honor.
This case should be dismissed.
It's a matter for insurance.
Insurance only covers repairs.
It does not deal
with my losses.
What losses?
Because of the accident,
I missed my chance
to get my taxi medallion.
You can't just buy it
next year?
The loan I got
expires in one week.
On top of that, a medallion
costs 300,000 this go-round.
Next year, 350.
So his entire claim
rests upon the assumption
that he would've won
this year's medallion.
The hallmark of America
is that the little guy
gets to see justice done.
We are all equals
in the eyes of the law.
That is why, out of all
the countries in the world,
I chose to come here.
What do you got to say
about that, counselor?
I say Atticus Finch
makes a good speech here,
but this is a fender-bender,
not a multimillion-dollar
lawsuit.
Vicarious liability
applies to discrimination,
harassment, and accidents.
Employers are responsible
for their employees' negligence.
Court finds
a reasonable suit here.
Trial starts tomorrow.
Thank you, Your Honor.
You're getting a good kick
out of this, aren't you?
I am.
But I'm taking this
on its merits.
And you better bring
your "A" game tomorrow,
'cause he's got
a legitimate claim.
He wants a trial?
I'll give him a goddamn trial.
Your Honor.
So how many cases have you won?
I only remember
how many I've lost.
None.
Wait, what happened
to the drinks?
I got a better idea.
Let's say we get a bottle
and take the party
back to your place?
Make it a bottle of Dom,
and you're on.
All right,
how about four bottles?
Come on.
You guys want to get a cab?
Definitely.
Cab, four bottles of Dom.
You want to spend any more
of my money?
Just relax, okay?
It's an investment
in the evening.
And, uh, I just said the thing
about the bottles
to get the girls
out of the bar.
Really? 'Cause it looked like
you were trying to get away
from those guys.
Taxi!
- What guys?
- The guys in the back.
You know what I'm talking about.
Come on, who are they?
What? Those two?
I... I... I don't know.
Where are all the... Cabs?
Well, it looked like
they knew you,
and not in a very good way.
I... I don't know.
Maybe they were, uh,
flirting with our dates, okay?
I'd be pissed too
if I watched those legs walk
away from me.
How are we doin', ladies?
My feet are killing me
in these heels.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey, Trevor, come on...
- Taxi!
- Seriously,
stop playing with me.
What was that about back there?
Look, I'm not playing
with you, all right?
But just play your cards right,
maybe you and, uh,
maybe Marcella will, uh,
maybe she'll play with you.
Okay.
Now, it's gonna be
a tight squeeze.
Who wants to sit on my lap?
Want to go after him?
No, we're gonna get to him
through this guy.
"Kaiser Chiefs'"
Good Days Bad Days
♪ ♪
♪ Follow the underdog ♪
♪ Hold on his collar tight ♪
♪ This city loves a scrap ♪
♪ One day it's gonna fight ♪
♪ Sticks and stones
and animal bones ♪
♪ Can't stop me from having
a good day on a bad day ♪
Ah-ha! Just like
the good old days, huh?
Are you kidding me?
This is way better
than the good old days.
I... I'm actually missing a shoe.
Hey, where are we?
Uh, I think we're in Hoboken.
♪ And bad days ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
You wanted to see me?
Did you go see Joy
after I told you not to?
How did you know?
I didn't. Until now.
I told you,
a puppy can't clean up
its own mess.
Mess? All I did was tell her
about my grandmother.
Your job
is to make my life easier.
If you can't understand that,
why did I hire you?
Police report summarized.
Traffic signal analysis.
Medallion bids,
attendees, and results.
That's why you hired me.
I thought you were all over
the Joy situation.
Instead,
you're all over page six.
You wanted me to do
pro bono work, this is it.
Pro bono enhances
a firm's image.
This makes us look
like wealthy bullies
against an everyman cabbie.
Does that seem like
it enhances our image to you?
I refuse to answer that,
on the grounds
that I don't want to.
Someone had a fun night.
Answer another call
you shouldn't have?
I... I... I didn't... I was...
Piece of advice...
when the big dog asks the puppy
something like that,
it's a rhetorical question.
Got it.
Before you go,
the phone call, the other day,
when you answered it
during the meeting...
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Won't happen again.
Who was it?
Um, it's just a friend.
You know, an emergency.
What kind of emergency?
- Um...
- Was it a friend
who almost got you busted
for drug trafficking?
That friend? Trevor?
He's not dealing anymore,
Harvey.
So it was him.
He called you from jail?
You know, I make a living
learning how to read people,
Mike.
So if I saw it,
Jessica did too.
Is that the kind of impression
you want to leave around here?
This guy is not your friend.
He is an anchor dragging
you down. Get rid of him.
He is my oldest friend, Harvey.
I wasn't just gonna let
him rot in jail.
What's gonna happen
the next time?
'Cause there will be
a next time.
You gonna bail him out?
Put yourself in jeopardy?
You know,
if it weren't for Trevor,
you and I never would've met.
Cut him loose.
We're here to see Mike Ross.
He's an associate.
His friend Trevor referred us.
Thank you.
Hey.
It looked like they knew you,
and not in a very good way.
♪ ♪
Hey!
Excuse me, officer.
Is... is Central Park that way?
Yeah, just go right there.
Uh, I'm sorry, I'm... I'm...
I'm really terrible
with direction.
Is it this street, right here?
- Yeah, this street, yes.
- This street.
Right here?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Trevor, it's Mike.
Call me back.
I need to know
what the hell's going on.
Did you get
the red velvet cupcakes?
Yes, three dozen, extra icing.
How the hell did that happen?
Okay. You know what?
There. Problem solved.
I asked you,
how'd you get that tear?
A couple of guys
came to the firm.
They were looking for me.
I don't know what they wanted,
but I'm...
I'm pretty sure it something
to do with some shit Trevor did.
And that big brain of yours
doesn't remember
me saying to cut ties
with that loser?
You know what?
You've been blowing off
Joy's deal
all week for your friend, okay?
So please.
First of all,
Trevor's not your friend.
You want to know why
I'm loyal to Ray?
I was taking a limo,
and I left $3,000 in it.
Ray happened to be the driver.
He found it
and tracked me down.
Not a nickel of it was missing,
and his first reaction
when this accident occurred
was to ask if we were okay.
Now, what would Trevor's
have been?
Cut him off.
Now, as far as
the licensing deal goes,
just because you think
I'm blowing something off
doesn't mean I am.
Now, watch and learn.
Everything's set
for you to walk away.
We're selling your stake
as a block.
Your, uh, headhunter's
lining up your replacement
as we speak.
Well, Harvey,
this was
the most wonderful surprise.
You're a long-time client
who wants to be with her family.
It's the least I could do.
And you'll have
all the free time in the world
to spend with them.
Joey broke the lamp.
Oh, that's great.
Now, how soon
can we send 'em home?
They're booked
on the first flight out,
tomorrow morning.
So when you had Donna
text you the girls' names...
I was talking
about her daughters.
And you were gonna
fly them out all along.
Do you remember when I said,
"You don't send a puppy
to clean up its own mess?"
Yes, Harvey, I do.
I'm not a puppy.
Court will come to order.
Mr. Santana,
your opening statement, please.
Driving a cab
is not very glamorous.
But it's an honest day's work.
Ever since I started,
I looked forward to a time
when I could tell customers
that they were riding in my cab.
That I was an owner-operator.
So I scrimped, and I saved,
until I finally had enough
put away to buy a medallion.
But...
Because of the actions
of this man,
I've lost that opportunity.
So make no mistake, this...
this trial is not about
a busted headlight.
This is a trial
about a broken dream.
Forget the case, they're gonna
make him president.
Statements
are like free throws... easy.
Nobody's playing defense.
Are we good at defense?
You would agree
that chauffeur drivers
cause more accidents...
Objection. Badgering.
Sustained.
Objection. Argumentative.
Leading the witness.
Ambiguous. Privileged.
Inflammatory. Sustained.
Anything further, Mr. Santana?
Yes, Your Honor,
I would like to call
to the stand Mr. Michael Ross,
please.
Uh...
What time had you called
for the limo
on the morning of the accident?
Uh, we were supposed to leave
at 8:30.
And what time
did you get to work?
Objection. Irrelevant.
It's highly relevant,
Your Honor.
It speaks to
the psychology of the driver,
Rahim Benghazi.
Overruled.
Answer Mr. Santana's question.
8:40.
So unless Mr. Benghazi
made up for that lost time,
you were going to be late
for that meeting, correct?
Yes.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
When the accident occurred,
you were on your way
to the medallion auction.
When and where was this auction
to take place?
9:00 a.m., City Hall.
According to the police report,
the accident occurred
at 8:53 a.m.
That means you only had
seven minutes
to get downtown
in rush hour traffic.
Objection, irrelevant.
I believe when
I made the same objection,
you told his honor
it was highly relevant.
Overruled.
You were running late,
only the stakes for you
were much higher,
weren't they?
These things
never start on time.
Then why was
the first medallion
sold at 9:03 a.m.?
You were scared your chance
at a medallion
was going up in smoke,
and you ran a red.
Then you used the accident
to paint me
and Ray Benghazi
as a couple of scapegoats.
You can't prove that.
What color was the light?
I take the fifth.
You can't take the fifth,
Mr. Santana.
This isn't a criminal case.
What color was the light?
He cut me off.
You claim to love
our legal system so much,
answer the question.
What color was the light?
Your Honor?
Answer the question,
Mr. Santana.
It just meant so much to me.
Your Honor,
can I sidebar
with opposing counsel?
We can roll the dice
with the jury,
but I'd rather settle.
Well, how much
would I have to pay?
Nothing.
You take responsibility
for the accident,
and your insurance company
makes Ray whole.
In return,
I waive my right
to collect legal fees.
I don't know what to say.
Don't say anything.
I've got
a reputation to maintain.
That goes for you too, judge.
Damn it, Trevor.
I left you like five messages.
Good to know your boy's
flaky with everyone.
I was taking it personal.
What do you want?
Well, Trevor owes us $50,000
he's never paid,
so you're gonna bail him out.
Listen,
I don't have that kind of money,
okay? I can't.
Well, if you're not down here
in an hour with it,
we're gonna take it out
on Trevor.
Tell him where the money is.
Whatever you do, don't show up.
Trevor!
You have one hour.
Hello? Hello?
What do you think you're doing,
leaving in the middle
of a trial?
I got some things
to take care of.
You mean someone
You never cut Trevor off,
did you?
No, I didn't.
My friend's in trouble,
and I'm gonna help him.
You know what?
This is what addicts do.
The second they start
making progress, they screw up,
because deep down they think
it's only a matter of time
until they fail.
They'd rather fall
from the third floor
than the penthouse.
Nothing you say can stop me.
Then tell me
what the hell's going on.
He's clean. No wires.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You remember what happened
with the guy.
He was 300 pounds.
Now, who'd you say
you were again?
Trevor's lawyer.
Trevor didn't mention a lawyer.
He doesn't know he hired me.
Come on.
Open the briefcase.
Where's the goddamn money?
That photo is a screen shot,
taken from my firm's
security video.
We know what you look like.
And if Mike Ross
doesn't hear from me
in the next five minutes,
he's calling the police.
No, man. You're not comin'
in here and threatenin' us.
You're looking at kidnapping,
extortion, and drug-dealing,
and the district attorney
happens to be number three
on my speed dial.
Well, if we're looking
at all that time,
you might as well add murder.
I got a better idea.
Retainer agreement.
If you sign right here,
you'll become
one of my clients.
And I won't be able
to testify against you,
even if I wanted to.
What about the money?
This envelope contains $10,000.
Consider it a down payment
on Trevor's debt.
Only here's the thing,
I don't do pro bono work.
And my retainer agreement
requires a down payment
of $10,000.
Now, as your attorney,
my job is to give you advice.
So here's the deal.
Sign the agreement.
I thought I said not to come.
Remember that 40 bucks
from the fifth grade you owe me?
If you were dead,
how would I collect?
Oh, man.
I'm sorry, I just...
Put you in trouble
just by hanging out with you.
So why'd you do it?
'Cause I'm a dick.
Bet you didn't think
you'd have to save my ass
so soon after bailing me out.
I wasn't the one who saved you.
Yeah. Well, as a friend,
the guy puts me to shame.
Harvey's not my friend,
trust me.
Well, he didn't put his ass
on the line because of me.
Listen, I pled you down
to a misdemeanor...
- Ugh.
- Drunk and disorderly.
And I paid the fine.
I think it might be a good idea
if you got out of town
for a while.
Montana.
Well, you said
you wanted a clean slate.
I figured 20 hours on a bus
ought to do the trick.
Oh, yeah, it'll do me good.
Wait.
When I get back,
you know who the first person
I'm gonna call is.
Yeah. The one person you know
who'll answer.
For you.
What's this?
I'm very happy
you took Ray on pro bono.
You, on the other hand,
can afford our services.
You want me to pay me
to represent me?
Mm-hmm. Ten hours
at $1,000 an hour.
Eh, yeah,
I'll let you do the math.
You can't be serious.
I'll tell you
what I am serious about.
I hear you're finally
mentoring the kid.
I don't know
what you're talkin' about.
Really, because I understand
that you dropped
the puppy analogy on him,
which is exactly
what I used on you.
May have slipped out
by accident.
Well, accident, on purpose,
the really important thing is,
is that I'm taller than you.
Yeah.
Yup,
you look much thinner in that.
You planted that story,
be man enough to own it.
I don't traffic
in the tabloids, Harvey.
But I can see how
whoever planted this
might find it amusing.
You know,
the great Harvey Specter
bullying a humble cab driver.
I mean,
it's a no-win situation, really.
Well, maybe you didn't hear.
I won the no-win situation.
Did it ever occur to you
that if you hadn't
done that to me,
I actually would have
owed you one?
Maybe if you didn't humiliate
me in front of the associates...
Louis,
for an average attorney,
100 million is a career case.
If I'm mocking you, it means
I think you're above average.
But stress balls?
You're making it too easy.
You put Trevor on the bus
to the boondocks?
Yeah. Can I ask you a question?
After all this,
you really
think I'm still buying
the Mr. I-don't-give-a-crap
thing?
Joy sent a little token
of her appreciation.
She got your hair just right.
Did she ever make
one of these for you?
Not that you'll ever see.
♪ ♪