Previously, on "Suits"...
Tara Messer,
will you marry me?
Yes, Louis, I'll marry you.
I don't care
how much money you make
or how many you women
you sleep with.
You have issues in your life
that are going to keep you
from having real relationships.
Benjamin and I have an overlap
on our software
with another company.
Louis pulled out every trick
in the book to get us this.
- Take the money.
- I don't want the money.
- Donna--
- I want something more.
- What do you mean more?
- I made a deal
that we would handle
the miners' case
in exchange for the chance
to be admitted to the bar.
Are you goddamn kidding me?
You're fired.
- Don't do it.
- He lied--not once, not twice--
I don't care
because we need him.
Monday morning, you better
start putting your money
where your mouth is and find us
another $50,000 case.
Tara left
a 15-second voicemail.
She's either gonna tell me that
she never wants to see me again
or she wants to make up.
What's that?
Your first year's salary
in advance.
Welcome back.
Harvey, I'm running out
of ways to tell you I don't want
to be a corporate lawyer.
I'm offering you a deal.
One for you, one for me.
I don't wanna just fund
the clinic for a year.
I want to fund it for two,
and any case I want
to bring the clinic onto, I can.
Done.
- And there's one more thing.
- You are not getting my office.
Oh, yes, I am,
and I will tell you why.
- Why?
- 'Cause she's gone, Harvey.
It's time for you
to take the reins.
Harvey.
What are you doing here?
Nothing, I was just
driving this baby around
and remembered
how much street parking you had.
Is that supposed
to impress me?
Well, I hope so.
Sure as hell impresses me.
Well, it's nice to see you,
but if you wanted
an appointment,
you should have called.
I'm not here
for an appointment.
I'm here to ask you out.
You're serious.
I've been doing a lot
of thinking lately, and...
- Harvey...
- Please, let me finish.
Things have changed
since the last time I saw you.
I'm not the same man that I was.
I made peace with my family;
I got my old associate back,
and as of this morning,
I'm the head of my firm,
and when I thought
of sharing that with someone,
I thought of you.
Well, it doesn't matter,
because it's completely
unethical for a doctor
to engage in a relationship
with her patient.
Not if enough time has passed,
and according to the APA,
as of three weeks ago,
enough time has passed.
- You did your homework.
- Sure did.
So the only question is:
Thursday at 8:00
or Saturday at 9:00?
One dinner,
and if this chemistry you
so clearly think exists doesn't,
then we part as friends,
no hard feelings.
If it doesn't work out,
no harm, no foul.
Thursday.
Oh, and if the car's too much,
I can always have Ray drive.
I like the car.
What did you say?
I couldn't hear you.
I like the car.
Good.
You're here early.
I need you to take point
on a consumer fraud hearing
for Sandra.
Nathan, I need to talk to you.
Okay.
I know things got heated
between us the other night,
but as far as I'm concerned,
it's water under the bridge,
so if you're wondering
if I'm still upset at you--
I'm not.
And this is to make sure
you're still not upset with me
after you hear
what I'm about to say.
Why am I holding a check
for $500,000?
Because I've decided to go
back to Pearson Specter Litt,
and I gave you my word that I
wouldn't leave you high and dry.
So let me get this straight:
You changed your mind,
and now Harvey Specter
is buying you back?
If it were up to Harvey,
you wouldn't be getting a penny.
I insisted on this.
Just like I insisted
on every other case I take
from now on being pro Bono.
It sounds like you insisted
on that
to make yourself feel better.
No, Nathan, I did that
because I care about
doing this kind of work,
and if you're okay with it,
I'd even like the idea
of us partnering
on a case every now and then.
But what if I say I'm not okay
with any of this?
I know that you were the one
that gave me another chance
to be a lawyer
when no one else would,
but don't punish the clinic.
It's a lot of money.
With that, you could replace me
and help a lot of people
for a long time.
- Is that for me?
- No, actually, it's for me.
You're later than usually
this morning.
I've been waiting for you.
Donna, about the other night.
I know you said you wanted more,
but before you say anything--
- I want to be a partner.
- Partner?
Yes.
I figured out what I want,
and I want to be a partner
at this firm.
Donna, I don't mean
to insult you,
but you're not even a lawyer.
Good, because my being
a partner isn't about the law.
It's about keeping
this firm running,
which I've been doing
for as long as I can remember.
I know that, but it doesn't
mean that I can get you--
I've given over ten years of
my life to this place, Harvey,
and I've done it all
from your desk.
All I'm asking is
for a seat at the table.
I'll have to ask Louis
about it.
Does that mean that
you're on board?
I don't know.
It's Mike's first day back,
it's a big ask,
and on top of all of that,
I've decided to tell Louis
that I'm taking full control
as managing partner.
Well, congratulations, Harvey,
but which is it?
Louis?
Mike?
"Big ask."
Because I'd hate to think
I mustered the courage
to do this,
and then once you get on that
elevator, it's out of your mind.
I give you my word.
I will not forget about it.
Okay.
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ Suits 7x01 ♪
Skin in the Game
Original Air Date on July 12, 2017
♪ the greenback boogie ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Did you sleep in here?
Just getting a feel
for my new office.
You think a bike rack
would fit on this wall?
You put a bike rack in here,
your first pro Bono,
you'll be representing yourself
after I shove it up your ass.
Wow.
That sounds uncomfortable.
Now, speaking of pro bonos,
when are you gonna get your
old man records out of here
so I can settle in
and get to work?
I'll get out of here
once we take of Neil Stillman.
Neil Stillman?
Detour industries?
No, Neil Stillman,
Jedi counsel.
Okay, I was asking because
Neil Stillman is
a corporate client,
so what happened to one for me,
then one for you?
Do I need to remind you that
at a corporate law firm,
we do the cases
that pay the bills first?
Besides, I haven't even told you
the best part yet.
You only got
two weeks to live?
No.
After we're done with this case,
I'm giving you Neil Stillman.
Harvey, I appreciate that,
but seriously,
if you're just gonna give him
to me when we're done,
why don't you give him
to me now?
Whatever it is,
I can handle it myself.
- I know that.
- Then what's going on?
It doesn't make sense for us
to be working together on this.
All right, you want the truth?
When Jessica
made managing partner,
she and I never really got
to do cases together anymore.
You used to work
on cases together?
Yeah.
She was me and I was you.
We kicked ass.
Right.
And what exactly did
you contribute to the equation?
Oh, movie quotes, mostly,
but that's not the point.
The point is we had
a great time doing it.
- Harvey...
- Mike, I'm serious.
Once Jessica stepped up,
our relationship changed.
And if you'd known
that was gonna happen,
you would have wanted one
last case together.
Exactly.
So what do you say?
We go out and have some fun
and kick some ass?
Or do you want to stay here
measuring for your bike rack?
It's not gonna measure itself.
All right, fine.
Kick ass.
But we do this,
I want on that Jedi counsel.
Robes, light saber,
whole deal.
Good, you're here.
Gretchen,
what are you doing here?
- I'm here to give you these.
- What are those?
Brochures from the top
nine mud resorts
in the northern hemisphere,
though I don't know
why a person would do
that in the first place.
It's like sitting in a bathtub
of your own poop.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Louis, you need
to take yourself some time off.
When's the last time
you even had a vacation?
Nine years ago July.
Goddamn travel agent sold me
a package
to Club Med Bangladesh,
so, hard pass.
What kind of person goes
to a sex club in Bangladesh?
It's not like that.
I had just seen
"Slumdog Millionaire,"
and I was trying
to find Freida Pinto.
I believe she considers London
her place of habitat.
No, I'm not talking about
the real Freida Pinto.
I'm talking about
my Freida Pinto.
There's many different
Freida Pintos out there, okay?
So just--I'm not an idiot.
Leave me alone.
Louis, I'm just worried that
if you sit around and stew,
this breakup's gonna
get the best of you.
Gretchen, I really
appreciate that,
but I'm not just
gonna sit around.
I'm gonna be pouring
my heartbreak
into those new associates.
Are you sure that's
the best idea?
Look...
I didn't just lose Tara.
I lost a chance
at being a father.
And those associates have
always been my children to me.
My children.
And the truth is,
I've been neglecting them
ever since they got here,
but that ends this morning.
I'm proud of you, Louis.
Thank you, Gretchen.
- Where the hell have you been?
- Neil, you called an hour ago.
Well, that means you should
have been here in 30 minutes.
Well, I got news for you:
I'm not Dominos.
That's too bad,
because slinging pizzas
might be the only job
you can get
if you don't stop
shitting the bed.
Shitting the bed?
How's that?
I've been trying to get you
on the phone for two weeks.
Jessica leaves, and all of
a sudden, I start falling
through the cracks?
You're not falling
through anything.
I'm here now,
and I brought the best
junior partner in the firm.
I don't give a shit if he's
the best junior towel boy.
I got something for you to do,
and I want it done yesterday.
Let me guess, you want to sell
your vodka business.
How the hell could
you know that?
Because you don't clean up
the balance sheet
of your third largest division
six months after you restructure
if you're not looking
to put it on the market.
Okay, you brought
the right guy.
My question is,
what took so long?
And my question is
what's the rush?
'Cause you also don't ram
a transaction through
if you don't have to.
I have an opportunity
to buy another company,
and I don't wanna
let it slip away.
What company?
I'll start vetting them for you.
They're Russian,
and they make
a little product called
none of your goddamn business.
Neil, what's with the secrecy?
We're your lawyers.
We need to know
what you're looking to do.
The secrecy is
in case you're not my lawyers
two weeks from now.
I don't want you knowing
who I'm going after.
Is that a threat?
It's just my way
of making sure
I don't keep falling
through the cracks.
Now let's talk terms.
Good morning, Gretchen.
Have you seen Louis?
I'm worried about
how he's doing after last night.
My guess is he's in
the bullpen
with his hatchlings.
His hatchlings?
I was concerned about him
as you were,
so I tried
to get him to take a vacation.
He said he'd rather focus
on raising those associates.
Focus on them or take it
out on them?
Knowing him, probably 50/50,
but the man turned down a trip
to the finest mud resorts
in the world,
so I decided to give him
the benefit of the doubt.
Then I will too.
Good morning, boys and girls.
Who's ready to tear
Watson Industries a new asshole?
That's what I like to see.
Now, on your desks,
I've made each of you a copy
of my initial brief.
Cling to it
as if you wrote it yourself,
and if any of you need
to go to the bathroom,
I suggest you do it now,
because for the next two weeks,
we are not leaving this room.
No one will be shitting.
No one will be pissing.
No--
Go ahead, ask him.
Ask me what?
I heard about
your reputation, but...
But what?
Don't you worry about
my reputation, son.
I am not the same Louis
I used to be.
I still may be tough,
but I have a soft spot,
so what do you need?
Two days off.
No problem.
Feel free to take
Saturday and Sunday off.
He meant in addition
to the weekend.
In addition?
Brian, is this true?
- Yes.
- Then...
Monday and Sunday
you shall have.
Okay, fine.
Monday and Tuesday it is.
- Thank you, Mr. Litt.
- No, no, just call me Louis.
Mind if I ask
what the occasion is?
- I'm gonna be a father.
- What?
We're gonna have a baby boy.
Something everybody here knows
is never gonna happen to you.
Gonna be a father
for the rest of his life.
- What'd you just say to me?
- I said it's a C-section,
'cause the baby's
actually sideways,
which means we have
to go in there...
You self-centered
piece of shit.
Do you think I care
about the graphic details?
- I just thought--
- Thought what?
That you don't give a shit
about your job?
Let me tell you something: When
you work here, you work here.
You don't think about home
and families and babies.
So the next time you want
to put your personal life
ahead of the needs of this firm,
you better goddamn come to me
a year in advance.
That's not fair.
He couldn't have known he was
gonna have a baby a year--
Let me tell you something,
Stephanie:
Maybe you don't know
how babies are made,
because when people are trying,
they know they're trying,
and just because no one
ever wants to try with you
doesn't give you the right
to tell me
how to run my associates.
You got that?
Got it.
You thinking
what I'm thinking?
Depends.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking we've got
a vodka company to sell.
You already said you wanted
to have some fun.
That's right,
and you put those two together,
what have we got?
Party.
See?
We're already on the same page.
Why don't you get
a kick-ass location,
and I'll get the models.
Models?
I like models.
Why can't I get the models?
You make a good point.
It's a two-man job.
We'll both get the models.
Harvey, seriously,
why do we even have
to have models at this party?
Well, two reasons.
First, people expect it,
and you've got to give the
people what they want.
Right, and second,
any dipshit who shows up
and hits on the models all night
isn't a serious bidder
for the company.
Huh, you really are ready
for my office.
Hey, speaking of which, when
exactly is that gonna happen.
I can't talk about that
right now.
I got to go hit on some models.
Hey, Harvey,
jokes aside,
what you said before
about us working together
like the old days,
I appreciate it.
It means a lot to me.
Me too.
Pussy.
Donna, do you have a minute?
I need your help.
Of course.
What's going on?
Louis is out of control.
When Esther got married
out of control,
or when Harvey made senior
partner out of control?
Worse.
Shit.
What did he do?
He just went off
on the associates.
He was abusive
and cruel and ugly.
Donna, I have never seen Louis
like this before.
Rachel,
if what you're saying is true,
then we need to figure out why,
because with Louis,
there's always a reason--
Tara broke up with him
last night.
- Oh, my god.
- I was there when it happened.
This is not something that
he's going to get over quickly.
- So what are you saying?
- I'm saying that
I think I should
take over the associates
until he's able to get
his emotions under control.
Rachel,
taking the associates away
isn't exactly
gonna stabilize him.
That's the one thing he has.
Yeah, I know that,
but I'm telling you,
if we're not careful, someone's
gonna do something to him,
and he'll be lucky
if it's just suing him.
Did you tell him that?
I tried to,
and he bit my head off
the minute I walked
into his office, so...
Okay, I'll talk to him.
But I'm gonna need you to tell
me exactly what he did first.
Whatever it is,
I don't have time, Donna.
From what I heard,
you had time
to go off on the associates
this morning.
Who told you that?
That's bullshit.
Are you telling me you didn't
go off on Brian Altman
and then make a horrible comment
about Stephanie Patel's
sex life?
- It's called discipline, Donna.
- It's called actionable, Louis.
You're lucky that there isn't a
lawsuit on your desk right now.
Well, thank you
for your counsel.
I know what I'm doing.
Louis, I am trying
to be understanding,
but I think Rachel should handle
the associates for right now.
- Is that a joke?
- No, it's not.
Well, then let me explain
a little something
to you called pecking order.
See, I am up here.
Rachel's down here.
And you don't give dominion
over your associates
to someone down here.
I know that,
but I also know that Tara
broke up with you last night,
and you're not
in your right mind.
I don't want to hear
that name again.
Louis, all I'm saying is
if you don't deal with it,
you're gonna keep abusing
the associates,
and then we're gonna have--
Hey, Donna, you know what,
I didn't want to do this,
but I did leave one name
off the chart.
Me.
Rachel.
You.
So don't you tell me what to do.
Louis, I'm gonna let that go,
because I know you're hurting,
but that right there
is exactly why I'm right,
because if you're willing
to talk to me like that,
god help those associates.
- Hello?
- Yes, is this Dr. Feelgood?
'Cause I'd like to schedule an
appointment as soon as possible.
I'm sorry.
You've got the wrong number.
This is Dr. I have work to do.
Well, in that case, I'd like
to schedule an appointment
as soon as possible.
Harvey, why exactly
are you calling me?
First, answer me this:
How many times
have you considered
picking up the phone
and telling me
that you've reconsidered
since you said yes?
Four.
If you don't count right now.
Then let's just say
I'm calling to tell you
that I've been
in a room full of models
for the last hour,
and all I can think of is you.
Still thinking
of cancelling on me?
No, Harvey.
I'm looking forward
to our dinner as well.
Did you move up the date
of our wedding
and forget to tell me?
No, I got to get dressed up
for this thing
that Harvey and I are going to
for a client.
A thing for a client.
That's not very specific.
Uh, yeah, I mean, it's just
kind of hard to explain.
Hmm, does it involve
three dozen models
and 1,000 bottles of vodka?
I guess it's not that
hard to explain.
Mm-hmm.
When were you gonna tell me?
If not before,
then definitely after...
Or never.
It's hard to tell.
I haven't really
thought this through.
- You know I'm kidding, right?
- Yes.
You should come.
I can't.
Katrina and I are taking
the Chippendales public,
so we're gonna meet
with a few of their top dancers
to go over some paperwork.
Probably take all night.
- So that's not funny.
- Yes, it is.
I'm serious, Rachel,
you should come.
I think Harvey got a helicopter.
We should take a ride
around the city.
I can't.
You go.
It's a long story.
I ju--
I might be taking over
the associates,
and if I do,
I just want to be prepared.
Rachel, that's amazing,
but are you telling me
that Louis is really ready
to give that up?
That's the long story.
But I'll tell you
about it later tonight.
- I can stay.
- No, you should go--
Great, okay.
I love you.
I love you too.
Donna, before you leave,
can I talk to you for a second?
What is it now?
We're running low
on coffee filters?
Can't find the sweet 'n low?
Or is Louis finally being sued
for being an asshole?
You want to tell me
what's going on,
or you want to keep
firing your pistol
in the wrong direction?
I'm sorry, Gretchen.
I am just sick and tired
of being everyone's go-to
and not getting what I ask for.
I don't mean
to sound insensitive,
but you're
a corporate secretary.
What exactly did you expect?
You really want to know?
I asked Harvey
for a seat at the table.
- What table?
- The partnership table.
- No wonder he shot you down.
- He didn't shoot me down.
He told me he would think
about it,
but I haven't heard anything,
and I don't know now if I will.
One way to get his attention
is to go in there
and take that check you gave him
and rip it the hell up.
- What check?
- The check you gave him
for your partnership money.
You didn't give him one,
did you?
No.
Let me tell you something,
Red.
You want a seat at the table,
you got to put some skin
in the game.
There he is.
Hey, Harvey,
this was a great idea, huh?
Glad I thought of it.
Are we having fun?
If you call
talking geopolitics
with a model named
Svetlana fun,
then that would be
a big, fat bowl of yes.
Easy, tiger.
The bartender's pouring doubles.
Mm.
And what are you getting at?
I'm having another drink.
I said for you to be careful.
I can handle my liquor.
Okay.
How many fingers
am I holding up, huh?
Huh?
You can't tell, can you?
Who can't handle my liquor now?
I'd tell you to put food in
your stomach, but unfortunately,
I only ordered enough to give
the appearance of having food.
So basically,
you're just trying
to get these guys hammered
so you can drive up the bidding.
No.
I told you,
the guys hitting on the models
aren't serious.
Now I'm telling you...
That the guys
who let themselves get drunk
aren't serious,
which means whoever's left
are the bids
that we have in our hands
at the end of the night.
You knew it the whole time,
didn't you?
Who do you think
you're talking to?
Good man.
There's just
one small problem.
What if, by accident,
I happen to be one of the people
that let himself get too drunk?
You just might as well
keep drinking,
'cause if we're not having fun,
what the hell are we doing here?
Yes!
Copy that.
Svetlana...
You know this office isn't
gonna pack itself up, right?
It's not packed
because one of us
has been at work
for the last three hours.
The other one of us
was sleeping off
all the work he did last night.
You mean you're hung over
from all the vodka you drank?
Yeah, that's what I just said.
I never should have
hired you back.
Well, it's too late
to fire me now.
Is it?
Because if you were
worth your salary,
you'd ask how many bids
we're sitting on.
I don't have to ask,
because I've got this.
Guest list was 500,
and half of them
came for the girls.
Half of the other half
don't have the capital,
and 60%
of the rest of them woke up
realizing they don't want
to work in the liquor business.
Take, I don't know, what,
47 off the top
for good measure?
Leaves us with three bids.
- Donna told you, didn't she?
- Probably.
Did she bother telling you
what we're doing now?
She didn't have to,
'cause you're Harvey Specter.
You've got one trick, and you
taught it to me years ago,
so let's go.
You know I have more
than one trick, right?
No, I know you think you do,
but just because you put
on a different costume
doesn't make it
a different trick.
Yeah, I liked you better
when you were drunk.
I liked you better
when I was drunk too.
I don't care what they say.
This is bullshit,
and I'm not gonna get played.
Gentlemen, we're so sorry.
It's my first day.
Evidently,
I booked the conference room
at the same time as Harvey.
Bullshit.
You think we don't know
what's going on here?
You double booked the room
to scare us into overbidding.
You're right.
We should have known
a couple of smart guys like you
would never fall for the banana
in the tailpipe.
We brought you down here
just because you were
the only two bidders
who came in at 100 million,
so now, you have to look
each other in the eye
while you go head-to-head.
So here's what's gonna happen:
You got one chance
to write down your best bid.
Winner takes all,
loser goes home.
We'll be back in 15 minutes,
and we better see
some more zeroes.
What if we collude,
right here?
Stick at 100
and you're shit out of luck?
Which, by the way,
is exactly why
you don't double book
a conference room.
There's only one problem
with that.
When we said you two were the
only ones that came in at 100,
we didn't say there wasn't
someone who put down more.
- Axelrod.
- Bingo.
Second bid came
in 20 minutes ago.
So if you two want to collude,
go right ahead,
but it better be for a hell
of a lot more than 100 million.
- How'd it go?
- That depends.
What was Axelrod's second bid?
200 million.
Well, then it doesn't
really matter how it went,
because whatever
those clowns come up with,
Neil Stillman's walking away
with a boatload of cash.
Speaking of boatloads
of cash...
It's a check
for half a million dollars.
I told you I was serious about
becoming a partner, and I am.
- Donna...
- Harvey, be honest.
You haven't given one thought to
what we talked about yesterday.
- I've been a little busy.
- And you've also been
avoiding the subject.
This way,
you have to take me seriously.
I do take you seriously.
Then walk the hell down
to Louis' office
and tell him I'm a partner.
Donna, I can't just ram
every decision down his throat.
Every decision?
You haven't even told him that
you're stepping
into Jessica's shoes yet.
I'm waiting
for the right time.
And if I were a partner,
I would tell you that
the right time was yesterday.
Donna...
Harvey, you think
I'm asking for charity, I'm not.
I am asking for you
to make official
what I have been doing
for years anyway,
which is giving you advice,
like you need to step
the hell up and tell Louis
that you're in charge,
and right this second, you're
either gonna take that advice,
or you're not,
but it is time
that you recognize me
for what I do.
My brother Thomas is
the clever one.
Teaches at Cambridge.
20 hours a week, summers off.
You're not listening to a word
I'm saying, are you?
- I'm sorry.
- Well, you should be.
I've been told
I'm actually quite delightful.
You are.
I'm just a little distracted.
Halfway through appetizers.
Doesn't bode very well
for how you'll be feeling
when our flambé arrives.
It's not that.
Jessica left the firm
last month.
Everyone assumes
that I'm next in line,
and now I've got Donna telling
me that if I don't step up...
Wait a second, I thought you
told me as of the other morning
that you're now head
of the firm.
I am. I just haven't
told Louis yet,
and Donna won't let it go.
I think this may have
been a mistake.
- What?
- You didn't come to me
to date me, you came to me
because you're in the middle
of another crisis
and you need me
to walk you through it.
That's not true.
Of course you don't think
it's true.
If you did,
you would have called my office
and made an appointment.
I don't need an appointment.
I'm sharing things
about my life.
Last time I checked,
that's what people do on dates.
Yes, it's what they do,
Harvey, but on first dates,
they also try to make
the other person feel special
and listened to.
Paula--
Do you know why it's unethical
for a therapist
to go out with her client,
Harvey?
Yeah, of course I do.
It's because it's natural
for a client
to transfer feelings of desire
onto his therapist
that aren't real.
- I know that.
- What you may not know
is that it's not unnatural
for a therapist
to feel the same way.
You don't think I've had
fantasies about you?
That one day you'd show up
at my office
as I was heading home
for the night,
and I turn around,
and you'd be there.
You wouldn't say a word, but...
You'd take me
in your arms and kiss me, and...
It would actually be the start
of something special.
Well, I have,
which is why
despite my better judgment,
I'm here with you right now.
- So what's the problem?
- The problem is those fantasies
weren't of me being
a therapist to a man
who's still too afraid
to admit that he needs help,
much less take control
of a firm that bears his name.
Thank you for dinner, Harvey.
If you need a session,
call my office.
Unfortunately,
I can't see you anymore,
but I can give you
a recommendation
for someone who can.
- Louis, what can I do--
- Do for me?
You could tell me from now on
if you have a problem with me,
you'll take it up with me
instead of going behind my back.
- What?
- That's right.
You think I don't know the whole
"Rachel should be in charge
of my associates"
bullshit came from you
and not Donna?
You're right.
It was from me.
And I came to you first,
and you bit my head off.
Well, then let me tell you
in a way
that won't harm
your pretty little head,
because I clearly forgot what a
delicate little flower you are.
Those associates are mine,
and the only way
you're ever gonna get them
is if you pry them
from my cold, dead hands.
Donna, unless
it's an emergency--
It is an emergency.
Harvey, I need to know
what you're doing about me.
Donna, right this second
is not the time.
It is the time,
because if somebody doesn't
do something about Louis soon,
this firm is gonna end up being
sued by our own associates.
I don't have the authority
to do anything,
and you don't even know
what I'm talking about.
Okay, Donna.
You win.
You're a partner.
Harvey.
We got a problem.
What is it now?
Take a look.
Where'd you get this?
It doesn't matter
where I got it.
It's out there.
You can't be sure
Neil knew this.
What difference
does that make?
Because if he didn't know,
it's just bad luck.
Harvey, he's the goddamn CEO.
He knew.
He kept it from us,
and he kept it from the guys
buying his company.
- You don't know that.
- Yes, I do.
I also know you still have time
to go stop this sale
from going through.
Are you kidding?
They signed the documents.
It's already gone through.
Money hasn't
changed hands yet,
so you still have time
to stop it.
- Mike--
- Harvey, if you don't
get over there
and find out before--
All right.
I'll handle it.
- And where are you going?
- I need to talk to Louis.
Whatever it is, it's gonna
have to wait until tomorrow,
because if you don't
get over there
before that money changes hands,
you are opening us up
to a shitload of trouble.
Kind of creepy in here
at night, isn't it?
Oh, I don't know.
I find it kind of peaceful.
Then why get rid of it?
And more importantly,
why'd you need the sale
to go through so quickly?
I told you,
I have another opportunity.
And what if I said
the real reason was
you knew you vodka business
was about to be sued
for using
another brand's recipe?
I would say
I did not know that.
- Well, now you do.
- It doesn't change a thing.
Those two dipshits already
signed the agreement.
Neil, this looks a hell of
a lot like you're asking me
to be a party to fraud.
I'm asking you to do your job.
Look out for my interests,
and take me at my word.
If I have reason to believe
that you're lying to me,
which I do--
The only thing you have
reason to believe is that
I will fire you
if you don't do this for me
and then find someone who will,
so this thing is gonna get done
whether you do it or not.
The only thing
that happens if you don't
is that the world will know
what people suspect already:
That you can't fill
Jessica's shoes.
How long do you think
it's gonna take after that
before every one of your clients
starts to leave you?
So you tell me right now,
are you in or not?
- Shit. Oliver.
- What's up, Mike?
How's your new job?
I'm sorry.
I swear I was gonna tell you.
Yeah, I heard,
but I guess when you move on,
you move on, right?
- Come on, it's not like that.
- Bullshit, it's not like that.
You left, Mike,
after everything you said.
Would you please
just let me explain?
I fought for your goddamn job.
I know that, and I will
always be grateful for it,
but I am telling you,
it's better this way, because--
Better for who?
Based on that extra cash
that you had to throw at Nathan?
I'd say it's better for you.
For everybody.
I can still have cases
with the clinic.
You and I can still
work together.
- Lucky me.
- Oliver, the only reason I went
back is that Harvey committed
to doing pro bonos, all right?
Half of my cases,
the kind the clinic does,
only this time,
with the resources
of a big firm behind us.
Oh, really?
What are you working on
right now, Mike?
What?
What's your first case back?
Eminent domain?
Civil rights violation?
Oliver, come on,
it's not that--
Tell me your first case back
isn't carrying water
for some corporate big shot,
and I'll shut my mouth
right now.
Marissa was right.
All you were doing with us
was biding your time.
- What the fu-- is going on?
- What do you mean?
Case is over.
You said you'd move.
I'm just getting
the ball rolling.
I can't work on my own cases
if I don't have my own office.
Listen, Mike.
You let the goddamn sale
go through.
- You don't understand.
- I understand that you said
that you wanted one last case
together before you stepped up,
but you clearly are
not ready to step up,
so I got to get
my pro Bono cases in
before this place
doesn't even exist anymore.
Are you finished,
or do you have a minute to hear
why I let the sale go through?
Oh, no, I don't care.
Mike, I have no proof he knew.
He's Jessica's client.
How's it gonna look
if he tells the world
that we can't handle
his business anymore?
Well, I'll tell you
how it looks right now.
It looks like you're afraid
and you're not in charge.
Okay, you say something
like that to me,
you better get ready for a hit,
because I am doing
the best I can.
No, Harvey,
you're not doing shit.
You're hiding,
'cause you're afraid.
You're afraid to take
responsibility for this firm,
and you won't admit it
to yourself.
I don't have
to listen to this.
Well, you're going to,
'cause way back when,
you cared enough about me
to tell me the same thing
to my face,
and I'm just
returning the favor.
I'm not her, Mike.
I'm not her.
You don't have to be her.
You just have to go back
to being you.
The Harvey I met the day
you hired me,
he would have gone in there
and told Neil Stillman
to go fu-- himself.
So it's up to you.
You can keep hiding out
in Jessica's shadow,
or you get out of it
and start being
Harvey goddamn Specter.
Do you find it peaceful here
in the day too?
If you're here to bring me
my check, then the answer's yes.
I'm here to tell you
that we stopped the sale.
What did you just say?
We're not taking part
in your fraud
so that you can dump
your shitty company.
You son of a bitch, I don't
remember giving you a choice.
Well, you did,
because your exact words were,
"Do it, or you're fired."
Then you're goddamn fired.
You can let us go if you want,
but the second you do,
we're putting out
a press release saying
Pearson Specter Litt
no longer represents clients
we feel are unethical
in their divestiture practices.
You can't do that, that's
attorney-client privilege.
No, it's not, because
we're not gonna name you.
But you can bet your ass
the whole world
is gonna know
who we're talking about.
What do you want from me?
Are you asking me
as my client?
Because I don't give
free legal advice.
Yes, okay.
You're still my attorney.
In that case,
here's what's gonna happen:
You're gonna go into business
with the guys
whose process you stole.
You're gonna quietly give them
10% of your company,
you're gonna triple your price,
and you're gonna have
a very public feud
over whose vodka tastes better.
And then we both profit
from a war
between two brands that have
the exact same product.
Win-win.
Maybe you are
as good as Jessica.
Maybe I am.
Maybe I'm not.
But the thing
we have in common is
we're never gonna be bullied
by any of our clients.
All right, Louis,
I've tried to be reasonable,
but I'm not gonna sit around
and watch this anymore.
As of this moment,
you're no longer
in charge of the associates.
Says you and what army?
I'm sorry,
I didn't catch that.
- I said you can't do that.
- Oh, yes, I can,
because even though Harvey
clearly didn't tell you,
as of last night,
I'm a senior partner.
- You're what?
- That's right.
I gave Harvey a check
for half a million dollars.
I'm a partner now, Louis,
which means your whole
"you're up here
and I'm down here" bullshit,
not anymore.
Partner?
You're not even a lawyer.
Neither are
the chief operating officers
of four
of the top nine firms
in the world.
This is bullshit.
I didn't agree to any of this.
I don't care whether
you agreed to it or not.
You're gonna live with it.
And I don't give a shit
what your supposed title is.
I'm not giving up my associates.
And if you think you're gonna
leave this bathroom
without giving me
the respect I deserve--
I'm not giving up
my associates.
- That's enough.
- Harvey, what the hell
kind of shit did you pull?
Shut up and listen, Louis.
Donna asked for a seat
at the table,
and I gave her one,
because when she worked for me,
she had my back,
and would kill anyone
coming for me,
and when she worked for you,
she did the same exact thing,
not to mention
if she left tomorrow,
this firm would be a pile
of rubble within 15 minutes.
So then give her a raise.
You don't make her
goddamn senior partner.
If Jessica were here, she'd tell
you to do the same exact thing.
Well, Louis,
Jessica isn't here,
but I am.
- Thank you, Harvey.
- Don't thank me yet.
You asked for a vote.
You got it.
But the person who's gonna
decide when that vote is is me,
and I say our first
order of business
is putting out word
that Harvey Specter
is the new managing partner.
Now, you want to vote on that?
Let's do it.
But if it's not unanimous,
we're gonna have a big problem.
No problem here.
What about you, Louis?
You got a problem
with me calling the shots?
No, Harvey.
No problem.
You're managing partner.
Good.
Then I suggest the two of you
get your shit together
before tomorrow,
because right now, I've got
some things to take care of.
I don't want to talk to you
right now, Louis--
I want you to have
the associates.
Whatever you said to Donna,
you were right.
- Louis...
- Rachel, just let me finish
while I'm still able
to get it out.
I know I can be rough on them...
But it's only because
I want to see them
become the best lawyers
they can be.
But I'm not
in the best headspace right now,
and if I keep taking my anger
out on them,
they will not become
great lawyers.
They might not stay
in the law at all, so...
It's better that someone else
takes over for a while,
and I cannot think
of a better person than you.
I'm sorry that I went
behind your back, Louis.
You were right to.
If you had asked me
face-to-face,
I don't even know
what I would have done,
and that--just thinking
about that makes me sick.
Rachel, you're family,
and if I lose you too...
Louis, you're not going
to lose me,
but I think
I know what you may need.
Please don't say vacation.
If someone else mentions
Martha's Vineyard one more time,
I swear to God...
I was gonna say closure.
If you're telling me that
I need to talk to Tara--
Louis, you were gonna
get married.
You were gonna be a father.
That can't all end
over a voicemail.
Treat them well.
- I knew it.
- Knew what?
You don't have the balls
to fill Harvey's office.
Okay, Donna,
just to be clear,
balls do not make the man.
- That's not what Rachel says.
- What does that even mean?
I think we both know
what that means.
Donna, for the record,
my balls
are within normal parameters.
So you just come down here
to give me shit,
or was there maybe
another reason?
What other reason
would I have?
I can't think of a single one.
- Then my work here is done.
- Good.
Because I certainly didn't
come down here to tell you
I remember the first time
you were in this office,
and I never thought
I'd see the day
when I told you
congratulations, Mike.
You deserve it as your own.
- Thanks, Donna.
- You're welcome, Mike.
Are you sure
you don't come with it?
I mean, there is a desk
right there
that literally has
your name on it.
Sorry, I wish I could,
but I actually got
a new office too.
- You did?
- Needed one,
because as of tomorrow,
I am officially
the firm's newest
senior partner.
Holy shit.
Are you serious?
Yes.
And from now on, it's,
"Are you serious, ma'am?"
Have you got that, pretty boy?
My God.
Harvey's created a monster,
hasn't he?
You have no idea.
Donna...
It's about time.
Hey.
I know we haven't spoken,
and we didn't exactly
leave things off well,
but...
I just really need
to see you tonight
if at all possible.
Guess you got some skin
in the game after all.
Sure did, Gretchen.
Sure did.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net