Previous on "Suits"...
I put Gallo away
for racketeering.
But that's not what
he really did.
What are you talking about?
We had him for conspiracy
to commit murder,
and the police let the tape
of that bastard admitting
that he did it
out of the chain of custody
for 20 minutes.
You had an alibi witness,
and your public defender
let her get away?
That's what I've been saying!
I didn't have
an alibi witness.
I had a no-show who
vanished into thin air.
Well, you could've
asked for postponement
to have time to find her.
And I would have,
except for one thing:
when I pressed her as to what
the two of them were doing
at the time of those murders,
she admitted they
were both on meth.
Gallo's filing came back,
and it needs to be filed by
his attorney of record.
You want me to represent
that animal?
Kind of funny, isn't it?
You fighting to get me out
when you fought so hard
to put me away.
It makes me sick
to my stomach,
but you're gonna give me
something in return.
Not only are you gonna
keep your hands off Mike,
you're gonna be his
personal protector in here.
You kept my wife
out of prison.
As far as I'm concerned,
that makes us square.
Harvey and Mike did it,
which means Mike's coming home.
Oh, my God.
Joshua called.
He's coming to town tomorrow.
Are you gonna
break up with him?
I don't know.
[dramatic music]
I really appreciate
you doing this.
If you weren't with me,
I can't imagine how I'd handle
whether or not Tara is
breaking up with Joshua.
Joshua--what is he?
Lord of the Kingdom
of Dicken-stein,
reigning over his subjects from
high atop Douche Mountain?
Anyway, thanks for being here.
Aside from Tara, you're the most
important woman
in my entire life.
Oh, my God, Louis.
Mudding is...
amazing.
I actually just fell asleep
for the last half hour.
Goddamn it, Donna.
I didn't bring you here
so you could fall asleep
while I'm pouring my heart out.
You're the most selfish
woman I ever met.
I thought you just told me
I was the most important
non-Tara woman in your life.
Wait a second.
I thought you just fell asleep.
And for the last
thirty seconds,
have you been mad at me
or upset about Joshua?
Holy shit, you're a genius.
Which is why when we get
back to the office,
you're reconciling everyone's
billings for the last six weeks.
Oh, Donna, that is
the worst form of torture
I can go through.
No, Louis, the worst
form of torture
is what you'll do if you
don't have something
to occupy your mind.
Oh, my God, you're right.
I don't care what the cost
or that I'm entirely naked
underneath this mud.
I'm getting us another hour.
Louis, you are not moving
another centimeter
until Renaldo comes back in here
and puts that privacy curtain
back up.
[dramatic music]
Oh, look who's here.
I'm not supposed to get out
till this afternoon,
but leave it to you to--
Mike, sit down.
Okay.
What's going on?
Cahill called and said there
was a problem with your release.
It's not a big deal, but it's
just gonna take a little longer.
- How much longer?
- A few days.
Harvey, I informed on someone.
If word gets out about that--
You think I don't know that?
But he pulled your deal
then reinstated it.
It's gonna take a little time.
Well, what the hell am I
supposed to do in the meantime?
Sit tight, and keep
your wits about you.
You made it this long.
You can make it a few more days.
Does Rachel know about this?
Look, she didn't know it was
gonna take this long
in the first place,
and I didn't see the need
to tell her now.
Do me a favor, and let's
keep it that way.
♪ ♪
Rachel, good morning.
I was looking for you before.
I wanted to say congratulations
on getting Mike out.
I appreciate that.
But we have some
other good news.
We may be on our way to getting
Leonard Bailey out too.
Did you figure out a way
to reopen the trial?
I did.
Rachel, this is good
in theory,
but there's no precedent.
Yes, there is.
Turner versus
the State of Michigan.
How the hell did
you find that?
It turns out being
a paralegal for so long
was a blessing in disguise,
because nobody is better
at research than me.
Great. Write up a declaration,
and get it to me
as soon as you're done.
And I'll get this thing rolling.
Jessica, I thought I'd
be the one to do it.
Rachel, you're not
a lawyer yet.
I don't need to be.
She's his public defender.
She'll do this for us.
Listen to me--sometimes things
don't go exactly as planned.
And nobody is better
at research than you,
but nobody is better at dropping
the hammer than me.
Listen to me, I'm gonna ask
you a question,
and I need to know the truth.
You know about this Cahill shit?
What Cahill shit?
Apparently Sutter wasn't
enough for that asshole,
because he's been seizing
our assets left and right.
You really think they
were gonna let her
keep direct proceeds
from insider trading?
I'm not talking
about direct proceeds.
I'm talking about
everything we have.
- What?
- Yeah,
including money she earned
before she ever got wrapped up
in that bullshit.
They can't do that.
Well, they're doing it.
And I don't care whether
you do something about it
from in here or when
you get out there,
but you're the one who convinced
us to take this deal, Mike,
so you better damn well
be the one to stop it.
♪ Suits 6x09 ♪
The Hand That Feeds
Original Air Date on September 7, 2
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
Hey, Counselor.
You didn't forget about me,
did you?
Your hearing's
tomorrow at 2:00.
I sent you the paperwork.
Right under the wire.
Cutting it close, huh?
I said I'd get it done,
and it's done, Gallo.
Now I'm leaving.
So soon?
I thought you might want
to meet and chat strategy.
My strategy is for you to get
your parole tomorrow
and then burn your existence
from my brain.
I don't think I like the way
you just spoke
You better come through.
I'll come through, Gallo,
but you better remember
your part of the deal.
What, protecting Mike?
What does Mike need protecting
for if I'm cool with him?
Save your bullshit.
I know you know
Mike was informing.
Yeah, I also know William
Sutter's going away,
which means Mike's getting out.
Well, he's not out yet,
so while you're both
still in there,
you don't take your
eyes off him.
I'm nothing if not
a man of my word.
Oh, and Harvey,
I don't want to stand
of the parole board
wearing this,
so bring me something
nice to wear.
I was a 38 slim
when I came in.
Now I'm more like a 40 reg.
I'll leave it up to you;
you're the dandy.
♪ ♪
This is Sean Cahill.
Well, Sean, this is Mike Ross.
What can I do for you, Mike?
You can tell me why the hell
you're going after
Jill Miller's assets.
I'm sorry, I wasn't aware
you were her accountant.
Well, if you don't back off,
I'm about to become
her goddamn lawyer.
- Excuse me?
- That wasn't part of her deal.
No, it wasn't, but I'm not
gonna let her keep
her money she made
committing a crime.
You're not just taking money
she made from a crime.
You're taking
the salary she made
from working at that company
for years.
Listen, that woman got out
of going to prison.
But every time they took
a position,
they sold the other side
to people who lost everything.
And I'll be damned if I
let her live high on the hog
while working people's
lives were ruined.
Sean, I know about
your mother and Spain.
But Jill Miller didn't
take her money.
I don't care.
I have the power to do this.
And this conversation is over.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
Jessica Pierson.
My secretary should've told you
I'm not taking new clients.
I take it you know
why I'm here.
I tried to be polite when your
protégé accused me
of not doing my job
with Leonard Bailey.
But I'm not gonna be told by
someone who harbored a fraud
what a bad lawyer I am.
I don't think you're
a bad lawyer, Georgina.
I think you're a good lawyer
that made a mistake.
And I'm here to give you
a chance to fix it.
And how's that?
Leonard Bailey's
alibi witness is dead.
That doesn't mean
her testimony is.
You want me to testify
to what she told me?
That would be hearsay.
It would be if she were alive.
But now that she's dead...
She's an unavailable
declarant.
Like I said,
you are a good lawyer.
And I'm not pretending I let
a solid witness disappear
when that girl was a junkie
and her story was
inconsistent at best.
And it still should've been
presented to a jury,
which is what we're
trying to fix.
The only thing you're trying
to fix is your reputation.
And you're not doing it
by smearing mine.
Georgina, a man's life
is on the line.
And I did my best
to defend it,
but I have no obligation
to do it again.
That's where you're wrong.
My protégé took the liberty of
drawing up a sworn affidavit
which states Maria Gomez
told you
Leonard Bailey couldn't have
murdered that couple
because he was with
her at the time.
Now you can either sign it,
or you lie under oath
that this isn't true.
And believe you me, you do not
want to be on that stand
lying to a jury
and have to face me.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Donna, cancel all
my meetings tomorrow,
and notify the parole board
that Gallo's ready.
- Harvey--
- I don't want to hear it.
Listen to me.
I was there with you
when you put him away,
and I wouldn't be able
to live with myself
if I didn't remind you what you
said about him at the time.
I don't need reminding.
You said he was a sociopath
who took pleasure
from hurting people.
Donna, I don't have a choice.
That was before you knew
that Mike was getting out.
If you just string him along
for a couple more hours--
Mike's not getting out today.
What?
Cahill called me.
The deal's gonna take a few
more days to go through.
And if Gallo even thinks that
I'm stringing him along,
Mike may never get out
of there at all.
I'll clear your schedule.
Hey, I need to talk to you.
Before you do, I just
want to say
I didn't mean to put it
all on you earlier.
No, that doesn't matter now.
Listen.
You said that when
you got arrested,
you turned down a deal
to turn on Sutter.
I need to know exactly
what they said.
I don't understand what
that has to do with Jill.
It doesn't.
It has to do with the fact that
I'm trying to get
you out of here.
What?
I might not be able
to do anything
about the money,
but maybe what I can do
is make it so that you
can be with your family.
No.
- What do you mean, no?
- No.
They're already going
after our money.
I don't want to do anything
that's gonna mess
with Jill's deal.
Listen to me.
That deal is as solid as a rock.
I wrote it myself;
they can't take it away from her
any more than they can take
my deal away from me.
But you need to tell me exactly
what Cahill said to you
when he told you
to turn on Sutter.
Nothing.
He never said anything to me.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you
I've never spoken
to Sean Cahill in my life.
♪ ♪
All right, I'm here.
But I gave you seven days
to find that witness,
and then you went
behind my back,
so you better have a good reason
why you're in here
asking to reopen this case.
We do, Your Honor.
We found Leonard Bailey's alibi.
What they found is
nothing but hearsay.
What is he talking about?
He's talking about the fact
that our eyewitness
died three years ago,
and Mr. Bailey's
original attorney
is going to testify
on her behalf
under the Turner v. Michigan
exception to the hearsay rule.
That exception involved
a written statement.
It is a written statement,
and we have it right here.
That is not
a written statement.
That is a bullshit affidavit she
cobbled together this morning.
What did you just
accuse her of?
I'm sorry, Your Honor, but I
find it decidedly convenient
that they don't have
the witness statement
written down on a notebook
or a scrap of paper
from the same decade
that it happened.
Well, we happen to find it
decidedly inconvenient.
And Georgina Casey didn't
write it down at the time
because she didn't do
an adequate job
representing her client.
Are you now saying that this
case needs to be reopened
based on Leonard Bailey having
inadequate representation?
Because that is a serious
allegation to make
about a fellow attorney.
That wasn't our plan.
But if that's what it takes
to give this man a chance
to prove his innocence,
then it sure as hell
is our plan now.
This is ridiculous.
It may sound ridiculous,
but if they were able to get
a successful attorney to admit
to a huge blunder,
then I'm ruling that this case
should be reopened after all.
♪ ♪
Cameron, what are
you doing here?
You know what I'm doing here.
Are you out of your goddamn mind
representing Frank Gallo?
- You don't understand.
- I understand plenty.
- No, listen to me.
- No, you listen to me.
That guy was a murdering
piece of shit
who should've been
put away for life,
and now you're trying
to get him out?
He's in there with Mike Ross.
I don't care.
Well, I do, because
like you just said,
he is a murdering piece of shit.
But what you don't know is,
I made a deal with him,
and I'm not gonna break it.
- Then I will.
- It's not up to you.
Well, it will be
when I play this for
the parole board.
What is that?
It's the tape we had
of him admitting
that he murdered that man
that you shit the bed with
and got excluded from evidence.
I didn't shit the bed with
anything, and you know it.
You try to bring that bullshit
to his hearing,
I'll march you out of there
before you get to hit play,
'cause it wasn't
admissible in court,
and it's not admissible there.
You tell yourself
whatever you want,
but I'm gonna do whatever
I need to do
to keep that bastard
behind bars.
Talk to you a second?
Of course.
You were right.
The whole time I was working,
I didn't worry about what
Tara was doing with...
him, which meant the first
time in my life,
I finished the billables
in record time.
And now you're
afraid to go home.
I can't help wondering
what's happening.
Louis, have you ever
heard of a jack story?
- No.
- Well, it's time you did.
A man gets a flat tire
on a country road.
He sees a house in the distance.
He walks up to the house,
and along the way,
he starts thinking, "What if
they don't have a jack?
"What if they have a jack,
"but they want to charge me
for it, and if they do,
"how much would they charge?
$100, $200, $1,000?"
- That's bullshit.
- Exactly.
So by the time the man
gets to the house,
rings the bell, and they
answer the door,
he tells them, "You know what?
Keep your goddamn jack."
- That's brilliant.
- So you get my point.
No.
Louis, you have no idea
what's going on in Tara's mind,
so the best thing you can do
is trust her.
Because if you don't,
I'm telling you,
you're gonna do something
that you'll regret
for the rest of your life.
All right, Donna.
I'll wait for Tara to call.
Okay.
Can I help you?
Help me what, rat?
What did you just say?
I said you ratted
on your own roommate.
Word's spreading, and there's
going to come a time when
you need my protection,
and I won't be there.
Hey, what's going on here?
Nothing.
It's not nothing.
You were threatening him.
You ever do it again
without my say so,
you'll regret the day
you met me.
Sorry, Frank.
Don't worry about it, kid.
I got your back.
No, you don't.
Everyone knows guards
are the last one
to find out anything.
So if word were spreading,
I wouldn't be finding out
about it from him.
He just did that because
you told him to,
because you want to remind me
of what's gonna happen
if Harvey lets you down.
Well, then, I guess you got
the message loud and clear.
Good luck to me on my
hearing tomorrow.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Did you do what
I asked you to do?
- I did.
- You better.
Because if you don't sound
like a human being,
you're gonna be in here
for another two years.
The hell is Cameron Dennis
doing here?
You let me worry about him.
Mr. Specter, please proceed.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the board,
Mr. Gallo has served 12 years
as an exemplary inmate.
We ask that you release him so
he can continue to live his life
outside these walls.
But before you decide on that,
we think it's best if you
hear from him in his own words.
You son of a bitch,
what the hell is this?
It's an action on behalf
of my client, Kevin Miller.
You abused your power when you
went after him last year.
I didn't abuse shit.
I beg to differ.
'Cause not only does Kevin
live in New Jersey,
but his accident was there too,
were means you were outside
of your jurisdiction.
You better rescind this suit,
because if they come after me--
They're not gonna come after
you, Sean, because I haven't
filed it yet.
And I'm not going to, as long as
you agree to get Kevin out.
[laughing] Are you crazy?
I'm not gonna do that.
Why not?
'Cause I'm not gonna
get held hostage
by the likes of you.
I guess what I'm
trying to say is,
I'm not denying
the person I was
or the things I did,
because I did those things.
If I could go back
and change what I did,
I would, but I can't.
What I can do is swear to you
that I will never go back
to being that person again.
You crossed the line when
you took Jill's money.
No, Mike, I didn't,
but I'm about to cross it now.
You want to see abuse of power?
Your deal is gone.
If there are no
other statements--
Matter of fact, I would, uh,
like to say a few words.
- And you are?
- Cameron Dennis.
I was the district attorney at
the time of Mr. Gallo's trial.
Mr. Chairman, Mr. Dennis
is about to play a tape
from the original trial.
It wasn't admissible then,
and it's not admissible now.
No, Harvey, I'm going
to read the transcript
of your own words from
Mr. Gallo's sentencing hearing.
"Frank Gallo is the scum
of the Earth.
"He's a sociopath
who has no remorse
"for the things he's done,
and he is an animal
who deserves to be locked up for
the rest of his miserable life."
I gave you immunity
for crimes you committed
before you got caught.
But your plea agreement says
you'll never practice law again
without a license.
You've been practicing
law in here,
which means that's a crime
that happened after
you got caught.
Bullshit.
Kevin and Jill both know
that I'm not a lawyer.
You know that
and I know that,
but if you fight it,
I will argue it in court
for the next two years.
And if you don't
drop this thing, you'll be lucky
if they let you out a day before
you were supposed
to get out anyway.
Mr. Chairman,
I'm telling you,
Frank Gallo has changed.
And I'm telling the board
he hasn't changed.
He's just trying
to blackmail you.
That's a lie.
Then take the stand
and swear it's not true.
That's enough.
Mr. Specter, this is a parole
hearing, not a court of law,
but if there's any truth
to what he's saying,
we need to know.
It's not true.
Unfortunately, this body
doesn't have the authority
to swear you in,
but I'm going to make sure
that we will tomorrow.
I'd like you to think
long and hard about
what you're gonna say then,
because you'll be
saying it under oath.
Mike, I need to tell you
what just happened.
I need to tell you
what happened first.
Abuse of power?
Are you nuts?
It's the only play I have.
Your only play is
to walk out of here
when your release comes through,
not threaten the guy
who made that happen.
Listen to me.
Cahill is seizing
their personal assets.
Yeah, I don't care if he
takes their house apart
brick by brick.
Harvey, Kevin wouldn't even
be in here in the first place
if it weren't for Cahill.
No, Mike, Kevin wouldn't
be here if he had chosen
to roll over on Sutter
in the first place.
And it's a good thing he didn't,
because you'd be stuck in here
with Gallo
for the next two years.
I don't care about Gallo.
Well, you should,
because he's not out yet,
and if it's up
to Cameron Dennis,
he's not getting out.
What?
Cameron got wind that I'm
trying to get Gallo parole.
And now I got to think
of something
or perjure myself tomorrow,
or he's gonna end up
right back in here.
Well, that's even more reason
why we can't leave Kevin behind.
If Gallo doesn't get out
and I do,
the first person he's gonna
go after is Kevin.
And I didn't sign on
to get someone killed.
No, you signed on
to get yourself out.
Now if you don't drop this suit,
Cahill's gonna threaten
to pull your deal.
[tense music]
What?
He already did.
Then why are we still
having this conversation?
'Cause like I said,
this is the only card
I have left to play.
So if you want me
to drop this,
you get Cahill to do the right
thing and get Kevin out.
♪ ♪
I have to say, for someone
who practices corporate law,
you know your way around
an appeals court.
Thank you, but you're not here
to offer me a job
as a prosecutor, you're here
to offer Leonard Bailey a deal.
So let's get to it.
Let's face it.
You may have that affidavit
from his original attorney,
but you have no DNA, no alibi,
and I'm guess not a hell
of a lot else.
What I have, Larry, is a case
that will embarrass
you personally
every day it drags on,
because you were the one that
tried it in the first place.
So give me a number, so I can
get on with my day.
Bailey does ten more years,
and we all go home.
When you say ten,
you mean nine,
and we both know I can
get you down to seven,
so let's just say five.
But I'll tell you what.
You let my client
walk right now,
and you get your dream.
We don't open this case at all.
No way.
Seven years,
take it or leave it.
Offer's good 24 hours.
No, this is unacceptable.
Well, it's the best
you're gonna do.
No, the best
I'm going to do
is get my client exonerated
from a crime he didn't commit
and make you look like a fool.
Then bring it on.
But you're legally obligated to
present my offer to your client.
And remind him,
if he loses again,
in 60 days his life is over.
♪ ♪
Thanks, Bill.
Sean, what's going on
with Mike's deal?
Excuse me?
Why hasn't it
come through yet?
Oh, there must've been
a mix-up in the paperwork.
Bullshit.
You're holding it up because
he's threatening to sue you.
Oh, you're right.
I am.
And if doesn't drop this thing
and agree to walk away,
I'm gonna dump his
deal altogether.
Sean, let his
deal go through.
Once he gets out, he's not gonna
follow through on this thing.
"Oh, Sean, put down your gun.
"I promise Mike'll
put his down too.
"And you can trust
the both of us,
'cause neither of us has ever
lied to you before."
If you didn't trust us,
you never would've come to me
in the first place.
If I had known this is how
it was going to end,
I never would have.
You son of a bitch.
We got you every goddamn
thing you wanted.
I held up my end
of the bargain,
not to mention the fact I gave
immunity to Jill Miller
when I didn't have to.
Bullshit you didn't have to.
She made your case,
and Mike risked his life
to get her for you.
You had no problem asking me
to risk everything
to get that kid out,
and I did it.
And now that ungrateful
son of a bitch
wants to bite the hand
that feeds him,
I'm gonna take away his dinner
and show him who his master is.
Sean, please.
Gallo might not get out,
and Mike's gonna be
stuck in there with him.
Well, all the more reason
he should put down his gun
and walk out that f---ing door.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Jessica, come in.
I'm sorry to drop by
unannounced,
but I need to talk to you.
No, no, I'm sorry that I had
to leave a little bit early.
I just wanted to get the place
ready for when Mike gets home.
Then I won't take up
much of your time.
They offered Leonard Bailey
a deal.
- How long?
- Seven years.
But I can probably get them
down to five.
Five more years for a crime
he didn't commit
doesn't seem really fair.
And losing a retrial
and dying in prison
doesn't seem fair either.
- But we're not gonna lose.
- That's not true.
There's a good chance we will.
- Jessica--
- Rachel.
Juries are unpredictable.
Even if they'd been told
to disregard something,
they know he was
convicted before.
This is a chance at getting
his life back.
What kind of life
are we talking about?
He's still going to be seen
as a murderer
even by the closest thing
he has to a mother.
I'm not gonna let him die
for a crime he didn't commit.
I don't want to let him
die either.
I want to fight
to get him out.
And I don't think you've been
practicing law long enough
to make that call.
Rachel, this is a win for him.
So get your mind right
so that we can walk
into that prison
on the same page.
Harvey, unless you're here
to tell me you've
come to your senses
about this animal,
this is gonna be
a short conversation.
I came here to show you this.
What is this?
It's a three-year
surveillance agreement
with the best detective
agency in the state.
And what makes you think
just because you follow him,
it's gonna stop him
from committing crimes?
Cameron, I can't have him
in there with Mike.
Well, from what I heard,
Mike's getting out.
It's not that simple.
What do you mean,
it's not that simple?
[sighs]
The SEC pulled some shady shit
with Mike's cellmate,
the same guy that helped get
Mike out in the first place.
Now Mike's been playing
chicken with them,
and if he doesn't drop it,
they're not gonna let him out.
Let me get this straight.
You want me to perjure myself
so you can put this
monster on the street
because your sidekick wants
to fight The Man?
Don't play that shit with me.
You've been crossing
lines for years,
and you didn't lose
a minute's sleep over it.
You're damn right I didn't,
because I was doing it
to put guys like Gallo away,
not let them wander
around at night
hoping some fat guy
with a Polaroid
is gonna keep him from
murdering somebody else.
And what if that person he
was gonna be murdering was me?
Because Mike is to me
what I used to be to you.
Then convince him
to do the right thing
like you tried to do
once with me.
Because, Harvey, you know what
you're doing with Gallo
is wrong.
♪ ♪
Hey.
You're not gonna believe this,
but I got Rachel on
the phone for you.
- What?
- Yeah.
She had my number
from the other night,
and she wants to talk to you.
Thanks.
And Mike, if you're staying
in here for me,
don't do it.
Hey. God, I can't
wait to see you.
I can't wait
to see you either.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I, um--I just
wanted to talk to you
about my death row client.
How can I help?
They offered us a deal
for him to get out
in five years,
and Jessica wants to take it.
But I want to fight for him.
Let me guess, she wants
to present a united front.
She does.
Well, I'm not sure
how I can help you
other than to tell you
to follow your gut.
You can help me understand
what it's like to be in prison.
♪ ♪
You better be convincing
out there.
Gallo, I'm about
to sell my soul
to make us even,
so sit down, shut up,
and make sure that
after today, I never
see your face again.
Mr. Specter.
Are you ready to be sworn in?
Ladies and gentlemen
of the board,
before Mr. Specter testifies,
I'd like to present Michael Ross
as a witness on behalf
of the state.
Mr. Chairman, this hearing
was called so that I could--
You'll get your chance,
Mr. Specter.
I'd like to hear what
the young man has to say.
I can have him sworn in.
That won't be necessary.
Mr. Ross, you are an inmate
here at Danbury,
is that correct?
Yes, I'm serving
a two-year sentence
for practicing law
without a license.
And what firm did you work at?
I worked for Mr. Specter.
Are you aware that Mr. Specter
originally prosecuted
Frank Gallo?
Yes, I am.
And who made you
aware of it?
Frank Gallo did.
He just mentioned
something in passing?
No.
No, on my first night here,
Mr. Gallo bribed a guard
so that he could
get into my cell,
and then he pretended
to be my roommate.
And after getting
me to trust him,
he told me that he had been
trying to get revenge
on Harvey Specter since the day
he'd been put away.
Then he told me that now
he was gonna get revenge
on Harvey by coming after me.
Was it clear to you what he
meant by "coming after you"?
He said he would kill me.
In fact, he tried to shiv me
the second night,
but a guard stopped him.
Just one more question.
Was Mr. Specter aware
of these threats?
Of course he was.
Why else do you think he's been
trying to get Gallo parole?
[tense music]
Thank you, Mr. Ross.
♪ ♪
Mr. Specter, are you prepared
to refute this testimony
under oath?
No, Your Honor.
I'm not.
We'll take
a five-minute recess.
You did this.
You were in on it with him
the whole time.
You're right. I did.
So you come after me,
not him.
I'm coming after both of you,
but I'm coming after him sooner.
Hey, you can't hide from me.
Oh, I don't need
to hide from you,
'cause it turns out
I'm getting out today.
And there's nothing
you can do about it.
♪ ♪
Five years is still
a long time.
Yes, it is.
But then you walk out
of here a free man.
A free man, but not
an innocent one.
You're still innocent,
Leonard,
whether the world sees
it that way or not.
But if the world thinks
I'm a convicted murderer,
then I might as well
die in here,
because there's not gonna be
a life out there for me anyway.
No one said it was
going to be easy.
But there's no point
in dying for a crime
you didn't commit.
I don't think
you understand.
I'm not doing this
just to stay alive.
I'm doing this so one day
I can knock on my kid's door,
and they'll know their father
is an innocent man.
If I take this deal,
that's never gonna happen.
If you don't take it,
it may never happen either.
You're pretty quiet.
What do you think?
I--I think
that Jessica
has a lot more experience
than I do.
That's not what I asked you.
I want to know what
you think I should do.
Leonard, the odds
of you getting out--
I said I want to know
what she thinks.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
I think you should fight.
Then that's what
I'm going to do.
Goddamn it, I said we need
to be on the same page.
He asked me what I thought.
I'm not gonna lie to him.
I never would've thought
Robert Zane's daughter
would be so naive.
Naive?
I was actually
starting to believe
that you cared about this case,
but the only thing
that you care about
is putting it to bed
as quickly as possible.
How dare you?
Playing the odds isn't
the same as not caring.
Maybe not, but Jessica, I have
watched you my whole career,
and this is the first time
that you've ever
backed away from a fight.
That's because you've never
seen me fight
when someone's life
is on the line.
- You--
- That's right.
I was in a situation like this
once before.
I did what you want me
to do now.
We lost, and it ripped me
to shreds.
So when I tell you I have a lot
more experience than you,
believe it.
Jessica, I'm sorry...
that you lost a case
like this before.
But the way to help Leonard
is not to convince him
to take some deal that
he can't live with.
It is to fight to give him
something worth living for.
♪ ♪
What the hell did you do?
I did what I said I'd do.
I kept that animal
behind bars.
I'm talking about Mike.
You cut a deal with him,
didn't you?
No, Harvey, he cut
a deal with me.
What are you talking about?
After you told him I was
involved with this thing,
he called me and asked if I
could do something
about his friend Kevin.
I said I'd look into it,
but he'd have to do
something for me.
And so you made some
bullshit promise with him
in exchange for doing that.
It wasn't bullshit.
I don't work for
the SEC, Harvey.
I put away real criminals.
And the person who put away
Kevin Miller
knows that it's worth it to let
a drunk driver out,
as long as it means
keeping a murderer in.
And to hell with
what happens to Mike.
Hey, he went in there
with his eyes wide open,
and Gallo can't do anything
to him anyway,
because he's getting
out tonight.
Don't you get it?
Mike's not gonna
be safe tonight
or any other night,
because Gallo can get to him
whether he's behind bars or not.
Well, like I said, Harvey,
he knew what he
was getting into,
and he came to me.
♪ ♪
Hey, where you been all day?
Been doing what I
said I was gonna do.
I'm getting you out.
You're kidding.
Do I look like I'm kidding?
So take that phone of yours,
call Jill,
and tell her you're
coming home--
tonight.
I don't believe it.
You really did that for me?
I did.
What about you?
I'm getting out with you.
Hm.
What?
I just can't believe I'm gonna
be tucking my kids
into bed tonight.
I can't believe I'm
gonna see Rachel.
I can't thank you
enough, Mike.
[knock at door]
All right, let's go.
It's about time.
Not you, Ross.
Just Miller.
What? What are you
talking about?
I'm getting out too.
I'm following orders, and my
orders are to bring him out.
Not you.
You did this.
I didn't do shit.
But I sure as hell am gonna
take advantage of it.
[suspenseful music]
I'm not leaving without Mike.
Yeah, you are.
And I don't care if I
have to drag your ass
out of here myself.
You're leaving right now.
Harvey, good, you're here.
What the hell's going on?
You said you'd
reinstate the deal
if Mike dropped his suit.
- And I did.
- Bullshit.
You pulled his deal, and now
he's in there all alone.
Now if you don't
pick up the phone--
Harvey, I didn't
pull anything.
- What?
- Mike called me.
He told me to hold off
his paperwork
until tomorrow morning.
Why the hell would
he do that, Sean?
Because he has a plan,
and he didn't want you to know.
I don't care what his plan is.
You--
Listen, he doesn't want you
to know, because he didn't
want you to stop it,
and now that you can't,
he's gonna need our help
to bring it home.
♪ ♪
[door opens]
Thanks, Jimbo.
Why don't you go ahead
and give me and Mike here
a little privacy?
What do you want, Gallo?
That's a stupid question
after what you pulled
at my parole hearing.
- You didn't deserve to get out.
- Neither did you.
And now you're not gonna.
[scoffs] What, you're gonna
kill me in this cell?
There are guards out there.
It just doesn't sink in
for you, does it?
Those guards out there
work for me.
See, Mike, I wasn't gonna let
what happened last time
happen this time.
No one's gonna come run
helping you at the last second,
because they're all locked up
tight in their bunks.
And irony of ironies,
because of some prisoners'
rights lawsuit way back when,
there are no cameras in cells.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
No, the time for
waiting is done.
[both grunting]
No, no, no, no, no.
I meant, don't you want to hear
about the camera that's in here?
- Bullshit.
- Smile, you son of a bitch.
No!
You did not keep yourself
in here just to do this.
Yeah, Frank, I did.
And now all those guards
that aren't in your pocket--
they're watching this right now.
And it's 60 feet from that
guard station to this cell,
so if I calculated correctly,
they've got Jimbo in cuffs,
and they're gonna be opening
that door right now.
Drop that knife
and step back, Gallo.
Oh, you piece of shit!
Doesn't change anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'll see about that.
♪ ♪
[exhales sharply]
[chuckling]
Louis?
Tara.
I've never seen how beautiful
it is in here at night.
Beautiful.
I want to tell you
what happened.
Please.
The reason Joshua came to town
is that I told him about you--
about us.
So did you break up with him?
Louis, he asked me
to marry him.
And what'd you say?
I told him...
I couldn't marry him
while I felt this way
about another man.
So where does that leave us?
I hope it leaves us
where you want us to be.
[dramatic music]
It does.
It absolutely does.
♪ ♪
You here to bring me
bread and water?
If it was up to me,
I'd let you starve.
Let me guess: you're here
to tell me how much time
they're tacking onto
my sentence.
Well, it doesn't
matter how much.
'Cause I'm gonna get to him,
and I'm gonna get to you.
Sorry, Frank, but you're not
getting anything
tacked onto your sentence.
Your parting gift is going back
to the maximum security hellhole
you came from.
No way.
You don't have the power
to make that happen.
You're right, I don't.
But my friend at the SEC
sure does.
Why are you so upset, Frank?
Does it have anything
to do with the fact
that every inmate in there
knows that you're an informant,
and you'll be lucky to make it
through your first night?
You think I'm afraid?
I think you're shitting
in your pants right now,
which is why I think
you'll be interested
in what's behind
door number two.
You stay here at Danbury,
you do five more years,
and if Mike so much as gets
a pebble in his shoe,
you go back to door number one.
I'll take that hatred
in your face as a yes,
'cause it's the same
look you had
the last time I put you away.
♪ ♪
What are you doing here?
Where's Rachel?
I'm just here to tell you
you're about to get a visitor.
You convinced my aunt
to come see me?
No, I couldn't convince her.
But I was able to track down
your daughter.
What?
You heard right.
Maya's right outside.
[panting]]
I'm gonna need a moment.
Of course.
I know you only did this so
she'll tell me to take the deal,
but thank you.
Leonard, she doesn't even
know about the deal.
Then what'd you tell her
to get her to come?
I told her we found new
evidence that her father
is an innocent man.
And she should hear it from you
before we go to court
to prove it.
So you do think I'm
doing the right thing?
Honestly, I don't know if you
are or you're not.
But what I do know is, when you
care about someone,
you have their back either way.
[uplifting music]
Hi, Daddy.
Hey, sweetheart.
♪ ♪
Did it work?
It worked.
[laughing]
We did it.
We did.
♪ ♪
Come on, let's get out of here.
Oh, one more thing.
Someone couldn't wait
for you to get home.
♪ ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man