Previously on
"Suits"
I'm here to tell you you're
backing the hell off my firm.
You got to sign something
saying that I had nothing to do
with this.
- I already did.
- It's on you now.
You want to see a copy
of the pictures
- your fiancée sent me?
- She didn't send you anything.
I made copies, one for each
guy in the joint.
Ah!
Happy anniversary.
It's so nice to be with a man
who's so thoughtful
after spending all day
with a man who doesn't even
know what the word means.
Talking about Harvey.
If you can't even separate
yourself from him
when he's asking you to leave
a job that you love,
makes me wonder if it's really
the job you love after all.
I was thinking maybe
some of that money
might go to your daughter.
I know you don't talk to her.
If you're playing with me
on this thing...
I'm not playing you, Frank.
What the hell are you doing
with Frank Gallo?
Does Rachel know about this?
- No.
- And you better hope
Gallo doesn't leave her
a message
the same way he left me one.
Alex has a gun to his head.
I have a way out of it,
but there's gonna be
some consequences for Mike.
Harvey, is there any other way
out of this mess?
If there were, I wouldn't be
standing here.
You think signing
Reform Corps.
Is gonna make this go away,
they have something on him.
Why don't you take the night
and decide
if you trust me enough to keep
working here or not.
The guard gave me a letter,
and that guard was murdered
by an inmate.
- You covered up a murder?
- They set me up.
I'm not asking you to let it go;
I'm telling you what would
happen if you don't.
♪♪
- I'm sorry, who's this?
- I get it.
I haven't returned your calls
for a few days.
- Now that you mention it...
- Listen, I'm sorry.
I've been totally under
the gun at the office,
but I think we're
out of the woods.
Then how about
you make it up to me
by letting me take you
out to dinner?
Thursday night.
Let me get this straight.
I get caught up with work
and my punishment is
you taking me out.
I'm British, Harvey.
We do things differently
across the pond.
Then I guess I'll
see you Thursday.
I guess you will.
Good night, Harvey.
Good night, Paula.
♪♪
- Hello?
- Mark, hi.
It's Donna Paulson.
Donna.
Wow. It's, uh...
Good to hear from you.
It's been a long time.
Yeah. I was, um...
I was just thinking about you
and I...
decided
to give you a call.
I'm... I'm glad you did.
You know,
I think about you
from time to time, too.
- This is weird.
- Oh, I don't know.
Ex-girlfriend calling,
out of the blue, late night.
- I think I've seen weirder.
- Oh, have you.
Well, nothing I can think of
this second,
but I'm sure I have.
Well, while you're
thinking about it,
why don't you
check your calendar
and... see if you can squeeze me
in for lunch sometime soon.
I don't have to
check my calendar.
I'm pretty sure I can
squeeze you in any time.
- Then how's tomorrow?
- Tomorrow sounds good.
The, uh, place with the thing
by the thing?
The place with the thing
by the thing sounds good.
See you there.
♪♪
What are you doing here?
I told you to take the night.
I don't need
to take the night.
I need to talk to you
right now.
If you're here to tell me
to drop Reform Corp.,
- you've wasted a trip...
- I'm not here for that, Harvey.
Alex told me everything.
♪♪ Dramatic music...
Prove it.
♪♪
I swear to God, if you're gonna
use this against him...
I don't wanna use
anything against him.
- I wanna help him.
- Bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
I listened to his story.
Anyone could've found themselves
in that position.
- So what are you saying?
- I'm saying that you and I
are supposed to be
Batman and Robin, we...
If we can't stop these guys
from getting away with it
and save Alex in the meantime,
then what the hell
are we doing?
I'm guessing you got a plan.
I'm guessing I do.
You think we need to find
our commissioner Gordon.
- How'd you know that?
- Because I know Batman.
And I know that he needs
someone on the inside
who's working with him
behind the scenes.
Look at you.
You do know Batman.
- You got someone in mind?
- Of course I do.
Unless you're
even dumber than you look,
it's the same person
you're thinking of.
♪♪
Robert, you have a minute?
I got a minute to find out
how you got into my house.
Laura let me in.
Yeah, of course she did.
She's under the misguided
impression that you're charming.
Now why don't you tell me
what you got in that box.
Just some files.
We were running out of space
over at my firm and I thought
maybe I could just
store them with you.
You think I didn't
hear about that class action?
Just about cracked
your firm in two?
Why the hell would I touch that
with a ten foot pole?
Robert, I don't have
a leg to stand on
other than to say
that Mike took this on
and found some bad shit.
I'm giving you an opportunity
to right some wrongs,
make a shitload of money
and all you have to do
is show up for one meeting.
I think I might have
some extra storage space here.
But, Harvey, if you
leave that thing with me,
the case is mine
and I run it how I see fit.
- Is that a threat?
- Maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
But once we step into that ring,
I don't give a shit
who you are,
I'm not pulling my punches.
I wouldn't have it
any other way.
♪♪
♪ See the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and Missy is so busy,
busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back, I'm 'bout to dance ♪
*SUITS*
Season 07  Episode 08
Title: "100"
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
♪♪
What the hell?
I thought you were on my side.
- I am on your side.
- Then why did Robert Zane
just come out of nowhere
and all of a sudden
- reopen that God damn case?
- Alex, relax.
He didn't open it up
against your client;
he opened it up
against Harvey's.
What good does that do?
They're in this thing together
and so am I.
Listen to me. You've trusted
me with the truth.
I gave you my word that I
wouldn't let you go down
- for something you didn't do.
- Well I guess your word is shit
because the second
this trial starts,
it's only a matter of time
till I've got a bull's-eye
- on my back.
- Well, then I guess
it's a good thing there isn't
gonna be a trial.
♪♪
What are you talking about?
I can't tell you
everything that's going on,
but all you need to do
is make sure
Masterson Construction
stands down.
♪♪
After that, you just
sit back and watch
this whole thing go away.
♪♪
God damn it!
God damn it, Gretchen,
I asked you for those
applications
to replace
Stephanie days ago.
- Where the hell...
- I have them right here.
Well, why didn't you
give them to me?
Because there was
a problem...
wait a second, wait a second,
wait a second, wait a second.
- This doesn't feel right.
- How can you know that?
Because when it comes
to applications,
I'm like rain man
and this pile
feels one applicant light.
That's because
Columbia university
chose not to send an applicant.
Well, why the hell
didn't you tell me?
Because it's one position.
We have applications
from 19 of the top 20 schools,
you fool.
- Did you just call me a fool?
- I call 'em like I see 'em.
Well, I don't give a shit
about the other 19
if there's even one that thinks
we're still
not good enough
after Mike Ross.
I'm not gonna let it stand.
Louis, if you go over there
and make trouble,
it won't only be
Columbia
withholding lawyers from us,
it'll be every
damn school in the country.
Gretchen, if you're gonna keep
talking, you might as well
say it to my ass 'cause I'm
going over there right now
to let them know
who's too good for who.
♪♪
- Roger.
- What the hell?
- What the hell, what?
- Don't give me that.
I did a little digging.
Robert Zane is about
to be Mike Ross' father-in-law
and I don't think
it's a coincidence
that all of a sudden,
he's coming after us
on the exact same case.
Roger, I'll take care of it.
You better take care of it,
Harvey.
Because I only signed with you
because you promised to stop
Mike Ross,
and I don't think
I have to remind you
that if Reform Corp.
Goes down,
Alex Williams goes down
and he takes
your whole damn firm with him.
I told you.
I'll take care of it.
But you're gonna need to do
something for me.
- And what is that?
- Open your God damn checkbook.
Robert, there's no cause
for you to talk
- to my client like that.
- Well, if you want me
to invite him
to afternoon tea, I will.
But if he wants this case to go
away, this is how much
he's gonna have to pay.
Are you out of your mind?
Robert, this isn't
a settlement offer.
This is a declaration of war.
Then let's go to war.
You think I'm afraid to put this
in front of a jury?
You won't get near a jury
'cause I'm gonna make sure
they know Mike Ross
handed you this case
on a silver platter.
And you don't have
the proof of that
or you wouldn't be
at a settlement meeting.
But I do have the proof
that you not only schemed
to extend sentences, but
murdered someone to cover it up.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm talking about the fact
that I have an eyewitness in
prison who'll testify in court.
And who is this witness?
You know who he is.
And he knows who you are.
And unless you take my deal,
you're gonna end up
behind bars yourself.
I am not paying
that kind of money
and I am not admitting
to anything.
Roger, you heard him.
He has a witness.
Then you better make sure
Frank Gallo
doesn't testify, Harvey.
Or I'll find somebody who can.
♪♪
I wanna speak to whoever the
hell's in charge of recruiting
and I wanna speak to them now.
Well, I'm afraid
that's not possible.
What do you mean
it's not possible?
I mean you'll have to
make an appointment.
We don't take in walk-ins.
Well, I'm not a walk-in.
My name is Louis litt,
from the firm
Pearson Specter Litt.
- Wait, you can't go in there.
- Oh, yes I can.
If you people think you can
dismiss our firm,
you have another thing com...
Sheila.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
Um, uh... well, I've worked
at Columbia
for the past six months.
But you said you would
never leave Harvard.
I did, Louis.
- But...
- But what?
My fiancé lives in the city
and I wanted to be with him.
- Fiancé.
- Yes.
We're getting married
in two weeks.
I'm sorry, Louis.
You don't need to be sorry.
And I understand why you didn't
send the applications over.
- You didn't want me to be hurt.
- I didn't.
But now that you know,
there's no reason
to punish you or the firm.
I guess not.
I'll send over our best
and our brightest
and make sure they understand
it's an opportunity
to learn
at the foot of a master.
It's good to see you, Sheila.
Good to see you too, Louis.
♪♪
Harvey, what happened?
They go for it?
What happened was your
backstabbing father-in-law
blew up the settlement.
- What? Why?
- 'Cause he's an asshole.
Now I gotta stop Gallo
from testifying.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm talking about
going to the prison
and convincing
that psychopath not to talk.
- Harvey, that's a bad idea.
- Don't you get it?
He talks, Alex goes down.
That's the whole thing
we're trying to avoid.
I'm not saying
it's a bad idea
to shut Gallo down.
I'm saying that you are not
the one to do it.
Are you out of your mind?
You're not supposed to be
anywhere near this case.
Reform Corp. gets wind of this...
and what, Harvey?
I shut down the star witness
on the other side.
They're not gonna be pissed.
They're gonna give me a medal.
What makes you think
you're gonna be better
- at that than me?
- Because I might've been
the one who kept him
there longer, but you...
You're the one who put him there
in the first place.
♪♪
Mm, what are you doing here?
- I thought you were off the case.
- I was.
Now I'm back on.
'Cause I need to
give you something.
Yeah, what's this?
It's a hell of a lot more
than whatever
Robert Zane
is paying you to testify.
It's on top of whatever
settlement
your daughter
is still gonna get.
All you have to do
is keep your mouth shut.
Yeah, I'm not interested
in your money.
No, Gallo,
you're not getting me, this...
you're not getting me.
I don't give
a God damn about your money.
Robert Zane already told me
you'd be in here
- trying to screw me over.
- I'm not trying
- to screw you over.
- Then why have you been
trying to get me to do
the exact opposite thing
- for the last month?
- Because-
- because the two of you
don't give a shit
about anything but yourselves.
The situation has changed.
You know what hasn't changed?
Denise.
What she thinks of me.
- Frank, that's...
- See, you came in here
trying to get me
to buy her love back.
I almost did it.
But I can't get anything
from her with just money.
I need her to see me
get up on that stand
admit what I did
and ask for forgiveness.
Robert Zane understands that
because he's got a daughter.
- I understand that...
- No, you don't.
I need her to see me do this.
And nothing you or Harvey
can say is gonna change that.
♪♪
And then you said,
"it's Mr. Dipshit,
thank you very much."
Well, if he's gonna
be a stickler
about what name
is on the reservation,
And then for
the rest of the weekend,
we didn't have to pay
for a single drink.
Which was a good thing because
you ordered Tequila shots
- for everyone in the restaurant.
- It was Cinco De Mayo.
It was August 9th.
I can't believe
you still remember that.
I remember a lot of things
about those days.
Which is why I can't believe
that there's not a, uh,
- a Mr. Donna Paulson yet.
- Well.
You know I have my standards.
Well, I'm glad to see
you haven't lowered them.
To tell you the truth,
I actually raised them.
At least professionally.
You mean you finally
stopped working for Harvey?
Yes and no.
I still work at the firm,
but I'm COO now.
- Donna, that is fantastic.
- It is.
So what about you?
No Mrs. meadows yet?
Um, actually, i...
I got married
about three years ago.
Mark, if you're married,
why did you
agree to have lunch with me?
Because you called
and you invited me
and... and I thought
it's just lunch, and...
this hasn't felt like just
lunch and you know it.
No, it hasn't.
To tell you the truth,
I think about you all the time.
And my wife
and I have been
at each other's throats
for months.
And then you called and
I thought that I would meet you
and just see what happened.
Well, I can tell you
what's not gonna happen.
I'm not gonna be
the answer to your problems.
Well, I'm... I'm so sorry.
Look, I'm not gonna lie
and say that I don't think about
you, too, from time to time.
I do.
But this can't be the way that
things start up again with us.
So if at some point,
you call and you say
that things are over
between you and your wife
and you wanna go out with me,
I'd be open to that.
But I'm not open to this.
I understand.
It was good to see you, Mmark.
It's good to see you too,
Donna.
Rachel.
Hey.
- You are a sight for sore eyes.
- Am I?
Whoa, what's going on?
Did you have a bad day?
I was actually
having a great day
until I found out
that the witness in the murder
case is Frank Gallo.
- Rachel, I was gonna...
- Gonna tell me?
When, exactly?
When the whole thing was over?
Because I also found out
that you and Harvey
went to my dad
to keep this thing alive.
- Rachel...
- How many times
do I have to tell you
I can take care of myself?
What did you want me to say?
That I shouldn't have gone
to Gallo?
Or that I shouldn't have taken
this whole thing on
in the first place?
Because I am never
gonna say that.
This has nothing to do with
any of that.
This has to do with you
respecting me as a lawyer.
So you're telling me that if I
had let you in on the plan,
you would've been good
with all of it.
I don't know if I would've
been good with any of it.
What I do know is that you
need to get through your head
that I am a grown woman
and that I am not
a damsel in distress
that needs protecting.
♪♪
Whatever it is, Donna,
I don't have it in me.
It's okay, Louis. I didn't
even know you were up here.
If you wanna be alone, I can...
Sheila's getting married.
I'm so sorry.
She didn't wanna tell me
because she thought
I couldn't handle it.
I get it.
Maybe.
But what you don't get is
what it's like
to find out twice in one year
that the person you thought
was the love of your life
doesn't want you.
I understand that
more than you think.
What do you mean?
I had lunch
with an ex-boyfriend today.
Someone I cared a lot about.
I looked him up, wondering if
there was still something there
and while we were eating,
he told me he was married.
Why'd he have lunch with you?
Because, Louis.
People are more complicated
than you think.
Well, it's not complicated
for Sheila.
She's found her man,
and that is that.
Louis, I'm not sure I feel
comfortable leaving you
up here all alone.
It's okay, Donna.
I'm not gonna jump.
Unless you can guarantee me
I can land on Sheila's fiancé.
Okay.
You're gonna be all right.
But I'm still not leaving
you up here all alone.
♪♪
Whatever it is,
I don't need to hear it
because I already know
what you're gonna say.
Well, I'm gonna say it anyway.
I didn't bring you this case
to take you to court.
I brought it to you so you
could give these people justice.
Bullshit. You brought it to me
to get you out of hot water.
And I like I already told you,
this is my case.
Don't you dare
tell me how to run it.
I know that Robert, but look,
if you dig too deep,
it's gonna end up
putting one of my own
behind bars for a crime
he didn't commit.
Well, it doesn't take too much
for me to guess who that is.
And I don't give a shit
about Alex Williams.
You know what I do
give a shit about?
The United States is 5%
of the world's population.
But it's got 25%
of its prisoners.
But that's not something
you white guys want to talk about.
- Robert...
- I grew up
in the roughest part
of Harlem there is.
Nine out of ten kids
on my block
ended up in places like that.
And every day of my life,
I think...
There but by the grace of God.
And they're taking these kids...
Like the ones I knew-
and they're
extending their sentences
and murdering some of them.
So no matter what you do
or what you say,
they're going to take my offer
or we're going to trial.
Either way, they're gonna pay.
♪♪ Dramatic music...
♪♪
Harvey. I was just about
to call you.
Since you didn't already,
I'm guessing you couldn't
convince Gallo
not to testify.
He doesn't want our money,
Harvey.
He wants his daughter's
forgiveness
and thinks the only way
he's gonna get it
- is by testifying.
- Bullshit. He wants something.
We just need to find out
what it is.
Listen to me.
I was in the room with him.
This thing with his daughter
is real.
He's not gonna back down.
Son of a bitch.
- What are we gonna do now?
- I hate to say it.
We may need to find
some dirt on Zane.
Harvey,
I'm not gonna blackmail
my future father-in-law
about a case that we gave him
to begin with.
- You didn't give it to him.
- I did.
And I did it to make sure
two things happened,
and one was saving
Alex Williams.
So if you don't wanna
find something on Zane,
I will.
Neither one of you has to.
- Rachel...
- Harvey, I know
how things work.
I meant, you don't have to find
dirt on my father because I know
how to stop Frank Gallo
from testifying.
But my dad isn't gonna be the
only one who doesn't like it.
You two aren't gonna
like it either.
- Why not?
- Because it involves
impugning his integrity
and doing it through me.
If you're saying what I think
you're saying,
that's playing with fire.
And I already told you
I don't have a problem
playing with fire.
My problem is being left out
of the game.
So if my dad has an issue
with it,
you tell him to take it up
with me.
Lewis, that woman from
Columbia university's
on the line again.
She'd like to know what you
thought about her candidate.
Tell her we already
filled the position.
Lewis, tell me
what's going on.
You went all the way over there
to get them on board
and now you're asking me
to lie to this woman.
What's going on is
I don't wanna see her,
I don't wanna talk to her,
I don't wanna hear her name.
So if you don't wanna lie,
then don't.
But I am not taking that call.
Look, Mike,
Rachel's plan could work,
but it's gonna piss Zane off
and you know it.
Not to mention what
it's gonna do to Gallo.
Rachel and I can take care
of the fallout, trust me.
Before you got there last night,
she made it clear
that she can handle herself.
Yeah, I don't care
what she thinks she can handle.
I'm not doing it.
Then what exactly
is your plan, because the
hearing's in five minutes
and we don't have another way
to stop Gallo from testifying.
What the hell
are you doing here, Bratton?
I'm to make sure
you're doing your job.
Bullshit,
I don't work for you.
I didn't say you did.
But if you can't
make this thing go away,
you're not gonna be working
for Reform Corp. Or
Masterson Construction either.
- Is that a fact?
- Sure as hell is.
You don't stop our prison friend
from testifying,
I'm gonna take this thing over
and the first thing
I'm going to do
is offer up a sacrificial lamb
named Alex Williams.
♪♪
How do you feel
about Rachel's plan now?
Gentlemen, this is
the second time
the issue of Frank Gallo's
come up in this case.
What is it this time?
What it is, your honor,
is Mr. Specter knows
Mr. Gallo is gonna
take him out at the knees
and he's gonna do
anything he can to stop him.
I'll do anything I can
because Frank Gallo
is about to commit perjury
and Robert Zane knows it.
You accuse someone of
something like that
in an open court, you better
damn well have proof.
Mr. Zane, watch yourself.
And Mr. Specter, he's right.
I know that, your honor.
Which is why I have proof
right here.
And what is that?
Pictures of Rachel Zane
sent by Frank Gallo
designed to intimidate her
father into suborning perjury.
That is a lie!
Whatever's in that envelope
is bullshit.
Mr. Zane, I'm going
to let that language go
and I don't want to
accuse you of anything,
but these photos do indicate
that a known criminal
is threatening your daughter.
I don't give a shit
what they indicate.
I've never seen them before
in my life
and I don't suborn perjury.
- That's enough.
- I don't know
what's going on here,
but until I get
to the bottom of this,
Frank Gallo is not testifying.
You son of a bitch.
You used my daughter against me.
I'm gonna God damn
knock you out.
Robert, don't you come at me.
You don't want me
coming at you because you know
- once I got my hands on you...
- You're done!
Which is why I'll drop you
before you do.
- Go ahead and drop me!
- Robert.
You're not gonna throw a punch
because you know you're wrong.
Robert, Robert!
Hey, Robert, Robert! Stop!
It was Rachel's idea.
- What did you just say?
- Harvey didn't even
- wanna do it.
- Bullshit, it was her idea.
Robert, she's a grown woman,
she made a decision.
You don't believe me,
you can ask her yourself.
But I'm telling you,
you wanna be angry at someone,
- do not take it out on Harvey.
- I don't care
whose idea it was.
You used her to slander me!
In open court!
You should be ashamed
of yourself.
And you... you tell your
Reform Corp. buddies
that Frank Gallo is gonna
take that stand
one way or another.
And there's nothing
they can do to stop it.
♪♪ Tense music...
♪♪
- Mark, hi.
- Hey, um,
I hope I'm not interrupting.
No, actually, I'm just, um...
I'm just finishing up
for the night.
Are you still there?
Yeah, um...
Sorry, um, I'm just...
- Mark.
- Hold on, please, Donna.
Let me just...
Let me just get this out.
Seeing you the other day
brought up a lot of feelings.
It did for me, too.
But you're married.
- Not happily.
- Mark...
the thing is, I walked away
from you once before.
And ever since...
I... I wonder what would've
happened if I hadn't...
I just... I can't walk away
from you again.
What are you saying?
My office is hosting
a conference this week
and everyone's staying
in the city, so...
I'm not going back
to Connecticut until Saturday.
I'd like to see you
before I do.
What am I supposed
to say to that?
You don't have to
say anything.
But I just wanted you to know
that I'll be staying
at the Carlyle
for the next two nights.
Room 508.
What about your wife?
I don't know how
I'm gonna handle that.
And I definitely won't be able
to handle it by tomorrow.
So if you don't wanna see me,
I'll understand.
But I had to call.
Good night, Donna.
Good night, MMmark.
Gretchen, I told you
I'm not taking any calls.
Louis?
Sheila. You called
my private line.
Is this a bad time?
I wouldn't say
it's a great time.
Louis, I lied
when I said I didn't tell you
about being at Columbia
because I didn't wanna hurt you.
Well, then why
didn't you tell me?
Because I haven't gotten you
out of my system.
And when I say that,
what I'm really saying is,
Louis,
I want your body one last time
before I walk down that aisle.
Say what, now?
I wanna devour every inch
of your flesh.
I want you to rock my world
six ways from Sunday.
- I want to...
- I think I get the-
- do not interrupt me!
Because I demand a travel
to the moon and back
seven to nine more times
in one life-shattering
12-36 hour period.
- Oh, my God.
- That's when I plan on
making you scream until
you can't scream anymore.
Sheila, where is this
coming from?
You know exactly
where it's coming from.
It started the second
you strutted into my office
like a viking God,
ready to pillage
a helpless maiden.
I was just coming in
to check on the candidates.
I didn't even know
that you were...
that's what makes it so hot.
Shirley, even though
this image
is making my viking mast
unfurl to full sail,
I don't think what you're
suggesting is a good idea.
Well, that's because
I haven't told you
that I'm finally gonna let you
do that thing
that you always wanted to do.
- Even the...
- Yes.
- And with the...
And what about the accent?
Oh, with all the accents,
Louis.
With all the accents.
- What about the lisp?
- No.
Ahh! Sheila, I can't!
I respect your integrity,
Louis.
But not enough to stop me
from waiting
for you tomorrow night
in our old hotel suite.
The war room?
The very one. Ah.
♪♪
Louis, you've gotta come down
to the bullpen for a second.
You're not gonna believe what
Brian cooked up
for the Langston settlement.
- I can't right now, Rachel.
- Why not?
It's only going to take
a second.
Because I'm not getting up
right now, Rachel,
and there's nothing you can say
to change that.
Louis, what's going on?
Just got off the phone
with Sheila.
She's getting married and she
wants to have one last fling
before she goes down the aisle.
And you don't
wanna do that because
you don't wanna be
that kind of person.
- No, I don't.
- So then what's the problem?
The problem is... is...
I haven't had anything
go my way in so long,
I can't even remember
what that's like.
And I could really
use a night where
I can forget my pain
and feel good about myself.
Louis, I can't tell you
what the answer is
because it's not a small thing
to do something like that.
But if it helps,
I know you have a good heart.
So whatever you decide,
it's not gonna change
how I feel about you.
Thanks, Rachel.
♪♪ Somber music...
♪♪
What are you doing here,
counselor?
I'm here because I have
relevant information
- on the Reform Corp. Matter.
- And if that's the case,
you should be
doing it in chambers
and Robert Zane should be there.
Your honor,
Robert Zane's not
in his right mind.
You saw what happened
to him yesterday
and that's why before you rule
on Frank Gallo...
- Stop right there, Mr. Specter.
- No, I'm not gonna
- Yes, you are.
- Stop there. Your honor...
Frank Gallo is dead.
- What?
- He was murdered
in his cell last night.
So whatever it was
that you were going
to say about
him is irrelevant.
The man can't testify.
So I think it's time
to let him rest in peace.
♪♪
Donna.
How long have you
been standing there?
I was just walking by
and I didn't recognize you.
And you thought,
who is that strange woman
in Harvey's office?
That's not what I thought.
Have you seen Harvey,
by any chance?
He's actually out
for the rest of the day.
That's okay.
I'll just see him tonight.
Oh, I get it.
You stopped by to surprise him
because it's your
two month anniversary.
- How can you know that?
- Because I care about him.
And you coming into his life...
Is a memorable event.
Well, it was good
to see you, Donna.
Carbone.
I'm sorry.
It's a hole in the wall,
but it's one
of Harvey's favorite places.
So if you're looking
for a reservation...
actually, I already have one.
Oh, let me guess.
- At Carbone.
- Yes.
Well, I'm sure
you'll have a great time.
Thank you for
the recommendation, Donna.
There you are. I've been
looking all over for you.
- What is it, Rachel?
- Okay, I was thinking,
we never got to have
those drinks we talked about
and, Donna, I know you've been
going through
a lot of stuff, lately.
So I thought maybe
you could use a night
where you just
lose your troubles
and just feel good
about yourself.
- I could.
- So, what do you say?
Is Harriet Specter available
to go out with
Michelle Ross tonight?
I can't tonight,
Rachel; I have plans.
That's mysterious.
What do you have, a hot date?
Yeah.
Something like that.
- Is he in?
- Yes, but you can't
- go in there.
- Try and stop me.
- Wait a second.
- You son of a bitch.
You murdered Frank Gallo.
Ashley, I'll handle this.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Bullshit!
- You said if I couldn't
stop him from testifying,
you'd find someone who could.
I meant I'd get
Thomas Bratton involved.
I didn't mean I'd kill a man.
And you did stop Gallo
from testifying,
so why would it matter?
Because he wanted to make sure
that Robert Zane
didn't reverse it,
so you had him murdered.
And how exactly did I arrange
this supposed murder?
The same damn way you killed
that guard and covered it up.
Once again, Harvey, I have no
idea what you're talking about.
And you can accuse me
of anything you want,
but that man was
a hardened criminal
who could've been killed
by anyone for anything.
And I am not gonna lose
a second of sleep over it.
I beg to differ.
- Robert.
- What the hell
is going on here?
I'll tell you what's going on.
I got something
for you to see.
And it's not on Netflix.
Frank Gallo,
prisoner 09842.
Danbury Federal Prison.
All right.
Enough bullshit.
I'm your lawyer.
None of this is admissible.
Now tell me the truth,
so I know what I'm dealing with.
All right, you want the truth,
let's just get to it.
There was a guard, sent a letter
to some lawyer on the outside
who was getting suspicious of
what was going on in there.
They wanted me to remind him
of where he was
in the food chain.
- And you were happy to do it.
- No, I wasn't.
We were hard men in there.
Tough guys, murderers.
That guard was just
a sweet, old man.
Never hurt a soul
in all his years.
And you expect me
to believe all that.
You can believe it or not,
it's the truth.
So I told them I wouldn't do it
until whoever was
running the show
came to me directly.
And they made that happen.
They had no choice.
Next day, the guy showed up
right in my God damn cell
like he owned the place,
- which he did.
- And who exactly was that?
Roger Shapiro.
CEO of Reform Corp.
And then what happened?
I, uh...
I got him alone that night
in the mess hall.
Wouldn't you know, the old man
still had some fight in him.
Next thing I knew,
it was him or me, so...
I had to put him down.
You killed him.
Yeah.
I killed him.
And then what did you do?
I told them I was done, out,
no more.
Next night, Roger Shapiro
sent five of my friends
to do the same thing to me.
Looks like you're in
some deep shit, Roger.
- I don't believe it.
- So you two
were in on this together.
To quote you,
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I certainly didn't go to
Robert's house this morning
and tell him that I think that
you had Frank Gallo murdered
so he wouldn't be able
to testify.
And I certainly didn't say
if you had,
you made a huge mistake
because now this tape
is a death bed confession
and by law is admissible.
And all that bullshit
I came up with,
about Robert being intimidated
by Frank Gallo,
well, that doesn't apply anymore
because Frank Gallo's dead.
- So what do you want?
- What I want
is for you to go away
for murder.
But that's not gonna happen
so I'll settle for the number
I wanted in the first place.
But you're never gonna pull
this shit again on prisoners
because if you do, I don't care
about Alex Williams.
This tape goes
to the department of justice
and you are headed
to one of your own prisons,
five seconds later.
I think that's something
that I could work with.
Now, if there's nothing else,
I'd like you both to leave.
Oh, we're not done
with you yet.
- What now?
- I'll tell you what now,
you're gonna write up
something for me
and you're not gonna like it.
But if you wanna
stay out of prison,
you're gonna make damn sure
it says exactly
what I need it to.
What the hell is this?
Tommy.
You mind telling me
how the hell you got in here?
People like me here, Tommy.
That's how I got in.
But the question you should be
asking is why I'm here.
I don't give a shit
why you're here.
I want my God damn
affidavit back.
Sure thing. You also want me
to sign over
the deed to my house in
the Hamptons, while I'm at it?
You can keep
your shitty house.
Because you're gonna need
someplace to go
after you resign.
What did you just say to me?
He said he's here
for his affidavit
and your resignation,
you smug piece of shit.
What you guys,
plan on beating it out of me?
Because that's the only way
you'd get it.
We don't need to
beat up an old man, Tommy.
We just need to show you this.
- What's that?
- That's a signed confession
from Robert Shapiro,
say he entered into a conspiracy
with Masterson Construction
to defraud
the United States Government.
And that that conspiracy
was arranged by you.
No way.
Roger would never do that.
Oh, he did it.
For the same reason
you're gonna give us
what we want.
We had him by the balls.
Just like I got you
right now, Tommy.
So you can pick up the phone
and call him,
or you can look at my face
and see I'm not lying.
But either way,
we're not leaving here
without getting what we want.
I'm not going
to stand here
and write my resignation letter
in front of you two, okay?
Then it's a good thing
we wrote one up for you.
♪♪ Dramatic music...
♪♪
By the way, remember when
I told you you owed me?
I'd pretty much
say we're even.
I don't think this word even
means what you think it means.
Oh, well, is that a fact?
You're damn right it is.
I turned down a job offer.
You were gonna go to prison.
You owe me for the rest
of your life.
Got it. Me and you, square.
Once again, I don't think
the word square
means what you think it means.
You're right.
We still gotta go eat on you.
Sorry, can't tonight, Alex.
I got other plans.
What are you doing here?
I came to apologize
for what I did.
I thought you said
it was Rachel's idea.
It was, but you said
I should've stopped it
in its tracks
and you were right.
Robert, I'm sorry.
I love Rachel. I would never
do anything to hurt her.
But I should've known to never
do anything to hurt you.
It takes a big man
to say that, Mike.
I appreciate it.
And I'd be lying if I didn't
admit it worked out
for everybody in the end.
Yeah, not everybody.
I'm not losing any sleep
over that son of a bitch.
He may not have threatened
Rachel to me,
but he sure as hell
threatened her to you.
I know.
And I know he was a murderer.
But... Harvey showed me that
tape.
You can see how much he cared
about his daughter.
Fact of the matter is,
they're never gonna see
each other again.
Then to Frank Gallo.
May he rest in peace.
I told them I was done.
No more, out.
Next night, Roger Shapiro
sent five of my friends
to do the same thing to me.
You're willing to testify
to that in court.
No way, I tell them that,
they'll put me away for murder.
- You're already away.
- Yeah, for seven more years.
I tell them this,
they'll put me away for life.
What if I can
get you immunity?
- You can't promise me that.
- No, I can't.
But if you did this for me,
there's no way
I'm gonna let them
convict you for murder.
Why should I believe you?
For the same reason you need
to take that stand.
I know what it's like
to have a daughter.
And I know you cut that deal
with Mike Ross
so that she'd forgive you.
But she needs more than that
to forgive you.
She needs to know her father
is a good man.
- I'm not a good man.
- Yeah, maybe not.
But if you got up there
and told the world what you did,
and stopped these monsters from
ever doing it again...
You let her see that...
She'll forgive you.
And I swear
on my own daughter,
I will not let you
go down for it.
Okay.
I'll do it.
Denise Gallo?
Who are you?
Someone who knew your father.
He, uh, wanted you to have this.
I want you to know,
he was a decent man.
♪♪
I believe I just figured out
why you fancy
this place so much.
- Why's that?
- Colors and the candle light.
They make you look
tremendously handsome.
Dr. Agard,
if I didn't know better,
I'd think you were
hitting on me.
If you didn't know better,
I never would've
gotten the chance.
- What's that?
- It's just a little something
I saw that made me
think of you.
- And...
- And what?
It's our two month
anniversary.
I didn't want to make
a big deal out of it.
And I certainly
don't expect you to
- to have remembered, but...
- Paula, of course I remembered.
Why do you think
I got you this?
That's the key
to your apartment.
Yes, it is.
This is incredibly sweet.
But it isn't gonna fool me
into believing
that you had the faintest notion
it was our two month
anniversary.
You're right. I didn't.
But...
I was gonna give you
these tonight, anyway.
Which, if you think about it,
makes it even more special.
Happy anniversary, Paula.
Happy anniversary, Harvey.
♪♪
I... I didn't know
if you'd come.
I'm sorry, MMmark.
I can't do this.
♪♪
I didn't know if you'd come.
How could I not?
♪♪
Synchronized by srjanapala
www.tvsubtitles.net