Just wanted to tell you
that I appreciate you
Patching things up with him.
I would do anything
for the woman that I love.
They are gonna come at us
any way they can,
And when they do,
It's not gonna be
about heat sensors,
It's gonna be about you.
I know I'm not the only guy
in that company
That knows
those sensors are faulty.
I'm sorry, what is it
you need again?
All the maintenance work orders
from the past six months.
I can't let you have that
without authorization.
Have you heard of the national
transportation safety board?
(evan) that's your secretary
unlawfully gathering evidence,
Which means there will be
no settlement of any kind.
And tomorrow, I'm sending this
to the district attorney.
Your whole story about how
louis got his name on the door
Is bullshit.
Jeff.
It's over, jessica.
We're done.
I can't believe you actually
got them to admit what they did.
You better believe it,
because it's happening,
And it wouldn't be
happening without you.
You mean without me
being greedy.
Joe, that's not
what I was gonna say.
No, no, no, I know that
you don't think I care
About these people, but I do.
But I'm also a working stiff.
I go paycheck to paycheck
for my whole life,
And then a thing like this...
Could turn your
whole life around.
Guy like you might not be
able to understand that.
I understand.
So it's a done deal?
Might take a few
days to finalize,
But yeah.
It's happening.
You have my word.
You're all right, mr. Ross.
Harvey, you know the only
times you've been here at night
Were the god-awful
dinner party...
And the other time.
Well, this isn't that.
I want to know why liberty rail
Has a video of you
in their file room.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking the fact
that our smoking gun
Just became inadmissible.
- Harvey...
- How'd you get those documents?
Are you asking
if I did something illegal?
Because I didn't.
Well, they went to the d.A.,
Which means they think you did,
So I'm gonna ask you
one more time,
How did you get
in their file room?
By walking through the
door they buzzed open.
And why would they do that?
Because I'm me.
What the hell does that mean?
It means that I led
the woman to believe
That I was an official
from washington.
Led them to believe it,
Or flat out told them?
Because one kills our case
And the other puts you
in a world of shit.
Harvey, I'm not an idiot,
And I don't appreciate
being treated like one.
I told you I didn't do
anything illegal, and I didn't.
Not an idiot?
What the hell were you doing
there in the first place?
- Harvey.
- It was mike's idea, wasn't it?
No, he didn't even
know about it.
- Where are you going?
- To see mike.
I told you, he didn't even
know I was going to do it.
I don't care, because he
sure as hell knew after.
Let's go.
[engine turns over]
I am so proud of you.
I've done that before.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about your case.
Ah.
You believed in it,
and you fought for it,
And I...
I love that about you.
And I love that you
love that about me.
When a person gives you
a compliment like that,
You're supposed
to give one back.
But I just did.
I said that you love
that I love that about me.
About you?
How would that make you feel?
So tired.
Well, we both know
why you're so tired.
Yeah, because I'm so good.
Don't you love that about me?
[knocking on door]
You knew donna bullshitted
her way into that company
And you let us use
those work orders?
How did you find out?
It doesn't matter
how I found out.
Answer my question.
Yes, I knew, but what
difference does it make? We won.
We didn't win,
Because evan smith has video
of donna in their offices.
- What?
- She know about this too?
Harvey, she's just
trying to strong-arm us.
Are you listening to me?
They have the opposing
counsel's secretary
Poking around
in their goddamn file room.
If I were the d.A.,
I'd sure as hell look into it.
- The d.A.?
- Yeah, the d.A.
Harvey, they let her in.
According to you,
but they're gonna claim fraud
Or theft
or any number of things.
What are you gonna do?
I'm making a deal to drop this
case, that's what I'm gonna do,
And you're gonna file
the paperwork as soon as I do.
So you're just gonna
let this woman
Blackmail you without a fight?
You're damn right I am.
There is no case,
And I wouldn't give a shit
about it if there was.
I care about donna.
And you think I don't?
You care so much for her?
Then draw up those papers,
Because I'm letting
evan know it's over.
(man) ♪ see the money,
wanna stay for your meal ♪
♪ Get another piece of pie
for your wife ♪
♪ Everybody wanna know
how it feel ♪
♪ Everybody wanna see
what it's like ♪
♪ I'll even eat a bean pie,
I don't mind ♪
♪ Me and missy is
so busy, busy making money ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance ♪
♪ The greenback boogie ♪
What are you doing here?
We have a situation.
Is the fate of the firm
hanging in the balance?
- No...
- Then I don't give a shit.
You told malone, didn't you?
I didn't get a chance
to tell him,
Because he had already
figured out
That I had been lying to him
this whole time.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, you're sorry.
This morning I thought
I was going away with him
For two weeks.
Now I don't know if I'm ever
gonna see him again.
He quit?
He didn't get around
to giving me his career plans.
You want me to talk to him
for you?
No, this is my mess.
And I will take care
of it myself.
You can take care of it
tomorrow.
Right now,
I'm making you a drink.
Zipadeedoodah or grab my sack?
- What?
- Messenger service.
Which one do we use?
- I-I...
- You know what?
Use whoever you want.
Just take care of it.
Louis, don't you have
your own secretary?
Oh, you mean norma,
who I can't find anywhere,
Who is probably taking
the day off again?
Last year, she tried to get
arbor day off,
And I told her to blow a goddamn
tree and get her ass in here.
You know what, louis?
Norma has taken 4 days off
in the last 36 years.
Why don't you back
the hell off of her.
What the hell is the matter
with you?
You usually jump on
the norma bashing train
Like a hobo in a 1940s
action movie.
- I'm sorry; I just...
- What?
I bullshitted my way
into liberty rail
To get some documents.
They caught me on video,
And now they're threatening
to press charges.
You're not saying anything.
It's nothing.
It's fine.
Then why did you look
so concerned?
I was concerned,
but they're threatening charges,
Which means they want something,
And I know harvey,
and whatever it is they want,
He'll find a way
to give it to him.
Okay.
Thanks, louis.
I'll take care of your stuff.
No, no.
You have enough on your mind.
I'll take care of it myself.
Mr. Specter,
don't tell me.
You're here to talk
about ms. Paulsen.
I'm here to tell you
you made your point.
(evan) and what point is that?
If you drop any charges
against donna,
We'll drop the lawsuit
against you.
Well, that's not
a very even trade.
I'm giving your client the
chance to get away with murder.
Last I checked, my client wasn't
being charged with murder,
And I don't need you
to drop your suit,
Because you have no case.
No case?
Your client put a faulty train
on those tracks,
People died, and they knew
it could happen the whole time.
And you have no proof.
And where I come from,
You cut a deal with me
to make sure I stop looking.
Then I guess we come
from different places,
Because I didn't give that video
to the district attorney
To leverage you into a deal.
I did it to blow you out
of the water.
This is a person's life.
Maybe you should have
thought of that
Before you sent her
to rob my client.
Evan, I care about this woman.
Look, I understand.
She's probably worked for you
for a long time.
Maybe you sleep together
once in a while.
But my job is to defend
my client
To the best of my abilities,
And that's exactly what
I'm going to do.
Holy shit.
You can't possible have
a check already.
I don't have a check, joe.
We have to drop the case.
What the hell are you
talking about?
We had drinks last night.
Yeah, we also had proof
last night,
And now we don't.
- Why not?
- It's complicated.
You know,
it's a lot of legal rigmarole...
But I'm also
not gonna stand here
And explain civil procedure.
Maybe I don't understand
civil procedure,
But I know enough to understand
when something doesn't add up.
We got the evidence
the wrong way.
Well, get it the right way.
Subpoena it or something.
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
That money was gonna
change my life.
And if you want to go to
a different law firm,
I understand.
You know as well as I do nobody
else is gonna take this case.
You told me you cared
about these people.
You gave me your word.
Yeah, and I wish I could
keep it.
I want those bastards
as much as you want this money,
But I've got no proof,
And you're not
a credible witness.
- Oh, that bullshit again.
- That's not bullshit.
If you had been straight with me
from day one,
We wouldn't even be in
this mess.
How much did they give you
to dump the case?
Had to be something.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't sell me out.
I'm sorry, joe.
It's over.
You're sorry?
[knocking]
Jessica.
Do you need something?
I came by earlier,
and you weren't in.
I had a meeting, and I
really didn't think you wanted
To be looped in on my schedule.
I don't,
and I'm not checking up on you.
I just didn't know if you
were coming in.
You mean you weren't sure
if I was ever coming in again.
You wouldn't be the first person
to leave a job
For personal reasons.
It sounds to me like you have
an agenda.
- I don't.
- Well, that's a first.
Are you saying that I came here
to push you out?
I'm saying that I've never known
you not to know what you want.
What I want is to talk about us,
But you don't seem to want
to do that,
So I'm focusing on this.
I'm not resigning
my senior partnership
The day after
what happened happened,
If that's what you're asking.
I'm asking if you plan
to resign it at all.
And I can't tell you that
right now, because I don't know.
Well, when will you know?
Look, jessica,
you're the managing partner,
So if you want to push me out,
push me out,
But if you're asking me
what I want to do,
I'm telling you
that I haven't decided.
How did it go?
Never mind how it went.
Where's mike.
Did he file those papers?
I-I-I don't know.
He's not even in yet.
Well, you tell him
not to file anything,
And you tell him to do
whatever he has to
To stick it to that woman.
Why?
Because it didn't work.
What didn't work?
I tried to make a deal with evan
to trade the case.
You mean you offered to drop
the case in exchange for me.
Yes.
And now what are we gonna do?
(harvey)
you're not gonna do anything.
I'm gonna do whatever I have to
To get terrance wolf
to back off.
Harvey, there's no way the d.A.
Handles a case like this himself
Just because I work for you.
Whether he handles it himself
or not doesn't matter,
Because this case won't even
exist in another hour.
How did it go?
I just told a man
that everything
I promised him was bullshit.
How do you think it went?
Oh, mike, I'm sorry.
Oh, you should have seen
his face.
That money was gonna change
his life,
And then I dangled it in front
of him and ripped it away.
Yeah, but it's not your fault.
You did everything you could.
He accused me of selling out.
You know you didn't do that.
Didn't I?
We gave up because...
Of me?
That's not what I was gonna say.
Yeah, it was.
No, I was gonna say
because of harvey.
What are you talking about?
Harvey never wanted
to take this case,
So he put a clock on it
to get me to drop it.
That's why we're where we are
right now.
Listen to me;
harvey is out there right now
Busting his ass
to fix everything.
No, donna.
He doesn't give a shit about
this case, and he never did.
Then why did he send me here
to tell you to do
Everything you can to stick it
to evan smith?
She didn't take the deal,
did she?
No, she didn't.
(mike) donna, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
that you were still...
On the hot seat?
Like I said, harvey's
busting his ass to fix it,
Which means he's gonna fix it.
Now, finish what we started
and figure out a way
To win this case.
Harvey specter.
I was wondering when you
would show up.
That's funny;
I was wondering why
You never sent me
a christmas card.
Ha-ha.
You don't seem
the least bit worried
About the pending charges
against your secretary.
I'm not,
because she did nothing wrong.
Well, you know what I think?
I think you wouldn't be here
if she did nothing wrong.
Listen to me.
She didn't steal anything.
She got those documents by
convincing them to let her in,
And that is not a crime.
And the last time
you were in my office,
You told me you hadn't committed
a crime to get the job done.
After I told you
you had an innocent man,
And all you cared about
was procedure.
All I cared about was the law.
Well, if you're so concerned
with people breaking the law,
Why don't you take a look
at those documents?
Because they prove liberty rail
actually committed a crime,
Unlike donna, whose only crime
is working for me.
I'm not investigating her
for working for you.
I'm investigating her
for felony fraud.
What the hell are you
talking about?
The woman that let her in
swears your secretary told her
She was with the national
transportation safety board.
That's a federal agency,
Which makes what she did
not a trick.
It makes it felony fraud.
My office.
Now.
Close the door.
Harvey, what happened?
What happened is,
you lied to me.
What are you talking about?
You told their secretary
you were with the ntsb?
- That's not what I said.
- Bullshit.
I know when I've been lied to.
Come clean right now.
I...
- Right the hell now.
- I never said I was with them.
I said, "have you ever heard of"
The national transportation
safety board?
How is that any different?
- I'm sorry, I...
- You're sorry?
Harvey, I swear I didn't know
that that made it a crime.
You knew when I point-blank
asked you,
And you lied to me about it.
Well, I thought that you
would take care of it.
How can I take care of it if you
don't tell me the goddamn truth?
Do you think that I didn't want
to tell you the truth?
- Then why didn't you?
- Because I was ashamed.
I know that it sounds stupid,
But you and mike and everyone
pull these rabbits
Out of your hats all the time,
and I just sit outside,
And I answer the phones.
And then I got those documents,
and people said I saved the day.
And the next thing I knew,
you were on my doorstep
Coming at me like I was
some sort of criminal,
And I panicked, and I lied.
- Donna...
- I'm sorry, harvey.
I know you are,
but this just got
1,000 times harder for me
to get out of.
[scoffs]
You mean for you
to get me out of.
Donna, you of all people
should understand by now
That to me
they're the same thing.
What are you doing here?
I went to see you at work.
They said you called in sick.
I said, what are you doing here?
I wanted to tell you
the good news.
I'm not dropping your case
after all.
Good for you.
Hey, joe.
I know you've been
jerked around,
But things are gonna change.
Gonna change?
Really?
I thought you said you got
the evidence in the wrong way.
Well, and you said we should
get it in the right way,
So that's exactly
what we're gonna do.
Like I said, good for you, but
you're not gonna do it with me.
Hey, joe.
I can't subpoena those records
without the legitimate client.
I have no basis and no standing
to move forward if I did.
Oh, now you have time to explain
procedure to me, right?
Okay, fine.
I deserved that.
But, joe, this case cannot
move forward without you.
You should have thought of that
before you cut me loose.
They got to you, didn't they?
They gave you a few dollars
to shut you up,
And then they sealed
the agreement
With no admission of guilt.
You know what?
I can't comment on that,
and you know why,
But let's get
one thing straight.
They didn't shut me up;
you did.
And if I took anything,
It was because I had
no other choice.
Joe, listen to me.
If the check hasn't cleared,
we can still get out of it.
Don't come by here anymore.
So much for really caring
about those people.
Go to hell.
I thought nobody puts baby
in the corner.
Since when am I "baby"?
Since you're sitting
in the corner.
You're usually a power table
kind of girl.
Well, I'm not tonight.
Jessica, what's going on?
[sighs]
It's over between me and jeff.
What?
What happened?
It's not important.
One day the man is calling me
about taking you to paris,
And the next it's over,
And the reason for all that
isn't important?
No, it isn't, because right now,
I have to decide whether
he should stay at the firm.
Well, then I'd say the reason
that you broke up is important.
And I don't want to get into it
right now,
Because it's not going
to change.
Wow, heard that before.
Leah, I'm not like dad,
and I'm tired of hearing it.
I know you always say
you're not like him,
But here you are scrubbing up
for the next surgery
Instead of fighting for the man
that you love.
You know what?
Most sisters would say,
"I'm sorry, jessica,"
And then give me a hug.
Jessica, I am sorry
that you're hurting,
And if you want something
sugarcoated,
I'll order you dessert, but that
is not how we show support.
You're right.
We show it by telling each other
what we think, so...
And what I think is,
Two days ago,
this man loved you.
So unless you cheated on him,
stole from him,
Or killed somebody,
it seems to me the two of you
Should be able to get past
whatever it is you did do.
Joe henderson backed out.
Harvey, did you hear me?
They paid him off.
We have no case anymore.
And right now,
I have a bigger problem.
Donna lied.
What do you mean, she lied?
I mean she didn't just bullshit
her way into that file room.
She used the words "national
transportation safety board."
In what context?
In the context of committing
a crime to help you.
Are you accusing me of knowing
that she did that?
If you didn't know, it's because
you didn't want to know.
Harvey, she told me
she didn't steal those things.
I believed her
the same way you did.
And you lied just like she did.
I did not lie.
Then how come when I asked you
where those documents came from,
You didn't say one word
about donna?
Because you wouldn't have
listened to another word
I said after that, and I was
trying to get the job done.
Well, you got the job done
by risking her.
And how is that different than
all the times you risked me?
Because she's different.
Harvey, I swear I didn't know.
Well, like I said, right now,
I've got a bigger problem.
Donna's gonna be charged
with felony fraud,
And she's guilty.
- Five elements.
- What?
Proving fraud consists
of five elements.
Okay, I'm aware of that,
and they have all of them.
What about injury?
How did donna injure
liberty rail?
- You know how.
- I know, and you know.
But evan smith isn't gonna sit
in front of a jury
And explain why
those documents have value
Without exposing her client
to criminal charges.
And without damages,
What donna did is trespassing
at the worst.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to stay
on the civil case.
Harvey, the lawsuit is dead.
We don't have a plaintiff.
Then get another one,
because I'm not letting
This woman get away
with a goddamn thing.
(wolf) all right,
I'm paying you the courtesy
of a meeting.
What's on your mind?
(evan) well, based on his
reputation, I would say that
He's going to try to weasel
his way out of this.
(harvey) what I'm going
to do is save mr. Wolf
From being embarrassed
in open court.
And I'm sure there's no side
benefit to you in the process.
On the stand, right?
So do you; that's why you
had her come down here.
And did she tell you
what donna actually took?
You told me what donna took.
And I also told you that it
proves they committed a crime,
But she can't say that,
which means all donna stole
Was a meaningless stack
of papers,
And without actual damages...
I know the law.
Then you know you've got
a shitty witness.
Well?
I can't get into the details
of those documents,
But that doesn't mean
that they don't have value.
Of course they have value.
The saved you ass.
They're confidential.
They have trade secrets.
The only secret that is in there
Is that your trains kill people.
(wolf) all right, enough.
Ms. Smith,
if you can't show damages,
I have no case.
You don't need damages.
You have intent.
And if you really knew
my reputation,
You'd also know
that I used to work here.
And I can tell you they've never
gone after anyone for intent
In the history
of the d.A.'s office,
And they're not gonna start now.
It was good doing business
with you, evan.
Hey.
How are things?
You mean the things
that you said that harvey
Would take care of?
Yes, those are exactly
the things I mean.
Well,
those are exactly the things
That harvey just took care of.
He did?
He did.
[exhales]
Louis, what's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
It's just...
I know it wasn't gonna happen,
But when you first told me
they might press charges,
The thought of you
behind bars...
Oh, come on.
It just would have been
some cushy, white-collar resort.
I could have finally gotten
my yoga certification...
It wouldn't have been.
But it doesn't matter,
because I was right.
Harvey did whatever it took.
Thanks, louis.
God, he doesn't even know
how lucky he is to have you.
Norma's still out, isn't she?
Her goddamn sister tripped
and fell in the tub,
And she went to help.
It's like she doesn't even care
about me at all.
[laughter]
[laughs]
[exhales]
But you do have access
to accounts payable,
So if you could...
Look... no... hey, please,
just hear me...
God damn it.
Another one wouldn't take
your call?
No, none of them will.
I've been through
this entire directory.
As soon as I use the words
"crash," "heat," or "sensors,"
They all stop talking.
Mike, people died.
Somebody's got to want to do
the right thing.
Well, if somebody does,
I can't find them.
Okay what about
the victims' families?
Oh, you mean
the original plaintiffs.
Yeah, the problem is,
they already have a settlement.
Go on.
Look at it.
They weren't stupid.
It prevents them from ever
going after them again.
Mike,
I'm just trying to help you.
I know you are.
I'm sorry.
I'm just frustrated.
If I can't find a new plaintiff,
I can't keep this case alive.
Wait a second.
You said no one at the company
will talk to you.
They won't, because they're all
afraid they'll lose their job.
All right, so what about someone
who has nothing left to lose?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about him.
So I rescheduled the meeting
that you missed with latham
For 3:00 tomorrow.
Here are the newest contracts.
Also, kathy finn called
about the takeover,
So I sent her the latest specs,
and I told her to sit tight.
And I noticed the left pen on
your desk set was out of ink,
So I had the cartridge replaced.
You could have done all of this
while I was out of the office.
I know, but then I wouldn't have
had a chance to thank you.
Donna.
[sighs] thank you, harvey.
You're welcome.
(wolf)
ms. Paulsen, mr. Specter.
(harvey) terrance, you better be
here to give donna a formal apology
From the d.A.'s office.
[laughs] no.
I'm here to give
her lawyer this.
Harvey, what is that?
Donna, leave the room.
(wolf)
you can tell her to leave.
Don't forget to tell her
her arraignment's
At 9:00 a.M.
Tomorrow morning.
Arraignment?
For what?
You son of a bitch.
You amended the charges
to intent?
You said it's never been done
In the history
of the d.A.'s office.
I decided to make history.
By going after someone
for stealing nothing.
She went in there to find
the hope diamond.
Just because she came out
with a piece of glass
Doesn't mean it wasn't fraud.
That's exactly what it means.
Every time I run into you,
You tell me whatever shady thing
just went down
Was about the greater good
or that it didn't happen
Or this, that, or the other,
but a crime was committed here,
And I'm going after her for it.
Bullshit.
You're going after me.
Oh, you're telling me
you didn't order her to do it.
No, I didn't.
Well, we'll find out...
When she's about to be convicted
And I offer her a deal.
What happens now?
What happens now is,
we go in there tomorrow
And enter a plea of not guilty.
But I am guilty.
Donna, intent to commit fraud
is a bullshit charge,
And he's just using you
to try to scare you.
Well, it's working.
I'm scared.
- Donna...
- What's the punishment?
It doesn't matter, because
I'm gonna get you out of it.
Harvey, what's the punishment?
Three to five years.
Oh, my god.
- Three to five years for what?
- Not now, louis.
I just saw terrance wolf
at the elevator.
Three to five years for what?
He's charging her with intent
to commit fraud.
Holy shit.
Louis, I don't want to hear it.
Get her out of this.
This isn't helping.
What the hell do you think
I've been doing?
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
I told her that you were never
gonna let her get in trouble.
It's not so simple.
What the hell isn't so simple?
She's guilty.
Wolf is trying to use her
to turn on me,
Because he thinks
I put her up to it.
Did you?
Harvey didn't even know
I did it.
You know what?
It doesn't even matter.
- Because I'm taking over.
- No, you're not.
He's trying to get her
to turn on you.
You cannot be her lawyer.
She's not going to,
so what difference does it make?
The difference is, if you're out
of the picture, wolf backs down.
From where he's standing,
I'm in the picture,
And he's never gonna back down.
You don't know that,
and this is donna's life.
And I'm not putting it
in your hands.
And it's not your decision
to make.
No, it's not.
It's donna's.
And she's sticking with me.
Louis, please,
I know that you want to help,
But just go.
- Mr. Jaworski.
- Yeah.
My name is mike ross.
I'm with pearson specter litt.
This is rachel zane.
She's one of our associates.
Sir, we'd like to speak with you
about the accident.
Look, I was already deposed
for that lawsuit.
The victims got paid.
I said everything
I had to say, okay?
We're not here
to come after you.
We want you to sue liberty rail.
Oh, yeah?
And why would I sue them?
'Cause while you might have been
driving the train,
That accident wasn't your fault.
Is this some kind of a joke?
No, sir.
It isn't.
They made you the fall guy.
Bullshit.
Why would they do that?
Because they needed
to blame someone,
And not only were you
at the wheel,
You had no memory
of what happened.
Nah, I don't believe it.
They're a good company.
They wouldn't do this.
Mr. Jaworski...
Look, I killed those people.
And they still gave me
early retirement
And let me keep my pension.
The reason they did that
was to keep you quiet.
I need you to get off
my property,
Both of you.
Sir, you know that we're telling
the truth.
Yeah, well, is the truth
gonna support the family
Of a guy who can't get another
job for the rest of his life?
If we win,
you'll be set up for life.
Ah, take a look at me.
I ain't the guy who wins.
I'm the guy who loses.
What if I can guarantee
to take care of all of that
No matter what happens.
What would you need me to do?
(man) all rise.
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
Am I gonna have to talk?
Just be polite
and say "your honor."
It will be over
before you know it.
(man)
state versus donna paulsen.
Is the defense counsel prepared
to proceed with the arraignment?
We are, your honor.
Ms. Paulsen,
you have been charged
With felony intent
to commit fraud.
This carries a maximum sentence
of up to five years in prison.
Do you understand the charges
against you today?
Yes, your honor.
How do you plead?
Not guilty, your honor.
(man) very well.
Mr. Wolf, is the state ready
to go to trial?
We are, your honor.
Trial is set to begin Monday.
Next case.
(harvey)
all right, you made your point.
Let's plead this down
to a misdemeanor
And both go back
to our real jobs.
This is my real job.
[faintly] maybe if you had
a little more respect
For what it stands for,
you wouldn't be standing here.
[faintly] listen, I'm gonna wipe
that look off your smug face.
You give it a try, harvey,
But I've got all the evidence
I need.
You're gonna have to go
find yourself a new secretary.
[exhales]
I see you're back
to not knocking.
I take it that means
you've made up your mind.
I have.
And?
And what I've decided
Is that you shut the door
on me the other night,
And it's not fair you to dictate
what I do and don't get to say.
I told you.
It doesn't matter
what you have to say,
Because whatever it is,
I won't believe it.
Well, what if I was here
to tell you that I love you?
Jessica,
you lied to me for months...
Jeff, please.
Just listen.
I know I hurt you,
But you were the one
Who wanted us to work together
and be in a relationship.
And you were the one who thought
it was a mistake.
Because I was scared.
But I changed my mind,
Because you refused to give up.
And now I'm refusing to give up.
I want you to stay here.
I want us to have both.
[light piano music]
Jessica...
You wanted me to let
my walls down.
Well, they're down.
(harvey)
donna, why don't you go home?
You know I like to be alone when
I'm getting ready for a trial.
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I think maybe louis was right.
You think louis was right
about what?
Maybe he should be
handling my case.
Okay, well,
if that's how you feel.
I knew it; I knew you would
take this as an insult.
How exactly would you like me
to take it?
I would like you
to take it seriously
And talk about it with me.
Okay, donna, why exactly would
you prefer louis to handle this?
Because I sat
in that arraignment today,
And it hit me for the first time
That I might actually go
to prison.
And you were more concerned
with attacking terrance wolf
Than you were with me.
So you think louis is right.
I piss off the d.A. Too much.
- Well, you sure did today.
- Because he's coming at us.
And you're pouring gas
on the fire.
Because that's what I do,
and I don't need you
Coming in here second-guessing
how I do my job.
Harvey,
why are you attacking me?
I'm not the enemy.
You sure as hell are right now.
What?
Why am I the...
(harvey) because I'm
getting ready for a fight,
(donna)
I'm not telling you that.
I'm telling you
that I'm petrified.
(harvey) and I understand, but I
don't have time to comfort you.
- Well, I need you to make time.
- And I can't, because...
Harvey, this is my life!
When I told louis how you
got me out of this thing,
He told me how scared he was
at the thought
Of me going to prison,
and I just... Need...
You... To...
Donna, the thought of you
going to prison
Makes me want to drop
to my knees.
You want to hear me say it?
There it is.
But that's not gonna happen,
Because I'm not gonna
let it happen.
But in order to do that,
you need to let me do what I do.
- Harvey...
- That's enough.
You want someone
to give you a hug?
Go to louis.
You want someone to get you out
of this thing,
You need to leave me alone.
I need to know everything
you have,
And I need to know right now.
What does that give us?
What do you mean?
It gives us standing.
Now we can subpoena
those records.
Well, that's not enough.
- It's a start.
- I don't need a start.
I need a finish,
and I need it now.
They're charging donna,
aren't they?
She was arraigned this morning.
If this thing goes to trial,
I can't guarantee a win.
So we're back to trading
the case for donna.
Yeah, and I don't want to hear
your moral objections
About those people getting away
with murder.
But if donna was arraigned,
It's not up to them
to drop the charges.
It's up to wolf, and you know
he's never gonna do that.
I'm not talking about
dropping the charges.
I'm talking about making
this whole damn thing go away.
Harvey, if you're saying
what I think you're saying,
That's obstruction of justice.
The way I see it, it's justice.
You know what I mean.
I do, and I don't give a shit.
- This is donna.
- All right, I get it.
But what if what I have
isn't enough?
Like you said, it's a start.
Have an official complaint
on my desk by the morning.
- And what are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna get us enough.
(joe) all right, I hear you.
I hear you.
Do you know who I am?
No.
Yeah, mike ross works for me.
Hey, I don't give a shit.
I told him not to take your case
in the first place,
Because I knew you were
a goddamn shakedown artist,
But now someone I care about
is in trouble,
Because you took a payout.
Get out of my face.
Listen to me.
If you don't do
what we need you to do,
I will hurt you.
You better be prepared
to kill me,
Because I'm not gonna give
that money back.
Well, if this is just
about money,
Then we don't need to fight
at all.
Harvey,
this is becoming a habit.
I've seen you more than
my last three boyfriends.
Somehow that doesn't
surprise me.
[laughs] you're funny.
I like you.
But I know you're not here
to mock my relationship,
So what's on your mind?
We wanted to give you this.
(evan) what's this?
(mike) it's the lawsuit we filed
on behalf of michael jaworski.
You know, the man you let
take the fall for the accident.
Michael jaworski can't sue...
(harvey) what?
To take care of his expenses?
Well, now I'm taking care
of his expenses.
And now we have standing,
And we are going to subpoena
those documents.
Am I supposed to start quaking
in my boots?
(harvey) nope, we know if
you can doctor a report,
You can alter
those maintenance records.
I didn't alter anything.
Well, that's not what
joe henderson said.
He said you came to him,
admitted everything,
And offered him a settlement
to keep quiet.
We didn't admit anything,
and that settlement is sealed.
Oh, you mean this settlement?
We had an agreement.
(harvey) well, here's the thing
about paying people off, evan.
Someone can always
pay them more.
[exhales]
His word won't hold up
against richard mcintyre's.
Oh, he's not saying that richard
mcintyre put him up to it.
He's saying you did.
That's bullshit.
And does that really matter?
What do you want?
You made the author
of that report disappear.
You made joe henderson
disappear.
Figure out a way to make
the witness against donna
Change her tune.
That's obstruction of justice.
That's not my problem.
You son of a bitch.
It's your call.
Maybe people will believe joe,
maybe they won't,
But instead of making money,
You're gonna be
defending yourself in court
For the next five years.
You're so sure we did this,
you're really gonna let us
Get away with murder
for your secretary?
(harvey) you're damn right I am,
and if I had to do it again,
I'd do it 100 times.
[exhales]
What's that?
You know what it is.
- Jeff...
- Jessica, you were right.
We either need to have both,
or it's not going to work.
And you don't want both?
Effective immediately,
I'm tendering my resignation.
Then I wish you luck.
Good luck, jessica.
- [laughs]
- do you remember?
Yes, of course I remember.
It happened right there.
[laughter]
Well, it was your fault,
'cause you made me
burst out laughing.
You didn't just burst.
You spat a piece of shrimp
across the room
And into the back
of my mother's hair.
[laughs]
And she didn't even feel it
because of all the hair spray,
And it stuck in there
like a tick.
Oh, my god.
I could hardly look at her
or that boyfriend
For the next two hours.
What was his name again?
Who cares?
He was such a loser.
Oh, come on;
he was the reason you had
That god-awful party
in the first place.
[laughs]
Thank you, harvey.
You don't need to thank me.
You already thanked me.
No, I thanked you for fixing it.
Now I'm thanking you for not
bringing it up all night.
I just figured if you wanted
it brought up,
You'd bring it up,
and now you have, so...
I told you I'd never let
anything happen to you,
And I wont ever,
So you don't ever have to
feel scared like that again.
[gentle music]
I thought you said you didn't do
the comfort thing.
I didn't say I didn't do it.
I said I didn't have time,
Because I was so busy
saving your ass.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
I'm sorry I snapped at you.
Anyone else every loses faith
in me,
It doesn't matter.
But with you, it's different.
I should go.
Why?
You know why.
You know I love you, donna.
♪ ♪